So you're here to write a new book?
I think you should revise your old one first.
The one about the theory of how to start liking someone...
How to calculate it?
How about I help you think of a new title?
Well, what should it be?
How about this...
"How to overcome defeat
from the start"?
It sounds good,
but unfortunately, I'm not very good at writing about the loser.
You said you were going to prove that theory you wrote about.
Or were you just saying that to sound good?
I really want to prove it. I'm not joking.
It's not to win against anyone,
but I don't want the love I once believed in
to become a lie in my own eyes.
That's it.
In conclusion, you're afraid of feeling guilty
Why are you saying something like this
when you don't understand a single thing in the book?
Do you think I don't understand?
I read it four times and took notes.
I'm sure I remember every line.
Four times?
Normally, people who disagree
would stop reading after the first time.
And...
if it turns out your theory is wrong,
will you accept it?
If it's wrong,
I'll rewrite it myself.
Well, be careful then.
When you're determined to prove that theory...
you'll become the subject of the theory yourself.
Okay then,
I'll make you believe it's real.
Go ahead, writer.
I'm waiting.
Well...
why do you choose to stay here?
Normally, you just stare at your computer screen all day.
Why can't I be here?
I paid for the package.
I thought you'd be the type to just let your emotions run wild,
but it seems you're more considerate than I thought.
Sometimes, using reason keeps us safe.
At least we know we're not going down the wrong path.
I'm not afraid of my own heart, but you're the one who's afraid
that one day reasons won't be able to overcome your feelings, right?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
I saw you looking at me just now.
You're blocking my view.
No, you were looking at me.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
I'll consider it a statistical accident .
An accident, huh?
Then you should be careful,
because it won't hurt us...
but it might make our hearts race instead.
Just eight seconds of eye contact is enough for hearts to start remembering each other.
At that moment, I thought it was just a short time
but my heart remembered it much longer than I thought.
Is it this quiet here every night?
It's nice, actually.
Yes, it is.
But sometimes the silence
can make those who are alone even lonelier.
I never thought I'd see this side of you.
There are some sides of me I don't easily show to others,
especially those who see everything in terms of equations.
I'm surprised to see this side of you.
Maybe it's because tonight is so lonely that
I accidentally said something I didn't want to say.
Maybe it's because someone was listening
and you felt more comfortable speaking up.
You speak as if you understood everything.
You probably think that...
people who read this have no right to criticize what they're reading, right?
I'm not saying they don't have the right
but...
it should come from genuine understanding,
not from prejudice.
You know,
there's a theory that says
people tend to speak harshly
to those they're afraid will know the truth in their hearts.
Afraid?
I'm not afraid of anything that can be proven,
especially...
your feelings.