It writes about love in such a deep way.
This book made me cry. Thank you so much.
Every rule feels like a moment I've lived through.
It completely changed how I see relationships.
I saw myself in every line.
10 Rules Before I Fell for You
is a book everyone should read at least once in their life.
Of course I understand it,
otherwise how could I write something like this?
Thank you for writing such a wonderful book for us.
There are so many positive comments.
I don't have to care that one meaningless comment.
It's as bitter as that comment.
Do you know how many months of research I do?
How many psychology books I read?
How many drafts I wrote?
And who is this "LeanNote"?
You really had fun doing that?
Ten rules, huh? Written like someone who knows love but actually doesn't understand it at all.
It's just one negative comment, I don't care.
Or maybe they're right.
No,
love has reasons, evidences, theories, and equations.
Okay,
then I'll show you how people who understand love write about it.
Hello, Ms. Ticha, are you the one who booked the long-term accommodation?
Hello.
Yes, it's me.
I'm Lean.
This is a forest garden house surrounded by mountains,
a little distance from Bangkok,
but very peaceful.
It is so quiet, isn't it?
Great, I can concentrate on my work.
Then you've come to the right place,
because the only noise here is the sound of crickets chirping
or dogs barking.
Sounds great.
You must be tired, go rest first.
I'll take you to your room.
Thank you. I'm really grateful for your help.
If you need anything else, please feel free to call me anytime.
because we're a small family here.
Thank you.
What a great weather.
It feels like time is slowing down.
Yes, that's right.
When you're here, you have to let time slow down a bit,
because you'll miss out on the peace and quiet times.
You sound like someone who's been through a lot!.
No, not really.
I've just seen people try to escape the hustle and bustle,
but end up bringing it along anyway.
By the way,
I think I saw you mentioned in your booking that
you work online?
If it's not too much of a secret, may I ask what you do?
It's not a secret at all,
I'm a book writer.
Really?
I love reading books,
but lately I haven't been reading much.
Really?
What...
kind of books do you read?
The kind that doesn't teach anyone how to love.
Maybe they didn't intend to teach anyone anything.
They just want people to understand each other better,
including themselves, perhaps.
Yeah?
But trying too hard to understand
might make us forget our true feelings.
Do you want to rest?
There's a traditional Thai dinner in the garden, waiting for you.
if you want a peaceful and delicious experience, don't forget to come.
Thank you.
The writing is beautiful.
It made me miss my lover.
A book that helped me understand love from a new perspective.
Please write the next book soon.
Afraid to admit your feelings - LeanNote
Another problematic comment.
I told you the author must understand,
otherwise how could they write it?
Do you know better than me or what?
My book is a bestseller!
I guess it's because of that problematic commenter that
I can't write my new book.
It's as bitter as the criticism.
Why didn't they respond me at all?
You're not really that tough, are you?
Don't get cocky.
You probably don't have anyone and you're probably not good-looking either,
that's why you don't reveal your identity.
What evidence do you have
that those ten ridiculous theories about falling in love
are actually true?
Are you Leannote?
Don't tell me that it is your book.
I'm the one you've been insulting for five minutes straight.
What a small world.
Maybe it's because some people just
like to stay in their own little world.
Those who wrote theories about how to start liking someone
are probably living in their own world too, right?
At least...
I'm not coward to express it, unlike some people...
Those who like to hide behind keyboards.
Maybe...
the person who wrote it just felt
scared and wrote it to convince themselves.
I'll use those ten rules
with you.
And you'll find out on yourself whether this theory is
true...
or just crazy as you said.
You don't want to prove any theory,
You just want to conquer other people's feelings.
And if I actually win,
will you still dare to stand here?
Let's see
if the person who wrote the theories
can actually put it into practice.
Then you'll know for yourself
that this theory isn't as crazy as you say.
So, go ahead..
And if your theory is true,
I'll accept it.
Saying that...
means okay, right?
It means I'm not a coward.