[Episode 24]
I just came to ask you something.
On Bo's wedding day,
you wanted to stand with Miao Jing, right?
Yi, I know what's going on
between you and Miao Jing.
I didn't come here to ask you for anything.
I think I've fallen for you.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I can't tell if this feeling is
admiration or dependence.
But to me, liking someone means liking someone.
Even if Miao Jing were here today,
I'd still say this.
I'm sorry.
I don't feel that way about you.
I knew the answer before I came.
But I felt like I had to say it.
Once I said it, I felt better.
I put this in the fridge.
It's in the fridge. Remember to eat it.
Otherwise, it will just go bad again.
Miao Jing is pretty thoughtful.
Yi, I should get going.
Tu Li.
If you ever need help,
you can still come to me.
Xiao Yu and Ma Yang didn't come out with you?
They are still packing up and will be out soon.
Hongshen sent over a file today.
They want the drafts.
It is that urgent?
Foreign trade has shifted a lot lately.
They probably want to catch the boom
over in Lingang
and lock things down as soon as possible.
Once the draft is done,
we need to issue the official report.
But we still haven't traced the source
of the empty-container data from last time.
We can't rush the schedule like this.
Besides...
Anyway, let's stall for time for now.
Then let's issue a broad assessment first.
It is not final until we issue
the official report anyway.
[Chen Yi: Where did you go?
Are you coming home tonight?]
A text from Chen Yi?
Did he upset you again?
Cen Ye.
If someone gave up their future
and stability for you,
and charged ahead no matter what,
could you accept that?
I think a good relationship is when
two people are evenly matched and truly fit.
If you love someone
to the point of losing your self-respect,
then they probably aren't right for each other.
You're so slow.
- We're ready. Let's go.
- I'm exhausted.
- What did you do? We've been waiting for ages.
- We've saved a lot of money.
- We redeemed lots of vouchers. It took time.
- I said there was no need. We were in a hurry.
That would be a waste.
Let's go.
- Buckle up.
- Okay.
[Diagonal Billiards Club]
You gave me this license plate number.
I've got my colleagues following up on it.
As for that boat,
it was likely a seasoned runner from Lingang.
They've already mapped out the route.
But these people are too cautious.
As soon as we move in,
they stop doing anything concrete.
I'm already applying
for inter-departmental cooperation.
All you need to do now
is keep a tight watch on him.
If he's hiding something,
he'll slip up sooner or later.
Uncle Zhou.
Things aren't like they were six years ago.
I know.
Yi.
You couldn't get it done for him this time.
Do you think he'll start suspecting you?
He never trusted me.
So what is there to suspect?
What about Kao?
He's handling all the contacts himself now?
Yeah.
Kao helped me when I was at my lowest.
They knew that,
so that's why they came after me.
They need Kao's power for their overseas route.
That's also why I've been able
to stay at Haoyun.
But when they were testing the waters,
you showed up out of nowhere.
Knowing how his mind works,
he won't let me stay on it for a while.
That's enough.
Don't dig any deeper,
or you might get pulled into our next move.
I understand.
Yi.
I know you know what you're doing.
Personally, I want you to walk away right now.
But as Wen's husband,
I also want to say one thing.
Thank you.
Cut the mushy stuff.
Don't joke around with me. I'm serious.
Tell me about yourself.
What did you tell Miao Jing?
What?
Did you two fight?
She moved out.
She moved out?
She moved out? It's that bad?
Then it must be a big deal.
Did you try to make it up to her?
If that would fix it,
she wouldn't have moved out.
Wen was the same.
Back then, when I made her mad,
if it was something small,
she'd pout and make a fuss.
She would give me a chance to apologize.
But when I crossed her line,
she was calmer than anyone.
No sweet talk would work.
No apology would work.
Then what do I do?
What do you do?
Wear her down.
Keep apologizing
and find the right moment to do it sincerely.
You little punk.
Stop making Miao Jing worry about you.
If you always make girls make the first move,
how will you ever find a wife?
Honestly.
What are you standing there for? Keep playing.
Beat me, and Miao Jing will come back.
I'll go for a long one.
Vehicle and vessel tax, property tax,
and land value-added tax are expenses.
And they're carried over directly.
Resource tax
and consumption tax involve no loss.
- Gosh, I think that's all of them.
- Good heavens.
These past two or three months felt like years.
How are things on your end?
Finally, there's something to look forward to.
I miss my fresh pork mooncakes,
butterfly pastries, and scallion oil noodles.
Hard to tell if you miss people or food.
What did you say?
I said once you're back in Hai City,
you'll miss the food here so much.
Rice noodle rolls, wontons, and beef balls.
Ma Yang.
What? Don't look at me like that. I'm scared.
I think you've got real potential.
What kind of potential?
The potential to hang out with Ding Lei.
Being annoying is also a talent.
Boss.
She's picking on me.
I won't eat with her tonight.
I'll eat with you instead.
Don't push your luck. I have plans tonight.
You think everyone is like you?
Jing already told me.
She's meeting someone tonight.
Well, who do you think the guy is?
Boss, you get to be happy again.
Everyone, go grab dinner.
After dinner, we need to finish this batch.
- Overtime!
- No.
You did threaten someone else's interests.
Been busy lately?
You haven't had time to come by
and fish or play pool with me.
Just regular work.
My workload is up to you, isn't it?
Mr. Liu called to thank you.
The shipment almost drew police attention.
Thanks to you working both ends,
we dodged a bullet.
Chen Yi.
Are you really on my side?
What do you think, Mr. Zhang?
Of course, I trust you.
After all these years,
the two of us have been through a lot together.
For the company to get this far,
you deserve a lot of the credit.
Take a look at this.
These audit risk alerts keep getting worse.
I was worried something might go wrong
and affect the plan with Hongshen.
But I spoke with Miao Jing.
She said she can take full responsibility
for the results of this audit.
[Auditor: Miao Jing]
I'm glad I have you both helping me.
Chen Yi.
Remember. We're family.
We're in this together, for life.
[Haoyun Logistics]
Any other questions, Mr. Chen?
I've reviewed all these reports.
They're very clear.
There are just a few points I don't get.
Go ahead.
Aren't these risk ratings too severe?
As the auditor, I have to ensure
the audit results are fair and accurate.
We're simply giving an objective warning
about possible risks and loopholes.
Of course, this assessment is only
for Hongshen Group.
So they can assess if Haoyun can operate well
during the investment period.
Looks like
auditing really does take skill and guts.
The tension in here is intense.
What is going on?
Isn't the project almost over?
I get it.
This is the final showdown
before the competency project audit wraps up.
The whole point is to own the room.
Jing is choosing duty over family.
Respect.
Will Mr. Cen follow up on this project?
Since you think the reports are fine,
then you simply don't trust me.
You don't trust me to handle this project.
Of course, I trust you.
I trust you, too.
Then we share the risk.
The project can wrap up sooner.
If there are no other issues,
today's meeting is adjourned.
The audit is actually nearly finished.
We also hope to wrap this project up soon.
That way, Mr. Chen won't have to
work so hard at Haoyun.
Why sign the audit form?
Once you sign,
you're taking full responsibility.
- Do you know what that means?
- I do.
That's why I have to sign.
I was wrong before.
If you move out or choose to go back
to Hai City, I won't stop you.
But don't take this risk.
I'm afraid I can't protect you.
- Isn't this trip a risk for you, too?
- That's different.
Miao Jing.
I thought there were many things
I shouldn't tell you.
So I kept them from you. I'm sorry.
But Zhang Bin is far more dangerous
than you realize.
Far more dangerous
than anything you've faced in an audit.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Chen Yi.
I'm not who I used to be.
But you're still stuck in the past.
You always think you have to protect me.
But have you ever thought
that I don't need your protection anymore?
Come with me to check the files.
You always think you have to protect me.
But have you ever thought
that I don't need your protection anymore?
[Haoyun Logistics]
I told you last night. Do handle it for me.
Mr. Cen, we're heading out.
Let's go eat.
Cen Ye.
Uncle Zhou.
No need to be so formal with me.
You've been back for a while,
but I haven't even taken you out for a bite.
I happen to have the day off today.
It's not too late to make up for it, is it?
Of course not.
I should be visiting you more often.
I'm not that old.
No need to talk about visits with me.
- Here. Have some porridge.
- Thank you.
You didn't invite Chen Yi today?
Aren't you two having a fight?
If I called him over,
wouldn't that make me the peacemaker?
That's an old man's job, not mine.
Jing.
How long will you be busy this time?
You mean how much longer
my audit at Haoyun will take?
Are you asking, or is Chen Yi?
That kid doesn't have the nerve
to send me to pry it out of you.
I'm the one asking.
That depends on how cooperative Chen Yi is.
Actually, I wanted to ask last time.
What exactly are Chen Yi and you
doing now with Haoyun?
Hot.
Jing.
What kind of person do you think Chen Yi is?
What do you mean?
If he'd gotten into the police academy,
and had to carry out a mission,
do things he had no choice but to do,
and take injuries he had to take,
would you blame him?
If it were for something that mattered,
of course not.
How you define "mattered" is hard to say.
I'm just worried about him.
As long as I'm at Haoyun, he'll be there.
As long as I'm in Teng City, he'll be on edge.
It's not that I don't trust him.
I just have to do something too.
I can't drag him down forever.
You're not dragging him down.
I watched both of you grow up.
You both always think of each other.
Okay, enough of that.
Here. Have some soup. It's getting cold.
I really didn't come here to play mediator.
Eat.
[Teng City Commercial Bank]
[The maturity proceeds of RMB 52,860]
What is it?
Someone sent me a gift.
Yi knows how things work.
I was wrong before.
You can move out if you want.
I won't even stop you
if you choose to go back to Hai City.
But don't take risks.
I'm afraid I can't protect you.
You're not dragging him down.
You both always think of each other.
Hello.
Hello. What can I help you with?
I made an appointment by phone.
A policy of mine has matured.
I'd like to ask about it.
Please show me your identification.
Okay, I found it here.
You should receive a maturity payout
on August 19.
The amount is 52,860 yuan.
Can you look up the policyholder's details?
Sorry, ma'am.
We can't access policyholder details.
You'll need to ask the insurance company.
Which insurance company?
It says Peng City Huishou Insurance Company.
[Peng City to Teng City]
[Teng City Commercial Bank]
[The maturity proceeds of RMB 52,860]
[Moments, Miao Jing]
[Family, Miao, Keeping a record
makes the waiting feel less empty.]
[You can request access below.
(Request Access)]
What's wrong at the pool hall?
I'm on my way.
Can you see Miao Jing's social media feed?
Do you realize how insane it is
to call a newlywed man at two AM and ask
if he can see the social feed
of a young, unmarried woman?
This is insane.
I know how to get you access.
What?
Ask her yourself. Have her let you in.
Wish you a happy marriage. Go to sleep now.
You can't keep asking me every day.
[You can request access below.
(Request Access)]
Who is it?
Yi.
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for Jing. Is she here with you?
She's not here.
Let's talk outside.
What were you thinking?
Coming here to look for her?
Did Jing come back to Teng City?
What are you talking about?
She's been in Teng City this whole time.
Where else would she be?
Why are you looking for her again?
Hasn't she been in Hai City?
We've been in touch all this time.
If you can reach her, just call her directly.
Why come to me?
I've called, but she won't pick up.
I...
- I'm really worried about her.
- Worried about her?
Then why did you leave her with me?
If you see Jing, send a message for me.
I came back this time
not to ask her for anything.
I came back just to see her.
Yi.
You're still like brother and sister
to each other?
What?
When you left her behind,
did you never think about the fallout?
Yi, what brings you here?
Help me get in touch.
Reach Fat Dragon and Ah Jiu for me.
What has Wei Ming Zhen been up to?
Okay.
- Be on it!
[Sunflower Kindergarten]
Left, right, left.
Okay, let's go. Keep up.
Keep up.
- Keep up.
- Hold on.
Yes. Have him keep up.
Yang's mom is here.
Yuan, Grandpa is here.
- Cheng.
- Mom.
Grandma.
Dad.
- Come here, come here.
- Yuan, over here.
Over here.
Sis, look.
My teacher gave me this as a reward.
A red flower sticker.
You're amazing.
Your teacher gave you a red flower?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
I'll take you out for a feast.
How does that sound?
Let's go.
[Teng City Commercial Bank]
[The maturity proceeds of RMB 52,860]
[Jing, it's Mom. I'm back.
I've been missing you.]
Thank you.
Don't feel pressured.
Monica backing off
isn't necessarily a bad thing.
She tried so hard to meddle before,
and now she's suddenly backing off.
Hai City must have found something else.
We have a lead on the vacancy data.
Haoyun's financial records show
a deeply buried funding gap.
That's right.
Hongshen is pushing hard.
If Zhang Bin wants to cover the shortfall,
he'll have to make a move.
- Zi Xin.
- Thank you, Yu.
You get celebration candy too.
Catch.
- Here.
- Congratulations!
This is yours. Here is a pack for you.
Jing, have some candy.
Director Cen.
You're getting married?
Who says a woman's good news
has to be marriage? I bought a house.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Once we get back to Hai City,
I'll invite everyone to my place for hot pot.
- Great!
- It's a deal.
That's our Yu!
When can I afford a place of my own?
Aren't you from Hai City?
Yes.
My parents wanted to transfer a house
under their name to me.
But Cen, you know I don't want one.
Otherwise, I'd have to obey them on everything.
When to work, when to get married.
If I did anything they didn't like, they'd say,
"We gave you the house.
Why won't you listen to us?"
The pieces we picked are pretty trendy.
Girls usually love them.
- Could you try them on for me?
- Sure.
This style is actually pretty trendy.
Doesn't it dig into your hand?
It won't help to ask me.
Don't you know what styles your daughter likes?
Hi. I'd like to see this one.
Take your time. Call me when you've picked one.
Okay.
- This one, right?
- Mom, I want this little bunny.
You've got nerve, picking that.
Look at the price yourself.
You're not backing out, are you?
You promised me a piece of gold jewelry.
I want to pick one I actually like.
Fine. I must have owed you in a past life.
You are my daughter,
so I have to spoil you however much it takes.
- We'll take this one.
- Thank you, Mom.
She has slim wrists.
Bracelets look great on her.
How about this one?
Hello?
You rascal.
- You rascal.
- Why don't you take another look?
See if anything else catches your eye.
I'll wait at the intersection.
- How about this one?
- No, thank you.
- Sure.
- Let's try it on.
Jing.
I have to step out for something.
Take the bus home later.
I'm sorry.
- I'll come back in a couple of days.
- Okay.
Be careful on your way home.
Take a look and see
if there is anything you like.
If your budget is tight,
we also have some pendants.
Thread one on a cord,
and it looks about the same.
It has to be a gold bracelet,
and it can't be too light.
I haven't seen my daughter in ages.
Okay.
The number you have dialed is powered off.
Please try again later.
Miao Jing, why are you still here?
Miss, I...
I filed a request with the school.
I applied for a winter break internship.
What happened to you?
Nothing. Just a bit of a cold.
Come on. Sit down. Sit.
You're burning up.
How can you do an internship?
Where's your family?
I'll call them to come pick you up.
Wei Ming Zhen is your mother, right?
Don't bother. You won't get through.
How could I not get through?
Did you have a fight with your family?
Even so, they can't just leave you here.
Hello? Who is this?
Hello.
I'm an advisor
at Jiaohai University's business school.
- Are you Ms. Wei Ming Zhen?
- Wait, listen to me.
If it isn't urgent, can you call back later?
I'm busy right now.
Wait up.
Hurry up.
Are you okay?
I only have two hours.
Say what you need to say.
Didn't you say two hours? Time's not up yet.
Walk around with me first.
I thought Teng City
would've changed a lot by now.
I didn't expect these shops to still be here.
That shop we just passed,
do you still remember it?
In fifth grade, you got perfect scores on
both exams, so I took you there for a burger.
Remember?
Yeah.
But you took a call and left
before you finished eating.
I walked home by myself.
And that wasn't the only time.
When you came back to see me in high school,
we met there too.
If you have something to say, just say it.
Stop dancing around it.
I just wanted to come back and see you.
And then?
There has to be more to it than that.
It's true.
If you came back just to tell me this,
then you've said it, and we've met.
You can go back now.
Where are you staying?
I'll have someone take you back.
It's not yet two hours.
Where are you going?