Hello, Alex? We have a problem.
Let's go out after your class.
Yes, if that's okay with you.
Why did you suddenly invite me?
What is that?
Do you have a problem with your mouth?
Like a mouth sore?
Okay.
- You?!
- What?!
Why did you assign Carlota
as Mikoy's secretary?
You're just doing this
to investigate him. Right?
Am I your boss?
Oh?
Why are you suddenly
so interested in Chiara?
Because I have a strong feeling that--
I have a strong feeling that…
she really likes cats.
Huh?
Is that really what you wanted to say?
Alex, is there something I should know?
Nothing!
I just wanted to say that
you should get her a cat.
I think she's ready
to become a "meowi" again.
Look, things are pretty busy
at the office right now.
I'll update you if anything new comes up.
Just keep your phone with you.
Wait, Alex!
What is it?
What?
Chiara!
There!
The tension's finally released.
What happened?
I was attacked, sir.
I got attacked
by mild-trentahin back pain.
But I'm okay now. Ma'am Chiara
is really good at massaging.
Oh, wow!
So, what now? Are you okay now?
Yes, I'm okay!
Thank you, Ma'am Chiara!
Feel better, okay?
I'll just get my bag.
Thank you, Ma'am Chiara.
I'll study what misua is.
Do you know each other?
So I know her very well.
What's misua?
Nothing!
What is it really?
Don't you know?
No.
It's noodles, like…
The thin ones.
Is your friend really like that?
Is he Indian or something!
Hey, that's foul!
You might get bashed online.
He really did something awful to me!
I even prepared for this movie date.
And then what?!
I bought a cute dress, did my makeup…
I did everything to look presentable,
and then he didn't show up?
He acts like he's
- some kind of gift to women?
- Sofie.
If he did that,
it's his loss, not yours.
No! No one's relaxing on this campus!
He'd better watch out for me.
Only his eyes will come out unscathed!
PHILIPPINE UNIVERSITY
Sofie!
You started this, so own it.
This.
General Ruiz passed through here.
Bok, there are many like that.
At the bar.
When we were together.
A glass fell.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT
And if she really is La Fornarina…
and her family were to do something dirty…
I'd get close to someone clean,
someone innocent,
someone like Mikoy,
because that's the perfect cover.
Everything you told me,
like timing,
the falling glass, the build-up,
gut feel…
We still don't have any solid proof.
It's all just a gut feeling!
Yes.
Just feelings,
but I'm pretty sure about mine.
You know what? I can't take this anymore.
What were you thinking?
Sending your chihuahua after Mikoy.
Mikoy, who doesn't even know.
Mikoy, who can't even fix his eyebrows.
Mikoy, whose only mistake
is loving our daughter!
And you think he won't find out?
You're ruining your relationship
with your daughter.
So you turned
her boyfriend into an operation.
Maybe you're forgetting, darling.
You know how intense
our daughter can get when she's angry.
You also know she's
in love like this only now!
And you know very well
what she is capable of--
What did you say?
You really call her a chihuahua?
But it's just that
I don't really like that girl.
Chiara, tell me the truth.
Mikoy?
Were you a masseuse before?
Wow!
How did you learn this?
Seriously, sweetheart, you're really good.
Nothing, I just…
I just get lost
in the reflexology rabbit hole online.
Be careful with that Carlota.
Why though?
What is she?
A killer?
No, I just really don't like her,
and I don't trust her,
so you shouldn't either.
Right.
You guys can start
bringing the things inside.
Go ahead.
There's more of that.
Careful, okay? Be careful.
Take care, mister.
There.
Chiara?
That makes sense.
Sir, there's more.
Hurry.
I'm so excited!
There's more downstairs.
That's two trucks.
Are you talking about me?
I'm okay now, Alex.
I'm good without the romantic traumas
and attachment issues,
especially with you, Alex.
But I can also say I want to try again.
Ben!
It's not you, okay?
La Fornarina.
That's the topic
we're discussing, not you.
La Fornarina.
I'm not new to this.
You're just not good at reading people.
Are you serious about this?
No, that's not it.
Wait, that's wrong.
- Oh my God.
- Here.
That's her.
She is La Fornarina!
But there's inconsistentency.
Why are you suddenly interested in Chiara?
It felt like someone
was investigating her.
A buddy.
But his tone
wasn't admiration.
We bring her in.
None, sir.
Tax-abiding, no criminal record,
not even a traffic violation.
You know, I wouldn't be surprised
if you and Bok
actually had something before.
Because you think alike.
You know, she was actually
the one who suggested before
that we should kidnap Mikoy.
Right, Bok?
Shut up.
How?
What's your plan?
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Hi, good morning.
Sorry, I didn't see you.
I won't allow it.
No, Alex, I won't agree
to that kind of set-up.
It doesn't suit you.
If you need a leading man
who has charisma,
that's me.
I'm way more handsome and more charming.
Just being realistic.
Hey. This isn't a romcom, okay?
Just surveillance for now.
What's all this?
It's like the floor is lava.
Sorry, I didn't expect
to bring this much stuff.
You didn't expect it?
Wow.
It's a lot of stuff.
So you actually know how to fold clothes?
I'm the one who folds
and hangs Mom's laundry.
Ah, lucky me indeed.
I even found a guy
who isn't afraid of house chores.
Chiara, you know,
we're like a married couple.
You're moving too fast.
How am I moving fast?
You're the one who suddenly moved in.
- Really?
- Don't you want me here anymore?
Hey, I never said that.
Of course, I really want this.
I think you should get that now.
Right now?
Yes.
Fine then.
Chiara!
Are you okay?
Oh?
I'm okay.
Just hungry.
Okay.
By the way, sweetheart,
I really appreciate it, you know.
You want me to rest,
but I really don't think I can.
I'm just not used to doing nothing,
and I also feel embarrassed
toward Papa Viktor.
You know, I've already
missed so much at the office.
They might think that I'm useless.
So you want to work again?
Just check in once in a while,
not full-time.
You know, just dropping by
every now and then.
Okay.
Really?
So, shall we?
Let's eat.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
I already scrubbed her profile.
Carlota Regalo.
Clearly well-trained.
She was never exposed.
There was also a hostage incident
in which she entered alone.
She neutralized the two hostage takers
in close quarters.
She got the hostages out…
without firing a shot.
Clean record.
You won't notice her
ulessshe wants to be noticed.
She's like a chameleon.
There were no red flags
during her service, either.
Not even for being late.
Surveillance first.
Alex.
It's uneven.
Wow!
I'm so lucky.
Of course!
I have a stylist and a personal chef too.
Here. Don't buy food anymore.
This tastes better.
Oh, my! Sweetheart!
You know, you're basically ready
to get married!
All I'm missing is a groom.
I see.
So what am I?
An intern or something?
Wow, okay!
You just moved in
and you already moved on?
Like that?
So, are you still hiring?
Oh, I see.
I'll pass. You're a red flag.
Here.
Oh, text me, okay, when you get there.
I'll get going.
Take care!
You were too late.
They already met someone.
The one Viktor assigned to him.
So you're telling me that Mikoy's
new assistant is an assassin?
A killer?
How did she know me?
How did she know my name?
Thank you so much!
Of course! I'm so happy for you.