A FILM BY HADRAH DAENG RATU
Come back with us on Radio.
Listeners who are willing to accompany
evening twilight from the border...
...let yourself flow slowly.
Brings memories and feelings
who have stopped by.
Let's listen to the song together
from Nike Ardilla...
...with the title "Star of Life".
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- Yes?
- Do you have pliers?
- Yes.
I'd like to borrow them for a moment.
- Let me borrow them, ma'am.
- Okay.
2Back then... What was it called?
The engineer, or the contractor,
promised...
...people can pass through here...
...but every year there has to be a
sacrifice.
People riding bicycles motorcycle.
A driver or the assistant.
Not long ago, someone had their head cut
off.
Alas Roban is a forest area
located in Batang Regency, Central Java...
...famous for its steep and winding road,
with sharp turns...
...and the mystical stories
surrounding it.
Sir, hurry up.
PEKALONGAN, CENTRAL JAVA
Come on, Gendis. Hurry up.
Yes, Mom.
Newspaper! Sir, ma'am.
- Get on! To Pekalongan! To Semarang!
- Hurry, kid!
- Come on, help me.
- Yes, Mom. One moment.
Get on, to Pekalongan, to Semarang!
Oh God! My stuff!
Oh no.
- Hey, ma'am!
- Sorry, sir.
- Watch your child!
- Yes, sorry, sir...
Who will be responsible for this?
Oh no. Enough, my child. No need.
Sorry, sir. We're in a hurry to catch the
bus.
Hey, if you're sorry, you can help me with
this.
Yes, sir. You can see it for yourself.
My daughter has limited vision.
And we're in a hurry, sir.
My capital is also limited.
If it's wasted like this...
...I'll have nothing.
Gosh.
Give it to me, kid.
Here, sir.
Okay, then. Be careful!
Watch your child!
Why is this happening to me?
Sir.
I want two tickets to Semarang.
Can't do that, ma'am. We're closed.
Gosh... Sir, just two tickets, please.
We can't, ma'am. We're closed.
That is no longer possible.
Just talk to the conductor.
- Oh no.
- Get on, to Pekalongan!
Gosh!
Come on, to Pekalongan, to Semarang!
Come on, kid.
Come on, Gendis!
Okay, mom.
Come on, kid. Hurry!
Sir, one more passenger!
- Oh no.
- Mom.
Mom. What's wrong, Mom?
We missed the bus.
What's wrong, ma'am?
We missed the bus, Sir.
There's another bus tomorrow, ma'am.
At six in the morning.
- Oh dear...
- Where are you going?
Semarang.
That is the bus.
Aren't there any night buses, sir?
We really have to get there early.
Tomorrow's my first day of work.
Actually there is.
But our driver is on break, ma'am.
Even if he's going, it will cost more,
ma'am.
More money?
Okay, that's fine.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh my...
Sir, this is all there is.
Please help me, sir.
Yes, ma'am. Come with me, ma'am.
Gosh, I wish you
hadn't bumped into the guy.
We have almost no money left.
Come on, kid!
Sir, she's gonna pay you double the price.
Just go.
Which way?
Through Alas Roban?
Nighttime, via Alas Roban?
- Come on, Gendis.
- Yes, ma'am.
Oh my.
Oh my...
Thank you, sir.
Oh my.
Oh my...
Do I have to return the money, sir?
We're talking about Alas Roban here.
Besides, that's just a myth, Sir.
If we go now,
we'll pass Alas Roban before sundown.
The important thing is, don't forget that
thing...
...sound your horn.
Come on. That's double the price.
Let's go, Sir.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I can't see clearly.
Why are you crying?
My goodness, I...
...was not angry at you.
I was angry at the situation.
Sorry, kid.
I promise you'll be able to see clearly.
We're going to Semarang...
...because at my new workplace...
...my salary is higher.
So, I can save up for your eye surgery.
Thank you, Mom.
Do you know...
...who's the first person I want to see
after the surgery?
Who, dear?
You.
Because Dad used to say...
...that you're really beautiful.
Really?
You're prettier, of course.
Your chin...
...your cheeks.
Your smell.
- Delicious!
Bastard.
Passing through Alas Roban at night.
Sur, wake up!
Sur!
YOU ARE ENTERING ALAS ROBAN AREA
The horn won't make a sound.
Sur, wake up!
YOU ARE ENTERING ALAS ROBAN AREA
Sir?
Wake up!
We've been through here twice.
What's wrong, sir?
We've passed through the same road.
Here.
To get rid of bad luck.
Sur!
What's wrong, sir?
Are you okay, child?
I'm okay, Mom.
What's wrong, sir?
I don't know yet, ma'am.
Hold on, let me check.
Get off first, okay? The bus is having
problems.
Where are we?
Where are they going? Come on.
Come on down.
What's wrong with you, child?
I really need to pee, Mom.
Gosh...
Okay, let's go.
Just put the doll there. Come on.
Slowly.
Sir, didn't you just replace the tire?
Sir.
Yes, ma'am?
May I borrow your flashlight?
My daughter needs to pee.
Yes, but...
...be careful.
Would you like me to accompany you?
No need. It's okay.
Thank you.
- Come on, child.
- Yes, Mom.
Are you done, Sur?
Why do they go so far away to pee?
Here you go.
Miss.
May I use the bathroom?
It's over there.
Thank you.
There, child. Yes.
- I'll close the door, okay?
- Okay.
Everything's okay, child?
Yes, Mom.
Gendis, are you done?
Gendis?
Are you done?
I'm done.
Let's go.
Go down slowly.
Miss, thank you.
Excuse us.
Why don't you stop by first, ma'am?
Eat here.
You still have a long way to go.
Is the mother not going to eat?
No, Miss. I'm...
...just going to help my daughter eat.
- Bye.
Ma'am, come on.
We're just waiting for you.
- Yes, Sir. Sorry.
- Hurry up.
Here.
Watch your step, child.
SEMARANG, CENTRAL JAVA
Your duties are only administration
and registration.
Sometimes accident victims like this...
...have no identification.
So, you try to find it.
You trace the family.
If they don't have any, then...
...we'll take care of them.
Sir...
...regarding the subsidy program
for employees with children...
...I'm planning to get eye surgery
for my child.
She has a congenital condition,
something like cataracts.
Yes, we have one.
After you've worked for a year...
...there's a 50 percent subsidy
from the hospital...
...for all types of procedures.
Including eye surgery.
Just ask the administration for details.
- Anything else you want to ask?
- That's it, sir.
Anto.
Just in time.
This is Mr. Anto.
Our ambulance administrator...
...and also the driver.
Anto, this is Sita.
Our new morgue administrator.
You'll be seeing each other often.
- Guide her, okay?
- Yes, sir.
- I'll take my leave.
- Have a good day, sir.
Anto?
I'm Sita. Nice to meet you.
Are you Tika's cousin?
Thank you very much for the job vacancy
information.
Yes, you're welcome.
Tika and I were classmates in high school.
- How much is this, ma'am?
- This is 30 thousand, this is 15.
How much for the garlic?
How much is each, sir?
Fifteen thousand.
How much is this, sir?
- Fifty.
- Fifty?
Not 15, sir?
Newspaper.
- Hey.
- Yes, Uncle?
Alas Roban has claimed lives again.
- Oh my.
- When was that, Uncle?
Two days ago. Here, it was in the
newspaper.
"Alas Roban has claimed lives."
- How many victims?
- Three people.
Two men and one woman.
- Where is that?
- You know, the one with the monument.
Where the road goes down
and then there's a right turn. There.
That's right, Uncle. That place is really
haunted.
- Haunted.
- There're also a lot of ghosts there, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
The ghosts resemble humans.
Yes, ma'am. So it's not just a rumor, huh?
- Yes, that's right.
- Yes.
Don't go that way at night.
Find another way.
We really have to be careful.
- Be careful.
- Yes, Uncle.
- Sir.
- Please, get on, ma'am.
I'm burdening you, Tika.
You've given me a job...
...you gave me a place to live.
And you also
have to watch Gendis every day.
You...
It's as if I'm a stranger.
Well, I'm actually glad.
I'm not alone at home anymore.
I have Gendis here.
Well...
Singgih only comes home once a month.
He's a government doctor after all.
No matter where he's assigned,
he has to go.
Well, at least
you still have your husband.
Rather than having none.
Ramdan...
...died in a work accident.
He worked overtime every day
so Gendis could have surgery.
Our lives are entirely dedicated to our
children.
I take care of Gendis by myself.
I'm the mother.
I'm the father.
Yes.
I understand.
I'm here now.
Do you want to put these ones in?
When I can finally see clearly...
...I want to go on a vacation
with Mom and you, Auntie.
To the mountains...
...to the beach.
To the forest.
To all the nice places.
Sita.
I'm going home. I was going to leave...
...but I waited until you finish
showering.
Gendis?
Why is it locked?
- What's wrong?
- Gendis?
Tika, I heard Gendis
talking to someone earlier.
- I thought she was talking to you.
- To me?
Gendis?
Open the door, child.
Gendis!
Gendis?
Gendis, it's Auntie, honey.
Gendis!
Gendis.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Gendis?
Come and eat, darling.
I've cooked for you.
Gendis?
Gendis.
You can draw?
Auntie, please be quiet.
Corpse Inspection Form
Found in Alas Roban
Excuse me, ma'am.
A human skeleton was found, ma'am.
A skeleton?
The resident who found it said that there
was only its destroyed clothes and a watch
and everything had been
handed over to the police.
He must have been lost in Alur Gembok
for a long time.
This...
Where was this found?
Alas Roban.
The place where you saw the white monkey.
If it's in this condition...
...usually we take care of the funeral.
Shouldn't we try looking
for his family first?
Well, it's gonna be difficult.
The odds are 1 in 100.
Anto.
The lady from earlier...
- Who...
- Mrs. Ema?
A police associate.
She's famous for her knowledge
about Alas Roban.
Things like this happen often, don't they?
Not often, but they do happen.
Alas Roban has many mysteries.
It's impossible to know what's inside.
All we know is that sometimes
there are accidents.
Sometimes bodies are found.
We passed by there
just two days ago on our way here.
Our bus broke down.
But luckily nothing happened.
The road is indeed steep and winding,
isn't it?
Ma'am.
A broken-down bus isn't a good sign.
You weren't traveling past midnight,
were you?
Because night travel is prohibited.
There are always strange incidents.
They even...
...take lives.
Mom?
What's wrong?
What's going on with you?
Gendis?
Your body is really hot.
Do you have a fever?
They're coming, Mom.
"They"?
Who are you talking about?
It smells bad.
Oh my, child. You have such a fever
that you're sleep talking.
I'll get you a compress, okay?
Mom.
Stay here.
I'm just going to get a compress.
You lie down.
Okay?
Just a moment, okay?
Gendis.
Why did you go out?
You have a really bad fever.
Come on, kid.
Come on, go to your room.
Gendis.
If you feel dizzy,
and your body feels hot again...
...tell Aunt Tika right away, okay?
Yes, Mom.
Finish your lunch.
- Be nice to auntie.
- Gendis.
Auntie.
Sorry I took so long.
You get ready. Let me handle this.
Gendis had a fever last night.
But she's better now.
Is my niece feeling better?
Yes. I kept applying compresses
last night.
She was sleep talking.
As a little kid...
...it's normal to sleep talk
when they have a fever.
I feel bad leaving her.
I feel uneasy.
Just focus on your work.
Child, I'm going to work, okay?
- Yes, Mom.
- I forgot.
Have you seen...
Wait a minute. Just a moment, Gendis.
Come on.
This...
Gendis can draw?
What's this, then?
You are entering Alas Roban area
Excuse me, ma'am.
Anto.
I just wanted to let you know
that yesterday's body
will be buried today.
Okay, I'll put it into the record.
Anto.
Was the one who found the body
the lady who runs the food stall?
Food stall?
Yes, the one right on the downhill bend...
...there's a food stall with a bathroom.
In Alas Roban?
Yes.
Gendis?
I'm bored.
Let's play.
What do you want to play?
Gendis?
What are you doing?
Auntie...
...I'm chatting with the food stall owner.
The food stall owner?
There's no one here, honey.
There is, Auntie.
Right in front of me.
Okay.
What do you want to do with me today?
Do you want to play with the doll?
No.
Wait...
So...
...what do you want
to do all day at home with me?
Play...
...hide and seek.
You're on guard, okay?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Gendis?
I found you.
Come on.
One...
Two...
Three!
Gendis?
Gendis! Don't run around.
Gendis!
Gendis, enough.
Enough, Gendis.
Gendis?
I'm not Gendis.
Auntie?
Gendis?
Gendis...
...have you apologized to Auntie Tika yet?
It's okay.
Sorry, Auntie.
Yes, honey.
No more running
around the house tomorrow, okay?
Yes, Mom.
Okay, go to your room.
Slowly.
It's fine.
She can do it herself.
Sita.
When I played with Gendis...
...I felt something...
There was something different about her.
I was confused.
How can she run that fast
without hitting anything?
And...
Her strength...
...was unnatural.
Mom!
Gendis?
You have a fever again.
Gendis.
It's me, your mom.
Mom is here.
Mom?
Mom!
Mom.
Just stay here.
With me.
No, I want to be with my mom!
Gendis!
Gendis?
Child, what's wrong?
Gendis, it's me, your mom.
It's me, your mom.
Gendis, it's me, darling.
Gendis, no...
There isn't anything.
It's me.
What's wrong? Honey, it's me, your mom.
Gendis, there's nothing there.
Gendis...
What do you think, Ma'am?
Well, it's a disturbance.
It could come from anywhere.
Moreover...
...Gendis is still a little kid.
Still innocent.
Many spirits like her.
Pretty girl...
...if anyone calls you...
...if anyone invites you...
...if your neck gets stiff...
...just refuse.
Don't let them in.
Okay?
The important thing is...
...get her to drink this later.
And here's another bottle...
Pour it around the house.
And don't forget the young coconut.
I've been worried
about this from the start.
Yes, but you didn't...
Drink this first.
The stall you saw
over there doesn't exist.
There's no lady, no one.
- Anto.
- There's only wilderness...
...and creatures we can't see.
The bus broke down, the magical food stall
that you and Gendis saw...
...was already a sign.
What sign?
here's something supernatural...
...following you...
...or Gendis.
Anto, please speak more slowly.
Sita doesn't understand things like this.
You know what happened
to my wife and child.
Yes, I understand.
- But I can't...
- What's going on?
Do you want to come with me?
My wife and child disappeared
while passing through Alas Roban at night.
Just like you,
they took a night bus trip...
...even though I had forbidden them.
They were found.
Their bodies were found a month later.
On the side of the road.
Oh, God!
Honey...
The Alas Roban myth really happened
to my wife and child.
I'm saying this
because I don't want any more victims.
You can't just use some
kind of bottled water or coconut water.
No way.
We have to get help.
Where should we go?
I have an acquaintance.
His name is Mbah Rejo.
He usually handles things like this.
Mom...
Mom!
Gendis?
Gendis!
Gendis, wake up.
Child, it's me, your mom!
Gendis.
Mom!
Gendis. It's me.
Tika.
- Gendis!
- Mom!
- Gendis.
- It's no use.
It won't work.
We have to take her to Mbah Rejo's place.
Sita.
We have to get out of here, Sita.
We have to take Gendis.
Come on.
Gendis...
There's a power...
...that's unusual...
...in this child's body.
An evil force...
...wants to control her body.
Gendis.
Kid.
Kid!
Gendis.
Mbah, what's wrong with her?
You're on the wrong path.
You humans...
...don't understand.
Gendis.
I...
...ask for God's protection.
The remaining soul...
...may the path back home
be made easy to eternity.
Gendis!
- It's me.
- Gendis.
Gendis...
Mbah, what's wrong with her?
What's wrong with her?
Tika!
You're...
...going the wrong way, Rejo.
That kid...
...would rather be with me.
No!
Poor thing.
Still not letting them go?
Mbah.
Leave this woman's body!
Go away!
It's not her body...
...that you should be worried about.
It's her soul.
Go back to where you came from!
Go home!
I ask for God's protection.
The soul of Dewi Raras...
- Tika...
- ...that still remains...
...may the path home be made easy...
...towards eternity.
Tika...
Tika!
Tika.
Tika?
Tika!
Gendis.
- Gendis?
- Tika...
Tika, are you okay?
Tika...
Dewi Raras' soul...
...the one who inhabits Alas Roban...
It's too strong.
Is that the figure following Gendis?
Yes.
But I'm sorry, I can't help you.
Gendis.
I'm sorry, okay?
I haven't been able
to give you a perfect life.
I'm sorry.
The bus he was driving pass midnight...
...plunged into a ravine...
...on a sharp bend...
...and a steep incline...
...in Alas Roban.
People usually call it...
...Skull Path.
Ma'am.
Excuse me.
We just found the bus driver's body
at the scene...
...while the bodies
of the other passengers
have not yet been found.
The bus driver who took me...
...passed Alas Roban that night...
...died.
His body was taken to the hospital.
Gendis.
Mom.
Gendis?
Gendis.
You don't love me.
Because I'm blind.
Because I'm blind!
My child!
Sita, this is a white monkey.
Are you sure Gendis drew this?
Who else?
Isn't white monkey...
...a myth that exists in Alas Roban?
The woman who was at the hospital...
Mrs. Ema?
That woman said something
about a white monkey.
She even knew I had seen a white monkey.
You also said that...
...that she knows a lot about Alas Roban?
She is quite famous.
The locals call her Pengayom Pasarean.
A sacred caretaker.
But as far as I know,
she's not like Mbah Rejo,
who usually handles things like this.
Well, I have to at least try.
I have to meet her.
There's no time left.
Anto, do you know
where Mrs. Ema's house is?
You're too late.
This child is already in Alur Gembok.
This is the gate.
Where you saw the white monkey.
Anyone who sees it
will experience misfortune.
Alas Roban used to be just a wilderness.
It supported life.
Until Ki Bahurekso arrived.
By envoy
of Sultan Hanyokrokusumo of Mataram.
He divided the wilderness...
...for human civilization.
Asphalt was laid
from upstream to downstream.
He is known for his success
in conquering the Alas Roban demons.
But what was agreed upon at that time
has been violated.
People instead turned Alas Roban
into a place of filth.
This forest was used as a dumping ground
for the bodies of victims
during the colonial era.
And this is what sparked the anger
of the guardians of Alas Roban.
Dewi Raras...
...she is known as the guardian of Alas
Roban.
It was Dewi Raras' anger...
...that made her try to invite anyone
who passed through Alas Roban at night...
...to join her world.
To this day, many terrifying stories
have emerged in Alas Roban.
And that's what happened to your daughter.
Isn't there anything we can do, Ma'am?
It's too late now.
Because anyone trapped in the Alur
Gembok...
...has less than seven days...
...to make it out alive.
Unless...
...we all return to Alas Roban...
...bringing your child.
Sita, wait.
Sita!
We have to try.
Maybe...
...this is the best way to save Gendis.
You heard it yourself, right?
Gendis was asked by the guardian there.
And what's the way out?
Bring Gendis back there?
Who can guarantee that she isn't in league
with the guardian of Alas Roban?
I don't want to go back there.
This is a suicide mission for all of us.
If I were you...
...I would kill myself for my child.
And if Gendis survives...
...who will she live with
if we're not here?
Gendis?
Gendis!
My child!
Sir, help me!
Yes, ma'am.
Sita.
Mrs. Ema told me
that something's wrong with Gendis.
How is she? Is she getting better?
She's getting farther away.
Time is running out.
If you don't want to lose her...
...we have to go back there immediately.
Before the day changes.
The longer it takes...
...the harder it is to save her.
Gendis.
Gendis, it's me, your mom.
Gendis!
Call the doctor!
There's no other way.
We have to go to Alas Roban now.
What should I do?
Can you?
Everything has been prepared.
They already know we're coming.
Lay her down.
O Most Gracious and Most Merciful God.
Forgive all mistakes of men...
...who are involved in many sins.
I'm begging before the ancestors...
...to open the invisible gate.
I come with a pure heart.
Don't disturb bad things.
I hope I'll be granted entry...
...and return home safely.
They won't let me in.
There's nothing else we can do.
Can I try?
Sita.
Sita, don't.
If you manage to get in...
...you go find your daughter.
Then come back here immediately.
Follow me.
I'm begging...
...in front of...
The ancestors.
Open...
...the invisible...
...gate.
I come...
...with a pure heart.
Don't bother...
...bad things.
I hope...
...I'll be granted entry.
And return home...
...safely.
Mom!
Gendis?
Gendis, it's me, your mom!
Gendis!
Sita...
Sinful!
Sita?
Ma'am?
What's wrong with her?
We must immediately ask
for Mbah Sakti's help.
Who is Mbah Sakti?
One of the descendants
of Pengayom Pasarean.
A native of Alas Roban.
Sir, could you please take me to Mbah
Sakti's house?
Okay, sir. Let's go.
Ma'am.
Sakti.
Help me.
We have to keep this gate open...
...until they return.
Wahyu.
Prepare everything now.
Yes, sir.
Come on, everyone.
Wake up, Sita...
Gendis...
Gendis!
Sita!
Sita.
Sita?
We need sendang water right away.
To calm her soul.
- Now!
- Let me do it, sir.
- Gendis?
- Mom?
Mom?
Gendis?
Mom!
Gendis!
- Mom!
- Gendis.
Gendis.
Gendis, it's me, your mom.
Gendis...
Mom.
No.
I'm...
...not your mother.
I'm not your mother!
They're getting farther away.
We have to keep the gate open.
Gendis?
Sita!
Sita.
Honey.
Sri?
Putri?
Sri...
Sri.
Leave this place.
Sri!
Ma'am.
Sita.
The ancestors...
...who are the ruler...
...of Alas Roban area...
I ask for forgiveness...
...because humans are always acting
recklessly...
...and making sin.
Where is my mom?
Your mom will be here soon.
Where am I?
In your new world.
Mom!
Gendis.
Gendis!
Mom!
- My child?
- Mom.
I can see.
Mom.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, my child.
Promise me you won't leave me again.
I won't.
I won't. Let's...
Let's go home now, okay?
Come on, kid.
Open the gate of heaven!
The gate of the earth!
The gate of the forest.
Mom!
Play the puppets!
Get up, Mom!
Go over there!
Over there, Gendis!
No, Mom! Come on, Mom. Get up.
Come on, Mom.
Gendis, look at me.
Hold my hand. Don't let go, okay?
Yes, Mom.
Let's close our eyes!
Keep going!
Keep going, don't stop!
Gendis!
Keep going! Until they come back!
Come on!
Where is Gendis?
No.
Give me back my child!
Please don't take Gendis.
I beg you.
No.
Give me back my child.
Your child will stay here.
No!
No! Please!
She's much better here.
With us, her presence...
...is much more appreciated.
Sita.
Gendis!
People who confess their sins...
...will return to purity.
Give me back my daughter...
- Delicious!
Gendis.
Give me back my daughter.
Give me back my daughter!
I beg you!
If I were you...
...I would kill myself for my child.
Take me!
Just take me! Take my soul!
Take everything! Take it!
Not my child! Please, not Gendis!
Take me!
But don't take my child!
Please, don't take Gendis!
Please don't take Gendis!
I beg you!
Gendis!
Gendis...
Gendis?
Sita?
No.
No...
No!
Don't leave me!
Don't! Don't leave me!
Gendis!
Ma'am, please... Please!
Give them back. Please!
Ma'am!
Gendis?
Gendis!
Auntie.
Where's Mom?
Here's your mom...
Mom?
You're really cold.
Wake up, Mom.
Ma'am.
She will never come back.
Mom!
Mom, wake up!
Mom.
Wake up, Mom...
Mom, wake up.
Do you know...
...who's the first person I want to see
after the eye surgery?
Gendis means sweet.
I always pray...
...that you have a sweet life.
Just like what you have given me.
You are my star of life, my child.
Thank you...
...for being in my life.
You must always remember...
...you are the most important thing
I ever had in this world.
I love you so much, Mom.
I love you too.
So much!
Yes.
Mom is beautiful.
Just like you, Gendis.
Thank you, Auntie.
You're welcome, dear.
Thank you, Doctor.
Nurse.
Thank you, Nurse.
Uncle Anto.
Thank you, Uncle Anto.
Mr. Yus.
Thank you, Mr. Yus.
OUR DEEPEST PRAYERS FOR THE VICTIMS
IN ALAS ROBAN.
MAY THEY BE GRANTED THE PLACE
BY THE SIDE OF ALMIGHTY GOD.
TO THIS DAY, THE MYTH OF ALAS ROBAN
STILL PERSISTS.
TO MOTORISTS PASSING BY,
FOR YOUR SAFETY, PLEASE ALWAYS BE ALERT...
...TO AVOID ANY UNWANTED INCIDENTS.
This is called the Padlock Channel
If someone goes missing there, it's
padlocked, they can't get out.
It's like a portal, right?
The one under the banyan tree
is a common occurrence.
The driver was followed.
Then, "You don't have to be like this,
you just come with me."
They got in into the car.
It smelled of blood.
Then he saw his face was all blood.
"You don't have to be like this,
you just come with me."
The one you often encounter
in Alas Roban...
...I used to find a skull.
That's why it's called the Skull Trail,
right, Ma'am?
Disposing of the corpse.
That person's greed.
Someone came and asked me.
"Sir, I want to ask, which one is the
restaurant here that has pecel lele?"
Oh, there aren't any.
He said, his friend had eaten there.
- There's a banyan tree down there.
- The white one.
About 300-400 meters,
which means it's down here.
- Yes, down here.
- There's nothing there.
Yes, this Alas can be said to be haunted.
Yes, if...
...if you don't waste money,
sometimes you can enter another realm.
I used to pass through Alas Roban often.
And there were a lot of accidents there.
From our ancestors, there must be a wayang
performance once a year...
...there is a wayang performance, sir.
If there is no wayang performance,
sometimes there are disasters.
Disaster.
The supernatural spirit is here.
In the Poncowati area.
Around Poncowati, it's called
Gunung Tunggal. White tiger.
- The forest here has been cleared.
- But there are a lot of tigers.
But they're not real tigers,
they're ghosts.
Some saw them, some didn't.
ALAS ROBAN HAS LONG BEEN KNOWN
FOR VARIOUS THINGS,
FOLKLORE THAT IS EMBEDDED
IN PEOPLE'S MINDS
NOW, THE AREA AROUND ALAS ROBAN
HAS UNDERGONE MANY CHANGES.
VARIOUS INFRASTRUCTURE DEVELOPMENTS
CONTINUE TO BE BUILT.
THIS AREA HAS EVEN TRANSFORMED INTO
AN INTEGRATED INDUSTRIAL AREA.
NEVERTHELESS, THE IDENTITY OF ALAS ROBAN
REMAINS THE RESULT
OF VERY LONG HISTORICAL ROOTS
...FROM THE STORIES AND NOBLE VALUES
THAT LIVE IN SOCIETY.
REGENT OF BATANG REGENCY
THIS STORY IS A WORK OF FICTION.
ANY SIMILARITIES IN NAMES, CHARACTERS,
PLACES, OR EVENTS...
...WITH REAL PEOPLE OR EVENTS ARE
SOLELY COINCIDENCE...
...AND NOT INTENDED INTENTIONALLY.