Watch on kissasia.li
=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 36=
Where do you think you are going,
Leng Xin?
So you were hiding in Liuhe Temple.
My master will be angry
if I act on my own.
But if I kill you,
he will forgive me.
Leng Xin, King of Killers.
You slaughter innocents
and treat lives as dirt.
A thousand deaths are on your hands.
The Bounty List offers
ten thousand gold for you.
Dead or alive.
Xintian, can you hit
my new mini thunderfire bomb?
I will use fake thunderfire bombs
to split them up.
Find your chance and shoot Leng Xin.
Young Master Chang!
Hua!
Surround the gate!
Yes!
Leng Xin.
Do you serve Prince Fu
or the Crown Prince?
I won't tell you.
You think you won?
Who said Leng Xin was only one person?
What do you mean?
Are you really Leng Xin or not?
You want to know?
Then I will never give you the answer.
Are you the real Leng Xin or not?
Guokai!
(Righteousness of Heaven and Earth)
(Jinyiwei Northern Bureau)
You are saying
she was not Leng Xin?
Then who?
My lord.
Look at Taozi's age.
Could she be the Leng Xin
who killed my father and the witness?
What do you mean?
I mean,
Leng Xin may not be one person.
What else could she be? A ghost?
Leng Xin may be a group of people.
Or an organization.
Do you have proof?
No.
I thought you might fight
with Zhang again.
Not anymore.
I'm no longer that Shen Bingfan,
always angry and quick to lose control.
I advised the Commander
to handle this quietly.
Bingfan.
You have grown up.
As for Leng Xin,
I will keep investigating.
But
I won't rush anymore.
(Honest and Upright)
Good.
This Ghost Festival,
our Northern Bureau laid
a brilliant Empty Fort trap
and eliminated
(Honest and Upright)
Leng Xin, the Bounty List's top killer.
Excellent.
In this operation,
our female Jinyiwei acted swiftly
and planned well.
I already
reported this
to His Majesty.
His Majesty heard the news
and was greatly pleased.
He has
formally promoted
Shen Bingfan to Qianhu.
Hua Mange
and Cheng Xintian
are formally promoted to Baihu.
Xu Duoyu
is promoted to
Chief Squad Leader.
We thank His Majesty
for his boundless grace.
Long live His Majesty!
Good.
The spring wind dares
to brush the willows.
The night rain comes unseen
to nourish the flowers.
Take him!
Go!
Shen Bingfan.
Until we meet again
in the martial world.
Feng Fuliu really is alive.
Is he?
You don't seem surprised.
Now you have something to do.
Yes.
As long as he is alive,
I won't stop chasing him.
Then, when will you
come home with me to meet my parents?
Beiming.
Tomorrow. Same place.
I will give you an answer.
(Hua.)
(Forgive me.)
(The Leng Xin who killed my parents
is still out there.)
(Until that person is caught,)
(I cannot confess my feelings to you.)
(Spirit of My Beloved Fa Yuanrong)
Yuanrong.
We finally avenged you.
(Spirit Tablet of My Sworn Brother,
Lord Shen Lian, Qianhu)
(Spirit Tablet of My Sworn Brother)
Shen.
Our secret
is safe for now.
Father.
Mother.
(Grave of My Late Parents)
Leng Xin has been brought to justice.
But I know
she was not the Leng Xin who killed you.
So I won't give up.
I will keep investigating.
I will catch every Leng Xin
and bring them all to justice.
Father.
You taught me
what justice is,
what courage is,
and what fairness means.
So no matter who you were
or what your true allegiance was,
I will always
follow what I know is right.
With a righteous heart,
one is invincible.
♪Whose face crosses my mind♪
I'm here.
Today,
♪I whisper in my heart♪
I will give you my answer.
♪Yet in the crowd, we brush past♪
♪Only then did I understand fate♪
♪Was hidden in the day we met♪
♪A fate that cannot be severed♪
♪Round and round♪
♪Threads of love bind us together♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪I wish you♪
♪could hear♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪Tucked away♪
♪inside my heart♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪I wish you could hear♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪Tucked away inside my heart♪
(Leng Xin)
Master, this is Leng Xin's sword.
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪