Watch on kissasia.li
=Angels and Guards=
=Episode 35=
Then what exactly is
the jade token used to command you?
Just a jade token. What else?
No one below a prince or high noble
could ever possess one.
It is priceless.
I see.
Someone central to the case,
and someone with the power
to command you.
That leaves only two princes.
Prince Fu and the Crown Prince.
You ask
too many questions.
Did you kill Guan Yunfeng?
Right!
Guan Yunfeng.
He should not have found out my secret.
He should not have found out
I knew martial arts.
So,
I had to kill him.
Do you understand now?
Do you understand?
Guan Yunfeng was protecting you.
How could you do it?
Protecting me?
Leng Xin needed him to save?
That is hilarious!
Guan Yunfeng was a real man.
He deserved better.
He deserved so much better!
I was such a fool.
Before he died, Guan said it.
Taozi.
Leng Xin.
Why didn't I see it?
You monster.
You will die horribly!
I'm sure I will!
But you won't live to see it!
Fine.
Then kill me.
Use your cruelest method.
The one you are best at!
Don't worry.
You are Xintian's dear sister.
I won't make it hurt too much.
Die!
♪In a fleeting moment♪
♪Whose face crosses my mind♪
♪Whose name is it♪
♪I whisper in my heart♪
♪Yet in the crowd, we brush past♪
♪Only then did I understand fate♪
♪Was hidden in the day we met♪
♪A fate that cannot be severed♪
♪Round and round♪
♪Threads of love bind us together♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪I wish you could hear♪
♪Afraid love will fade like smoke♪
♪Afraid memories will fade like dreams♪
♪This longing I cannot say♪
♪Tucked away inside my heart♪
I killed her.
Good! Another one dead.
Go join Guan Yunfeng.
Xintian! Xintian!
Xintian!
She is dead.
Nothing stands between us now.
Will you run away with me?
Run away with you?
After all the people you killed?
In your dreams!
Xintian.
I killed because
I was raised to be a killer.
Killing is all I know.
If I didn't kill, I couldn't survive.
But I don't like killing.
Xintian.
You are the only one
who was ever kind to me.
I truly care about you.
Let's go.
Let's leave this all behind.
I will care for you like my own sister.
Please, Xintian. Come with me.
Taozi.
Just looking at you now
makes me sick.
I regret it.
I regret being kind to you.
I regret taking you in.
Someone like you...
After killing so many people,
you deserve to be cut to pieces.
You should rot in hell!
I was so good to you.
Why would you curse me?
Curse you?
I want to do more than curse you.
I want to kill you!
I will kill you with my own hands!
Fake.
It was all fake.
Everything you did for me
was fake!
Yes.
It was fake.
Did you really think
someone as evil as you
deserved kindness?
No one will ever love you.
You are just a pathetic thing
nobody cares!
I will ask you one last time.
Are you coming with me?
Are you coming?
Tell me!
Never.
Fine.
Then die.
Go join the dead.
I'll send you there.
I'll kill you!
Wait.
You are scared.
Beg me.
Taozi.
No.
Leng Xin.
I could never be afraid of you.
Listen to me.
Untie me if you have the nerve.
Fight me.
Fight you?
You?
You want to fight me?
Xintian.
You are adorable.
What is wrong? Are you scared?
You don't dare, do you?
You don't dare.
Fine!
You are my dear sister.
I will listen to you.
I will untie you.
Let's fight.
Hurry up.
Come on.
You are older than me.
I will give you three moves.
Leng Xin.
I will kill you myself.
Take him!
Who did you say you were?
Mr. Duan, I'm...
You are an assassin.
I'm not!
Take him somewhere no one can see.
Yes!
Move!
Let go of me!
Stop!
Mr. Lu.
Lu.
What was that you shouted?
His name is Xu Duoyu.
He is a registered Squad Leader
of our Northern Bureau.
He is no assassin.
Even a Jinyiwei
cannot force his way
into the imperial city.
I have urgent confidential business.
I must see Young Duke Chang Beiming.
Confidential business?
That sounds reasonable enough.
Entering the imperial city
without an edict or golden token
is treason.
I could execute him on the spot,
and no one could fault me.
Mr. Duan.
He is with our Northern Bureau.
Lu Guokai.
What rank are you?
You dare bargain with me here?
You are not qualified.
Then am I
qualified enough?
Mr. Zhang.
Are you all right?
Mr. Zhang, if I don't get inside,
disaster may fall
on the Northern Bureau.
Guokai.
Return to the Bureau at once.
Yes.
Zuo Da. Jiang Biao.
Stay and guard the imperial city.
Yes.
The rest of you,
come with me.
Yes.
Zhang Weimin, why are you everywhere?
This is not your
Northern Bureau's post. How dare you!
Zhang Weimin, you dare hit me?
Mr. Duan, are you all right?
You...
I told you.
You cannot beat me.
Leng Xin.
Today, either you die
or I do.
You are mad!
You think I won't kill you?
Leng Xin.
You are a coward!
What did you say?
I said you are a coward.
You want people to be kind to you,
but you are terrified when they are.
You want to be loved,
yet you are afraid of it.
You fear your master.
You are nothing but his weapon!
How pathetic!
Shut up.
I will kill you.
I will kill you!
(Young Duke.)
(Taozi is Leng Xin.)
(Bingfan and Xintian are in danger.)
How are you alive?
Without this little act,
how could we make you tell the truth?
An act?
I knew it
as soon as Bingfan started.
Everything just now
was meant to provoke you.
(Then kill me.)
(Use your cruelest method.)
(The one you are best at!)
Understand now?
I don't believe it.
I checked.
She had no pulse!
There was blood at her mouth.
Taozi.
No.
Leng Xin.
You are far too sure of yourself.
I knew Leng Xin likes to kill
with one thrust to the heart.
So,
thank you for the fruit.
I put an orange under my arm.
When you checked my pulse,
I squeezed it tight
and cut off the blood flow.
So you felt nothing.
As for the heart you stabbed,
and why it felt no different,
Duoyu knew you might try that.
So he made
a soft armor called Trueheart.
It has blood pouches inside.
When pierced,
it feels exactly like the real thing.
It even bleeds.
The blood at my mouth?
I bit myself.
You...
You tricked me!
Leng Xin.
Today is the Ghost Festival.
It will also be your death day.
Don't run!
You sneaky wildcat.
Don't let her escape.
Get her!
Take men and put out the fire.
Yes!
The rest, follow me!
Put out the fire!
Put it out!
♪Because you once entered my dreams♪
♪Truth and illusion blur in wine♪
♪My heart drifted lost♪
♪Yet found you in the crowd♪
♪My blood still burns
as the world surges♪
♪The land is fair, and you are free♪
♪Sword drawn, lost in obsession♪
♪I've softly let it go♪
♪The vow you made was true♪
♪Yet like clouds, it stops for no one♪
♪Put away those dreamlike words♪
♪And forget at world's end♪
♪Embracing memory♪
♪Through blossoms and dreams♪
♪You hide in the crowd, silent♪
♪I wish to let it pass♪
♪And run toward this vast life♪