( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Sayaka, we were best friends.
The one who drugged Sayaka
was her friend from middle school.
Sayaka!
I became the detective for Sayaka's sake.
For my beloved wife.
It gave me a real sense of purpose.
Sayaka would never know pain in her life.
That's none of your concern!
And when I finally caught the culprit...
I could feel the dopamine overflowing.
To give me such pleasure...
I'm truly blessed
to marry a woman like Sayaka.
Don't worry, Sayaka.
Everything has been resolved.
How can you eat,
given the circumstances?
I need to make up
for the wedding money I gave.
What are we going to do about her?
Report her?
Let's not get hasty.
She drugged Sayaka!
She gave her sleeping pills.
That's nothing lethal.
Then what about the threat you sent?
Threat?
Don't play dumb. I'm asking about the letter.
What letter?
I love you, Sayaka.
Kazu. What do you think "true love" means?
You really are a dummy, Sayaka.
The two of us staying together.
That's "true love".
Sayaka?
What the... What's going on?
Sayaka? What's happened to you?
Are you two getting married?
So am I! Look!
There's my husband!
How do I deal with this?
How can I make myself look "normal"?
He's always by my side,
and loves me, no matter what.
That's it.
He told me,
She's had her wedding ruined.
staying together...
Not once, but twice.
is "true love"!
It's causing Sayaka to break down.
I love you, too.
Let's stay together forever, and ever!
Is this something she'll recover from?
If she doesn't,
does she become my responsibility?
This crazy woman will stay with me, for life?
Stay back!
- What's up with that?
- He pushed her.
- What's she going to do?
- She said they were getting married?
Yikes.
Don't go.
Kazu, please. Don't toss me aside.
You won't, right?
You vowed to love me for life.
No. I can't. I can't deal with this.
You just said you loved me.
This woman is done for.
I can't look after her for life.
I've got no obligation to.
Right. A divorce.
Sayaka.
Staying with me won't help you.
I only wanted you to become happy, but...
It seems I can't give you that happiness.
I'm sorry.
That was embarrassing.
What?
I knew it.
You don't love me at all.
I've had enough.
Let's get divorced.
Stunned?
That was all just an act, Kazu.
There's something you've misunderstood.
You must think Honoka sent the threat.
But she didn't.
I put that letter in the post myself.
You did?
This was all planned out?
The threat, and the sleeping pills, too?
No.
The sleeping pills weren't a part of my plan.
I didn't even notice Ueno
was "Honoka Aizawa".
I can't believe she still holds a grudge
for what happened in middle school.
What a shocker.
Though I admit, she helped me with my tests.
So I guess I'm grateful to her.
What tests?
Test one.
How would you react, upon reading the threat?
Test two.
Would you accept me, past and all?
Test three.
Would you support me,
even if I attempted suicide?
No, don't tell me...
Of course I wasn't going to kill myself.
What the hell?
You were amazing, Kazu.
You had perfect scores across the board!
Until now.
Test four.
Would you still love me, if I lost my mind?
Unfortunately, you failed my final test.
What a shame.
In any case, we're over.
I'll send you the divorce papers,
and submit them to your office tomorrow.
No, you can't.
Please, give me another chance.
A divorce after the wedding?
Think of the rumors...
I love you.
You just pretended like you didn't know me.
You pushed me aside,
and said you couldn't make me happy.
Your declaration of "true love" was a sham.
Don't let some tests decide
there was no love between us.
I had already decided to accept your past.
If that's not love, then what is?
You're being patronizing.
"Accept your past"?
You think you're so magnanimous.
I've always disliked how you belittled me.
You only wanted a girl,
who was weaker and submissive to you.
No, that's not true.
You don't love me.
You love how you feel
when you're supporting a weak girl.
No, I...
I love you, Sayaka.
Really, again?
You're acting like a foolish parrot.
What exactly do you love about me?
I...
I love that you're a great cook.
Okay, and?
I love that you're docile.
So you love how I'm subservient.
And?
I love how our bodies are compatible.
Then why not hire a housemaid,
and buy a doll to pleasure yourself?
Good bye.
Don't you dare run, Sayaka.
Who'd love an easy woman like you?
Me, that's who.
Hear me?
You'd end up the same with any man.
Make yourself that marketable
"depressed girl", why don't you?
No.
No, no... I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry, Sayaka. Let's talk this out, okay?
We're husband and wife now.
Sayaka?
Thank you for the warning.
Sayaka.
A bit of advice, for your sake.
Don't ever recover, okay?
Because if you do, he'll toss you aside.
Like he did with me.
Why would you say that?
I'm not so benevolent
that I'd wish for your happiness.
When she collapsed, I got chills.
I couldn't help but record the whole thing.
You're the worst.
No.
You are.
I was first suspicious when you invited her
to our wedding at all.
But...
- Akira's just a friend.
- No, she's not.
Akira...
is your previous wife, isn't she?
Was it so wrong to invite her?
Who would want to see
their husband's ex-wife at their wedding?
Think of me, who had to see her ex-husband
doting on his new wife.
Why do you think our guest list was so short?
You and your constant remarriages...
But now we're just...
"Friends"? Of course not.
Wait, you still...
What? Don't be stupid.
You play the "good guy",
but think nothing of how others feel.
The hell?
I bet Sayaka gets depressed too,
just like I used to.
You sure love your mentally ill girls, huh?
As we spent time together,
I slowly recovered.
I was appreciative of you, and our marriage.
But you clearly didn't agree.
You couldn't be happy for her.
I said I'd support...
You wanted to support me so badly?
Pathetic.
I thought it was for the best.
I searched for the culprit, for your sake.
You were just enjoying yourself.
It was the spice to your mundane life.
I just...
Did it for the sake of your "beloved wife"?
Then of course you'd work hard.
I just wanted to protect you.
Get a life.
Protect you, support you, blah, blah, blah.
You certainly love to wax poetic.
Your support is barely surface level.
I was happy to hear you work for "my sake".
But it was really
for your own self-satisfaction.
Kazuomi. Do you want Sayaka to become happy?
- Huh?
- Do you honestly want her to find happiness?
Of course, I...
Thought so.
I could tell, you know?
You wanted me to stay
a depressed, obedient girl.
Otherwise you can't be the hero.
No.
All that "good intent"
you love preaching about?
It was never for anyone else's sake.
Everything you do comes right back at you,
and serves to boosts your own ego.
So quit saying it's for "my sake".
You seriously give me the creeps.
Then...
Then what should I have done?
I sacrificed so much for you.
Hey. Quit playing the victim.
You think you've been so charitable.
But that "kindness",
is only a burden to others.
[Sayaka Wakamatsu]
A broken-hearted man turns over a new leaf,
and preaches "love", like Romeo.
But Kazuomi Hayashida is no Romeo.
He is a self-conceited clown.
You know your mother needs you, Sapphire.
When he declared this woman was a stalker,
I couldn't help but laugh.
If he knew this was my mother,
I bet that man
would use his self-serving "good intentions"
as an excuse for the mistake.
You haven't returned
any of the money I lent you.
Sapphire, please.
This is the last time.
Now that's my son.
I love you!
Love you lots!
Did your mother leave?
Good morning, Sayaka.
Morning.
You're in high spirits, Sakuraba.
Maybe it's because you stayed the night.
I needed the perfect subject
for my exhibition to be recognized.
And when I saw her, wedding dress and all,
I knew she was the one.
Can I get some shots today?
From behind my camera,
the Hayashida couple
felt like a sham wrapped in a bow.
So I made a proposition.
Why not test to see
if your husband truly loves you?
Can you edit this picture for me?
I want to see if he will still love me,
even if I'm not the woman he thought I was.
A rash individual like Kazuomi
never had this thought cross his mind.
That the "nice guy" who assisted him,
had a very hand in the threat.
Let alone plotted the downfall
of their married life itself.
Yes, she's the perfect subject.
And now she's all mine.
I wish I'd met you earlier, Sakuraba.
Then I could've avoided
that narcissist entirely.
She instinctively seeks a host
who will save her.
This woman,
who so quickly abandoned that man,
now attempts to feed off of me.
Received any new love letters recently?
He hasn't sent any more after the 10th one.
"I was wrong."
"I'm happy to see you moving on, Sayaka."
"If possible, I want to be at your side."
I couldn't read any more than that.
I'm here for you now.
I can't believe I met someone like you.
I'm truly blessed.
Are you, now?
I only fell for her face.
I have no earnest love for her.
[Loveri]
"You've been matched with Yuki".
What's this about?
You're so busy with work all the time.
- I got lonely.
- I don't tolerate any cheating.
I wouldn't want any diseases
transmitting to her.
I'm sorry.
I won't.
I'll delete the app, and my account, too.
She needs to be educated.
Do you promise to only look at me?
I love you.
You love me too, right?
Of course.
Let's continue our photoshoot.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
I must make Sayaka
the absolute, perfect subject.
So I'll correct her flaws, one by one.
Everything is for her sake.
Not.
Are the people around you
truly as good as they say they are?
Do you, the groom,
take her as your lawfully wedded wife?
Yes, I do.
Is the person you're facing now,
truly taking action for your sake?