( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Sakuraba.
This ceremony will help Sayaka and I move on.
You didn't invite Kaori Wakamatsu.
She may be Sayaka's mother.
But she's also the culprit.
Hayashida.
I've made a massive oversight.
Mrs. Wakamatsu?
One moment, please.
I am the bride's mother.
Allow me to inform Mr. Hayashida first.
The culprit may be someone else entirely.
[Gentlemen]
Jesus, how many times will we repeat this?
As many times as we need to.
Kazuomi doesn't seem to mind.
They could at least refund us
for our first wedding gifts.
He's practically ripping us off.
Sayaka has such bad taste.
[Ladies]
It's like our warning meant nothing to her.
Do you think they'll last a year?
Absolutely not.
Especially with that husband of hers.
You ought to consider canceling.
No. We won't be canceling.
Sayaka and I prepared ourselves for this day.
This is for Sayaka's sake.
Folks, please ready your glasses.
Your glasses, please.
To the bride and groom's blessed future.
Cheers.
Folks, I thank you all for attending today.
How delicious.
We will now present a special slideshow
of the happy memories shared
between the illustrious bride and groom.
Please, sit back and enjoy.
[September 14th, 1993 - Kazuomi]
[July 24th, 2000 - Sayaka]
- There's Sayaka!
- So adorable.
[When she smiles wide, her eyes close! Cute!]
[A big fan of pigtails]
[Feeling like a princess!]
[Class A]
Did you add a slide?
This powerpoint isn't the correct one.
Sakuraba?
So, you were Sayaka's classmate.
Did you drug Sayaka
with the sleeping pill?
Sleeping pill?
He lost me.
What are you talking about?
This is a photograph from our last ceremony.
As you can see, Sayaka's champagne
has turned a dark blue.
What?
Her drink looked normal
in a picture five minutes prior.
Who is he, Sherlock Holmes?
Let him have his fun.
As a person working backstage,
your presence would be easily forgotten.
You took advantage of this fact,
and snuck up on Sayaka in that time.
You had to have, for one reason.
"Your violin performance will begin shortly."
"Please head backstage to get ready."
That'd distract Sayaka from her glass, no?
Then you'd simply call for the guests
to drink their champagne.
Why would I do something like that?
A student in Sayaka's middle school album
caught our eye.
One with your first name, and face.
"Honoka Aizawa".
That's you, isn't it?
I'll assume your last name
changed upon marriage.
Why didn't you tell us?
So what if we were middle school classmates?
These are baseless accusations.
We have proof, of course.
What?
Here's a video from the last ceremony
that captures what occurred,
right after Sayaka collapsed.
One particular individual
had kept her camera rolling the entire time.
This is the video from the ceremony.
I wouldn't include it in the slideshow.
Sayaka!
Sayaka?
You're holding a champagne glass here, no?
You had to retrieve the tainted glass.
After the ceremony, it was reported missing.
I heard no one could find it.
Until the next day,
when it had magically turned up again.
I suspect you returned the glass,
after washing the substances out.
As a staff member here,
it would be entirely possible for you.
You drugged Sayaka, didn't you?
What an unnecessary video.
You're correct.
I drugged Sayaka.
What the hell? You could've...
Wait.
Honoka.
Why?
Really?
You're asking that, now?
You messed up my life.
What, so she was crazy in middle school, too?
Didn't you all know someone like her?
A girl the bullies wouldn't touch,
despite having no backbone?
Well, that's exactly who Sayaka was.
Aizawa is indeed my maiden name.
You're right that I was her classmate, too.
But did you know Sayaka and I
were best friends?
Best friends?
Why would you hurt your friend?
"Why"?
Has Sayaka ever told you...
about the time she shoplifted?
Shoplifted? Wow...
Sayaka would never. Right?
She did.
You're falling right for her "weak" act.
Lies.
Sayaka tried to steal a bra.
I was her co-conspirator.
We attempted to shoplift together.
And we failed.
The rumors spread through the school
like wildfire.
But...
I wasn't scared, because I had Sayaka.
I planned that shoplifting scheme
for her sake.
And what did I get in return?
She said I forced her to join me.
Sayaka would never lie.
Her lie turned me
into the "bad girl" of the school.
Middle school was hell for me.
I'm sorry.
Sayaka.
Don't apologize to a scumbag like her.
Our classmates treated me like trash.
They'd call me a "slut", or an "easy girl".
They'd post videos of me,
crawling around to find my school bag.
Sayaka watched it all happen,
without saying a word.
And here I thought we were best friends.
Hilarious, right?
Sayaka couldn't speak up.
When I was forced to bow down,
and apologize to her.
She only looked down on me in silence.
How did you even feel?
Why did you have to bow down to her?
The bullies. They pressured me to apologize.
I'm sorry I forced you to shoplift.
I'm sorry.
Because I was the "bad girl",
who pressured her friend into theft.
But you...
You didn't even remember who I was.
I got over my trauma,
married someone I loved,
and found my dream job.
I had finally gotten my life back on track.
Only for you to come stumbling in
as one of my customers.
It had been a decade since I saw you,
and I still felt like puking on the spot.
That's why you drugged her?
This is ridiculous.
- What?
- You have ruined this sacred moment for us.
Shut it, you toxic mother.
You're the root of all this.
The root?
This woman couldn't stand to see
her own daughter become a woman.
She wouldn't buy a bra,
or menstrual pads for her.
Let alone give her the money
to buy them herself.
- That's how this woman is.
- Quiet.
And since she had no money,
I proposed she shoplifted instead.
Your daughter had to wear
her one sports bra to tatters.
Enough, this is just uncouth.
"Dirty."
"Filthy."
"Clean up after yourself."
That's what you told your daughter
when she got her first period.
I am Sayaka's mother.
I am allowed to raise her as I wish.
That attitude is exactly
what makes you toxic.
Sayaka was only your doll.
You were raising her
to look good as a mother.
No one even invited you today.
I have had enough of this slander!
I was suspected
of drugging my beloved daughter.
Could you people be more disrespectful?
Your accusations were entirely baseless!
This woman is the culprit.
Everything was her fault.
Don't act like you're so innocent, hag.
"Hag"?
Your parenting is at fault.
Were you irritated to see Sayaka mature?
To watch her become a woman?
Ironic, given you're a woman yourself.
Aren't parents happy see their kids grow?
It's because she's a woman.
Pardon?
It's because Sayaka is a woman.
I always wanted a baby boy.
What a rotten bunch.
You and your daughter both.
Let's settle down.
You've had enough, no?
Sayaka had a stomach ulcer.
Your pill may not even be at fault.
My daughter is all better now.
We shall simply pretend this never happened.
Now if you will excuse me.
Don't run.
You can't turn a blind eye to this.
Please, just stop.
"Stop"?
It's too late for stopping, Sayaka.
Do you want my forgiveness?
Then apologize to me.
"I'm sorry I forgot.
I'm sorry I stomped my friend into the dirt."
Get on your knees and apologize, now.
Don't bow down to her.
What? Still taking her side?
Let me take this opportunity to inform you.
Sayaka's exceptional at coaxing out
the "good-intentions" of those around her.
She's a parasite who feeds off of it.
That's a bit...
And, Kazuomi Hayashida.
You have just become her new host.
Congratulations.
Kazuomi. Kazuomi!
Calm down!
Damn it!
Are you satisfied?
Drugging your friend for the sake of revenge.
I never wanted to kill Sayaka.
What's so funny?
You would've gotten away with it,
if you knew about the changing color.
Oh, I knew.
I used that pill on purpose.
What?
Your blue champagne
gave me the brilliant idea.
I would mix this pill
into her precious drink.
I wanted to taint her memories.
I wanted her to flounder
in front of all your guests.
That was all I was aiming for.
That, "was all"?
I never thought
she'd start coughing up blood.
Your excuses mean nothing.
Kazuomi, back down.
I'm telling you, I never planned to kill her.
Sayaka. You believe me, right?
We were best friends, after all.
Just so it's known,
I drugged Sayaka for her sake.
For her sake?
I had to take extreme measures.
Or Sayaka would never know pain in her life.
That's none of your concern!
You say it was for her sake.
But your act of "good-will",
was nothing more than petty revenge.
Try telling the police you meant well.
I'm sure they'll be thoroughly convinced.
Finally, it's over.
This time for sure.
I've snuffed out everyone
who wishes harm on Sayaka.
I've managed to protect her.
Sayaka?
Sayaka!