( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Limpy
If I go all out,
I won't be able to control myself.
When my strength runs out,
remember to take me with you.
No need to go that hard.
Since when do people from Black Street
start putting their lives
in other people's hands?
Old Gu,
your temper hasn't changed a bit.
Always picking on the weak.
You're here.
Then I'll go take a breather.
Go on.
You old geezer,
why are you here too?
My son is here.
Of course I had to come.
Let's get out of here.
If we stay any longer,
this old geezer's gonna drop dead from rage.
You and your son can leave.
But they
have to stay here.
After all,
the Imperial Capital
isn't a place just anyone can mess with.
Uncle Gu,
these are Shanhai City's people.
We have to leave together.
Young man,
some matters
aren't for you to meddle in.
I know.
As a junior, perhaps
I'm not qualified to speak with you.
But at least in this moment,
I represent Shanhai City.
As long as they live in Shanhai City,
they are our people.
If we can't even protect
our own citizens,
then Shanhai City
will lose its very foundation.
Wouldn't you agree?
Shanhai City can't be insulted,
but the Imperial Capital can?
If they die here,
it all ends.
Protect them,
and you won't be leaving either.
If Uncle Gu insists on fighting,
then Shanhai City
will oblige you to the very end.
Old Liu,
is this your stance too?
Help me down, would you?
My legs have gone numb.
Sitting on this thing
is uncomfortable.
Old Gu,
do you really want to fight?
I admit you're strong,
but the Imperial Capital
isn't weak either.
Son,
let me show you what your old man can do.
Know why they call me Liu Wudi?
Because I
am invincible in this era.
Afraid to die?
Actually,
I'd like to experience it.
Invincible in this era.
Sword Rain!
What kind of immortal art is this?
That's a character from the MMO Xiankui,
the Gentleman Sword's second skill,
unlocked at level 15.
I've played it.
Don't tell me what blessed him
was a video game.
No.
It's just that his immortal spirit power
is overwhelmingly abundant,
so he developed his own techniques.
In other words,
the rest of us walk the original immortal path,
but he
has forged a new one.
He
is truly cultivating immortality,
an immortal path of his own.
Nature as essence, spirit as function
Cultivate both to attain the immortal path
The human heart is perilous, the Dao heart subtle
Be refined, be one, hold to the mean
The human heart is, in essence, the heavenly heart
Human heart is Dao heart, Dao heart is Heaven's heart
Originally one, divided through neglect
Thus split into two functions
Liu Wudi's third skill:
One Spear Pierces the Heavens!
I knew it.
All those losses weren't my fault.
Used outside, these skills...
they work incredibly well!
My teammates were just trash.
It's not on me.
Old Daoist,
You holding up?
I've got a few more ideas here.
Want to try them?
You up for it?
Brilliant Starlight!
That name alone sounds powerful.
What?
Let's try again.
Come on.
Why is there no damage output?
What the hell?
What went wrong?
I didn't fully replicate the game skill.
Just borrowed the look.
Could it be...
I'm out of mana?
Old Gu,
How are things on your end?
Can you still fight?
Compared to back then,
you've gotten stronger.
Not too shabby.
I remember as kids,
I beat you spoiled young masters
till you didn't even dare look me in the eye.
Now that we're grown,
it should be the same.
I remember one time,
I dragged you into the bathroom...
Shut up!
Today,
what you and I represent
are the Imperial Capital
and Shanhai City.
This pointless nonsense
needs to stop.
I'll ask you just one thing.
Is Shanhai City
ready to go to war with the Imperial Capital?
No, no, no.
Shanhai City can't beat the Imperial Capital.
In that case,
why do you dare provoke me?
Shanhai City can't beat the Imperial Capital,
but I can beat you.
I guarantee
no matter who stands in front of you,
from this distance,
I can kill you.
So sign a written guarantee
to make it official:
These troublemakers
will be taken back to Shanhai City for handling.
Everything that happened at the Imperial Capital
has nothing to do with Shanhai City.
Are you threatening me?
That's right.
I am threatening you.
Will you sign it or not?
Waters of the Heavenly River!
Dark clouds press down, the city about to fall!
Look, you got it all dirty.
Chengfeng, quick, quick.
Come on.
That Uncle Gu of yours,
he's getting on in years.
Can't even hold a notebook steady.
I'll wait for Shanhai City's word
on how they handle that crew.
Let's go.
Let's see how he wrote it.
No problem.
He just left like that?
Don't let his pathetic act fool you.
This guy is rotten to the core.
As long as I don't actually kill him,
he'll always find a way to stab me in the back.
Now that he knows my true strength,
he won't give me another chance
to get close to him.
No matter how strong a person is,
they still fear a scumbag.
Wonder which cities they'll screw over this time.
At least Shanhai City won't get caught up in it.
That's good enough.
Gentlemen,
any other thoughts?
He still owes Black Street two lives.
More than two people died
in the Imperial Capital.
Forget it.
Mark it down in the ledger.
We'll collect when the chance comes.
Regardless,
we have to give Old Gu some face.
Black Street will close down for two years.
Any objections?
None here.
Then it's settled.
Once we reopen,
if you try to kill anyone in Shanhai City,
I'll still step in.
Xiaofeng, let's go.
You go on ahead.
I've got something to take care of.
Alright then.
Why does he think we enjoy killing?
I'm sick of it already.
Tongtong doesn't like it.
I can recite ten full Buddhist scriptures
on the virtues of peace and kindness.
You know that stuff too?
Just a little.
Let's go.
Mission accomplished.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Master Mao's press conference
for "Above the Immortals"
is now officially beginning.
Alright, alright, alright.
Hello.
This manga is incredibly popular right now.
The redemption and emotion throughout
have moved us deeply.
I'd like to ask,
under what circumstances did you
get the inspiration for this manga?
First of all,
thank you all for loving this work.
As for the question
about my inspiration,
it's because
one day,
I saw a brother and sister
walking down the street.
The sister was gravely ill, beyond cure.
The brother carried her on his back,
seeking doctors and medicine all the way.
Even when faced with cruel fate,
even facing such injustice in life,
they never abandoned each other.
The brother protected his sister.
The sister cared deeply for her brother.
They were each other's warmest support.
On their faces, there was a kind of...
a kind of smile.
A smile I had never seen before
in my entire life.
And in that very moment,
I felt that this smile
could heal everything in this world.
The seed
has already bloomed.
Now,
it's your turn to take the stage.