( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Defeated.
Haotian can never be defeated.
Right.
Unless...
I'm not Haotian.
That's right, I'm not Haotian.
Where's the prize?
Let's congratulate Shanhai City
on winning the championship!
That's right.
What an exhilarating battle that was!
Now, please welcome Mr. Gu Changkong
to present the award to the champion.
Damn it.
Gouye!
Just kidding.
The last bit of strength I have left
is saved for presenting the award.
Let's welcome with a round of applause
Mr. Gu Changkong...
Black Street's
Zhou Sangou, to present the award!
Farewell.
Sangou.
Got it.
Gouye.
You never let us down.
Fatty.
Take Gouye home.
Okay.
No need.
I once said,
if he died in Imperial Capital,
I'd build him an enormous tomb.
He belongs to Imperial Capital.
Staying here is his fate too.
Stop them, now!
You take Tongtong and go first.
Leave this to me.
I know what you're thinking.
Come back alive.
Got it.
Stop nagging.
Who's that?
Don't just stand there, this way!
Hurry, hurry, hurry, over here!
Xu Siguo.
Get them safely out of Imperial Capital.
Gu Changkong's target isn't you.
You hear me?
Let me come with you.
I promise I won't slow you down.
I'm giving you an order.
From this moment on,
their lives are in your hands.
Go now! Go!
Hurry, go!
Quick, quick, quick!
What are you doing? Come with us!
I'm your bodyguard.
I don't need you anymore.
Do you understand?
Hurry up and go!
I've already been paid.
Hand it over. Come on.
Follow him, hurry!
Follow Su Yang.
Go now, or you won't make it out.
In all of Black Street,
you're the only one I actually like.
Go after them!
They all die today!
Move!
What's the situation now?
A perfectly good plan
got ruined by a bunch of lunatics.
I shouldn't have listened to you.
What's the plan now?
If we let them escape like this,
neither you nor I
can answer to the Council of Elders.
I know.
As long as they die in Imperial Capital,
whatever happened in between,
I still get the final say.
Come with me.
The divine radiance of Haotian
descends upon the mortal world,
yet I have brought shame to Haotian.
I have sinned.
With my soul,
I ring the bell of destiny.
With my will,
I link heaven, earth, and the mortal realm.
Let Haotian's divine radiance
once again
descend upon this land.
Welcome the Immortal Descent once more.
Su Yang is your friend.
Who'd be friends with a lunatic?
But you're also from Black Street.
What?
Admiring me now?
The divine might of Haotian
shall not be insulted.
Su Yang must die.
Black Street
no longer needs to exist.
If it weren't for that so-called blessing,
someone like you
wouldn't qualify to enter Black Street.
Believe me?
Forget it.
It doesn't matter.
You know what I fear the most?
Are you stalling for time?
What I fear most is that one day,
once you Blessed Ones get stronger,
bombs won't work on you anymore.
So I'd rather go out with a bang
than someday
be butchered like a pig at will.
That
would be way too uncool.
I wonder if those so-called Immortals
backing you ever told you
not to stand too close to a bomber.
Remember,
my name is Qiu Ge.
Damn it.
The Council of Elders
will definitely come down hard on us.
Kill Liu Chengfeng,
take down Shanhai City.
Only this way
can we appease the Council of Elders.
Hunt them down with everything we've got.
They must die in Imperial Capital.
Qiu Ge probably isn't coming back.
The carriage can't outrun them.
This last line of defense
is up to us now.
Liu Chengfeng,
take them and go first.
Qiu Ge stayed behind on purpose.
This is the finale she wanted.
Whether it's her or Sangou,
deep down,
they each have their own pride.
Hyah!