( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Smash the Imperial Capital.
How confident are you?
Didn't you ask me this a few days ago?
Smashing the whole Imperial Capital,
time's a bit tight.
But one district, we could try.
Escaping would be the tricky part.
Luckily, I had Xu Siguo modify the carriage.
Mobility's much better now.
What I mean is,
I think you misunderstood.
When I said "smash it,"
whatever that means,
from this moment on,
it's Black Street's job now.
I feel like
I'm still pretty useful, you know.
Good luck.
Let's go.
Let's give a warm round of applause
to welcome our host!
Alright.
Oh, for heaven's sake!
What do you want now?
Sorry,
I'm in a hurry.
When's the draw today?
I promise,
I won't threaten you today.
We'll do the draw fair and square.
Today's the grand final.
Just one match.
There's no draw.
No draw, huh.
Then the match officially...
Wait.
After all, this is the grand final.
Look, none of the officials
have arrived yet.
Why don't you wait a bit?
How about
I take a look at the prize first?
A prize of this level,
I'm not even worthy to look at it.
Then how about another draw...
Hello, everyone.
Quite the grand entrance.
This guy,
he was insufferable back in school.
Looking at him now,
he's even more revolting.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Gu Changkong.
I'm delighted you could all join
the Imperial Capital's inaugural
Path to Immortality Tournament.
As the host,
we naturally uphold
a fair and impartial stance.
So,
for this grand final,
we, the Imperial Capital,
will only send out
one contestant.
As long as the Shanhai City team
can defeat him,
they'll win the grand championship
of this tournament.
This is the champion's prize.
I can't wait to see
who this prize
will ultimately go to.
Let the match begin!
Why don't you have any teammates?
In this mortal world,
no one is worthy yet
to be my teammate.
I get it.
You're a show-off with no friends.
I'm in a hurry.
Let's make this quick.
I hope you're worthy enough
to make me summon an immortal.
Speed: Tier Three.
Is this all you've got?
Sangou,
I'll leave the award ceremony to you.
I trust that with your skills,
you can definitely retrieve what's inside.
What?
You don't want the Divine Blessing anymore?
If I'm not mistaken,
the moment I step onto that ring,
I'll die.
Am I right?
What are you talking about?
The box is empty.
After you showed the artifact to everyone,
you took it away.
This trick?
I knew it when I was four.
Looks like I underestimated you.
You're smarter than I thought.
I can sense it.
You have a bigger scheme in play.
Now you
are worthy of knowing my name.
I am
Haotian.
Is "Hao" even a real surname?
Ignorant mortal.
The match ends here.
Will you accept the award yourself,
or shall my men escort you there?
Don't worry.
In front of everyone,
I'll stage your silencing.
I just came here to slack off.
Didn't expect to hook a shark.
Mighty is the Lord on high,
gazing down in splendor,
watching over the four directions,
seeking the people's peace.
Haotian's
Divine Radiance!
You know what?
Outside Black Street,
people call me Boss Dog.
And besides,
being this close to me
is very dangerous.
Even with a Divine Blessing,
you're still this useless?
That kinda hurt.
You're too weak.
First time I've seen a maniac
get pummeled like this.
He can't actually be losing, can he?
Did you see the look in his eyes?
He's just toying with him.
This idiot.
Going crazy at the worst possible time.
Is now really the time to play around?
He's playing.
He just loves playing around.
Taking this long for a single fight.
So tedious.
Guards!
Hurry up! Don't run!
Move!
A weapon?
I've got one too.
Strength: Tier Seven.
Just as I
predicted.
You can't handle Tier Seven.
You dare make me kneel before you?
Haotian's might
shall not be insulted.
Don't try to play the victim here.
I just hit you once.
You knelt on your own.
Not my fault.
You dissipated the force yourself
to avoid breaking your bones.
If you don't believe me, let's reenact it.
This is exactly how I hit you.
Celestial Punishment, transform!
If I were the one on that stage,
the Celestial Punishment would kill me.
This guy
is pretty strong.
Xiao Wu.
If I remember correctly,
your hometown is the Imperial Capital, right?
That's all in the past now.
Mortals are mortals after all.
Get him!
So this is what you call
Celestial Punishment?
No.
Impossible.
No one survives Celestial Punishment.
You
are defeated.
You lost.
Call me Boss Dog.