( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Leave some men behind
to kill them.
The rest of you, follow me!
Keep chasing!
Yes, sir.
Kill them!
You need to get out of here, now.
You're not the one they're after.
I'm getting paid for this.
You barely make anything a month.
Why risk your life?
But my salary is five times yours.
Gu Changkong.
We're old classmates, after all.
How about you let us go?
If you don't die,
how do I justify attacking Shanhai City?
So you're saying
this hurdle
we're not getting past today, huh?
Tell you what.
Cooperate with me,
and I promise your death will be less painful.
How's that sound?
Why waste breath on them?
Just attack!
Hurry up and leave, now!
Go!
No.
We die together!
If you come over, I'll just die faster!
Zhu Rong!
Flames!
Are you okay?
Liu Chengfeng.
Hiding behind a woman now, are you?
She's quite the catch.
Once you're dead,
I'll gladly take her off your hands.
At a time like this,
cut the lovey-dovey stuff.
So devoted.
I'm touched.
Let's see what you can do now.
Kill him!
She looks badly hurt.
Does she need a doctor?
What's the situation?
Qiu Ge died in battle.
The others are trapped.
Status unknown.
We're the champions.
We only took back what was ours.
Why did it have to cost two lives?
We want to leave the Imperial Capital.
Are we wrong?
We listened to Little Cleaner.
No killing or setting fires,
no causing trouble.
And in the end,
what did we get?
So
if I kill every single one of you here,
I wouldn't be wrong either.
Watch over Little Cleaner.
Today,
I can finally stop being reasonable.
What are you standing around for?
Get him!
Whoever kills him
gets ten million!
Next,
it's your turn.
You're awake.
Idiot.
Still breathing, you damn cripple?
My clothes are ripped.
Tongtong bought them for me.
I want to see Tongtong.
What a bitch.
What do we do with them now?
Hang their corpses at the Black Street entrance.
Three years...
Did you forget about the fool?
Tell me,
a guy who can't even count
actually knows how to use a smartphone,
to take notes and record videos.
The little bit of brainpower he has,
he used it all on Tongtong.
Is he really a fool, or just faking it?
Kill them now?
I'm worried Tongtong might wake up.
I mean them.
Now that you're all back,
there probably won't be enough room in the carriage.
And if we haul their corpses
back to Black Street,
they'll have started to stink.
How about this.
Let's come back in a freezer truck next time to kill them.
Works for me.
We'll have to come back again anyway.
Aren't you celebrating a bit too soon?
You think you can get away?
Father.
Why are you here?
If you're here,
it means I lost at the Elder Council.
I refuse to accept it!
I still have a chance to bounce back! I—
The moment this old Taoist showed up,
even the sky changed.
He's got some tricks.
Su Yang!
Go crazy on him again!
Bro,
are you calling a dog?
Besides,
he's clearly a tough nut to crack.
True.
Such a powerful aura.
And here I thought we'd survived.
Don't worry.
I'll collect your bodies.
I'll head out with Tongtong first.
Go.
Fuxi!
Eight Trigrams!
The Imperial Capital isn't a place you can enter
and leave as you please.
Since you're here,
you can all stay for good.
Looks like
we really can't get away this time.
To think the Imperial Capital has a master like this.
I really hadn't heard of him.
Well, Taoists
focus on cultivation.
If they have any money in their pockets,
they won't show their faces.
So it's perfectly normal
that you haven't heard of him.
But I wonder about the one in front of us,
what's his deal?
I've got a feeling
this old Taoist
is freakishly strong.
So what now?
Give up?
Or risk our lives and give it a shot?
Let's give it a shot.
We can't just stick our necks out to be slaughtered.
That's just too embarrassing.
Your martial arts attainments have reached the grandmaster level.
What a pity.
You lack a bit of...
intent.
The pressure's so intense!
At your age,
instead of cultivating peacefully in a temple,
why pick fights with us youngsters?
It's beneath you.
Just earning my meal ticket.
As for Fuxi's Eight Trigrams art,
I've studied it quite a bit.
Set up your formation.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't beat you.
I'm getting old.
Fighting always takes a toll on my body.
The outcome's the same anyway,
so let's just skip the
exhausting middle part, shall we?
Black Street's got another cripple.
You're not alone anymore.
The result should be about the same as if you did it.
His walking days are over.
If you don't believe me,
I can do it again.
No need for that.
Anyway, your ultimate fate
is death.
For now, as long as you can't move,
that's enough.
This Taoist,
out of everyone I've ever met,
ranks in the top three.
I can hold out for five minutes max.
I'll use my life
to leave him gravely wounded.
If you go crazy,
you'd be the one gravely wounded,
and he'd die.
You two could come at me together.
That's fighting dirty.
Fighting fair
requires you
to be alive first.
Haven't seen anyone this strong in ages.
I want to kill him.
You only lasted three seconds?
Which means,
if I fought him for half an hour,
that makes me stronger than you
by countless times.
You can't beat me.
Why don't you cripple your own leg,
just like old man An,
and skip the middle part?
How about it?
I don't think so.
They'd dock my pay.
Besides,
how do you know
I can't beat you?
Fine then.