( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
How long has she been asleep?
A whole day now.
We need to speed up the tournament.
Go tell Limpy.
Tell him that during the semifinals,
he must forfeit outright for Frostwind City.
That'll save us a round.
Tongtong
can't hold on much longer.
For the next couple of days,
you should rest up too.
That Immortal Artifact
won't be easy to get.
Friendship first,
competition second.
Milk tea's on me, everyone.
What a coincidence.
I prepared milk tea
for our friends from Qiushui City too.
Don't be shy.
Please.
Your milk tea
is way too cheap.
My teammates
wouldn't bother with it.
My teammates hate the rich by nature.
They can't stomach expensive stuff.
Then do you dare drink mine?
Do you dare drink mine?
Let's drink together.
Let's give a warm round of applause
as we welcome Shanhai City,
Qiushui City,
Xingguang City,
and Frostwind City's contestants
to the stage to draw lots.
The semifinal rules are:
Number one faces number two,
and three faces four.
That junk lantern you gave me last time
was complete garbage.
You're screwed.
I can't beat you.
But Fatty Geng wants me to fight you.
And I'm afraid of pain.
So...
Surrendering outright is too embarrassing.
How about you lightly hit me a few times,
and then I'll fly off the stage.
The reward?
The reward is,
just the two of us settle it.
No other teammates need to fight.
That way, Shanhai City
goes straight to the finals.
Deal.
Hey, you two,
I'm still standing here.
Why haven't you left the stage yet?
You haven't drawn yet.
How am I supposed to leave?
Just cheat like last time.
Well, you've gotta draw one first.
Get back here.
Shanhai City, once again,
has drawn the first match slot.
Keeping their record going,
I'd like to call them
the King of the First Match.
The first match
will be number one Shanhai City
versus number two Qiushui City.
Let the match begin.
Watch us crush you this time.
As if you could.
Damn fatty.
By the way,
how much stuff did you slip into my drink?
Just a tiny bit.
Bullshit.
Even though it's a fake fight,
we still gotta make it look real.
I get it.
I'm great at this.
As expected.
I've lost.
You're a formidable opponent too.
Okay, okay, okay.
Qiushui City
has chosen to surrender.
With their captain defeated first,
this outcome is understandable.
Indeed.
Now let's look forward to the next match,
Xingguang City versus Frostwind City.
I hereby declare
that Xingguang City
forfeits.
Xingguang City has also chosen to forfeit.
Frostwind City
forfeits.
Frostwind City's captain has also forfeited.
So that means
Shanhai City wins the championship?
That appears to be the case.
Since Frostwind City forfeited early,
the original schedule has been disrupted.
But sticking to principle,
the finals will still be held in six days,
as originally scheduled.
Let's congratulate Shanhai City
on earning the right to challenge the Imperial Capital.
Who will win?
Let's wait and see.
Slow down.
I'm in a hurry.
What's the rush? My legs are numb.
How can I not be in a hurry?
Any normal person squatting that long,
whose legs wouldn't go numb?
I'm walking as fast as I can.
Besides, what good did your coming here do?
You'd have lost anyway.
Look at this result.
How long were we
in that bathroom anyway?
Strange.
Why is the Imperial Capital
so insistent on keeping the match schedule?
Throughout this whole tournament,
aside from their crazy promotion,
the Imperial Capital doesn't seem
all that invested in the match itself.
Even at the venue,
it's just two commentators running things.
What role is the Imperial Capital
really playing in this match?
Speak.
Based on my private investigation
over this past while,
this Gu Changye
has been in close contact
with many smaller city heads.
As for Gu Changkong,
he's been staying home the whole time,
never showing his face.
And every document he's read
has been put through a shredder.
So I
specially hired over a hundred people
to collect those paper shreds.
It took a massive amount of time
to piece them back into text.
However,
most of it was useless information.
But a few keywords among them
were rather interesting.
What keywords?
What lousy tea is this?
Those, those keywords are:
The Second Celestial Advent,
Immortal Summoning,
Immortal Artifact.
That's all.
No kidding!
Do you know how hard it is
to piece shredded fragments
back into actual text?
If it weren't for yours truly,
you wouldn't have even these few words.
Based on this alone,
we can't deduce much yet.
But what's certain is,
Gu Changkong and Gu Changye
definitely have their own scheme.
Damn it.
Every crossroad is blocked off.
They're trying to completely cut off
any chance I have of leaving the Imperial Capital.
Gu Changye wants me to summon an immortal.
I don't know what he's planning,
but putting my life in someone else's hands,
I can't do that.
Should I go find him or not?
So you came after all.
You knew I'd come.
The Imperial Capital's people
already came to you, didn't they?
You even know about that?
Don't be nervous.
The Imperial Capital's people
aren't as merciful as me,
letting you go time and again.
So for you,
the most likely outcome will be
death.
In all of the Imperial Capital,
I'm the only one who can save you.
So unless you're hopelessly stupid,
you were bound to come.
Have a seat.
Let's have a little chat.
What did the Imperial Capital folks tell you?
Gu Changye wants me, on the day of the finals,
to summon another immortal.
Gu Changye...
that guy
really has some ambition.
Let me break it down for you.
Gu Changye
plans to, after the match ends,
at the awards ceremony,
make a move against his own brother.
And you
are one of his trump cards.
If he fails,
you'll die right along with him.
And if he succeeds?
You know too much, so you'll die anyway.
So...
So you have to save... save me!
Why on earth would I save you?
You don't actually think I'm some naive do-gooder, do you?
I have a key.
It can open the Immortal Burial Ground.
One key
buys my life.
You should've said so earlier.
I'm a very reasonable man.
If you'd handed it over sooner,
you'd probably be on the highway by now.
Could you maybe
give me one more little surprise?
Like,
The Second Celestial Advent.
I don't know.
Are you sure?
I
do have some ancient texts,
which let me get a head start
in the early stages.
But that
doesn't mean I know everything.
Just asking.
If you don't know, you don't know.
It's not a big deal.
By the way,
do you want to leave right away,
or watch the finals first?
Now.
Right
this instant.
Alright.
Get him a car.
I won't see you out.
The Immortal Burial Ground.
Wang Qiusheng is gone.
In all my life,
no one has ever dared stand me up.
Forget it.
He was just a bonus anyway.
Once I deal with things here,
I'll go settle the score with him.
You may leave now.
Leave Meiyan to me.
Everyone, let's continue.
He's here.
Come, Young Master Gu.
This way.
Please sit here.
Everyone, take your seats.
Listen carefully to Young Master Gu.
Tomorrow, after the awards ceremony,
when my brother gives his speech,
we strike immediately.
Counting my own men,
that's eighty of The Blessed in total.
Gu Changkong will die for sure.
I guarantee
that from this day on,
the Imperial Capital will open
all trade with all of you,
including financial support.
In that case,
Young Master Gu,
we hope from now on
you'll look out for us.
Of course.
Yes!
We pledge our service to Young Master Gu.
That's right. Come on.
Excellent.
Cheers.
Sangou.
Tomorrow is the finals awards ceremony.
Stay at the Gu residence tonight,
just in case something goes wrong.
No problem, right?
No problem.
You should know,
I do trust you.
But in my position,
I have to be cautious about everything.
Otherwise, trouble's bound to come.
I understand.
Good.
Then go get some rest.
I've already had someone
prepare a room for you.
Zhou Sangou.
He's quite handy to have around.
A pretty decent talent.
What a pity.
We need a fuse, after all,
a sacrificial pawn for Shanhai City.
The Blessed...
Are they truly out of reach?
Easy now.
Thanks.
Got a little gift for you.
Here.
One piece of good news,
and one piece of bad news.
The bad news is,
your body
won't last another seven days.
The good news is,
tomorrow is the final.
Your life
is saved.
Brother Su Yang,
Uncle Limpy,
Let's take a picture together.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
How do you feel?
I feel great.
I thought
I'd be terrified.
But instead,
right now,
I'm really happy.
Because
you're all here with me.
Lie down properly.
Another new day.
I'm still alive.
And
you're all still here.
That's wonderful.
What's the plan for tomorrow?
Win the championship,
and wait for the prize, duh.
What if something goes wrong?
Then we grab the Immortal Artifact
and run.
Run?
What else?
You want me to kill people?
I'm not some psycho killer.
I said I'm not a psycho killer right now.
Tomorrow I'll take Tongtong to the venue.
If the Immortal Artifact works fine,
we head straight back.
Why are you the one taking her?
You'd rather leave her with an idiot?
You...
It's gotta be you.
What if the Immortal Artifact doesn't work?
Then you take Tongtong and leave first.
I'll stay in the Imperial Capital
and go crazy one more time.