Ride the horsey.
Father, faster!
Are you having fun?
Yes.
Crown Prince.
Here.
Is it good?
What's wrong?
Call the Imperial Physician!
Hurry! Call the Imperial Physician!
Someone, hurry!
- Your Highness!
- Huayong!
Huayong!
Your Highness!
=Blossoms of Power=
(Adapted from the novel, After My
Bloom, All Flowers Wither by Jin Huang)
=Episode 2=
Commandery Princess Zhaoning
arrives in the Imperial Capital.
Will she bring the northwest
style of makeup with her?
I wonder which prince His Majesty
will betroth the commandery princess
from the northwest to.
Anyone but
that short-lived Crown Prince.
Any of the other princes
could be a match.
(Tingyun Villa)
Move a little faster, all of you.
(Wedding Scrolls)
On the wedding day,
the whole city will be filled
with lanterns and red decorations.
There won't be enough
red silk or lanterns to sell.
Young Master,
what can I get for you?
Well,
(Wedding Scrolls)
I see you've stocked up
on red silk for all the princes.
Why is there none for the Crown Prince?
Keep your voice down.
That's a taboo.
The Crown Prince was poisoned.
Everyone knows that.
How could the commandery princess
possibly marry him?
You truly
have remarkable insight.
Of course.
On this whole street,
no one has a sharper eye than I do,
and see if there's anything you need.
(Suzhou Post Station)
It seems Your Highness
has recovered well.
Now I can rest easy
leaving Your Highness
in the local governor's care.
What do you mean?
Your Highness is a man unrelated to me.
I only came to your aid yesterday
because the situation was urgent.
Now that Your Highness is out of danger,
I should avoid
any appearance of impropriety.
Shen Xihe.
I've been hunted
ever since leaving Guangling.
Then I happened to run
into you at death's door.
Don't tell me
it was all just a coincidence.
You've been back to the imperial capital
to receive an imperial marriage.
You made me owe you my life,
and stayed by my side day and night.
What's this?
Now you're putting on
an act of playing hard to get?
Hard to get?
Have you forgotten, Your Highness,
that yesterday you were the one
who threw in the jade pendant?
As for status,
you are no match for the Crown Prince.
As for reputation,
you cannot compare to the Second Prince.
As for looks,
you are far behind the Sixth Prince.
As for talent,
you cannot compare to your
own elder brother, the Fifth Prince.
Why would I ever fall for you?
How dare you!
You saved my life.
I'll let it slide this time.
There's no need to feel indebted
to me, Your Highness.
Let's just pretend we never met.
Let's part ways here.
Your Highness.
I've followed the trail
and found the Jade Frost Flower.
But the hiding place
had already been dug up.
The Rouge Ledger is nowhere to be found.
As for who took it,
I have failed in my duty.
I still haven't found out.
Prepare the horses.
Your Highness.
They took our horses.
There's only this one left
in the stable.
(Seriously injured. Not fit for riding.)
She must have it.
I really underestimated her.
Shen Xihe.
Just you wait.
(Crown Prince, Prince Ning, Prince Ding,
Prince Yu, Prince Lie, Prince Xin)
Your Highness,
why does it seem
like you know these princes?
Your Highness is even
better informed than me.
Know your enemy and yourself,
and you stand an equal chance
of victory or defeat.
Know neither your enemy nor yourself,
and you'll lose every battle.
Marrying the wrong man
is like entering the wrong forest.
The path is full of thorns.
One should make plans
as early as possible.
The Second Prince, Prince Ning.
The Fourth Prince, Prince Ding.
The Sixth Prince, Prince Yu.
Among these three princes,
Prince Ning is the foremost.
He is backed by a veteran
who has served three reigns,
the Ministry of Justice,
and the Ministry of Rites.
The Ninth Prince, Prince Lie,
is Noble Consort Rong's second son.
Though still young,
he holds an exalted status.
Prince Lie is bold and high-spirited.
He will make
a formidable battlefield general.
Most importantly,
Changqing is there
to strategize for him.
The Fifth Prince, Prince Xin,
is exceptionally gifted.
But after Prince Xin's Consort
passed away,
he lost heart and turned to prayer.
He withdrew from worldly affairs.
Changqing has always been ambitious.
Everyone thinks he's stayed out
of worldly affairs all these years.
But they've forgotten what he was
like before Gu Qingzhi's downfall.
How decisive
and meticulous Changqing was.
- He will return.
Qingqing.
(The Late Lady Gu)
I failed to protect you back then.
It was my fault.
Today, I oversaw the execution
of all 69 members of the Gu family.
Do you hate me?
Why should I?
The Gu family held too much power.
The Fan family had long wanted us gone.
My father was outmatched.
He accepted defeat.
Gu Qingzhi.
You have no heart.
Your blood runs cold.
Only by being heartless
can a lady
truly live free and happy.
I wonder, Your Highness,
what you plan to do
with me, the last survivor.
I pleaded with Father.
You are still my Princess Consort.
What an unwise decision.
Protecting the powerless daughter
of a condemned official
who has nothing but a pretty face
will only make more enemies for yourself
and drive a wedge between you
and your trusted followers.
Your Highness should personally
see me on my way.
Qingqing.
I, Xiao Changqing, swear on my life
to protect you
for the rest of your life.
Your Highness, your love
is destined to be wasted on me.
This is Sangluo liquor,
specially sent by the Fan family.
A rare vintage.
Qingqing.
Qingqing!
(Qing)
The trap you risked your life to set
to bury the Fan family
with the Gu family,
I've carried through for you.
I'll stay by your side
until the day I die.
Your Highness.
Prince Lie was ambushed.
Commandery Princess Zhaoning saved him,
but stole the Rouge Ledger.
Escort Prince Lie
back to the capital at once.
Recover the Rouge Ledger
at any cost.
Yes.
Move it!
Hurry!
They look like a band of bandits.
These men live by the blade.
They're ruthless.
Your Highness, should we save them?
Of course.
Though Commandery Princess Zhaoning
is clever,
at the end of the day,
she's still a young lady.
Faced with a force like this,
how could she not lose her composure?
Wait.
The commandery princess
doesn't seem to be in the carriage.
Fall back.
Your Highness,
it seems
commandery princess
doesn't need our help.
She foresaw
today's ambush.
I'd heard Commandery Princess Zhaoning
was raised in luxury.
How did she develop
such remarkable composure?
That's foresight.
It's a step above
keeping calm under pressure.
Now that the bandits are dealt with,
Your Highness,
the commandery princess
should be able to continue her journey.
Such a direct attack
doesn't seem like
Xiao Changqing's style.
Your Highness truly
sees through everything.
The bandits have all been driven off.
It's not that simple.
Xiao Changqing
always plans before he acts.
If the bandits couldn't deal with us,
he could call in
the local authorities to wipe us out.
According to Changqing's style,
he'd send government troops
to eliminate the bandits
under a legitimate pretext,
and the commandery princess
was accidentally killed.
The authorities,
under orders to suppress the bandits,
would execute anyone
who refused to lay down
their arms and surrender.
You were right!
You got it exactly right, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
should we step in?
Who are you?
How dare you kill government troops?
That's a capital offense!
The Embroidered Envoys
are conducting official business.
Anyone who interferes
(Embroidered Envoy)
will be executed without mercy.
I was ordered to come here
and suppress the bandits.
I had no idea
I'd disturbed the Embroidered Envoy.
Please forgive my offense.
The Embroidered Envoy?
They are the Emperor's most secret
covert organization.
There are only thirteen of them.
They hold the tiger tally and
have the authority to command troops.
They can throw any official below
the third rank directly into prison.
All civil and military officials
fear them deeply.
Only the Emperor
knows their true identities.
The bandits have all been captured.
You should return and report back.
Yes.
(This scent...)
(Tagara Incense again.)
Where are you headed?
Reporting to you, sir,
we're on our way to Guangwu City.
Who would've thought
we'd run into bandits?
Then be on your way.
The city gates will soon close.
You may leave!
Thank you for your help, sir.
We'll take our leave.
The Embroidered Envoy suddenly appeared
and even helped us.
The Embroidered Envoys
never linger for anyone.
What happened today is truly unusual.
The Tagara Incense he's wearing
is of the finest quality.
Just one tael
is worth a hundred taels of gold.
Why would
an Embroidered Envoy
use something so precious?
Besides,
this Embroidered Envoy
has the exact same scent
as Hua Fuhai.
It's too much of a coincidence.
Your Highness.
Why didn't you take this opportunity
to take the Rouge Ledger
from the commandery princess?
Unless she gives it up willingly,
taking the Rouge Ledger from her
will be no easy task.
What about the Immortal Vine?
Even if you don't need it now,
you can present it to Grand
Empress Dowager as a birthday gift.
The Immortal Vine
is shaped like a lover's knot,
symbolizing everlasting unity.
How could I give it to Grandmother?
Oh, no.
My brilliant prince
has really fallen for her.
It's not love.
It's like
seeing a bright moon in the sky.
If I didn't admire it,
I'd be the one who lacked appreciation.
Your Highness,
your poison is acting up again.
(Prince Xin's Manor)
Changqing, how could you send men
to kill Commandery Princess Zhaoning?
She stole the Rouge Ledger from you,
and you're still protecting her?
The Duke of Wei is loyal to the throne.
He's an upright official.
So what if she took it?
You risked your life
and went through countless hardships
to obtain the Rouge Ledger.
What is it for?
No enemy on the battlefield
can defeat you.
But the schemes of powerful ministers
are far harder for you to withstand.
With the Rouge Ledger,
we can root out the corrupt officials
at court.
Then we can build our own influence.
Only then will your position be secure.
Changqing,
I've told you many times already.
I don't want
to get involved in politics.
Right now, you're only
the General of the Imperial Guard.
You have no place at court.
How can you protect
the one you care about?
Your Highness.
Commandery Princess Zhaoning's party
is nearing
the imperial capital by water.
Changqing,
you mustn't harm her again.
You can't bring yourself to do it?
No.
That lady is cold and heartless.
I can't stand her.
They're too close
to the imperial capital.
Whether you like her or not,
you can't touch her for now.
Boatman,
when will the boat depart?
In an hour.
If there are enough passengers,
- Your Highness.
- we can set sail now.
We'll go buy some flowers.
Please wait a moment.
Come take a look.
Just let me know.
These flowers are so beautiful.
They really are.
Look over there. It's so lively.
It is.
Come on, let's go take a look.
Let's go.
You're hurt.
Where's your owner?
So you're all alone, too.
How about I take you home?
You...
shall be called Du Huo.
It seems you really like that name.
Your Highness,
you've protected
the commandery princess all the way.
Even if you're not
expecting anything in return,
you should at least get
a word of thanks.
Instead, you're hiding here
spying on her.
This commandery princess
has more than just two sides.
She has quite a few.
Little fox.
Whether she's a fox or a tiger,
if we've got the Rouge Ledger,
we'd better keep our distance.
Tian Yuan.
Her smile is truly beautiful.
Your Highness,
don't you think
the commandery princess
seems rather calculating,
even a little frightening?
What's frightening about her?
She's clearly
adorable.
- All right.
- Bravo!
Take this one.
This one's pretty.
Over here!
This way!
It's so lively.
Be careful.
Here, take it.
These are yours.
Come on, let's go
set floating lanterns adrift.
Your Highness,
it's the Fishing Lantern Festival.
The people pray
for abundance year after year
and that everything goes smoothly.
Your Highness,
it's so adorable.
Have you given it a name?
It's called Du Huo.
Why would Your Highness give a cat
such a strange name?
When all flowers have withered,
I alone remain.
Isn't that fitting?
Good!
Enjoy the lanterns.
I'll head back and get some rest.
- Good!
- Great!
Excuse me, is this
Commandery Princess Zhaoning's boat?
May I ask who you are?
I am Cui Jinbai, Vice Minister
of the Court of Judicial Review.
Greetings, Your Highness.
May I ask why you wish to see me?
I have been waiting here
for Your Highness
regarding the case
of the escaped maid Ling Long.
I need to ask you a few questions.
Please rest assured.
I won't keep Your Highness for long.
This way, please.
What does Your Highness
usually like to eat?
I prefer light food
and dislike greasy dishes.
I don't have any particular favorite.
What do you usually do
in your spare time?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
I blend incense and do needlework,
read and practice calligraphy.
In your daily life,
do you have any special preferences?
If I had to name one,
I'd enjoy collecting
rare flowers and herbs.
I savor their fragrance and admire them.
"Clad in orchids and duheng,
I pluck fragrant blooms
for the one I long for."
What refined taste, Your Highness.
But what does any of this
have to do with the case?
Ling Long was your personal maid.
She knew your habits
and preferences inside out.
I'm concerned someone
might exploit those small details.
That's why I took the liberty of asking.
Do you enjoy going on spring outings?
Do you prefer mountain scenery
or waterscapes?
(Tagara Incense again.)
Vice Minister Cui,
there's no need to avoid me.
Why not come aboard my boat
so we can continue our conversation?
- Very well!
Why are you wearing
a veiled hat, Vice Minister Cui?
The journey here
left my face sunburned.
My appearance is rather untidy.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Vice Minister Cui is in charge of
criminal investigations and sentencing.
I'd like to know,
if someone impersonates
a court official,
what crime should that be?
This incense is poisonous.
Caning.
Imprisonment.
Execution.
Choose one.
You're faking it.
I'm only honest with the lady I love.
If Your Highness is willing...
Your Highness!
Let go of Her Highness!
What's wrong?
The commandery princess threw
a numbing powder at me.
What if the anesthetic harms you?
She's still
a kindhearted young lady.
If it's meant for self-defense,
it should be laced with poison.
Just like Hua Fuhai,
it's that Tagara Incense again.
What a pity.
I only mixed
a numbing agent into the powder.
Poison would've been even better.
You're still upset
she didn't poison you to death?
She knew I was in disguise.
Yet she exposed me right to my face.
She's more like
my confidante.
My confidante?
Wait.
Don't tell me you've fallen for her.
A Crown Prince as frail as a willow,
yet infatuated with love.
There couldn't be a better disguise.
(Shangjing, Imperial Capital
of the Daxing Dynasty)
Come take a look!
(Ningxiang Tea House)
Misters. Please come in.
Have a seat inside.
Your tea is ready, Mister.
This way.
Watch your step.
Right there.
Your Highness, it's so lively.
The commandery princess's party
has entered the imperial capital.
Your Highness,
it's time to leave.
Make way!
Do you all have a death wish?
Move!
Are you deaf?
I'm talking to you.
Move!
Are you deaf?
I'm talking to you!
Third Brother.
- Second Brother.
- Third Brother.
- Easy.
- Come.
Slow down.
Blood!
How dare you!
Do you have a death wish?
I think you want to die!
I can be even bolder.
Want to find out?
Do you know who I am?
I'm the Third Young Master
of the Marquis of Jining's Manor!
What a loudmouth.
Third Young Master!
You dare whip me?
Get her!
Someone!
They're fighting at the city gate,
and assaulting the descendants
of meritorious officials!
Surround them!
- Yes!
Why are you surrounding me?
Over there!
(Zhang Pengzhan, Prefect of Shangjing)
Prefect Zhang Pengzhan of Shangjing
pays my respects to Your Highness.
I arrived too late.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Prefect Zhang,
someone tried to kill me.
I... I didn't know.
I don't even know her.
How could I have tried to kill her?
I know.
You didn't mean to.
Your horse
was driven mad by the scent of basil.
Someone
tampered with your horse.
Reporting to you, Prefect,
we found traces of incense powder.
Prefect Zhang,
I'd like a basin of clean water.
Yes.
This incense powder
contains an ingredient
that reacts with basil.
When the two are mixed,
the water turns red.
Brilliant, Your Highness.
Then I'll ask everyone
to place their hands
in the water, one by one.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
No!
It wasn't me!
It wasn't me, Your Highness!
If not, why is there the scent
of basil on your hands?
It was Second Young Master Li.
He personally gave me the powder.
Don't you dare slander me!
Mo Yu!
What are you doing?
Second Brother,
we're brothers.
Why are you framing me?
I just wanted
to get blood on your hands.
So Father would come to despise you.
But...
I never expected to implicate
the commandery princess.
- Does ignorance make you innocent?
Greetings, Your Highness.
- Greetings, Your Highness.
Please rise, Xihe.
There's no need for formalities.
(Plum blossoms kissed with snow.)
(This fragrance is Spring in Snow.)
(All are rare medicinal herbs
that are beneficial to one's health.)
(Worth more than gold.)
(The Crown Prince really
has been ill for so long.)
I heard everything.
You tried to kill
the commandery princess.
You intended to provoke a conflict
between the two houses.
Your crime is unforgivable.
Please forgive me, Your Highness!
I was merely jealous
of my third brother.
He was always Father's favorite.
That's why I made such a grave mistake.
Please spare my life, Your Highness!
I'm not the victim.
Begging me won't help.
I failed to know my place.
I offended the commandery princess.
Please spare me, Your Highness!
Please forgive me, Your Highness!
If you want my forgiveness,
you should at least tell the truth.
Who is the real mastermind?
I...
Think carefully.
If you're imprisoned,
what will your wife
do to your sisters and concubines?
You framed your own brother.
How will
your father deal with you?
I...
It was Xiao Jing.
He said...
He said he wanted to avenge his aunt.
(The Xiao is the Duke of Wei's concubine
left behind in the imperial capital.)
(Seems like)
(she's enjoyed
an easy life for far too long.)
- Take him away!
Thank you, Your Highness,
for standing up for me.
You have traveled
all the way from the northwest.
We mustn't let you suffer
or disappoint
the soldiers of the northwest.
I've had a long and tiring journey.
My appearance is not presentable.
I'll pay my respects
at the Eastern Palace another day.
Then I'll await you
at the Eastern Palace.
Your Highness,
the commandery princess
is bound to see you differently now.
Naturally.
The Crown Prince has lived
in seclusion for too long.
He doesn't know propriety.
He even dared to touch
the commandery princess's hand.
That was rather improper.
Good thing he won't live long.
Throw Xiao out.
You're not worthy
of being my enemy.
As long as Prince Kang's Manor
still stands,
I'll make sure
you die a miserable death.
The young master I marry
will be the one I love.
So you intend
to choose your own husband?
If Your Highness has the time,
allow me to be your guide.
May I show Your Highness
around the capital?
♪I've hidden so many words♪
♪Too reluctant to tell you♪
♪So never uncover♪
♪The sand that slips away
with one grasp♪
♪The flower that withers
after one bloom♪
♪Silently buried deep inside my heart♪
♪Every answer I gave♪
♪Was both bittersweet and absurd♪
♪Hiding my tear-filled eyes
when I hurt you♪
♪How hard it truly was?♪
♪The wounds that healed
with just a little comfort♪
♪The lies made whole
with a single embrace♪
♪Pretending to be brave
as if I'd never been hurt♪
♪It's a shame I never could♪
♪Give you a moon in return♪
♪With the same open heart you loved me♪
♪I've crossed the wasteland of memories♪
♪Never knowing I was lost♪
♪Why don't you take me away?♪
♪Lead me out of this endless game
of hide-and-seek♪
♪You'll never♪
♪Know how much I long to, long to♪