( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
As if they were born on different planets,
there are two people who are completely different.
Could these two
ever fall in love?
Nonsense.
Unless their souls swapped bodies.
"Check In to You"
(Episode 1: Who Are You?)
We blended 45% Guatemala, 30% Colombia,
and 25% Ethiopia.
Increase the Ethiopia by 5%.
Yes, understood.
I'll be on my way, then.
Hey!
Here are the hot dogs.
One hot dog set.
Be careful in the rain.
High five with uncle before you go, princess.
Have a safe trip.
- Drive safely.
- I will.
- Make sure to eat the hot dogs!
- Okay.
Whoa!
How about a hot morning instead of a hot dog, boss?
It's noon, not morning.
Oh yeah, a hot noon!
And I told you, I'm not the boss.
I'm the manager.
Right, right.
Manager Yoon Jio.
Then who's the boss?
I don't know.
You don't?
The boss changed last year,
but I've never seen them.
We've never even spoken on the phone.
Do they own so many places they just forgot?
The previous boss told me
that the new boss
is young, and their face...
- Huh?
- is practically glowing.
Awesome.
- On top of that, their character...
- Good character too?
It's apparently outstanding.
Then what is the second thing I hate the most?
Making mistakes.
No, that's the third.
Punctuality?
Fourth.
Needless waste.
Ah... yes.
But you just committed my second,
third, and fourth biggest pet peeves all at once.
You made a mistake,
which made us waste time, money, and energy,
and now we're going to be late.
I apologize.
I'll never make a mistake,
waste anything, or be late...
Weren't we going there without an appointment?
I made a promise to myself.
That I'd get there within an hour.
Ah... right.
Well,
at least you can act like a proper boss.
But I'm seriously curious...
What is the number one thing you hate?
You... never told me.
Clinging to things that don't make money,
and calling it "values."
I'm sure they're someone who values
meaning more than money.
That's why they trusted me with this place
for over a year.
A perfectly flawless person actually exists.
Looks, wealth, and a great personality.
By the way,
aren't you close to your deadline?
Yoon Jio, you're a devil!
Are you stuck on something?
Yeah.
It's a romance web novel...
but there's no romance.
What do you think love is, Jio?
Love is...
seeping into someone else's world?
Oh...
Something like that, I guess?
BADAM STAY
This is a really wonderful place.
This is ridiculous.
With scenery like this...
Do you also have a sentimental side, President?
It'll definitely sell for a high price.
What?
Let's head in quickly,
I don't want to waste time.
What brings you here?
Are you an employee here?
Yes.
You don't have a reservation, do you?
Please come this way, I'll show you around.
What's your name?
I'm the manager, Yoon Jio.
Manager?
Getting drunk during work hours and
turning this place into a dump makes you a manager?
Excuse me?
You said your name is Yoon Jio?
You're fired, effective immediately.
Who... are you?
Cha Dokyung.
The owner of this place.
Glowing...
His face is...
practically glowing.
It really is... glowing.
From his face.
What?
- *Blegh*
- Ah, wait!
Check In to You