( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
(Episode 2: Soul Check-In)
Haa... Handle it quickly.
Take care of it quickly!
Ah, I'm sorry, I...
It's seeping in... That's enough, stop!
Throw it away.
Yes...
I'm... sorry.
I didn't realize you were the boss.
It's fine.
Well, as you know,
running a guesthouse means
sometimes drinking together
with the guests...
and chatting with them
is part of the job...
Right, that makes sense.
You're pretty cool about it, Boss.
You're just going to let it slide?
No, it's hopeless.
Huh?
Then...
you're not firing me, right?
You've trusted me with this place all this time.
Yeah, fine.
Really?
Ha... Thank you.
I'll work really hard.
You can stay until it's sold.
Excuse me?
- Secretary Ha.
- Yes, President.
Rip out all this tacky stuff.
If we remodel it luxuriously
and rebrand it with a premium image,
it might be presentable.
You're selling Badam Stay?
Yeah.
Ah, but you promised the previous boss.
That you'd keep this place as it is.
Words are cheap in business.
- You absolutely can't do that here.
- Is there nowhere else for you to make money?
There should be plenty of places that pay more than here.
I didn't work here for the money.
Then what?
Because it's a precious place.
Because it has value.
I imagined the boss
was someone
who recognized that value.
Does value that doesn't make money
even count as value?
What?
You live like that
because you cling to such pathetic sentiments.
I'll be staying here for a while.
Show me to the best room.
Does value that doesn't make money... even count as value?
- Yoon Jio, is this all you can do?
- Why are you so irresponsible?
- It's a complete mess.
- I told you to redo it.
Thank you.
Because it has value.
I imagined the boss was someone
who recognized that value.
Huh?
Whoa!
- Oh!
- Ah!
H-hey, where are you looking?!
You're the one... exposing yourself.
What's that sound?
Huh...?
Wait a minute!
Why did I get... so big?
Aaaagh!
Why is it so loud?
My muscles.
Where did my muscles go?
- Aaaagh!
"Check In to You"