( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 13=
Do you even know
what a male escort house is?
Of course I do.
A place for male companions.
Then why are you enjoying it so much?
Since we're already here,
we should blend in.
Otherwise it'll be too easy
to expose ourselves.
You just enjoy watching them.
You really do know me well.
Still looking?
You're better looking than all of them.
Shen Zhinian.
I'm helping you carry out your task.
This place only receives female guests.
If a man wants to enter,
he can only come
as a female guest's attendant.
If I act too serious,
won't people grow suspicious?
How do you know that?
You've been here before?
Guess.
The auction's about to begin.
Mm.
We'll split up.
Stay here and keep watch.
Don't let anyone buy the item.
Yes.
Wen Ling,
go scout the surroundings.
Yes.
Young Master,
Jiang Fu and Lu Jianglin are here.
They're Father's men.
Luckily Jiang Fu has never met me before.
What exactly is being auctioned tonight?
Should we notify His Majesty?
Let's wait a little longer.
We'll see once the auction begins.
Mm.
So it's fruit wine.
Rich aroma. A fine wine.
Your injuries haven't healed yet.
You shouldn't drink.
Your Majesty,
this is my first time attending
a lantern festival.
My first time entering
a male escort house.
My first time drinking
in a pleasure house.
I used to think
people should always live by the rules.
But now I feel
that while we're alive,
we should see more
and experience more.
Cold hearted.
Sharp tongued.
Shen Zhinian,
I think sneaking out of the palace
has truly made you fearless.
Seal it with a stamp.
In my next life, I'll become a leopard
and come find Your Majesty again.
Seal it with a stamp.
In the next life,
Mother can be my daughter.
How many people are you trying to stamp?
Ah?
Nothing.
The auction begins now.
The first item,
a gold bracelet once owned by
an imperial consort of the former dynasty.
Starting bid, one hundred taels.
- Is this the item?
- Two hundred taels.
Three hundred taels.
Any higher bids?
No.
Three hundred taels, first call.
Do you really recognize the item?
Three hundred taels, second call.
Sure...
- Sure...
- Fine. Four hundred taels.
You'd better handle this properly.
If we return empty handed tonight...
Six hundred taels.
Then prepare to lose your head.
Seven hundred taels.
Yes.
Sold.
Second item,
Wen Qianji.
This item was handcrafted by
an imperial consort of the former dynasty.
Playing with it daily
can make the fingers slender
and the skin smooth as jade.
This is the item.
Starting bid,
one hundred taels.
(One hundred taels)
Room Xing bids one hundred taels.
Room Yue,
three hundred taels.
Room Xing, four hundred taels.
Room Yue, eight hundred taels.
If this bidding keeps going,
it'll be disadvantageous to Your Majesty.
Do you have a plan?
Who is it?
Oh dear.
Sorry, wrong room.
The young escort beside you, Madam,
is exceptionally handsome.
Why have I never seen him before?
I brought him with me.
Madam, would you be willing
to let me have him?
Get lost.
Please don't be angry, Madam.
I'll leave at once.
Leaving now.
Still outside?
Room Xing,
one thousand taels.
What are you standing there for?
Pour me some wine already.
One thousand five hundred taels.
Room Xing, two thousand taels.
Drink up.
And this is how you're serving me wine?
I'm not drinking.
Don't use this as an excuse
to stir up trouble.
Doesn't Your Majesty want
to stall for time
so Jiang Chen can keep bidding?
I deeply regret
disturbing you earlier, Madam.
I've come especially
to offer you a toast.
The young escort beside you, Madam,
is truly stunning.
I wonder whether Madam would be willing
to let me join in?
Absolutely not.
He's my favorite little companion.
I don't share.
What a pity.
And who might you be?
He's my little companion too.
Madam, you certainly have exquisite taste.
Why aren't you coming over?
Learn from your older brother.
Then I won't disturb you any longer.
Madam, please enjoy yourselves.
What do we do now?
Drink.
Madam.
What are you doing?
Wasn't I supposed to serve Madam wine?
Drink it yourself.
Then should I remove my clothes as well?
That's unnecessary.
I was only asking.
Didn't I tell you
to stay downstairs and bid?
Why did you come up?
I left Luo Hao downstairs to wait.
But the price has already
risen to ten thousand taels.
I didn't bring enough silver.
According to Jinsong Pavilion's rules,
you must have enough silver
on hand to place a bid.
So I came up to ask Your Majesty
whether you've brought enough silver.
Let them bid.
Room Xing bids thirteen thousand taels.
Any higher bids?
Thirteen thousand taels, first call.
Thirteen thousand taels, second call.
Thirteen thousand taels, third call.
Sold.
Good.
Thirteen thousand taels
for this worthless thing.
Lu Jianglin,
if this doesn't contain
what Duke Zhen wants,
I'll have you torn apart
and fed to the dogs.
Yes.
How do you open this thing?
I don't know either.
Move aside.
- Farewell, Your Majesty.
No idea what it even is.
His Majesty wants it,
and so does Duke Zhen.
Willing to spend
over ten thousand taels on it.
The military tally.
What?
Although His Majesty
controls the troops in the capital,
they're nowhere near strong enough
to rival the Zhen State Army.
That's how he maintained peace
with Father before.
But Father's ambitions
are growing greater and greater.
If His Majesty wishes
to contend with him,
he must find the Chifeng Army
left behind by his maternal grandfather.
But didn't the Chifeng Army
get wiped out ten years ago?
The commander died in battle,
and the remaining forces scattered
across different regions.
As long as
the military tally is recovered,
they can all be gathered again.
If the box truly contains
the military tally,
then war may break out very soon.
For Young Master,
would that be good or bad?
What do you think?
Everyone says Young Master
is indifferent to fame and ambition,
gentle and righteous,
and even turned against Duke Zhen
to protect His Majesty.
But I feel that you
have plans of your own.
Everyone has plans of their own.
Send a secret message to Father.
The military tally has fallen
into His Majesty's hands.
What do you mean by this, Young Master?
(I never expected that
after searching for so many years,)
(I would truly find it.)
Is Your Majesty unable to open the box?
Want to give it a try?
Yes.
If you open it, you'll be rewarded.
If you fail,
then you'll be punished.
This looks like a puzzle box.
As long as the characters
are arranged correctly,
it should open.
(These characters together...)
(sound like a song
from my previous life.)
Phoenix.
Perches.
Parasol.
Long.
Night.
Bright.
(She actually knows the secret code?)
It opened.
Is this what Your Majesty
has been searching for?
Then today, I've completed
the task Your Majesty assigned me.
Your Majesty,
may I have my death-exemption medal now?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪