( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 14=
Your Majesty,
may I have my death-exemption medal now?
No.
How exactly did I offend him again?
What's wrong, Young Lady?
I'm really exhausted.
The rumors say
he's moody and unpredictable.
Turns out they're completely true.
He changes his face faster
than turning a page.
Serving the ruler
is like serving a tiger.
(But I truly don't have much time left.)
Phoenix Perches Parasol,
Long Night Bright.
Those two lines were the final words
of the Chifeng Army's commander.
How does Shen Zhinian know them?
Shen Zhinian once mentioned to me
that her maternal family
lives in Chizhou.
Send people
to bring them to the capital.
Yes.
(Ten taels)
Why did Mother only send
a few dozen taels this time?
How is this supposed to be enough?
Once Young Master
enters official service,
Eldest Young Lady, you won't
have to worry about silver anymore.
Shen Nanqiao!
Lu.
Did you manage to obtain that item
at Jinsong Pavilion last night?
Is Duke Zhen
finally going to value you now?
Wretched woman!
Do you have any idea
how badly you've ruined me?
Thirteen thousand taels of silver!
What am I supposed to do now?
What thirteen thousand taels?
Why are you still pretending?
Tell me.
Did you set me up on purpose?
From the peach tree to Jinsong Pavilion,
there was never any hidden master.
You deliberately harmed me.
No, that's not it.
Lu,
listen to me.
There really was
a mysterious recluse who told me.
Otherwise, how could I possibly
have helped you
gain the favor of Dowager Consort Liu?
If I believe you again,
I'll probably end up dead
without a burial.
Lu!
Don't panic.
What exactly happened?
I truly regret not chasing
after Shen Zhinian back then
and leaving with her.
Lu Jianglin,
I treated you with nothing but kindness,
yet you resent me?
Shen Zhinian betrayed you,
and you still can't let her go.
What's so special about her?
Has there been any movement
from Duke Zhen's side?
Jiang Fu only returned
to the residence this morning.
Less than one hour later,
she was carried back out.
They say she received fifty lashes.
She was beaten half to death
and ordered to repay the silver.
What about Lu Jianglin?
He went to the Duke Ding Manor,
but for some reason,
Duke Ding drove him out.
How strange.
Who exactly is Lu Jianglin working for?
How did he learn
about the Chifeng Army tally?
As long as he keeps running around,
he's bound to leave traces behind.
(Tinglan Palace)
By the Mandate of Heaven,
the Emperor decrees.
To Shen Zhinian of the Shen family,
graceful and virtuous,
refined and dignified in conduct,
you are hereby
promoted to Lady of Beauty.
Respect this decree.
Congratulations, Lady Shen.
His Majesty already said last time that
he would promote Your Ladyship to Lady of Beauty.
Now the decree has finally arrived.
Come.
Bring the gift I prepared.
We're going to visit Lady Liu.
Young Lady,
why are you still bringing her gifts?
She nearly got you killed.
Don't forget, she saved you
in the Cold Palace.
What if she was the one who poisoned us?
It wasn't her.
Even if she wanted me dead,
she would've first investigated
my crimes thoroughly.
Besides, I'm not only visiting her
to give thanks.
It's also because
she's the longest serving consort
in the palace
aside from the Empress.
I want to ask her
about His Majesty's taboos.
Shen Zhinian,
what is the meaning of this?
I came to thank Your Ladyship.
To thank Your Ladyship
for saving Handan.
You're thanking me
with something this worthless?
I know that Your Ladyship
enjoys boundless honor and wealth.
Naturally, nothing is lacking.
I heard Your Ladyship
was once bold and carefree,
and especially fond of archery.
So...
You've certainly done your research.
But keep your little schemes to yourself.
I stopped touching bows and arrows
after my coming of age ceremony.
Why care about the opinions of others?
If it's something
Your Ladyship truly loves,
why not take it up again?
I'm not a man.
I won't be fooled by your sweet words.
Speak.
Why exactly did you come to see me?
I wish to know
what taboos His Majesty has.
Shen Zhinian,
you've got some nerve.
You actually dare ask me
how to win His Majesty's favor?
Lives are at stake,
so I beg Your Ladyship to enlighten me.
I will surely
repay the favor in the future.
What do you mean lives are at stake?
Don't tell me you're trying
to save Lu Jianglin?
You still want someone like him?
That's not the case.
Then why?
Since you're unwilling to say,
I won't press further.
But if you think a single bow
will get you your answer,
it won't be that easy.
As long as Your Ladyship
is willing to tell me,
I would do anything.
I don't need you
to risk your life for me.
But since you've gifted me this bow,
I'll give you one chance.
If you can beat me,
I'll tell you.
I'll give you a handicap.
You go first.
You still have time to admit defeat.
Kowtow to me,
then get out.
Your Ladyship,
your turn.
You will personally serve as my target.
Your Ladyship, let me do it instead.
Arrows have no eyes.
Be careful,
or you may not leave here alive.
You still have time to admit defeat.
Your Ladyship,
please.
Do you know that if my arrow
misses by even an inch,
your face will be ruined?
Forget it.
His Majesty's birthday banquet
is approaching.
Bloodshed would be unlucky.
I'll spare you today.
Only this once.
Thank you, Your Ladyship.
The Dowager Consort once told me
that when His Majesty was young...
If I danced in red,
he would give me medicine.
Is that true?
Yes.
I always treated you as a friend.
I even risked execution to come see you.
And you still don't trust me?
His Majesty agreed.
He put on that shameful dance outfit.
Wonderful.
Dance again.
Dance another one. Get up.
Fine.
How boring. Let's go.
Give me the medicine.
What medicine?
Do you deserve it?
The dance ended,
but there was no medicine.
Only humiliation and deception.
So His Majesty
suffered so much as a child.
He's experienced too many betrayals.
That's why it's difficult for him
to truly trust anyone.
It seems I can't obtain
the death-exemption medal
through favor alone.
Then what will you do?
How about we
forget about the death-exemption medal?
Being a favored consort isn't so bad.
Favor is the most unreliable thing.
It can disappear at any moment.
Once favor is lost,
I can't even protect
the people around me.
If favor can't earn me
a death-exemption medal,
then I'll earn it with my own abilities.
Young Lady, you mean...
If I can't become a favored consort,
then become someone
who can work for him instead?
He brought me out of the palace
because I could help cover
for him, didn't he?
That means I can still be useful to him.
Make preparations.
I'm going to see His Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Something has happened at Xunlu Pavilion.
Isn't the poetry competition
being held there?
What could've happened?
Ever since this year's
competition began,
Lu Jianglin has always taken first place.
But lately, he's missed
four rounds in a row.
And during those same four rounds,
a brilliant scholar
from Jin suddenly appeared.
Every poem he composed
completely overwhelmed
our scholars of Daliang.
The poetry gathering at Xunlu Pavilion
was established by Your Majesty
as a path for scholars
of humble birth
to enter official service.
Duke Zhen
has secretly tried to sabotage it
all along, but failed.
Yet during this gathering,
many people from Jin suddenly appeared
and suppressed every scholar in Daliang.
A mighty nation like Daliang,
and between one Duke Zhen
and a few poets from Jin,
none of you can handle it?
Sorry to trouble you.
Please announce me.
Lady Shen, please enter.
Why are you here?
Your Majesty,
I had some free time today,
so I made some pastries
and brought them
for Your Majesty to try.
Just now at the door,
I overheard you discussing
the poetry gathering.
I humbly wish
to give it a try.
That's right.
Lady Shen is exceptionally talented.
Those people from Jin
and Hu won't stand a chance.
Take this token
and go to Boyue Pavilion.
Review the winning essays
from previous years at Xunlu Pavilion,
as well as the competition rules.
I obey Your Majesty's decree.
Your Majesty,
are you truly allowing Lady Shen
to participate in the poetry gathering?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪