( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 16=
Sir, you've been competing in Daliang
for two days now.
Have you seen any scholar here
refuse to admit defeat?
You simply can't accept losing.
- Sore loser!
The people of Jin are unethical.
Shameless!
Fine.
I concede.
Come.
Pour the tea.
- Good!
(Tinglan Palace)
Lady Shen,
His Majesty asked me
to deliver this to you.
It's your reward
for winning the poetry gathering.
Thank you.
Look, Young Lady.
It's a golden hairpin.
Young Lady, let me put it on for you.
(He gave me a gold hairpin.)
(I should prepare a gift in return.)
(Yuehui Pavilion)
It's finally almost done.
I should still have time
to give it to him tonight.
Mm.
It's beautiful.
It's a lively fox.
If it's a gift for His Majesty,
why carve a fox instead
of mandarin ducks?
People say foxes bewitch their masters,
but they don't know
that foxes stay loyal to one mate
for life.
People also say
they envy mandarin ducks
more than immortals,
but they don't know
mandarin ducks
change mates every year.
They're fickle.
I didn't know
mandarin ducks are unfaithful.
They are.
His Majesty always says
I'm a devious fox,
but he doesn't realize
he's actually complimenting me.
Foxes are good.
There's something I've wanted to say.
Yes?
I've observed His Majesty before.
I think he truly cares about you.
Perhaps a little.
I'm not sure.
So what if he does?
No one can live a lifetime
relying on another person's sincerity.
When you were back in Chizhou,
you used to envy the loving couples
in huaben.
But since entering the palace,
you've become so burdened with worries.
I want to help you,
but I don't know how.
I'm fine.
I mean it.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
You can get along with His Majesty
like an ordinary married couple.
Maybe you'd be happier that way.
I'm getting along well with him.
But being like an ordinary couple
is impossible.
He's the Emperor, after all.
Besides,
his moods change without warning.
Trying to guess
what he's thinking every day
is even more tiring than dealing with
Madam Shen back then.
His Majesty is ten thousand times better
than Madam Shen.
That's true.
At least he's young, good-looking,
and has a strong body.
His lips are soft
when he kisses.
Young Lady, you shouldn't say
such things out loud.
Go see if His Majesty
has finished his work.
Invite him to come over for dinner.
Mm.
I'll go right away.
Your Majesty, this is the latest report
from Tinglan Palace.
Mm.
At the third quarter of Shen hour,
Lady Shen carved a fox hairpin
and said...
She said that being favored is useless,
that Your Majesty is difficult to please,
and that men...
That men are all useless.
What else did she say?
She also said
foxes are the truly loyal lovers.
They're faithful
to only one partner for life.
Foxes?
Nonsense.
That actually isn't nonsense.
I've heard such sayings
about foxes being loyal.
You mean
she wishes to spend her whole life
as husband and wife with me?
That's what you wish for too.
It's not that I doubt her.
The unrest in the nation is one matter.
Whether Manshu Tears can be cured
is another.
I've walked on thin ice my whole life.
I may fall
and never stand up again one day.
Your Majesty,
I'll definitely find the antidote.
It's been quite a while
since someone was sent to His Majesty.
Why haven't they returned yet?
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
His Majesty won't be coming tonight.
He has gone to Lady Liu's.
You may leave.
Yes.
His Majesty must have gone there
for some important matter.
Perhaps
you should rest first.
What a waste of all this food
and this bowl of botuo noodles.
Sit down.
We'll eat together.
Allow me to serve you.
No need.
Serving a bowl of botuo noodles
isn't tiring.
Don't be upset, Young Lady.
His Majesty cares about you the most.
I'm not upset.
I used up all the sadness
of this lifetime
in my previous life.
Also,
being sad over a man
is the most worthless thing of all.
You've always had your own mind.
Back when Master
arranged your marriage to
that broke Young Master Lu,
you helped the Lu family move
from a run-down shack
into a proper manor.
You were never afraid of hardship,
but you shouldn't always have to suffer.
I hope you'll meet the right person
and live a good life.
Kind Handan,
thank you.
(Tinglan Palace)
♪A fair lady sighs, what eve is this?♪
Young Lady,
it's getting late.
Let's return to the room.
His Majesty won't be coming tonight.
I'll sleep
after I finish carving the hairpin.
I'll fetch you a cloak.
Sure.
♪The partridge's cry
is full of resentment♪
♪You do not know that nothing
is sweeter than a fleeting love♪
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
Nian.
My Nian, you have grown up.
Mother.
Mother,
you finally came.
Yu's good.
He's good-looking,
clever, and filial.
Mother,
who's Yu?
I begged Heaven for a chance
to let him meet you.
Yu
is Nangong Xuanyu.
Mother,
what are you talking about?
Nian,
I need to go now.
Take good care of yourself.
Mother.
Mother,
don't go.
Mother...
(Shen Nianzhi,)
(why do you always cry in your dreams?)
Your Highness.
I think I hear
someone playing the guqin.
Most likely some lonely soul
unable to sleep,
playing a tune in the night.
Your Highness, you're frail.
You shouldn't stay in the cold wind.
It's fine.
The music is beautiful.
When I first met him,
he stood under a tree
in plain robes.
He was thin as a pine.
But his eyes
shone like stars in the night sky.
With a mere glance,
I fell for him.
It has been ten years,
but he has never once smiled at me.
One day,
His Majesty will see
how good you truly are.
Where's he now?
At Tinglan Palace.
Tinglan Palace again.
Is Shen Zhinian
that good?
Yu.
My mother came.
She said you were good-looking.
What did you call me?
Your Majesty.
What did you
call me?
Oh.
I was asleep.
I dreamed of my mother.
She called you Yu.
She said you were good-looking.
Your mother?
Mm.
Since I came to the capital,
I've never dreamed of my mother again.
She told me to stay away
from the capital
and its bloodshed.
But I failed.
She probably
doesn't want to see me anymore.
The Dowager Consort
probably wishes to see you,
but the road is too long.
She has yet to arrive.
The road is long?
Mm.
The imperial temple
sits high in the mountains.
The journey is long,
but the scenery along the way
is beautiful.
The Dowager Consort keeps stopping
to admire the sights.
That's why she hasn't appeared
in Your Majesty's dreams.
It's difficult enough for a woman
to travel such a long distance.
Your Majesty must be patient.
Wait patiently for the Dowager Consort.
Let her enjoy
the scenery at her own pace.
Shen Zhinian.
That may work on children.
I'm not a child.
Your Majesty grew up too quickly.
You may allow yourself
to be a child sometimes.
Children are weak.
I never want to be a child again.
Don't coax me like that anymore.
The Dowager Consort didn't want
Your Majesty to get involved in bloodshed
because she was worried
about your safety.
Your Majesty,
you were born for greatness.
You will surely
restore the glory of Daliang
and bring all lands to bow before you.
The Dowager Consort could see this.
She would be happy.
♪The world is gentle
only because of you♪
♪In the palace, through dawn and dusk,
who keeps a lamp burning♪
♪Time silently scars those left behind♪
♪I walk through the palace
day and night, just for my beloved♪
♪All my tenderness is for you,
I'd stay alone for you♪
♪I don't ask for equality,
only that you hear me♪
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪