( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 15=
Lady Shen.
Lord Jiang.
I didn't expect His Majesty
would allow you
to enter Library Pavilion.
His Majesty asked me to attend
the Xunlu Poetry Gathering.
I came to look through past poems.
It seems His Majesty is fond of you.
You grew up with His Majesty.
I suppose you understand him well.
If you spend more time with him,
you'll know him too.
He doesn't feel secure easily,
and he doesn't trust people quickly.
You'll inevitably be treated coldly
at times
when serving by his side.
But once he trusts you,
he treats you very well.
Besides, I think...
What is it?
His Majesty was willing
to set aside his pride at Jinsong House
and kneel to pour liquor.
He doesn't just like you,
he trusts you too.
Please don't take
what happened at Jinsong House
to heart.
I never meant to offend you.
I know.
I happened to be looking through
the records from the past
Xunlu Poetry Gatherings.
(Rules of the Xunlu Poetry Gathering)
These are the rules. You can have a look.
On the day of the gathering,
I'll accompany you there.
Why are you treating me
with such kindness?
I want him to be happy.
When we were children,
I pitied him for being weak
and admired him for enduring so much.
I treated him like a younger brother.
Later, I admired
his courage and ambition
as he dared to fight
against fate itself,
and I came to see him
as the ruler of Daliang.
People are always like this.
They place their hopes
in someone stronger than themselves.
They hope someone else can do
what they cannot accomplish for them.
Lord Jiang, you're a frank man.
Let me explain to you how things work
in the Xunlu Pavilion.
Alright.
I didn't know there were so many rules.
His Majesty didn't mention any of this.
That's just how he is.
Please be patient with him.
If only His Majesty
had half of your good temper.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Mm.
Your Majesty.
I shall take my leave now.
Why the hurry?
You're making it seem like
I'm disturbing the two of you.
We shall play a game, Official Jiang.
Sit.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Are you expecting me
to serve the two of you
while you play weiqi?
- Please, Your Majesty.
I had no idea
you two were so in sync.
Your Majesty, you can't place it there.
A true gentleman doesn't speak
while watching a game.
That was a terrible move.
You do it then.
I'll do it.
See, Your Majesty?
That's how weiqi is played.
What you were doing earlier
was utter chaos.
Playing weiqi
is much like governing a state.
Only through great chaos
can true order arise.
(Of all places,)
(he picked the only losing move.)
(Do you really not know how to play?)
Your skill has improved greatly indeed,
Your Majesty.
Let's go.
Attend the Xunlu Poetry Gathering.
Yes.
I'll return first.
Rest well.
Won't you stay a little longer?
I have memorials to review.
Your Majesty,
I reviewed the game of weiqi
from earlier
and realized
you intentionally let Lord Jiang win.
Should I not
have beaten him earlier?
I can't beat him.
You may do as you please.
I bid farewell to Your Majesty.
To think His Majesty
would intentionally lose to Lord Jiang.
Those two were quite interesting.
These flowers are beautiful.
Why are you still in the palace so late?
I went to the Library Pavilion
and happened to play a game
with Lady Shen.
Are you close with Shen Zhinian?
We met a few times.
What kind of person
do you think she is?
She's beautiful
and somewhat talented.
That's all?
Then why does His Majesty
like her so much?
Don't overthink.
Focus on recovering.
Do you like her too?
You were speaking up for her.
You even played weiqi with her.
I just happened to run into her
at the Library Pavilion.
His Majesty sent her to attend
the Xunlu Poetry Gathering,
so she asked me a few questions.
That poetry gathering was founded
by Dowager Consort Qin
in her younger days.
He never took me there.
Does His Majesty like her that much?
You shouldn't dwell on these.
Get well soon.
You're just like Father.
You're heartless.
At least His Majesty won't upset me.
You two are worse than he is.
Eunuch Pan,
help Her Highness back to rest.
Your Highness, Lord Jiang is busy
with official duties.
Let him return.
I take my leave.
Who knows whether he's busy with work
or busy because of Shen Zhinian?
Didn't you say
you wouldn't interfere in the game?
I had intended
to remain behind the scenes
and watch them destroy each other.
But a new piece suddenly appeared
on the board.
If I don't act now,
it may fall into someone else's hands.
You always say weiqi must be played
with patience and caution.
Isn't entering the game now too risky?
You're mistaken.
I'm not a player in this game.
I'm the one manipulating it.
They may know how to fight and kill,
but they don't understand
that a move must be laid out in advance.
That's why they're bound to lose.
(Xunlu Pavilion)
Third round, Lin Qing of Jin won.
You dare challenge me?
Get lost.
Who else
dares step forward?
Just let him have the win already.
Why should we?
Right?
Exactly.
I'll challenge you.
Has Daliang run out of talent?
Sending a woman to compete instead?
If I dare step forward,
why would you fear
accepting the challenge, sir?
Miss,
don't cry after you lose.
That young lady certainly has  courage.
(Deek Hunt Poetry Gathering)
Can she do it?
She must have confidence.
(All those poems
were written by me in my previous life)
(to help Lu Jianglin win first place.)
(No wonder he kept winning.)
(Looks like Shen Nanqiao)
(memorized my poems from my past life
and gave them to him.)
What?
Afraid now?
I'll take your challenge.
But if you lose,
you must kneel and serve tea in apology
to the master of Xunlu Pavilion.
Me, lose?
That would never happen.
Absolutely impossible.
Let's begin.
What's this?
Do you need to stare at my handsome face
before you can write?
The closer I stand,
the better I can admire
your expression after you lose.
You're certainly confident.
Very well.
Today, I'll teach you
how a gentle lady should behave.
(Deep in the valley grow orchids,
their green leaves perfectly poised.)
(Their faint fragrance)
(drifts beyond the doors of clouds.)
(If the peony understood
the grace of noble solitude,)
(why fear dust and mud)
(sullying its pure white petals?)
I'm done.
(She wrote the exact same poem as I?)
(What's going on?)
How does she know the last two lines?
This is another form of a poetry duel.
You write the first half,
and I answer with the second.
I underestimated you.
(Snow presses upon jade-like boughs,
showing pure hues of elegance.)
(A faint fragrance...)
(What comes next?)
Snow presses upon jade-like boughs,
showing pure hues of elegance.
A faint fragrance drifts softly
through the humble gates.
If all flowers understood
such graceful poise,
why fear frost and bitter winds
that pierce to the bone?
- Excellent!
- Nice poem!
That's brilliant!
Miss, where exactly did
these poems come from?
I wrote them myself.
Impossible.
Would you like to continue, sir?
Daliang only won through petty tricks.
You people don't keep your word.
You've been competing in Daliang
for two days now.
Have you seen any scholar here
refuse to admit defeat?
You simply can't accept losing.
Sore loser!
The people of Jin are unethical.
Shameless!
Fine.
I concede.
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪