=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 19=
Anyway, you should be punished too.
Someone was badmouthing me,
and you didn't speak up for me.
How would I dare interrupt?
You just enjoy
watching people scold me.
(Nangong Xuanyu has become so childish.)
Want to see
the most charming man in Daliang cook?
Your Majesty.
I never expected the noble Lord Jiang
to know how to cook.
My tastes are rather light.
I'm not used to food prepared by others.
Lord Jiang, you have
a full collection of spices.
He has a particular fondness for them.
He knows
all kinds of spices.
But they all
look pretty similar.
They're different.
Each blend
brings out a different fragrance.
I never knew you knew spices so well.
I learned it from Madam Lian,
who served beside His Majesty's mother.
She was especially skilled
at making fish congee.
It's a pity...
When I went to collect her body,
there was a basket beside her.
Inside the basket,
there was a Peng fish.
Let's not bring up sad things.
Come.
Try the congee.
Have a taste
of the fish congee
made by Daliang's most charming man.
Must you mock me like this?
Those were Lady Shen's exact words.
Also, stones like jade
lay heaped together,
and verdant pines stood in rows
like emeralds.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
So you do know when you're wrong?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, let's return to the palace.
Come.
The Prince of Jin was right.
The moment the white flute was played,
he immediately coughed up.
When Nangong Xuanyu
was exiled to the imperial temple,
the late emperor forced poison into him.
It flares up every full moon,
causing unbearable agony.
In recent years,
he has kept a white snake by his side.
That snake
is used to suppress the poison.
How did the Prince of Jin
come to know
such a secret about him?
This man is dangerous.
Your Lordship,
we'd best be cautious.
This is Daliang's capital.
Does he think he can rival me?
Father.
What have you done
to His Majesty, Father?
What are you talking about?
What could I possibly have done?
You're a minister of Daliang.
You should serve His Majesty with loyalty.
Go back.
I ask nothing of you
for the sake of the Jiang family.
Simply live out your days
as a carefree nobleman.
Daliang has suffered
through years of turmoil.
The people have only recently
regained peace and stability.
I hope you won't stir up more trouble.
Leave.
Useless trash.
Yes.
Young Master is kind
and loyal.
He must've been bewitched
by Nangong Xuanyu.
That's why he spoke out of turn.
If I had known,
I never would've let him befriend
Nangong Xuanyu.
(The one controlling the game
must never act rashly or impatiently.)
(Father misplayed his hand this time.)
What will we do next, Young Master?
Wait.
Are you really fine?
Shouldn't we visit
the Imperial Hospital?
It was only a rush of blood
this morning.
I'm fine now.
I should get going.
I'll come tomorrow night.
I bid farewell to Your Majesty.
Young Lady, the escort agency
just sent word.
After the gold token left the palace,
it disappeared.
What?
I'll go see His Majesty
and find a way to reclaim it.
Your...
(Cold Palace)
Why would His Majesty
go to the Cold Palace?
There's a secret chamber here.
That explains why he appeared here
the first time I met him.
We haven't found
Lady Shen's maternal family
at Mount Nanhua.
How should we report this to His Majesty?
It's more a matter of how His Majesty
will explain it to Lady Shen.
This is bad.
We secretly brought them
into the capital,
and now we've lost them.
Send more men to continue the search.
Yes.
(He captured my mother's family.)
(What is he trying to do?)
Your Majesty,
our men haven't found
Lady Shen's maternal relatives
at Mount Nanhua.
Send more men.
We're short-handed.
Duke Zhen's forces
are quietly advancing
toward the capital.
Your Majesty also needs more men.
Duke Zhen won't start a war so easily.
His troop has fought too many battles.
All they want now is a peaceful life.
Keep them occupied for now.
The matter at Mount Nanhua
can't be delayed any longer.
Yes.
Right. Tomorrow night,
I want to make up a proper wedding night
for Zhinian.
Have Eunuch Ming
prepare my chamber.
Understood.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
May you and Lady Shen
share a lifetime of love
and grow old together.
Smooth talker.
What reward do you want?
Help yourself.
Sure.
I won't hold back then.
Take your reward,
then go do your job.
Also, the Prince of Jin
has snuck into the capital
and is showing himself everywhere.
He must have some purpose.
Find out what it is.
Understood.
(This is Nangong Xuanyu's
secret chamber?)
Shen Zhinian, 19 years old.
Her father is Shen Maoxue,
a finance officer of Chizhou Prefecture.
Born to a concubine.
Lost her mother at seven
and was raised under Madam Shen's care.
(This is...)
(He has been investigating me
all along.)
(He recorded every word I said)
(and everything I did.)
Madam Shen refused to let her mother
be buried in the Shen family tombs.
She carried the memorial tablet
and chased after her mother's coffin
through the snow
for two days and two nights.
(What am I)
(to him?)
(Were all those feelings he showed me
just an act?)
(Nangong Xuanyu,)
(you're better at pretending than I am.)
(Death-exemption Medal)
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
He's been acting in front of me
the whole time.
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪