This marriage,
I've agreed to it.
Pinru.
You...
You're joking, right?
You're not that kind of person.
You said
you weren't interested in material things.
He's offering far too much.
What would I get
from being with you?
Cramped in a rental, eating instant noodles?
Staring at luxury goods through windows,
just to dream of them?
Or live in misery at the bottom forever?
Let's break up.
Let's part on good terms.
I'll compensate you.
Kid, face reality.
Ants belong in their anthills.
A toad
will never get to taste
swan meat.
What are you crying for?
A real man doesn't shed tears easily.
Just this small amount of money
exposed someone's true colors.
Heaven is helping you out.
This is a huge blessing.
Brother Ming...
That was three years of my love.
I delivered food every day,
scrimping and saving,
slaving away,
all for her!
Enough.
Your bro here hasn't even had his first love yet.
At least you got three years of her youth for free.
Trash like you isn't welcome here.
Now get the hell out.
Otherwise,
I won't mind sending you off myself.
Noda Tomoko.
Get to the Lin Family within ten minutes.
You know the address.
One second late,
and you'll bear the consequences.
Noda Tomoko?
You actually know Lady Tomoko's name?
Seems this little toad
has been hearing some rumors.
You actually dare order Lady Tomoko
to come within ten minutes?
Who do you think you are?
The Emperor himself?
Men!
Break his legs for me!
Tear apart that bragging mouth of his!
Hold on.
What?
Scared now?
Then get on your knees,
and lick the dirt off my soles.
Then bark like a dog a couple times.
If you do that,
I might consider only breaking one leg.
You bunch of snobbish dogs.
You're forcing my hand.
Today, Master Pang
will show you what real power means.
Brother Ming!
Get him!
Thank goodness,
you're finally awake.
I was worried sick.
That Professor Sun is truly amazing.
Please make sure to keep him there.
I'll arrange to bring my mom over right away.
Feifei.
My illness...
might not have been cured by Professor Sun.
Not Professor Sun?
Then who was it?
What method did they use?
Hurry, tell me.
He used a...
very special method.
Su Xiaowan,
why is your face so red?
Like a boiled shrimp.
Something's off with you.
Very off indeed.
Spit it out.
Is there some secret
you can't even tell me?
Is it that...
that miracle doctor
did something unspeakable to you?
Don't talk nonsense.
Nothing happened.
In any case,
I'll bring the real miracle doctor
to treat Auntie's illness.
That's it for now. Bye.
Blushing, flustered,
incoherent.
Oh, Su Xiaowan, Su Xiaowan.
This girl
definitely has something going on.
And what's more,
it's something big.
Breaking and entering,
assault and battery.
I'm calling the police.
I'll have you all arrested.
Don't call the cops.
Today, I'm going to
kill them with my own hands.
Call our men.
Get every fighter we have here.
Bring weapons.
If I don't finish them off today,
I'll write my name Dongchuan backwards.
Pinru.
After all, we've shared three years together.
I'll give you one last chance.
I've made myself very clear.
It's over between us.
Take your friends
and leave immediately.
Don't make me say something harsher.
You're getting the wrong idea.
I just wanted to give you a chance to grovel.
After spending three years as your simp,
I'll let you have a taste
of what it feels like to be one.
Since you don't appreciate it,
you won't even get to lick Master Pang's shoes.
You hear that?
The Noda Family men are here.
You're all dead.
Eldest Miss, Second Miss.
I, Dongchuan Quanyilang,
am unworthy
of you both coming here in person.
Mr. Wu.
Honey.
Stop calling my sister from now on.
Call me instead.
I'm cuter than her,
more obedient than her,
better at making you happy than her.
Wu Ming.
Please give your orders.
The entire Noda Family
will go through fire and water for you.
From now on, I want the Noda Family
to honor Master Pang as your head.
Brother Ming.
That's a bold move.
Master.
I, I, I...
Rise, rise.
Brother Pang.
Congratulations.
I knew you were destined for greatness.
My dear son-in-law.
Earlier...
Earlier, your mom and I misunderstood you.
We were just testing you,
to see if your feelings for our Pinru
were sincere.
Yes, yes, yes.
Earlier was purely a test.
From now on, we're family.
The Lin Family is counting on you.
Just now,
you couldn't be bothered with me.
And now,
this Master is way out of your league.
Brother Pang.
Let me explain.
I really do love you.
Everything earlier was fake.
My parents forced me to do it.
Forgive me, please forgive me, okay?
Let's start over.
Brother Pang, let's start over.
Brother Ming.
Let's go.
Brother Pang.
Brother Pang, let me explain.
I do love you.
Why can we share hardships
but not prosperity?
Brother Pang.
Life is like a play,
and a play is like life.
Brother Ming.
I want to get drunk tonight.
Sure, I'll join you.
Open! Open! Open!
Your foot...
didn't go numb for no reason.
This time,
we're up against a true master.
Striking pressure points from afar,
immobilizing with golden needles.
Impressive skills.
Find him at any cost.
With the Gao family closing in,
he may be our casino's only hope.
Sister Qian.
The Gao family are legendary gamblers.
And Young Master Gao's offer isn't low.
Why don't we...
seek shelter under their big tree?
Silence!
Golden Hall is the Wang family's lifeblood.
How could we just hand it over?
Yes, yes, yes.
Sister Qian,
I was wrong.
Go.
Use every resource we have.
Leave no stone unturned to find him.
Yes.
Sister Qian,
should I call him over?
No need.
Sister Qian.
The usual.
Yamazaki 25 on the rocks,
and a cigar.
Jingjing.
Look at that guy over there.
He's got such style.
Come on.
Let's go get a free drink.
Rourou,
this isn't really appropriate.
Let's not.
What are you afraid of?
Watch me.
Hey, handsome.
Drinking alone is so boring.
Come have a drink with us.
Kids shouldn't drink.
You're such a buzzkill.
Playing hard to get?
Reverse psychology.
I get it.
We only came over 'cause you're cute.
No need to be so uptight.
I said,
no drinking.
You...
Rourou,
maybe we should just leave.
No way.
How can you not drink on your birthday?
No drinks on your birthday,
and life's not worth living.
Take it.
Bottoms up.
You have to finish this bottle today.
If you don't drink, you're disrespecting me.
But Rourou,
I really can't drink.
What are you doing? Pervert!
Congenital ventricular septal defect.
Her heart muscle is extremely fragile.
Do you want her to die on her birthday?
You're talking nonsense.
Jingjing went last week to...
Rourou,
the doctor really did say
I can't touch alcohol for six months.
Not even a drop.
Why didn't you tell me something so serious?
I...
And you.
How did you know?
You weren't following us, were you?
You creep!
Where are you going?
Hey, little lady.