No matter what you hear
or what you see
even if the sky falls
do not take a single step closer
Violators will bear the consequences
Yes, Master
Is he
Is he really dead?
Not only is he dead
When I moved him just now,
his body had already gone stiff
Uncle Pang
Is he really never coming back?
Though he always tried to steal our martial arts
he really was good to me
And what about Master?
How devastated he must be
Wu Ming had me find seven bronze lamps
Do you know what they're for?
Brother Pang loved wealth
Maybe they're burial offerings
to light his path to the underworld
I believe Wu Ming must have a deeper purpose
It can't be as simple as burial offerings
Do you think
they could be used to revive Wu Pang?
After all, China's ancient traditions
hold mysteries beyond comprehension
No way
His body's already stiff
I know
medicine has many miracles,
but
if he really comes back to life
then Master wouldn't be human,
but a god walking among mortals
So
I don't think it's likely
If it were possible
I'd willingly trade my life
for Brother Qian's life
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Exactly seven lamps
What is he doing?
This...
A true heir of the Wu family.
With such heaven-defying methods,
you truly haven't disappointed me.
But
how foolish
to pay such a heavy price.
A-Yi
A once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
is right before your eyes
If you fail again
you'll never get another chance
Why did they all go out?
That gust of wind just now was so strange
By all logic
this place shouldn't have wind year-round.
This is bizarre.
I feel so cold
And
it's not the wind's chill
it's the kind
of cold that seeps into your bones
like falling into an ice cellar
What about you?
Me too
Get out!
It's not cold anymore
I feel warm all over
Look, the lamps lit up again!
Brother Qian!
Don't go in, it's dangerous!
Master is still inside!
It's dangerous!
Master, hurry and come out!
Master!
President Su.
Look, 500,000 likes already.
And it keeps soaring.
The whole internet is bashing him.
This Wu Ming is an absolute fraud.
A charlatan, a quack.
Look at this one.
Says he stole his dad's life-saving money.
Causing the old man to die with regrets.
Now look at this one.
Says he isn't even a doctor.
Just a lunatic.
Associating her with this internet pariah,
that's digging her own grave.
She'd be doomed beyond redemption!
Those are all fake.
I know whether Wu Ming has real skill.
But Feifei's current condition,
who among you has truly cared?
Are those baseless rumors
really more important than her life?
Of course we care.
We care about her commercial value.
About what the company invested in her.
About the tens of millions of fans
and their expectations for her.
President Su.
Feifei is a ticking time bomb right now.
One spark could set her off.
Sending her to that Wu Ming now,
do you know what that means?
It means
she's giving up her career.
Giving up ten years of her hard work.
The company will never allow that.
Wan'er wouldn't deceive me.
I trust her.
I'll bear all the consequences.
Bear them?
Feifei,
in your current condition,
you can't even shoot commercials.
Can you afford the massive penalty fees?
Can you bear
the whole industry blacklisting you?
You can't.
Sky-high compensation,
total ruin,
none of it matters.
Feifei,
I'll pick you and Aunt up early tomorrow.
We're going to the Dao Clinic.
If anyone dares to stop us,
the Su Group will show them
what total ruin really means.
President Su,
the Dao Clinic is closed today.
I'm scheduled to see Wu Ming at this time.
I'll call him.
We're sorry.
The number you have dialed is switched off.
Please try again later.
Thank you.
He made an appointment but is avoiding us.
Afraid he can't cure her and lose face, right?
Feifei,
the internet has totally exposed him.
He's just a swindling charlatan.
Feifei has so much negative press already.
Paparazzi catching us would be a disaster.
Feifei, there's still time to leave now.
Wan'er,
what's going on with Wu Ming?
Please be patient.
Can you tell me where Wu Ming is?
He's right inside.
Can you take me to him?
Only when the clinic master comes out
can you see him.
He's clearly here,
yet refuses to see us.
Are we being toyed with?
Zhonghua Dao Clinic,
just wait for your name to be ruined.
Feifei, paparazzi!
Wan'er,
since they refuse to see us,
let's not force the issue.
Sis.
This Wu Ming is so unreliable.
When I see him,
I'll give him a real piece of my mind.
Something may have happened to him.
He's such a proud man.
He'd never break his word.
You two, come with me.
Fine.
I'd really like to see
what excuse he has for avoiding us.
Was this place bombed?
How did it end up like this?
It must've been struck by lightning.
You guessed right.
This place yesterday
was struck by lightning for 20 minutes.
I knew it!
I saw it clearly from the hotel rooftop.
That lightning
struck one spot like crazy.
Dark clouds were full of electric snakes.
It was like a tribulation scene.
Wu Ming must've acted to defy fate.
That's why the lightning tribulation came.
Nonsense!
What tribulation?
What defying fate?
If you ask me,
you've read way too many fantasy novels.
In my opinion,
it must be some new weather weapon.
Or...
Or maybe it's a coincidence.
Otherwise it defies the laws of nature.
How could it strike just one spot?
This place must've sinned terribly then.
If you can't say anything useful, don't.
Is Wu Ming inside?
Yes.
Since the lightning struck yesterday,
he hasn't come out.
Master gave orders:
as long as he doesn't come out,
no one is allowed inside.
What on earth is going on?
Last night,
Brother Pang was shot dead with 3 bullets.
Master brought him back.
Then
he locked himself and Brother Pang
inside the room.
Oh, right.
And seven bronze lamps.
Master ordered:
no matter what happens,
no matter what you see,
no matter what you hear,
nobody is to approach the room.
Only when he comes out himself.
Seven bronze lamps?
Could they be the Seven-Star Life Lamps?
Lightning struck for 20 minutes.
Then Wu Ming really is defying fate,
enduring the lightning tribulation.
I told you, you've read too many novels.
But isn't this exactly a tribulation?
Look,
there are so many tall buildings around,
and lightning rods too.
Why would it strike only Wu Ming?
He must be defying fate.
I study traditional Chinese medicine.
Many things are mystical, I admit,
but something this absurd,
I still can't accept.
Stop arguing, you two.
Are we really not going in to check?
If something dangerous happens,
we could rescue him in time.
I think Wu Ming might've been struck dead.
Against the force of nature,
humans are mere ants and rubble.
Huizi.
How about
you go inside and check?
No.
Huizi will never disobey
Master's words.
Tch, I think you're just scared.
Afraid of strange things happening
and getting yourself involved.
I...
If you're not scared,
you go.
Of course I'm not scared!
Fine, I'll go!
If something really happens,
it'll be too late to cry.
Forget it.
Since Wu Ming said so,
I'll save him some face.
I trust Wu Ming.
Miss Su
Wu Ming
Are you in there?
Don't tell me you really got struck dead.
You bastard,
I haven't settled the score with you yet.
You can't die on me now!
Though this Wu Ming is truly despicable,
I still don't want anything to happen to him.
Sis,
why don't we go in and check on him?
They don't want to go in.
There might be danger inside.
You wait for me out here.
I'll go with you.