Stop right there!
Go, go, go!
I...
Stop!
Xiao Qi.
That pervert you brought in
defiled my sister!
How will you answer to her?
I...
I never imagined that
that pervert would be so vile.
I misjudged him.
You can run, but you can't hide.
I know where their clinic is.
I'm going to settle this right now.
Enough.
Let's check on my sister first.
Let's go.
Damn it!
I, Su Wan, remained chaste for 28 years.
My first time...
was given away in such a daze,
to a bastard I'd only met twice!
He doesn't know how to be gentle with women!
I'm going to kill him!
Wait...
My nearsightedness...
My 800-degree myopia is gone!
What's going on?
My whole body feels full of energy.
Miss, I'm sorry.
Sis.
You're awake, sis.
You seem to be in a good mood.
You look great.
Do you feel...
any discomfort anywhere?
No.
Why do you ask?
Take a moment and really feel.
Your legs,
your waist,
your chest...
Any discomfort anywhere?
Or any pain?
Why are you asking that?
Good, as long as you're fine.
But...
I...
I don't remember anything after I passed out.
Waking up now, I feel much better.
It must be that
Professor Sun's treatment worked.
Right, right, right.
Sis,
Let me take the pulse to check.
Since sis doesn't know she was defiled
this matter...
better not tell her.
About being violated by that jerk,
I have to pretend I don't know.
I can't let them know that I know.
It's too embarrassing.
Damn that Wu Ming.
Seems the elder miss is unaware.
And the second miss
doesn't want her to find out either.
So my crisis is over.
The elder miss looks much more energetic.
It seems
we misjudged Wu Ming.
But still,
Does treatment require sleeping together?
I've never heard of such a thing.
Forget it, forget it.
As long as the outcome is good.
Blood like a torrent,
pulse like thunder.
Sis,
this isn't a human pulse.
You're like a bull.
Watch how you talk.
I...
I'm just making a comparison.
What I mean is,
your pulse is incredibly strong.
Sis,
your skin has become so smooth too.
You've become prettier.
And younger, sis.
You can focus now.
Without your glasses,
you can see clearly.
After I woke up,
my vision became extremely sharp.
Even a tiny insect 200 meters away,
I can see the fuzz on its legs.
What on earth is going on?
Could it be...
all because of that pervert?
Seems he really does have skills.
But his character is truly rotten.
Sis,
I don't know either.
I mean,
isn't it good that you're better?
It seems that
Professor Sun's skills are remarkable.
I must tell Grandpa this great news now.
Stop right there.
I haven't settled accounts with you yet.
Trying to sneak off?
What accounts?
I told you to stay away from Wu Ming.
Not only did you not listen,
you brought him right back here.
I...
I really can't explain it.
The Wu Ming I brought back
cured your illness, didn't he?
Tell me,
how do you want me to punish you?
How about
I send you to Africa to dig mines?
Elder miss,
that's way too harsh.
Second miss,
if you don't beg her for me,
I'll expose that they slept together.
Sis,
Xiao Qi only meant well for you.
Can't you let her off just this once?
Fine.
Don't let it happen again.
Forget it.
If I push Xiao Qi any more,
she'll spill the secret.
And I'll be the one humiliated.
Covering for the jerk who violated me.
The latest LV model.
Oh Wu Qian, Wu Qian.
With your level of counterfeiting skill,
fooling country bumpkins might work,
but fooling us...
And this Rolex,
didn't even use sapphire glass.
And this box of American ginseng,
it reeks of sulfur.
Cheap, dime-a-dozen junk.
This is your sincerity in proposing?
Auntie,
I spent all my savings on these.
Look,
here, here are the receipts.
Bullshit!
A lousy delivery boy, out in all weather,
even starving for ten years,
you couldn't afford any of this.
My daughter,
Lin Pinru,
top student at the dance academy.
Suitors line up from here to Paris.
And someone like you?
A toad lusting after a swan.
Pah!
Dad,
Wu Pang and I truly love each other.
Is money really that important?
Can love put food on the table?
Can it be spent like money?
Can it buy you a Hermes Birkin?
Can it boost your father's career?
Look.
Open your eyes and take a good look.
Gifts from Young Master Higashikawa.
Hermes,
Cartier,
even the doghouse is custom LV.
Its leash is worth more than his life.
Uncle, Auntie,
I, Wu Pang, promise
once Pinru and I are together,
I'll have you living in a grand mansion,
dining on delicacies every day,
driving a Rolls-Royce.
I'll make Pinru
the happiest princess in the world.
Pinru,
just listen to him run his mouth.
Spouting nothing but nonsense.
He's bragging up to the heavens.
He'll bring the sky crashing down.
He's nothing but a pure loser.
Uncle, Auntie,
I'm serious.
I'm not bragging.
Marvelous!
How marvelous!
Young Master Higashikawa,
you've finally arrived.
Come, hurry.
Please, have a seat, have a seat.
Young Master Higashikawa.
Sit, sit, sit.
I was rather curious
about what fine young man could win
Miss Pinru's heart.
Who would have thought,
it's nothing but
a yapping little lapdog.
Pinru, quick,
pour Master Higashikawa some water.
I won't.
Uncle Lin,
Auntie Lin,
we're all reasonable people here,
so I won't beat around the bush.
This brand-new
Ferrari SF90,
Miss Pinru,
suits your elegance perfectly.
This Maybach
is for you, Uncle.
A businessman
must always maintain a certain dignity.
Pardon me, pardon me.
Auntie,
this is at Yunding Villa,
the most exclusive
detached mansion,
covering three acres of land.
It all depends on Miss Pinru.
As long as she agrees
to marry me, Kenichiro Higashikawa,
then all of this
will belong to the Lin family.
Excellent!
Master Higashikawa,
you are far too generous.
I'll decide on this marriage.
I agree to it.
A hundred times yes!
I agree as well.
Look,
we look just like father and son-in-law.
Ridiculous.
It's the 21st century now.
Arranged marriages, really?
Pinru's marriage in our family
is for her alone to decide.
Right, Pinru?
That's right.
My life
is mine to decide.
This marriage,
I accept.