[♪ upbeat music plays]
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION - SOME
SCENES WERE GENERATED USING AI
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
[♪ gentle music plays]
Hwayeong.
[♪ tense music plays]
[♪ melancholy ballad plays]
[song continues]
[music distorts, stutters]
-[device beeps]
-[automated voice, in English] Power off.
[in Korean] Just listen to it.
Come on, just try listening to it for now.
Music is good for treating anxiety.
It's out of battery.
Huh?
I charged it yesterday, though.
Give me a second.
-I should have a power bank.
-[announcer] …is now departing.
Do you want to chew on this?
Chewing on something can help you relax.
I told you I'm okay.
You're not okay, though.
You were crying yesterday.
Excuse me, please wake up.
Seonu…
Sorry?
You were saying "Seonu."
[♪ somber music plays]
Do you know me?
Sorry?
Did I ever ask for your help?
Ah…
Well, no, but I--
I'm sorry you had to help me
like that yesterday, but…
I never asked for your help.
So just be on your way
and stop crossing the line.
[stammers] What?
STYLE
::cue()
Wait, when did I ever cross the…
[ship horn blowing]
Excuse me!
[sighs]
What the hell? Sheesh.
Hey, I need to get on a ferry right away,
so I'm going to need a prescription.
-[horn honks]
-I'll head to your hospital.
I'm heading over right now.
[ship horn blowing]
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
[Ms. Hwang] The last ferry came
and went ages ago.
How come Dr. Do Jiui still isn't here?
I know. He couldn't have deserted his post
on his first day, right?
-Sheesh.
-By the way, Ms. Hwang,
a newbie is joining us next week, right?
I'm going to be really nice to her.
Newbie?
You said the new nurse
is in her third year. I'm in my fourth.
Doesn't that make her the newbie?
[chuckles] I guess you're right,
but she won't be your typical newbie,
just so you know.
She hasn't even been a nurse
for that long,
so imagine how awkward she'll feel.
I should help her out.
I've even organized
all the handover notes.
-Oh, okay. Well done.
-[chuckles]
As to who will end up helping whom,
we won't know until she gets here,
but well done.
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
[grunts] Dr. Do.
Hmm, what?
Goodness, Dr. Do!
Do you have any idea what time…
My gosh. You look like death.
What happened to you?
I'm sorry. I fell asleep on the ferry.
So you were sleeping on the ferry
all this time?
Yes.
[scoffs] Must be nice being
that unbothered.
Sleeping fine while ditching work.
-[♪ gentle music plays]
-[Hari] Do you want to chew on this?
Chewing on something can help you relax.
FEELING DOWN?
HERE'S A PICK-ME-UP!
[sighs]
EPISODE 2
THE WOMAN WHO CROSSES THE LINE
[music ends]
-[Jiui] Bellflower roots?
-That's right.
-They're precious wild bellflower roots.
-Mmm.
So, about that…
You saved the chief's life last week,
so the youth association
told me to give it to you.
It's from the youth association?
Thank you.
[coughing]
By the way, Mr. Lee Jangsu,
what brings you in today?
I'm just here
to get those meds I always take.
Those meds you always take? [sighs]
[coughing]
You already took
two weeks' worth a week ago.
Two weeks' worth
will barely cut it anymore.
My wife also takes it and all,
so give us about
a month's worth this time.
Did you just say you share your meds
with your wife?
Yes.
No. Proxy prescriptions are illegal.
Strictly speaking,
it's not a proxy prescription,
since I'm also taking those meds.
I still can't do it.
And the coughing might turn into pneumonia
if it continues for two weeks or more,
so I'll give you three days' worth.
Come back after finishing it.
I'm busy as hell because of the anchovies!
And you expect me to visit regularly?
That's the only way I can properly
assess your condition, sir.
I know my condition best.
STYLE
::cue()
I'll take care of myself,
so just give me 30 days' worth.
-I can't do that.
-That's how it's always been!
You're just going to cut me off like this?
[Ms. Hwang] Cough medicine,
something for your phlegm,
antibiotics, and this long one is
the stomach coating agent.
Take one packet in the morning
and in the evening after a meal.
[grunts] Did you really
only put three days' worth in there?
[chuckles]
We only put in
as much as the doctor prescribed.
That's the law.
Is there a law saying
civil servants can ignore residents?
Who said anything about ignoring anyone?
That's not it. It's just how the law is.
Hey, you think I don't know the law?
Law this, law that!
Looks like I'll have to take legal action
against you civil servants
who love the law so much
as a wake-up call!
Wait!
Have you been drinking?
Calm down a little, so I can explain…
-What should we do?
-Sorry?
Word is Mr. Lee actually went to
the county office to file a complaint.
Ah.
[nurse] Looks like things will get
quite troublesome for a while.
Doc, loosen up a little, will you?
Duking it out with the residents
is never easy.
It can't be helped.
-Thank you for the meal.
-Thank you.
Which brings us to my point.
If it won't be a big issue,
how about we just do as they ask?
That's better for everyone, no?
Giving patients
whatever prescriptions they ask for
isn't necessarily "better for everyone."
Nothing good comes
from giving in to patients.
I'm not saying this for my own good, okay?
It's because I'm worried about you guys.
If you keep doing as you please,
something terrible is
going to happen to you!
You'll see once it happens to you.
-Gosh, so frustrating.
-What do you…
[Mr. Park] Is anyone in?
-[Ms. Hwang] Oh, my!
-[Jucheon] Huh?
[Ms. Hwang] Oh, goodness!
I see you were still eating.
-Hello.
-[Ms. Hwang] Goodness.
You were discharged
from the hospital already?
[chuckling] Yes.
I got treated right away, after all.
-Dr. Do's stubbornness saved my life.
-[Ms. Hwang laughs]
Had it not been for Dr. Do Jiui,
I'd be on my way to Heaven by now.
[Ms. Hwang, Mr. Park chuckling]
[Mr. Park sighs] My, my, my.
[Ms. Hwang exclaims]
Isn't this monkfish liver?
What a precious treat!
Not as precious as my own life.
[Ms. Hwang, Mr. Park chuckling]
Goodness, Dr. Do.
Thank you so much.
Once I make a full recovery,
I'll pay you back for everything.
You can count on it. [laughs]
Okay.
We took too much of your time
when you were eating.
-Let's go now, Chunsik.
-That's right.
You must be tired
since you just got discharged,
-so go home to rest up.
-Okay.
-Thank you, everyone. [chuckles]
-Goodbye.
-Take care.
-[Ms. Hwang] Oh my, thank you.
-Have a safe trip home.
-[Mr. Park] Sure.
I love you, Dr. Do.
What?
You're totally
in the chief's good graces now.
On this island,
once you get on his good side,
your quality of life skyrockets.
Last time, he brought me pizza
from the mainland
because he liked my acupuncture treatment.
[chuckles] I got pizza for acupuncture,
so can you imagine how well
he'd treat you for saving his life?
Pizza?
Just because
he liked your acupuncture treatment?
Yes! Pizza!
[Jiui chuckles]
[♪ playful music plays]
-What the heck?
-[clears throat]
STYLE
::cue()
[sighs] Let's see…
[exclaims]
Ms. Eom. What's going on here?
What now?
I mean your slippers.
They're the same as mine.
Did you pay a premium
for the overseas shipping too?
I heard these were really hard to get.
A premium?
Let me see now.
[exclaims]
Did they always have this color?
I've never seen it before.
What are you, a detective?
What are you looking at my feet for?
I'm just fascinated, that's all.
I think we have pretty similar taste.
Similar, my ass.
How could I possibly have similar taste
to someone who owns a clinic in Seoul?
Just get back to work!
[Ms. Eom huffs]
He's such a weirdo! [sighs]
Damn it!
Who the hell pays a premium
for a flimsy pair of slippers?
I do not like him one bit. [exclaims]
[grunts]
[stomach growling]
[groans]
[groans] I'm so hungry.
[phone chiming]
[doctor 1] It's only 8:00 p.m.,
but none of the stores are open…
[doctor 2] Our island only has
one supermarket.
[doctor 3] Ours doesn't even open
at times.
I realized the value
of convenience stores.
[doctor 4] If you come across these
on your next trip to the market,
you have to stockpile them.
They rarely stock up on beer,
so finders keepers.
[doctor 1] I should rush over there now!
Some beer to keep me company
on these long nights!
Oh, beer…
Beer.
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
They don't have any ales or IPAs, though.
I wonder if the chief
would get some for me.
[chuckles]
Hey, I got here first.
You can't just take them all like that.
-Hey…
-Granny, put these on my tab!
Okay.
Goodbye!
Excuse me, do you have any more beer?
No, that was it.
Wow, I can't even.
What the hell?
[♪ playful music plays]
LUCKY SUPERMARKET
[Hari] Mmm.
You drink every day?
Man, what's that voice I hear?
It seems to be crossing a line.
You probably shouldn't be drinking.
If you drink like that every day…
It's just bad for you.
I'm guessing that's a roundabout way
of telling me to hand some over.
But stop crossing the line, okay?
-That's not it. I just--
-Hey.
Do you know how suspicious you are?
What do you mean?
I mean, why do we keep
running into each other?
Are you…
a stalker?
[stammers] A stalker?
Listen, you're the one
who's always butting in, okay?
I boarded the ferry first,
and I also came here first.
So if we're talking about stalking,
I'd say you fit the profile more.
If not, never mind.
"If not, never"…
[chuckles, scoffs]
[exclaims, distorted]
[both grunting]
Look at me. I almost crossed the line.
[exclaims]
[groaning]
STYLE
::cue()
[gasps]
What the hell?
Hello.
[Jiui sighs] So she's a nurse.
-[sighs]
-Say hello, everyone.
This is Ms. Yuk Hari.
I'm Eom Jeongseon, a fourth-year nurse.
You're third-year… so, class of '19?
I was in the class of '18.
Yes, class of '19.
I'm sure I have a lot to learn from you.
Right. I look forward to working with you.
[Ms. Hwang]
A lot to learn from her? Please.
Ms. Hari here is an intellectual who used
to work in a university hospital's ER.
Not just any hospital, but Asong Hospital.
I'm sure the operating room
was practically her living room.
But still, isn't this her first time
at a public health center?
Mmm. It may be her first time,
but ever since she was a kid,
she visited the island every holiday,
so she's well-acquainted with Pyeondongdo.
Wow, then you must be
really close to the villagers here.
That's great.
I think it's way harder
to get close to the villagers here
than it is to work here.
That's because you slack off all the time.
I'm Yong Jucheon
of the Korean Medicine Ward.
[Hari chuckles] I look forward
to working with you.
And this here is Dr. Do Jiui, the surgeon.
He's the very man
you busted your ass carrying over here.
[exclaims]
So you're a doctor.
Uh, yes.
[Ms. Hwang] Huh?
Have you already greeted each other?
[chuckles]
Well, I don't know if I can say that.
It might be crossing a line.
[Ms. Hwang] What are you talking about?
I'm Hyeon Chiyeon.
I look forward to working with you.
Now then, doctors,
please get ready to see patients.
-Okay.
-As for us,
let me just pull you aside
for a quick chat. This way.
[Hyeon] Never expected to see her here.
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
[Ms. Hwang, Hari chuckling]
My, you used to be so tiny,
but you've grown so much.
But why did you come here
from such a good university hospital?
Ah…
Well…
I was just wondering why you came
all the way to this island from the city.
If there was a story behind it.
-I just wanted to take a break.
-Mmm.
Take a break?
Right.
Let's do that.
-Take it slow and easy.
-[Hari] Mmm.
-[chuckles]
-[phone ringing]
-Let's catch up again later.
-Uh-huh.
[ringing stops]
This is Hwang Sinhye from
the Public Health Center speaking.
Though working here may look peaceful,
it's actually a war zone,
and the work we do is just as complicated
as working in an operating room.
It's not the kind of place
where you can just take a break,
is all I'm saying.
I see. [chuckles]
I look forward to your guidance.
-Mm-hmm.
-Ah!
What should I do first?
Ooh…
[stammers]
Why don't you start by switching out
the toilet paper rolls in the bathroom?
Ah…
Toilet paper?
Okay. [chuckles]
-This way?
-Mm-hmm.
[Ms. Hwang chattering]
Why on earth did I mention toilet paper,
after putting on such a front?
[gasps]
[sighs]
[mouse clicking]
[no audible dialogue]
[sighs]
Of all people, why…
Dr. Jiui, you're going to
have to go somewhere.
It's a patient who just had
a cancer operation,
but his daughter's
having trouble reaching him.
She's asking if we can check in on him.
-Me?
-Who else? Should I go?
I don't know my way around yet.
Don't worry about that.
We'll send another person with you.
All settled, right? Mm-mmm.
[♪ playful music plays]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[metal creaking]
Oh, gosh.
[boat approaching]
Easy, easy!
Seriously…
Hello!
[captain] Hey!
Looks like it's starting to drizzle.
[Hari] I know, right?
Sir, you said it was nearby.
Why do we need a boat?
It's only five minutes away by boat.
Oh, come on…
[captain] What business do you have there?
A patient's guardian
requested a home visit.
A patient on that side? Who's sick?
Do you know Mr. Kim Jeongbae?
Kim Jeongbae? Who could that be?
Oh, that guy?
I guess it's the guy who keeps to himself.
But I don't think it'll be easy
getting in that house.
The guy seemed to really hate
people entering his house.
Oh…
So he hates it when people cross the line,
like someone I know.
[captain] What?
Ah, it's nothing.
We can go there now, right?
-Of course. Get in.
-[stammers] Wait.
[stammers] Isn't there
some other way there?
Some other way?
Well, they are connected.
But if you were to walk,
it would take at least 40 minutes.
With the mountain path
being really hilly and all. [laughs]
Who would be dumb enough to do that?
[captain, Hari laugh]
Forty minutes? Okay.
Wait, Dr. Do. You're going to walk there?
You take the boat.
I'll walk. See you there.
Wait… [stammering]
Doctor!
[♪ playful music plays]
Where the heck am I? Damn it.
[panting]
[Hari] Hey, wait up.
[panting] We could have been there
in five minutes.
Why punish ourselves by walking there?
I never asked you to come with me, okay?
You could have just taken the boat.
It's not like there's anything I can do
without a doctor.
Why should I go there by myself?
I was talking to myself.
Tells me not to cross the line
but gives me so many causes for concern.
-Ms. Yuk.
-Okay, okay.
I'll stop talking to myself.
Hurry up. [groans]
Haven't you been here before, Ms. Hari?
Who would walk here?
Everyone takes a boat.
Let me see.
[insect chittering]
[screams]
Hey, will you please…
That's not it. Your shoulder, Dr. Do…
What about my shoulder?
The other side…
What is it?
Uh… You know what? Never mind.
You think helping is crossing a line,
so I'm not going to say anything.
-But that's going to bite, though.
-What?
[exclaiming]
Don't move. It's venomous.
Help me with this. Now!
I want to help, but I have to be careful.
What?
You see,
I learned something thanks to you.
No matter how much someone's struggling,
helping when they don't ask for it
is crossing a line.
It's trying to get in!
Hurry and do something!
What can I do? I can't cross the line.
-[stammers] Cross it.
-What?
Please cross the line!
-Damn it…
-Cross it?
-Cross it. It just crawled inside!
-[exclaims]
-Get it out.
-Just so we're clear,
you said to cross it.
Put your hands inside and take it out.
It's way inside!
-Lower!
-Where? Okay.
-Oh, come on!
-Okay.
-[Jiui exclaims]
-[Hari grunting]
-It's not there. What?
-Uh, Ms. Hari, it went down.
Right now…
-Left waist!
-Darn it!
STYLE
::cue()
-[gasps]
-[Hari] Stand still!
[Jiui] Oh, come on!
[exclaims] I think it bit me.
That was my nail.
Stop playing around, seriously!
I'm not.
-[breathing heavily]
-Oh, oh! Here it is. Hold still.
-I caught it.
-You caught it?
[exclaims]
Shouldn't we trap that guy somewhere?
You said it's venomous.
What if it bites someone?
-Why would we do that?
-Damn it.
-They don't bite if you leave them alone.
-[sighs]
Dr. Do, you owe me one now.
Pay me back later.
But…
But that guy's venomous.
Its fangs were terrifying. Did you see?
[thunder rumbling]
[Jiui panting]
This place…
[both groan]
[Jiui] This is…
Uh, are you sure this is the place?
It doesn't look like anyone lives here.
This has to be the place.
Just a second.
[Hari grunts]
DO NOT ENTER
[door creaks]
Mr. Kim Jeongbae,
we're here from the public health center.
Mr. Kim Jeongbae, are you home?
I'm pretty sure this is the place.
Hold on.
[stammers] Are you going in?
That would be a bad idea.
She said it's a patient
who was treated for cancer recently.
If you're going to cross any lines,
you have to make it count.
Especially when saving someone.
[stammers, grunts]
-[thunder rumbling]
-Oh, man…
Hey, Ms. Yuk?
It doesn't look like anyone's here,
so let's come back for them next time.
-Mr. Kim Jeongbae!
-Come on.
Mr. Kim Jeongbae?
Let's go inside.
Wait, Ms. Yuk. Why would you go in there?
How dare you enter my home
without permission?
Who the hell are you?
We're from the Public Health Center.
Your daughter said
she couldn't get in touch with you--
Get lost!
Yes, sir.
Now that we know he's fine, let's go.
Hurry up.
Since we're here,
how about a simple checkup? I think that…
What else do we need to check?
…would be a good idea.
But…
he's smoking.
[♪ somber music plays]
Sir.
I heard you recently had surgery,
but you're smoking right now.
That's why your daughter was so worried
and called us.
So what?
Get the hell out before you regret it.
-[lighter clicks]
-We have to go, Ms. Yuk.
-I feel sorry for your daughter.
-Ms. Yuk?
She's been losing sleep over her dad,
who doesn't even care about his own life.
Why get the surgery
if you're going to act like this?
I'm going to contact your daughter.
She needs to know
what kind of state her dad's in.
That way, she'll get to decide
whether to give up on her dad or not.
[♪ tense music plays]
Say one word to my daughter,
-and I'll really kill you.
-Whoa! Sir!
I guess you are ashamed,
seeing as you're angry.
[Jiui] We're sorry. Come with me, Ms. Yuk.
-Sorry, sir.
-I'm not done talking!
-[Jiui] Hurry up!
-[Hari] What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
-What?
-Come with me.
What on earth are you doing right now?
What?
Don't you know that bringing up smoking
with a cancer patient only riles them up?
I'm just frustrated!
Why would it make you…
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[owl hooting]
[insects chittering]
Hey, what was that about earlier?
That man still has a chance.
How could someone try so hard
to ruin a second chance at life like that?
Not everyone can get a second chance.
Some people try their hardest to live,
but end up dying anyway.
If I were that man…
I'd try to live seeing only good things,
doing good deeds,
and thinking good thoughts.
So I can live for a long time.
[♪ mournful music plays]
CHAVOXIFEN
CHAVOXIFEN CITRATE
[Jiui stammers] There must be a way.
There's no such thing.
That's not true. It's too soon to--
What can we do now? The sun's gone down.
-[animal howls in distance]
-What?
I think we're lost.
-[bird squawks]
-Oh, crap! [sighs]
-Right?
[animal howls in distance]
[Jiui] Huh?
What do we do?
Why are you asking me that?
-[♪ mysterious music plays]
-Oh, man…
-[rustling]
-[bird squawks]
[both gasp]
Oh…
-[exclaims]
-[rattling]
-What is that?
-What is it?
Never mind.
I thought it was something else.
Come on!
Aim the flashlight properly!
You should be aiming it properly, okay?
Didn't you learn in science class
that you're supposed to raise it high
so that the light spreads more?
Darn it…
How can you talk science when you
can't even see what's under your feet?
Are you sure we're going the right way?
Oh…
I think I saw this tree earlier.
Is this place haunted by ghosts?
That's strange.
I thought we were going the right way.
[stammers] Ghosts?
Yes, ghosts.
Oh, come on! You scared me!
Is my face really that scary?
I've seen worse, but I'm bearing with it.
[breathing heavily] I don't think
we'll find our way out at this rate.
Let's split up and look around.
Hey.
[wind howling]
Ms. Yuk!
Uh, split up? I don't want to! [groans]
[stammers] I don't want that.
Let's stay together.
We won't find the way like this, so--
Let's just stay together.
Is it because you're scared?
[sighs]
Wow, it's one thing
after another with you.
-[stammers, grunts]
-[vehicle approaches]
-Oh…
-Huh?
-[Hari gasps] Dr. Chiyeon!
-What are you doing here?
You didn't return, so here I am.
With the sun setting
and the boats no longer running.
-[gasps, chuckles]
-[sighs] Man, I'm so relieved.
[Hari chuckles]
-Hop on.
-Okay.
Oh… How should I get on?
Should I get on down there?
Okay. Sure.
Keep backing up.
Good, just like that.
Yes, just keep backing up.
But are you sure I can get on?
STYLE
::cue()
I don't think I'd fit.
Another ride will come.
This is a two-seater.
-Wait a second!
-I'll see you later.
[Jiui] I said wait a second!
Take me with you!
Hey!
I'm scared!
Come on.
Are you sure he'll be okay?
He seems to be a scaredy-cat.
He's a big boy.
-Hold on tight.
-What?
Oh, okay.
-Not there. I meant the handles.
-What?
Oh. Um, uh, right.
You still have a habit
of jumping to conclusions.
Excuse me?
Do you really not remember me?
Wait.
Oh… [chuckles]
I'm sorry.
What?
I have a boyfriend.
-Hey, wait--
-I told you I have a boyfriend.
[♪ comedic music plays]
CLIFFSIDE RAW FISH RESTAURANT
[Hyeon sighs]
Just tell me, okay?
If you buy me a meal.
What?
[exclaims] Come on. We've met before?
-Hello.
-[owner] You're here?
-Hey.
-Auntie!
[gasps]
Dr. Do.
How did you get here so fast?
Thanks to you…
I almost ended up dying, okay?
[retches]
[yelps] Ma'am, go slower!
Go slower! [yells]
[screams]
Slower!
It was seriously a white-knuckle ride.
Cheer… [grunts] …up!
Here.
You're drinking?
You're meant to drink on days like this.
[owner] You're here?
-[Jangsu] Yes.
-Hey, welcome.
What's this?
Oh, my.
I see Dr. Stickler was here.
The great doctor who won't give
proper prescriptions
because he suspects
his patients of foul play.
That's right.
You see, just like you have your rules,
we have our own rules here in Pyeondongdo.
For every new arrival,
our youth association determines
who's the senior and the junior
by having a drink-off.
Whoever gets wasted first
becomes the junior,
and must obey the senior's every word.
See where this is going?
That's why the owner here
is my big sister now.
-Right.
-Geumja, my sis!
Gosh, that's so gross.
[Jangsu, captain chuckling]
What do you say?
Would you, Dr. Stickler-for-the-Rules,
like to partake in our ritual
so we can establish a proper hierarchy?
Well…
I guess he doesn't have
what it takes. [chuckles]
Is it because all he's done is study?
He's a total nerd. [laughs]
-Let's just go.
-Yeah, let's go.
We have to get back quickly--
If those are the rules here,
I'll give it a go.
Dr. Do, no…
You mean it?
Yes.
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
Those guys, they're not human
when it comes to booze, okay?
They're hounds. Boozehounds.
Gosh, I'm so worried.
A man should be able to drink this much.
Don't you think so?
[sighs]
[Jangsu scoffs, pants]
This here's a creamy soju.
[Jiui sighs]
[gags]
[retches]
-[Jiui sighs]
-[grunts]
I'm not like him.
Not bad.
You can actually hold your liquor.
-[sighs, grunts]
You haven't forgotten, have you?
The rules in Pyeondongdo.
Whoever loses this
has to become an obedient little bro.
I'm very curious
how much of an obedient little bro
Dr. Stickler over here will be
once I beat him.
[chortles]
[gags]
[glass thuds]
[Jangsu groans, retches]
[Jiui] I'm also curious…
[clamoring]
[spectator] Wow, look at him go!
…what I'm like when I'm drunk.
2013 HANGUK UNIVERSITY
PRE-MED SEMESTER KICK-OFF PARTY
[♪ triumphant music plays]
[Geumja] He won.
He actually won.
-[gasps]
-[Hari] Mm-hmm.
Another?
[panting]
[exclaims, slurring] What the…
Do you know who I am?
I'm the Bloodstained Fist
of Pyeondongdo, you prick!
Huh?
[whimpers] Blood…
[whimpers]
[groans]
[groans, slurring] What's this?
What happened to my hand?
Forceps, please. [sighs]
[Jangsu groans]
[groaning]
Looks like you can feel your hand.
[Hari] What should we do?
I think we can stitch him up.
There doesn't seem to be any nerve damage.
You're going to stitch him up?
Out of the question. We had alcohol.
This could cause huge problems
down the line,
STYLE
::cue()
and it has happened before.
Article 7 of the code of medical ethics.
A physician shall not practice medicine
while under the influence
of alcohol, narcotics, or drugs,
or in a physical or mental state
that may cause harm to the patient's life
or physical well-being.
If they complain later
that a drunk doctor operated on him,
you'll both be in big trouble.
Let's have him go
to the hospital early tomorrow.
[snoring]
He definitely won't go.
The boats head out tomorrow,
and missing just a single day
is a huge loss in anchovy fishing.
But he still needs… [sighs]
[snoring continues]
[inhales sharply]
Let's do it tomorrow morning.
It just needs to be done within 24 hours.
For the record, I clearly warned you
that this may cause problems later.
Don't worry. I'll take responsibility.
You should go home too.
[♪ contemplative music plays]
[Hari] Dr. Do.
Dr. Do.
Yes…
Yes?
Um, it's been eight hours.
Don't you think we're good to start now?
Let's treat him quickly
so you can get some rest too.
You're still here? Why?
Because we still have a patient.
Doesn't he get on your nerves?
He filed a complaint,
forced you to drink alcohol,
and picked on you.
Um… [sighs]
You're right. I don't like him.
[inhales sharply] But…
like him or not,
lacerations are lacerations.
Oh…
[exclaims]
What now?
[Hari chuckles]
-[exclaims]
-[chuckles]
[both laugh]
[sniffles]
STYLE
::cue()
[Jangsu] What the heck is this?
What on earth happened to my hand?
You were drunk yesterday
and broke a mirror,
so I stitched up the wounds.
Me? Drunk?
Get a load of this hotshot from Seoul,
blaming me for something I didn't do!
My boat's heading out today!
How am I supposed to
pull the nets with my hand like this?
I won't let this slide, okay?
I'm going to sue you
for also causing me emotional--
What are you going to do
if you don't let it slide?
[Ms. Hwang] Mr. Park!
Everyone knows
you become an animal when you drink.
I'm so sick of this.
Why come all this way
to bitch at the doctors
who are performing their sacred duties?
-No, that's not--
-Don't talk back to your chief.
Pulling the chief card on me.
Like you always do.
[Mr. Park sighs]
-Dr. Do Jiui, come over here.
-Oh.
What's this?
[Mr. Park] This right here is maeuntang.
-[Ms. Hwang] Oh, goodness.
-[Mr. Park chuckles]
It's made with all-natural ingredients,
so it'll be delicious.
You should have it for lunch.
Thank you, sir.
[Mr. Park] All right, then.
-Good luck today.
-Thank you.
Stop interfering and come with me.
Chop-chop! Leave.
Come on.
[chuckles]
-Let's go.
-Hey!
-[Ms. Hwang chuckles]
-Thank you, sir!
-[Mr. Park] Bye!
-[Ms. Hwang] Take care!
[Mr. Park] Okay!
[Hari] I think Mr. Lee Jangsu acted out
like that because he was embarrassed.
[Jiui sighs]
He was defeated
in the chief elections for years,
and now he's even lost his title
as the heaviest drinker to you.
But still, taking it out on me…
It's not like it'll solve anything.
It may not solve anything,
but it can mask your embarrassment.
Isn't that the easiest way out
when you want to hide something?
Getting angry.
[♪ contemplative music plays]
[inhales sharply]
In that case…
What do you think Mr. Kim Jeongbae…
wanted to hide?
What?
-I'm going to go see Mr. Kim Jeongbae.
-Me too!
Dr. Do!
What the heck? Are they BFFs already?
[panting]
[thunderclap]
Mr. Kim Jeongbae!
Damn it.
[thunder rumbling]
What the hell is it this time?
Sir, may I take a look at your foot?
-Why would you look at my foot?
-We just need to check really quickly.
Come over here if you've got a death wish.
-[Hari gasps]
-[thunderclap]
Ms. Yuk.
I'm okay. Hurry and take a look at him.
-Let me see your foot.
-What do you think you're doing?
Let go. I said let go of me!
I'm sorry. One second!
[exhales sharply]
-You knew you were diabetic, didn't you?
-Diabetic, my ass!
It's just a little bruise!
Bruise?
I'm a plastic surgeon,
and I've amputated dozens of toes
during my residency.
You think I can't tell a bruised foot
from a diabetic one?
So what? What do you want me to do?
You have to go to a hospital right now!
If you don't treat this,
you could lose your leg,
and worst case, you could die of sepsis!
-I don't care.
-Sir!
This is my problem,
and I'll handle it myself!
So please,
don't tell my daughter about this,
and pretend you didn't see anything.
STYLE
::cue()
I'm begging you!
No.
I don't think I can do that.
Looks like we'll have to
tell his daughter, right?
Ms. Yuk?
Dr. Do, just a moment.
Please wait here.
What?
Ms. Yuk!
Oh…
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
Dr. Do.
Yes?
Aren't you hungry?
Do you want to have some ramyeon?
[♪ upbeat pop song plays]
-Ramyeon?
-Yeah.
[sniffles]
-Well…
-[sniffles]
[song continues]
Why'd you make it
when I'm the one who suggested it?
This was me repaying my debt.
-Your debt?
-Yeah.
You mean the spider?
Oh, come on.
I saved your life from a venomous spider,
and you want to call it even with this?
No way. I'll get something bigger later.
I already made it for you, okay?
[chuckles]
[knocks on door]
Are we expecting someone?
[Hari gasps]
BREAK ROOM
[thunderclap]
Help me.
Please…
Help me live.
[thunderclap]
STYLE
::cue()
-[Jiui grunts]
-[Hari gasps]
[groans]
How does it look?
The redness is widespread,
and judging by the fluctuance,
it looks like a late-stage abscess.
Let's perform an I&amp;D.
Right. I'll make the preparations.
[sighs]
[Jeongbae] Doctor…
Will I really make it out of this alive?
Of course, sir.
[sighs]
-I'll bring the antibiotics.
-[Jiui] Okay.
Why did you change your mind?
She told me not to feel guilty
for being alive.
She said that would cause
too much pain to those left behind.
That's what that nurse said.
I'm just going to
keep living like this until I die,
so stop harassing me and get lost!
What about the family you leave behind
if you die like this?
Do you think your family
will be able to just go on living?
How do you expect your family
to go on living
if you leave them no chance
to do anything about it?
So, please…
Please do it for your daughter, sir.
Okay?
[Jeongbae] What she said
brought me to my senses.
When my wife was sick,
that was the one thing
I struggled with the most.
Seeing my wife
consumed by guilt for being alive.
But I…
[sobbing] …have been doing the same thing
to my daughter.
[Jeongbae sobbing, sniffles]
STYLE
::cue()
[sighs]
He seems to have fallen asleep.
What do we do now?
[Jiui] He had a lot of pus in him,
so I think we should
monitor him here a little longer.
Shall we let him sleep for a while?
Yes.
[Hari sighs]
I thought things would be easier
at a public health center,
but I had it better at an ER. [chuckles]
[inhales sharply]
Mmm…
By the way, how did you know
that Mr. Kim Jeongbae was a diabetic?
[inhales sharply]
You said it yourself.
That the easiest way
to hide a secret is to lash out.
[inhales sharply]
For suffering patients with secrets,
the answer is always treatment.
Oh…
-By the way, are you okay?
-Hmm?
Ah… It's fine.
I'm sure it'll heal in no time.
Stay right here.
It's fine. I'm okay.
Just sit back down.
Why leave it like that?
We have medicine and a doctor to help you.
Wait here.
[stammers]
I'm really fine, though…
[softly] Let's see.
Man, that must have stung.
[♪ romantic ballad playing]
Dr. Do.
You said treatment was the answer
to a suffering patient's secrets, right?
I did.
Then what's your secret?
What?
You're also hurting.
Every time you have to get on a boat,
you get so anxious you need medication.
And you get mad
when people try to help you.
Like someone who wants to hide something.
I'm not crossing a line here.
I'm asking as a nurse.
Just like you want to treat me
because you're a doctor…
I'm a nurse…
so I want to help you,
since you're suffering.
Okay?
[sighs]
Don't tell me if you don't want to.
I can just find out myself. [chuckles]
[song continues]
STYLE
::cue()
[breathes shakily]
[sighs]
[ship horn blows]
When you arrive on the mainland,
your daughter will be waiting for you.
-I'm sorry about everything.
-[Hari chuckles]
Don't worry about it. [chuckles]
Good luck with your treatment.
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you.
[♪ heartfelt music plays]
Thanks for giving me the courage.
[sighs]
Shall we go?
Yes.
[ship horn blows]
-About Mr. Kim Jeongbae…
-Oh?
Maybe we should have given him
some meds for seasickness.
Huh?
Well, getting seasick wouldn't be good.
He works on a boat for a living, remember?
-Oh…
-[chuckles]
-Yes.
-You're right.
PYEONDONGDO FISHING
Hello, Mr. Park!
-[Jiui] Mr. Park.
-Have you been somewhere?
[Jiui] Are you feeling better?
[♪ upbeat music plays]
You lying bastard!
[gasps]
FOR SUFFERING PATIENTS
WITH SECRETS,
THE ANSWER IS ALWAYS TREATMENT
A LITTLE JOKING AROUND ON SET
REALLY BRINGS THE PLACE TO LIFE
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
[stammers] Mr. Park, what brings you here?
-[shouts]
-[Mr. Park] You lying quack!
Is he seriously trying to ruin my life?
-[exclaims]
-[Jiui] Hey, Lee Jangsu!
What did I do wrong just now?
[screams]
[Hari] Were you waiting for me?
We have plenty of time to spare.
Would you like a drink?
Was that so hard?
[Jucheon] It's like something out of
a late '80s movie.
[Hari] Doctor, come with me.
[Hyeon] Are we really going to sleep
in the same room?
[Hari] Do you regret it?
Translated by Yoon Hyuk Park