( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I just got here
Are you sure it will work?
I'm telling you
It won't work
Why
Move
No kidding
Got caught like this?!
I don't last a day every time I break out
then they got me back in
Keep it down
You've tried so many times anyway
Does it matter with one more try?
Show the cards
Hurry up
Pair of 10
Pass Pass Pass
Nah, nothing
Hurry, still counting the cards?
Got so many left?
pair of two
Nope, pass
Find him
What for?
Look at those two - what's their deal?
Is that even a question?
It's so obvious
They even wear couple outfits
You two
Don't you think it's rude
to talk about us in front of our faces?
Didn't you turn down my proposal?
Well...
I really miss the days that I can run my gear high
So I finally convinced ZhengHan to join
Chen YuChuan
You'd better keep your words, man
Aren't we missing someone
Right
I'm not an idiot
Only a fool would run with you guys
Not him
Where the hell did he go
We still got places we haven't checked yet
Keep looking
Let's go
Not someone Boss Chiang sent to whack me
nah...
This place is way too dangerous
Hide yourself
Thanks, bro
Go
My leg
To the back door
Holy crap
He's transformed
You come to save me?
Thank you
Whatever
Which one is it?
I don't know
Got Lee Xun
He's at the back door
Lee Xun
Get him out of here first
Wait a second
where the hell am I going to hide if I bail now
Chen YuChuan seems to be quite experienced
when engaging with Azure Dragon Syndicate
might be a better idea
to stick with him
1 2 3
Hsu ChenHan
It's me
no, no, no
Don't
Hsu ChenHan, wake up, man
It's me, Pan Hao
I'm so dizzy
You are?
It's okay
Come with me
Let's go
Is he alright?
You're the one I should be asking
I thought you were dead back there
Sorry, I made you all worry
Seriously, man, who the hell are you?
Why would killers come after you?
I know, I get it
just like in the movie
Cops go undercover in the gang
and find some key evidence
then, the gang wants him silenced
Give me a break
Who the hell still does undercover ops nowadays?
What do you think this is - Infernal Affairs?
That's how it always goes in the movies
Well, we're not filming a movie, man
Hold up, it's way too noisy
What just happened
Did I have another episode again?
Bro, call it what you want…
but the episode of yours saved our asses
If you hadn't lost it
We'd all be six feet under right now
So... where are we heading now?
Have a big feast, of course
then, let's go happy happy happy
Happy my ass
Did you forget how you get busted the last few times
crap, right...
Quit messing around
So, where are we going?
Let me tell you…
Don't look
what's happening
Help! Help!
Sun Rou Rou
No way
Welcome to ACE
Miss Rou Rou
This way, please
Madam Qin already gave instructions
watch your head
Complimentary champagne and fruits
and some special hors d'oeuvres
Bon appétit
So I've heard
the club has some new arrivals
Send them over, I wanna check them out
Not a problem
We'll get it ready right away. One moment, please
You finished handing out flyers—why aren’t you changing?
What are you sneaking around here for?
I...
Let me tell you
If you’re at the bottom in sales again today
you won’t just be handing out flyers
I’ll give Lily and Joe the night off
and you'll scrub the toilets
Polish the glasses
no, please
Mop the floors
I’ll give Lily and Joe the night off
I can choose whoever I want
no...
to clean the bathrooms
Boss Tony—
There's only one group of guests
there are so many of us on standby
You don’t really need me, right?
This club runs on customized selection service.
Everyone goes out
Come,makeup—fix him up
I’m not feeling well
My appendix—
I need sick leave
That’s the most dramatic sick leave excuse
I’ve ever seen. Denied.
Boss Tony—
Pan Hao, quit struggling
Learn from me -  appreciate
these "productive" days
hey
Everyone, stay sharp today
Show some energy, okay?
Yes
Hold still
Dear Miss Sun Rou Rou
Here
is your exclusive
selection lineup
Come over and greet
Hello, beautiful
What is that?
Pandemic style?
Take if off!  Tony--
NO!  Boss Tony--
Seriously no…   Pan Hao
It really is you, Pan Hao
Rou Rou
I looked for you for so long after graduation
and missed it every time
the neighbors said you've moved away
I was heartbroken for a long time
never thought I'd run into you here
What's the deal now?
How do I know
Weren't you schoolmates
I was his junior high schoolmate
she should be from the senior high
I've made my choice
I want him
I haven’t seen you since the graduation
thought I’d never see you again
Something happened at home
back then
You really haven’t changed a bit
Even that shy look is exactly the same
You didn't change at all
Still as beautiful as ever
Thank you
To celebrate seeing each other again
let's have a drink tonight
ah, sorry
you do it
Taste really good
Take a sip, too
Try it
Taste good, doesn't it
Hey, hand me your cell phone
the gift
you still have it?
Of course
It's the first birthday gift from you
even though you didn't give it to me in person
I treasure it very much
and had kept it with me
Where's Pan Hao
He took off suddenly
Do you remember
the arcade we used to go to?
When we played the claw machine
you'd always say you would win
my favorite one for me
Of course
I tried like forever back then
without luck
and you laughed at me the whole afternoon
I'm definitely getting that chubby penguin this time
It's super cute
also,you like it a lot
But someone said he'd get it for me last time, too
ended up spending 300 bucks
and the claw didn't even get close
That's because it's too sneaky
I got it— I got it—
I'll get it this time
oh, Come on…
This machine is rigged
The claw is way too loose
It’s definitely a scam
I’m filing a complaint!
Hey, don’t be mad
even though we didn't get it this time, there's always next time
But that serious look you had just now—
was hilarious
I mean… cute
Come on
Let’s go shoot some hoops
what
Come on
Let's go
Time really flies
when being with you
I'm very happy today
me too
I’ll come see you in a couple of days
There's so much to be caught up with
See you soon
here
watch your feet
bye
To the day after tomorrow
there're 47 hours, 59 minutes, and 55 seconds left
don't they say "time flies"?
How come there're still 27 hours, 27 minutes, and 45 seconds left?
Time
please move faster, will you?
Please
Get out of my way!
I’m taking him home tonight
Ma’am —sorry
How about a fruit platter on us
Go away
Gorgeous
Daniel's new
He's not taking private booking
So what’s that supposed to mean?
You don't think I can afford it?
Fine
Here
Is it enough
how about I have a drink with you instead
you?
I don't want to drink with you
I want Daniel tonight
But    Belle
With a request that exclusive,
our Daniel’s gonna get shy
You know how this works
in our line of work
This supposed to be mutual
Forcing him takes all the joy out of it
Forcing him? Me?
What are you implying?
I’m taking Daniel with me tonight
I wanna drink with Daniel
girl you stop that
How about this—
Allow me to  arrange
an exclusive VIP session
with our top-ranked host
Hunter, to serve you
that should be acceptable, right?
Pardon me
Dear, whatever service you wish for
may be fulfilled
you okay?
I guess so
But it can’t keep going on like this
The bureau has made arrangements
We leave tonight
Daniel Daniel
Daniel, where are you
Daniel Daniel Daniel
Daniel Daniel
Daniel, where’s my sweetheart? Daniel
Daniel
Daniel, come out already!
over here
Daniel, are you hiding in there?
Didn't know you're so popular
Even Chang YiHao
can't stop her from wanting to take you home
Daniel
Daniel, come on
Where is he
Sorry
You can't come in here
Daniel?
Daniel is over there
You're in the wrong place
Let us take you to him, ok?
Daniel is waiting outside
in the lobby
Daniel's out there
yes
Daniel
Sweetheart, I’m coming!
Where are we going?
Sir Zhong arranged a meet-up
We’ll know the details when we get there
Playing chess at this late hour?
Do you just need some company
or showing him the disciplines?
Boss, I'm off now
Who's messing you up now?
you always play the chass when you're not in the mood
I'm happy
with you by my side
Drink it while it’s warm
I made it especially for you
Here
Stay in the car
till I'm back
What do you mean?
I'm going with you
If I’m not back in ten minutes
drive yourself back to the club
what about you
Don’t forget—I’m a cop
got the stuff?
yes
Move, move! Up ahead!
Guard all exits
Grab them once they're here
Listen up
This time, failure is not an option
If anything goes wrong again—
none of you walk away
Yes sir
Bro. Biao
Sir Zhong
We’re hiding at a motel in the suburbs
I've sent you the location
Good work. Stay safe.
copy that
Sir
We’re temporarily hiding at
the Brainwave Research Center
Stay low
I’ll send backup
Take him
Stop running
If I’m not back in ten minutes,
drive yourself back to the club
Why isn’t he back yet?
Stop
You hear me?
Officer Chen
Smart people live longer
Sir Zhong is a good example
He knows how to make the right choice
Otherwise
on a cop’s lousy payroll
how can he afford the oversea expenses for his wife and kids
You want me to betray Lee Xun
No way
I’ll have to send you on your way
Get in the car
Stop!
Are they still after us?
Didn’t I tell you to leave first?
Why did you come back?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
I couldn't do it
I can’t just leave you behind
just like you can’t stop protecting me
sorry for making you worry
Also
this isn't your responsibility, okay?
nice music
There
Lee Xun, you’re not getting away!
Speed up
Go around to the front
They're getting really close
can’t shake it off
Speed up
Do you even know how to drive
Up ahead, turn there—
What are you honking for?!
Can’t you see I’m pushing a cart?
Get out of the car if you got guts!
one-on-one
It's so late now
Why would there be an old lady out collecting junk?
Boss, that's recycling
not junk collection
Can’t you see I’m pushing the cart?
Go deal with it
Boss, rules of the Azure Dragon Syndicate
No elderly nor kids
Wouldn’t that break the rules?
Who said anything about hurting her?
I meant go help her
Lee Xun is getting away—move!
Granny, let us pass, okay?
You brat!
Look at this mess you've made
What the hack about collecting cardboards now?
Get lost
Who's going to drive if you get off?
Did Lee Xun send you guys to ruin me
Get out of my way!
Drive
Boss, I'm not in the car yet!
wait up
They’ve got to be here. Search!
Let’s see where you can go now