( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Let me see where you can go now
After them
Hurry!
Yuchuan!
hey, do me a favor
What the hell just happened?
Weren’t you meeting Sir Zhong?
how did it turn into the Azure Dragon Syndicate coming after us?
He's probably bought off
by the gang months ago
what now?
We keep laying low at the club
I’ll figure out the rest
You don’t really have to worry about me
I'll protect you
I promised Auntie
A promise is a promise
right?
Besides, I've freeloaded off your family for decades
Let me repay the favor
Your favorite braised pork knuckle
Come on
Thanks, uncle Lee
that's so unfair
You gave him my favorite!
hey, you can have the fish
Uncle, Auntie—look at him!
You two fight like kids
have the fish
Yuchuan finally has a day off
Do you have to argue with him?
Give it back
Even if it costs your life?
Of course
hey
what's up with you
being so spooky in the middle of the night
I was too hungry to sleep
just having some ice cream
where were you off at this late hour
do we need to report to you?
So energentic
Want some? To refill your energy
you have it
top sales of the club needs it more
that's true
Speaking of which
Tony asked to me to go full-time
bet you didn't hesitate
Of course, an opportunity like this
you don't just let it pass
Do your best, then
I always DO
I'm going to take a shower
my turn afterwards
they’re surprisingly in sync
when they brush me off
Sir
We're hiding at
the Brainwave Research Center
Alright. I’ll send backup
Sir Zhong is a smart guy
He knows how to make the right choice
Sir
When were you bought off?
Since you already know
there’s nothing for me to hide
Ah-Biao holds some evidence
together with Lee Xun’s testimony
it’s enough to bring down the Azure Dragon Syndicate
you’re telling me this now
for me to still trust you?
it doesn't matter if you believe me or not
I just call to warn you
Ah-Biao's run out of patience
You’d better stay at the club and not wander off
They won’t dare make a move
Why
something about their gang rules
I don’t know the details
all I know is, to them,
the club is off-limits
Fine. I knew you're bought by Ah-Biao
what’s the point of this call?
Shouldn’t you be hoping
they caught Lee Xun?
Some things aren’t up to me
Yuchuan… this is the only thing I can do
Take care of Lee Xun
and yourself
Sir Zhong called
What did he say
He said Ah-Biao’s losing his patience
we should keep hiding at the club
the gang won't make a move here
why
it seems to be related to their gang rules
but no details were given
that makes sense
They probably knew we're here long ago
yet they haven't taken any actions
feels like they’re holding back for some reason
what do you think
is stopping them from
making a move here
Why don’t you go sound Uncle Ma out?
okay
Don't be mad
He's still at the club
Not going anywhere
No need to worry
Chen Yuchuan—
Even if we got the diamonds
as long as we don't have Lee Xun,
we have no leverage against Chiang
Since the gang can't touch the club,
then we’ll make them leave on their own
By the way
Sun Rourou’s operation is going smoothly
Pan Hao has taken the bait
We should be able to close the net soon
That’s my lady
Impressive
I’m working this hard
for the two of us
If this ends smoothly,
we'll go somewhere
no one knows us
and do whatever we want
Wasn't she supposed to come in two days?
Why hasn’t she even texted?
waiting for a client or your girlfriend
you're right
am I waiting for a client
or the one destined for me
That’s her, not me. Stay away
ACE men, listen up
Spending money is easy, making it is the hard part
Love will fool you
Women will fool you
but Money never lies
Time to work
Let's go
Been ready
Never seen anyone who's so eager to work
It’s called professionalism
that's strange
Where did he hide the diamonds?
Pan Hao,move
what are you doing?
What are you looking at?
Hurry up, it’s time to work
She's not going to pop up magically
Let's go
Wait a second
My phone’s almost dead
I need a charger
You’re such a pain - Hurry up
Cover for me
Fine
Weird…
Didn’t I close the door?
hey
A client requested you
Hurry up. Are you working or not?
Tony, thanks for taking care of Rourou for me
Rourou?
The client is Amber
Am...
chop-chop
She specifically requested you
with two bottles of champagne ordered
Come on
Amber...
Boss Biao, the mission failed
Dear Amber
sorry to keep you waiting
Jay
Come over and sit
have a drink with me
Rourou
if you don’t show up soon,
Amber might just
eat me alive tonight
Here, dear Amber
I'll make sure you're happy tonight
Welcome to ACE
I’m Tony, the manager
May I have your name?
Hello, my name is Lee Xiaozhen
Nice to meet you, Zhen
Is this your first time here?
yes
This way, please
have a seat, plesae
thank you
Zhen—
Do you have any preference
or would you like me to introduce some options
Is he available?
you have a great taste
He's one of out top stars
He’s currently with another client
But he should be available soon
Would you like me to
reserve the rest of his evening for you?
Can I book him for the whole night?
It is possible
but the rate will be a bit higher
Do you have a budget in mind?
Please arrange it
No problem
Leave it to me
I'll take care of it
Have a seat for now
ok
Cheers
bottoms up, Vivian
Give me a kiss
You’re so annoying
Excuse me, Vivian
I didn't order this
Sorry
Hunter won't be able to continue serving you tonight
what do you mean
I've already paid
don't be upset
Although Hunter isn't available
I've upgraded you to a duo service instead
Hello, beautiful
Hunter
Hunter, I don't want that
Vivian
Wait for me
Hunter loves you the most
I’ll make it up to you
Love you
Hunter
Zhen
Tell me how you want to play
I’m all yours tonight
yes
This is Junshan Yinzhen
It’s harvested only in early spring
The yield is extremely limited
That’s why it’s so precious
It’s picked before the buds fully sprout
so it doesn't have the usual grassy taste
Instead, it brings out
a subtle sweetness and aroma of corn
Zhen—
You spent all this money
taking me to such a high-end hotel—
just to have tea?
You don’t like it?
How come
Zhen—
how about
we do something else?
okay
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
11 12
Here you go
Zhen, I thought we’d play something
more exciting
This Is exciting
Playing “Heart Attack” reveals a person’s reactions best
You’re younger than me but this weak?
Fine, again
okay...
Let’s try something more stimulating
Yes
Xiaozhen
This… this is what you call exciting?
stimulating your taste buds
I can’t take it anymore
The night is short—let’s get straight to it
Hold it
I didn’t book you to have sex
No sex?
Sorry
you don't need to apologize
It’s just that for someone like me—
with an "compulsive behavioral disorder”
who excels in that department to the extreme—
this is a bit torturous
Zhen—
I’m curious about something
You paid so much to book me,
and pick such a fancy hotel—
why don’t you want to have sex
In fact
it's my husband’s birthday today
Today is your husband’s birthday
Then why aren’t you celebrating with him?
He passed away last year
Every year on his birthday,
we would come to this hotel,
to have tea
play "heart attack"
and have barbecue
This year
It's just me
It's kind of ridiculous
When I passed by your club today
and saw many posters
Then I saw you
and found your eyes
look just like my husband’s.
That’s why you chose me
to relive the time you had with him
I’m sorry. I know it sounds absurd
But I really…
didn’t know how to get through today
It’s okay...
It's not absurd at all
alright, I've decided
Tonight, treat me as if I were him
I'll stay with you
and go through all your birthday traditions
okay?
Boss Chiang
Tips
Thank you
for being with me when I need it most
Madam Qin
Is everyone here?
Yes
everyone's here
I believe you all know
this industry is extremely competitive
I also believe you’ve been dedicated
and working hard to serve every client
But ever since Leo and his group left,
you boys took over,
the sales is less than a third of what it used to be
Can someone tell me why?
Less than a third of before?
I’m already making that much
If that's a normal monthly income,
then wouldn’t I be making a million a month?
One week
I’m giving you one week
If sales doesn’t improve,
you can all pack up and leave.
Ma'am
Maybe you could consider
giving us a little more time, after all—
This club isn’t a charity
nor a shelter.
Prove with your performance that you deserve to stay
You're right
Everyone needs to step it up
Tony and I will do our best to support you all.
If anyone can’t handle it
and wants to leave early,
that’s completely fine too.
Relax, men
I alone
can carry a week’s sales for you guys.
Alright
you all heard what she said
Pull yourselves together
Go get dressed
be ready for tonight
Energy up
Let's get it
ACE
she's really bold
If sales doesn’t go up in a week,
she'll fire everyone
She never leaves room for negotiation
still not used to it?
What’s the point of getting used to it?
This isn’t an ordinary challenge
Those new guys
are still adjusting
and we’re pushing them to hit numbers?
That’s like throwing ducklings into the sea
However, a few of them do have potential
such as Hunter
That guy never turns down a client
and Justin
He’s not as capable as Hunter,
but he has his own way of entertaining clients
One week is really too short.
It's impossible
We have to help them hold the line
let her see results
that’s the only way to turn this around.
Easy to say. How?
Same as always
Your specialty
Bring back regulars
get VIPs
The most important thing now is
for each of them to secure their own client base
Don’t force it
Got it
Boss, this is the current
progress report on several Azure Dragon Syndicate lawsuits,
including Lee Xun’s case
The evidence is in our hands
As long as we got Lee Xun, there won’t be any problems
Alright. I see
Good work
Brother Yu called me early this morning
must be serious
Chiang
thought your business is booming lately
keeping you busy
I was worried you might have forgotten the diamonds
so I figured I'd give you a reminder
How could I ever forget your matter?
My guys are just incompetent
They still haven't found Pan Hao
How about this—
I’ll send you his head
don't be like that
We’re brothers — no need to be so formal
I know this isn't easy
I’ll give you seven more days
If there’s still no result after that,
I won’t be so polite anymore
I’ll send my own people to handle it
You understand what I mean, right?
okay
Within seven days,
I’ll give you an answer
Ah-Biao
within seven days
If you can't took care of Pan Hao and Lee Xun
you're off the case forever
Yes, boss
she's coming
not coming
coming
Don’t you think this outfit looks odd on me?
Relax
Don’t overthink it
Just treat the clients
like they’re your computers
Everyone
Guests tonight
are all VIPs I personally invited.
Give them your best, okay?
Yes, no problem
We’ll definitely give it our all, right?
Let’s do this
not coming...
Hello
Is this Mr. Hsu?
Yes, speaking
Hi, Mr. Hsu
We have good news
After matching, we’ve found
a heart suitable for your sister.
The transplant surgery has been scheduled
but you need to pay the deposit first
and settle the previous hospitalization fees
Really? That's wonderful
What about the cost?
It will be around 300,000 NTD
This amount must be paid as soon as possible
so we can proceed
with the surgery process
Can it be paid in installments?
I’m a bit tight lately
Sorry, Mr. Hsu
Hospital policy requires
the deposit to be paid in full
Please arrange the payment quickly
I understand
I’ll get the money as soon as possible. Thank you
Bro
you okay?
you don't look well
I’m fine. Just a bit of allergies today
Not feeling great
300 thusands
I have to hang in there
for Xiao Xin
Justin
Look at Hunter
He's down to his paints
Why are you still wrapped up like a rice dumpling?
Beautiful, no rush
the night is still young
Let me toast you first
no need to rush for the drink
have some fries
Here
Hold on, Ms. Lin
Sorry for
making the mess
It’s okay, it’s okay
Justin
Justin, what’s going on?
Cheers
Is Justin acting strange?
what now?
Dear
No worries
You're jsut too beautiful
Our little Justin saw you
and got a tiny bit shy
Justin, where are you going?
Justin is going to the bathroom
I'll be your company
Let's have some drinks
Dear Lin
Sorry
what's wrong
he's not feeling well
Asa is helping him and will be back in a bit
Dear, for my sake
have some drinks
please
Cheers
Wasn’t it supposed to be two days?
It’s already the third day
not even a single message
Thinking about that girl again?
I didn't
what girl
I'm telling you
Clients here are just playing along
Don’t take it too seriously
or you’ll be the one who gets hurt
Stop provoking him
his heart has gone somewhere else
why did you take my washbasin
to wash your underwear?
The most important thing right now
should be figuring out how to boost our sales
that's true
boys
hold there for a second
I've got something important to say
Your performance tonight—
I think you all know how it went
If this continues and sales doesn’t improve,
you’ll be packing up soon
So I’ve decided to give you special training
From etiquette to hyping up the atmosphere,
I’m retraining everything
Starting tomorrow, come in two hours early
This time I want to see your attitude
Got it?
I have a question
I had the highest sales record tonight
Do I still need the training?
You? You’re promoted to assistant instructor
Teach everyone how to charm clients
Great
Leave it to me
I’ll turn them into sales kings in no time
Remember
this is the highlight of your opening performance
Put more power into your movements
you can't do it this way
Your expression must match your movement
zero point
Pay attention to client’s strengths
and compliment them.
Here I go
Yo...
Beautiful, your look today—
fashion and sexy
It's ok to make mistakes while practicing
But if this were on stage,
you’d ruin the entire performance vibe
You don’t actually have to drink it in
the atmosphere is what matters most
Daniel
Chang Yihao, you demonstrate first
that's right, drink the liquor in
then spit it back out.
so..."yo" is not correct?
Swallow — and smile
Remember
The stage is a battlefield
Alright, one more time
Ready… five, six