[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 1]
Long time no see.
How have you all been,
my old friends?
I slept for a very long time.
Now that I'm awake again...
I can't remember
[Episode 1: Convenience Store 444]
what year it is, or any of the things
that happened before.
Where am I?
This is a place of the void,
called the Sea of Illusions.
Only in the illusion
can we reunite.
I am fortunate to see you again.
[Ya]
Yes.
They should all be here,
waiting for a reunion.
After that farewell,
[Convenience Store 444]
I never saw Zhao Li again.
Ya and I got married,
and we have been living a normal life.
We opened a café.
To commemorate,
I named it
Convenience Store 444.
[Xia Dongqing]
Convenience Store 444
is still attracting some
strange customers.
Hello.
This is our special
Coffee 444.
It's limited every day.
You are lucky.
This is the last cup.
Want to try it?
I bought water.
It's on the house.
Today
is the last day of the year.
Are you hitting on me?
Uncle, how old are you?
Caffeine inhibits
A-ped activity in my body,
preventing cAMP from breaking down
and prolonging the effect
of adrenaline.
What do you mean?
I'm afraid
my heart may beat too fast.
My heart is already beating very fast.
You are waiting for someone?
A... man?
Trust me.
In terms of love,
it's better not to use these.
What do you mean?
I think
you are troubled by love
and want to use magic
to make someone love you.
Don't touch it!
This is my magic formation!
You don't understand.
On New Year's Eve,
when the clock strikes,
the living and the dead
can meet.
Then are you a living person
or a dead person?
If I'm waiting for a living person,
I am a dead person.
If I'm waiting for a dead person,
I am a living person.
Take a guess—
am I dead
or alive?
Sir,
you have a customer.
Honey.
Honey!
Did you miss me today?
Sorry.
I was too busy and forgot about you.
So sweet.
It's the last day of the year.
How's business?
Sir, what are you looking for?
Who are you looking for?
Wait!
What exactly are you looking for?
Have you seen her?
Who is she to you?
My name is Li Lei.
Her name is Han Meimei.
She's my girlfriend.
Is she still in the human world?
Are you crazy?
We are sophomores
at Huazhong Medical University.
She must have been here.
Han Meimei! Han Meimei!
Young man, keep your voice down!
-Han Meimei!
-Stop shouting!
This is my shop!
Come out!
Calm down. Stop shouting.
Han Meimei!
Han...
What...
What's going on?
Why am I floating in the air?
Who the hell are you?
You are not welcome in our shop.
If you come to make trouble again,
it won't be as simple
as throwing you out.
Did you hear me?
You must be Li Lei's girlfriend, right?
Why did he come here?
How did he know I'm here?
I thought you had left.
I went to the restroom.
It's almost the new year.
I can't leave.
I will see him very soon.
So you are seeing another man
behind your boyfriend's back.
Li Lei is my ex-boyfriend.
We have already broken up.
Are you sure you broke up?
Very sure.
This only shows
your intention to break up.
She cheated on him anyway.
I didn't!
Han Meimei!
You cheated on me!
Li Lei?
How do you know I'm here?
Are you stalking me?
I know!
You must be here to see
that GB38!
GB38?
Is it a screen name?
Sounds unreliable.
How do you know?
You stole my diary?
October 28th.
I couldn't help but take
another look at GB38.
He is absolutely perfect.
Stop reading!
I couldn't take my eyes
off him!
November 10th.
I can't use words to describe
his perfection.
I don't think I could ever
know another man
so thoroughly in my life.
-He's calm.
-Shut up!
He's good at listening.
He never talks too much!
I can't help but think of Li Lei.
He's too noisy,
childish,
unintelligent,
and emotionally unstable!
I want to break up with him!
Li Lei!
I'll kill you!
Give me back my diary!
-Tomorrow...
-Give me back my diary!
is New Year's Eve!
I must see you!
Give it back!
You know what?
There is a café
called
Convenience Store 444.
Give it back to me!
Shameless thief!
We've already broken up!
You have no right to interfere!
You're too willful!
Breaking up just like that?
Do you know him?
How many years have we known each other?
I don't know him,
but I know you!
We're not right for each other!
Don't go yet!
-Don't touch my bag!
-Why are we not right for each other?
-Tell me!
It's just a skull specimen.
GB38?
Don't touch it!
Give it back to me!
Li Lei,
please remember,
we've already broken up.
Please stop pestering me.
If you keep this up,
I'll only hate you more,
and we can't even be friends!
Why did she treat me like that?
What right does she have
to treat me like that?
Young man,
that girl isn't quite right.
You can just find someone else.
How could you say that?
Do you know her?
How could you casually judge someone?
I don't know her.
I don't.
I love GB38.
I want to be with him.
I can feel his soul.
I talk to him every day.
Even though he never responds,
in the ringing
of the New Year's bell,
maybe I can hold his hand.
You bought this magic formation online,
didn't you?
Is it reliable?
Wild guess again.
I'm not
that stupid.
You even broke up with your boyfriend
for him.
That's different.
Even without GB38,
he and I would still
have broken up.
I never liked Li Lei at all.
Then why
did you get together?
He chased me for 7 or 8 years.
I just went soft on him for a moment.
There are 3 minutes left
until the new year.
Han Meimei and I
met in junior high school.
To win her over,
I memorized a lot of English words.
We went to the same high school
and then the same university.
I chased her all the time.
I'm so tired.
But in the end,
she still didn't fall for me.
You are a very
loving boy.
You are still young.
There's a long road ahead.
You will definitely meet a girl
whom you love very much
and who loves you back.
My love has been exhausted.
I will never love again.
Stop being so depressed.
I don't get it either.
How could a person
like a skull?
Actually,
she just doesn't like me.
You see,
in many things,
effort is useless.
You've figured it out?
You're right.
Maybe when I wake up tomorrow,
my happiness will come.
I will meet
a new girl.
I will like her very much.
And she will like me too.
It's midnight.
It's a new year.
I should go now.
When you get a new girlfriend,
bring her to the store.
I'll treat you to coffee.
Happy New Year.
GB38,
would you like a cup of coffee?
My treat.
He is GB38?
This wine is pretty good.
Honey,
you have no idea how exhausted I've been
these past two days.
Good thing Li will come back tomorrow.
Want me to have a drink with you?
Did I give you permission?
This wine is expensive.
Just treat me as your escort.
Let me have a glass.
Get another glass.
Since then...
how many years has it been?
Ten years.
Ten years?
I really miss him.
I feel like
he's always been with us.
Let's just pretend
he is right here.
Zhao Li,
we really miss you.
It's a new year again.
I hope you can open the door
and join us
for a drink.
Sorry, we are already...
♪ You came into the world
before I was born ♪
♪ I came when you were already aged ♪
♪ You regret my lateness ♪
♪ I regret your earlyness ♪
Two people but three glasses of wine?
This glass is for me.
Happy New Year.
Zhao Li, I really missed you!
You are back!
Men and women should keep proper distance.
You young
married
woman.
Besides, I don't really like
getting too close to a woman's body.
Zhao Li.
Wait...
I knew
you would definitely come back.
Wait.
What are you doing?
You...
You are hurting me.
Why are you...
It's my first time meeting you two.
And I'm not Zhao Li.
But my surname is also Zhao.
My name is Zhao Hengzhi.
Zhao Hengzhi?
[Zhao Hengzhi]
Did anything strange
happen
here today?
Strictly speaking, it should be yesterday.
Did a girl named
Han Meimei
come here
with a skull?
Oh, right.
You can verify
my identity.
I am Han Meimei's
college counselor.
Zhao Hengzhi?
Did Han Meimei...
succeed?
Did that skull
turn into a man?
A foreign man.
A Frenchman,
speaking French.
I...
I really shouldn't have...
I was really careless.
I didn't expect...
I shouldn't have taught her that!
What?
It was you who taught
Han Meimei that magic formation?
You even teach this
at your university?
I'm just an ordinary
university teacher.
But my family
is engaged in supernatural professions.
Right.
You are a demon hunter?
Pretty much.
Our family has a name,
called the night watchmen.
A skull turned into a human.
I must turn him back into a skull,
or I'm really in big trouble.
It was also me who told her
about this place.
Because I thought
casting a magic formation at
Convenience Store 444
would have a higher chance of success.
What else do you know?
Abnormal time.
Every generation of night watchman
has recorded it in their notes.
You are the Saintess of the Nine Heavens
from Kunlun.
Your name is Ya.
I am the Saintess of the Nine Heavens.
Hello, my name is Wang Xiaoya.
Your name is Xia Dongqing.
You have Yin-Yang eyes.
You can see things
that normal people can't.
Your body
once merged with a
very powerful ancient god.
And that Zhao Li you mentioned,
the Ferry Man.
He always likes to
announce his name.
I am Zhao Li,
the Ferry Man.
According to the night watchmen's notes,
he likes to wear eyeliner,
style his hair,
wear an outfit of
pitch-black clothes,
and play around in the three realms.
The Ferry Man
is incredibly badass.
Does this Zhao Li you mentioned
really look like me?
You three...
once saved the world.