[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 2]
The magic can only last for one night?
Send it back yourself.
Is there any other magic
that lasts a bit longer?
I said, send it back yourself.
Fine.
We couldn't really communicate anyway;
there's a language barrier.
He's a foreigner?
Does he speak Chinese?
Chinese?
He doesn't even speak English;
he only speaks French.
Good thing I have a translation app.
Well, how was your chat?
Nothing much.
He fell in love with me at first sight,
recited some love poems or something,
then said he wanted to marry me,
have kids,
and even teach me
how to make the bread
his mom used to bake.
There's a generation gap.
More like a centuries-long time warp.
Two coffees? I only ordered one.
Is the other one on the house?
They're both on the house.
The new beans
we got in today are excellent.
Give it a try.
I don't drink coffee.
Did you forget, uncle?
Not hot; I want it iced.
Did you forget?
Let's practice more by then.
Arrange another game with them.
Sir, do you have a restroom?
May we use it?
Out in the backyard.
-Thanks, sir.
-Thanks.
Let's go.
That's not how we should play.
Hurry up.
Let's go. Quit wasting time.
That backpack looks so heavy.
I'd say it's over 30 jin.
Kids these days
have a heavy school workload.
I don't see any boy with a backpack.
What are you two talking about?
What's there to talk about then?
Let's go practice. Let's go.
Nice. It's pretty nice.
Right?
Ghosts
shouldn't be appearing in broad daylight,
right?
Found it.
It's a looping spirit,
one of the four types of ghosts.
Unlike ordinary ghosts,
they don't know
they're dead.
They just repeat the scene from the day
they died over and over.
Obsession.
Do you night watchmen
deal with things like this?
We do.
Of course we do.
[Chapter 2: Night Watchmen]
We night watchmen
empowered by the righteousness
of heaven and earth,
are dedicated to ridding the world
of treacherous fiends and evil spirits!
Where's the music coming from?
I'm playing it on my phone.
Every time I recite that speech,
this background music
makes it sound more... imposing.
[Class 2, Senior 3]
Hello, Granny.
You're back.
How were your classes today?
Pretty good.
Are you tired?
Go back to your room and review.
It's still early.
Only 10 o'clock.
Review for another three hours tonight.
Mom will make some chicken soup for you.
Okay.
Dapeng,
you must work hard.
You're repeating the year.
Do you know how much
a year's tutoring costs?
If you fail again,
Mom will be really heartbroken.
Look at
[Final Sprint
for the College Entrance Exam]
your third great-uncle's child—
he got into a top-tier university
on his first try.
You're not naturally bright,
so you have to work twice as hard!
You can't let Mom
lose face in front of the relatives.
This chicken is really good.
Free-range chicken.
I picked it up
at the market this morning.
[Good Luck on the College Entrance Exam]
I've pinned
all my hopes on you.
As long as you can get into
a good university,
every hardship and sacrifice I make
will be worth it.
This is it.
Actually,
we could just clear it with a spell.
But looping spirits
only trap themselves in their own memories
and don't harm people.
If we just eliminate it outright...
It's a bit pitiful
if we just reduce it to nothing.
After all,
it was once a living,
breathing person—
and so young.
Morning, Princess.
Want to take a bath with me?
Oh my god!
I've unlocked the shared bath achievement
with my husband Yuanji!
Let me see! Let me see!
You are amazing!
-You're amazing!
-You're incredible!
How did you do it?
How long did it take?
Is there some trick to it?
Come on, share it with us!
Yeah, I want to know too!
Wang Fang,
you're playing mobile games again.
Director,
I've finished writing
the scripts for today.
Generated by AI, huh?
I think they're pretty decent.
Xiaoni,
how are the numbers looking lately?
None of the seven influencers our team
is responsible for are performing well.
The performance metrics
have remained flat.
Stop spending all your time
on in-game romances
and come up with some real ideas.
They'd have to listen first.
I spend forever
planning skits for them,
and then they say
they're too tacky or bad for their image.
They all think they can just stand there,
do a bit of dancing,
and go viral overnight.
As if
the platform were short on pretty girls.
They all crank up the beauty filters,
and in real life,
they don't even look as good as me.
Why don't you become a streamer yourself?
I think that's actually viable.
The content has become too homogeneous.
We have to highlight
what makes them stand out.
Director,
the boss wants everyone
in the conference room
now.
"Clouds adorn her gown;
flowers mirror her beauty.
The spring breeze brushes the railing,
rich with fragrant dew.
Had one not beheld her
atop Jade Mountain's peak,
one would take her for a fairy
from the moonlit Jade Terrace."
Yan Yuzhen?
Smart move.
Riding on Yan Yuzhen's popularity.
Looks like
she's had a bit of plastic surgery.
I... will be back.
She's really beautiful.
The filter isn't even that heavy.
There are some traces of plastic surgery,
but nothing excessive.
My goodness,
2.73 million likes!
And it's still climbing!
It's 2.9 million now!
And this is her only video.
Posted just three hours ago.
Videos like this are common,
but for one to blow up this fast?
She is pretty and has luck on her side,
so the traffic just comes.
Does she have an agency yet?
We're the best
MCN agency around.
And you're my best director.
I leave this woman to you.
You must sign her.
Check her background
to see if there's any dirt.
A hero's origins don't matter—
let alone an influencer's.
Her username is perfect.
No need to change it.
We'll reach out to her immediately.
Move fast.
I must get this woman.
Copy that.
Director,
Yan Yuzhen requested
to speak with you directly.
She wants your phone number.
Give it to her.
Hello?
Are you Yan Yuzhen?
Hello, Director.
I'd like to meet you.
Meet me?
I've checked around.
You are indeed
the best MCN agency right now,
and you are the best director.
I'm willing to give you this chance.
Thank you for your trust.
Do you have time
to come in and chat at our office?
Actually, would it be convenient
for you to come meet me instead?
Sure.
Just name the time and place.
How about
your coffee shop?
Convenience Store 444.
Tonight.
How did you know?
Yuanji.
I've soaked for too long,
and I have no strength left.
"The maid helped her up,
languid and delicate."
Hello. It's you.
Is your boss around?
Our boss went out.
I'll have an Americano, iced.
Sure.
Basketball boys!
Want some iced coffee?
My treat.
Dapeng.
Your name is Dapeng, right?
You like basketball?
Are you good at it?
I used to play all the time.
After starting high school,
I barely played at all.
Why?
My mom wouldn't let me.
She said it'd distract me from my studies.
Do you play?
Not really. I'm no good at it.
I like watching the games though.
You must know Jordan, right?
Who doesn't know Jordan?
The guy who liked to chew gum
and stick out his tongue
when he played—
the God of Basketball.
I can do all his layups.
I play really well.
My buddies
even call me Little Jordan.
Sounds like
you really love basketball.
Do you still want to play now?
No.
Basketball won't get me anywhere.
If only I were good
at studying.
Then my mom would be very happy.
I have to go to tutoring.
You play so well.
Has your mom ever seen you play?
My mom hates it when I play basketball.
It doesn't matter.
I just want my mom to be happy
and proud of me.
That is
the most important thing to me—
more important than anything.
Sir!
Could you please
throw the ball back over here?
Thank you!
-Come on, let's keep playing!
-Come on!
Nice shot!
Hello, Granny.
Dapeng,
you really need to work harder.
You're repeating the year.
Do you know how much
a year's tutoring costs?
If you fail again,
Mom will be really heartbroken.
Look at
your third great-uncle's child—
he got into a top-tier university
on his first try.
You're not naturally bright,
so you have to work twice as hard!
I've pinned
all my hopes on you.
As long as you
can get into a good university,
every hardship and sacrifice I make
will be worth it.
Why did you come to this apartment?
Who are you looking for?
I...
I'm here to see the place that's for rent.
Young man,
you must not move in here.
Why not?
This place is haunted.
The mother was stewing chicken
over a small charcoal stove
in the room. The buildup of
carbon monoxide poisoned them,
and the smoke suffocated the son to death.
Really?
I'm telling you—
I can still hear it.
Zhao Hengzhi?
You're here.
You're here too?
I've found out everything.
Who are you people?
What are you doing in my home?
We're here for your son.
He's not here anymore.
Who exactly are you?
I'm calling the police.
We're not bad people.
We came
for Dapeng.
I was very tired that day.
How could I have known
that I'd fallen asleep
while stewing the chicken?
How could I have known
the chicken soup would boil over
and put out the fire?
He had no idea.
He was still studying
and just fell asleep right here.
I'm the worst mother in the world.
I killed my son
with my own hands.
What do I have left to live for?
Did you know?
Even now,
Dapeng is still working hard
toward your dream.
Now?
My dream?
Do you know
what Dapeng's dream was?
I've got a basketball game arranged.
It's almost time.
Li,
I have an important guest.
Don't let anyone into the back room.
Got it.
Welco...
Look.
He's so handsome.
My Queen,
this way, please.