[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 3]
There are only 2 of us.
Besides,
I thought you didn't know how to play.
Let's go.
Let's go play over there.
Are we really playing? It's so late.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Let's start playing.
Can I play basketball now?
I can lend you my body.
Mom doesn't like me playing basketball.
She hasn't even seen you play.
How would she know
how good you are?
Come on.
You
play better than all of them.
Show your mom
how excellent you are.
Your shot's pretty on point.
Looks like I'll need to mark you
more closely.
Nice three-pointer.
Come on, pass me the ball.
Pass it to me. Come on.
Guard him! Over here!
Guard him!
It's okay. Focus on the next play.
I can't stop him by myself.
Help defense!
It's okay. It's okay.
Block him! Block him!
So accurate.
I think I saw my son.
Mom.
This is my dream.
The words on the desk,
the wind through the basketball hoop—
only after life and death
stood between them
did she finally see clearly.
With the smile of someone
who had been truly understood,
he crossed the River of Forgetfulness.
Some regrets
refuse to settle
until the soul has grown light enough
to let them go.
[Chapter 3: Guhuo Bird]
Honey.
Can you stop listening to
horror stories?
It's my only hobby.
Well, at least think about
prenatal education.
What kind of pregnant woman
still wears makeup?
I'm just trying to
brighten up my complexion a bit.
So naggy.
You never listen to anything I say.
♪ One dies, two live ♪
♪ Three together live happily ever after ♪
-What are you singing?
-♪ One dies ♪
Wait, what are you singing?
A horror nursery rhyme.
If you keep nagging me, I'll use this
to educate your son.
Cut it out. It's bad luck.
♪ One dies, two live ♪
♪ Three together live happily ever after ♪
Can't you stop singing?
Luo Hao...
What's wrong, Honey?
My belly hurts.
Is it the baby?
What's wrong?
Luo Hao!
Hurry!
To the hospital...
Okay.
Okay!
Hang in there, Honey!
Li.
I've got an important guest.
Don't let anyone in the back room.
Okay.
Welcom...
Your Majesty the Queen.
Please.
I'm back, Heavenly Maiden.
Yan Yuzhen?
Born from imagination,
carried on people's lips.
Desire never dies—
it renews itself endlessly.
Yan Yuzhen,
it really is you.
It's the eternal queen,
Lady Yan Yuzhen.
I said
I'd come back.
You've changed a bit.
Well, I've had a little work done
on this face.
More than just a little, I'd say.
This face is more fashionable
and fits the current trends better.
I know
that you married Xia Dongqing
and opened this café.
Are you really okay with
living an ordinary life for him?
I've got work to do,
and I'm pretty good at it.
It's been 10 years.
Dongqing was just a college student
back then.
He was so young.
What are your real intentions
in coming to see me?
To cooperate with you.
Don't worry.
I've turned over a new leaf.
Seducing men one by one
and feeding on their life essence
was just too exhausting
and inefficient.
I want to become an influencer—
a top-tier one.
Once I've built my following,
I'll expand the brand and monetize my IP.
When the time comes,
I'll turn the name "Yan Yuzhen"
into a global IP franchise.
You want to be an influencer?
Don't forget,
I've always been very popular
throughout Chinese history.
I'm basically
a top-tier IP myself.
I just don't understand.
Why do you want to be an influencer?
Oh, you.
Don't overthink it.
Beauty like mine is just born to
stand out.
Throughout history,
beauty has always been a marketable asset.
Back in my time,
if a woman
wanted to climb the social ladder
with her looks,
she had no choice but to depend on men.
Even an emperor wasn't reliable.
But things are different now.
I'm this beautiful,
so why wouldn't I monetize it?
Hello. What can I...
Isn't this a convenience store?
We're actually a café,
just named "Convenience Store."
You know, our boss might be a bit...
Do you have any food?
Yes.
We have cakes,
pasta,
and steak.
What do you want?
It must be very expensive.
Did you see that?
Not very clearly.
But something feels off.
I need to go to the café first
to handle a few things.
Alright.
Then I'll go check what's going on.
Li,
where's my wife?
She's inside.
Boss, Boss. Come here.
There's a
super beautiful woman inside.
A beautiful woman?
Even more beautiful than my wife?
She totally crushed her.
Then I must have
a good look.
H-Hello,
I'm the boss here.
Sanlang.
Sanlang!
I missed you so much.
Miss.
Lady.
It's improper for men and women
to have physical contact.
Really improper.
Sanlang,
I'm Yuzhen.
How about
we get to know each other again?
You shameless vixen!
You...
Let go of my wife!
We're all old acquaintances.
What's that fuss about?
"Flying into a rage for a beauty"—
that's not my poem.
If the customers outside hear this,
that'd be awkward.
Come on, let's drink.
Bottoms up.
Beautiful, are you alone?
Come over and drink with us.
Let's drink. Getting shy, isn't she?
ID card.
The deposit
is 200 yuan.
Hot water for bathing
is available from 8 a.m. to 8 p.m.
There's an electric kettle in the room.
Boil your own water
if you need it.
[Golden Pages ]
Hello.
Do you need room service?
Are you crazy?
[Mom]
Mom.
I'm okay.
I can't tell you where I am.
I can't say it!
If I tell you,
Luo Hao will find me.
He'll come to hurt us.
He wants me and the baby
to go to hell together with him!
I'm not crazy!
Everything I said is true, Mom.
Mom.
Watch out for mirrors.
Ghosts
can come through them.
Can I help you?
Sorry, I got the wrong room.
♪ One dies ♪
♪ Two live ♪
♪ Three together live happily ever after ♪
It's time to sleep.
Let me put you to sleep.
♪ One dies ♪
♪ Two live ♪
♪ Three together live happily ever after ♪