[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 4]
One dies.
Two live.
Three together live happily ever after.
One dies.
Two live.
Three together live happily ever after.
He's coming.
He's coming!
I'll get you out of here.
I won't let him get his hands on us.
One lives.
Two die.
Mom, come here.
Dad's here.
Come on.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Are you...
There's...
A ghost!
What's with all that scream?
People are trying to sleep here!
Are you crazy?
1.8 million followers,
6 million likes.
More than that, it's still growing.
These fans
cast their gazes on me,
give me their attention,
and think of me day and night.
They
are my believers.
Worship generates spiritual power.
I'll become more and more powerful
and more and more beautiful.
I seem to already feel
their admiration for me
slowly
flowing into my body.
As an influencer,
you're absorbing the power of worship
and admiration
every minute and every second,
with no restriction of region
or time.
You could even say...
I'm like a god.
You should feel honored,
because you
are witnessing
the birth of a new god.
Yan Yuzhen—
the Venus
of the new world.
Dongqing!
Yan Yuzhen?
Zhao Li?
You ruined my painting.
I hate you.
I won't take the blame for this.
I'm not Zhao Li.
I'm Zhao Hengzhi.
I'm not a ferryman,
but a night watchman.
I just changed my hairstyle.
So you're human.
What's a night watchman?
A night watchman is...
That Yan Yuzhen—
why does she look like a foreigner?
That nose looks like it's been done.
You're even more annoying than Zhao Li.
He's more annoying than me.
Smell this. What is it?
It smells a bit off.
I've never smelled
anything like this before.
It was left behind by
that demonic creature.
It's amniotic fluid.
How do you know?
Before marrying Sanlang,
I had a child with the Prince of Shou.
It was a daughter.
She didn't get to grow up.
Such things
would not be
recorded in history.
I think it was a Guhuo Bird.
Guhuo Bird?
The demon
that specifically kidnaps children?
Women who lose their children
or die in childbirth
are said to turn into a demon
called the Guhuo Bird
because of their overwhelming resentment.
Wherever a Guhuo Bird appears,
it leaves behind a substance
similar to amniotic fluid.
Did that person have a child with them?
Not necessarily.
The Guhuo Bird
is a monster often associated
with babies.
I guess...
No need to guess.
It's here.
[Account Balance]
[Available Balance: 3.68 yuan]
Baby.
I'm sorry.
I don't have any money left.
But don't worry.
I'll definitely find a way—
a way to bring you into this world.
Hello.
You came by our café yesterday.
Convenience Store 444.
It's so late.
Why aren't you going home?
I can't go home.
Why?
There's a demon chasing me.
A demon?
It's my husband.
He died and turned into a demon.
He wants to take me
and my unborn baby
down to hell with him.
Thank you.
Eat more.
With all this drifting
from place to place,
your baby
probably can't take it.
He might follow me here.
I ran away from home.
But no matter where I run,
he tracks me down.
Do you have any mirrors in this café?
Mirrors?
What about mirrors?
Anything that reflects light
can serve as a medium for demons,
especially mirrors.
Every time,
it's through the mirror
that I see my husband.
When did
your husband pass away?
Last year.
Around this time last year.
Last year?
Is the baby you're carrying
his?
What's that supposed to mean?
Of course it's his!
When your husband passed away,
how many months pregnant were you?
Seven months.
It's been a year.
You've been pregnant with this child
for 19 months.
Nineteen months?
Why is that?
I...
I can't remember.
How did your husband die?
I...
Hang in there!
Careful.
I was bleeding,
and he was very anxious.
Worried about getting stuck in traffic,
he carried me all the way to the hospital.
One dies,
two live.
One dies, two live...
One dies, two live!
Dongqing.
That's enough.
Don't be nervous.
We were just asking.
You...
What do you guys want?
Why do you keep
asking about my husband?
Who exactly are you?
Don't get worked up.
Don't you want to
see for yourself?
Hello, what do you...
Do you have any food?
ID card.
Do you remember now?
You're afraid of mirrors.
What you saw in the mirror
was yourself.
One dies, two live—
that's what you've always thought.
Who was the one that died?
[In Surgery]
Doctor.
How did it go?
I'm sorry,
but we failed to save the baby.
Then...
Then what about my wife?
I'm sorry. She lost too much blood.
No way...
Her blood type is very rare,
and we couldn't find
enough for a transfusion.
No way...
No way!
I'm not me.
I'm not me!
I'm not me! I'm not me!
I'm not me.
One dies,
two live.
You thought if one died,
the other two could live.
You chose to give up your own life.
You erased your own identity
from your mind
and became your wife and child.
My wife...
And my child...
They've always been by your side,
trying their best
to wake you up,
even at the cost
of turning themselves into demons.
Meihui...
Meihui!
Meihui.
Meihui...
Although it's hard to let go,
you still
have to move on with your life.
Meihui...
The love that's gone
doesn't want you to stay trapped
in delusion.
It has become a guiding light of wisdom,
hoping only that you wake up
and live your life well.
Thank you for helping me fulfill my wish.
Now I'm sure
you're not Zhao Li.
Why?
That brat Zhao never sheds tears.
Get lost already.