[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 5]
[My dear princess, did you sleep well?]
[Yuanji]
Yuanji, my dear husband.
Hold on.
I want to go take a shower first.
Don't go.
Stay with me a bit longer.
Give me a kiss,
okay?
Wang Fang?
You fell asleep again.
And you didn't even eat.
I have no appetite.
Your dark circles
are as heavy as a panda's.
Didn't you sleep well last night?
Did you
do something bad in your dream
with that husband of yours, Yuanji?
Good afternoon,
my princess.
So sweet. "My princess."
Oh my god.
If only Yuanji
could say that to me.
[Director]
That must cost a lot of money.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Director.
Now?
Okay, I'll be right there.
I don't even look like myself now.
It's the "blue enchantress" look.
You look pretty.
The last video
got 700,000 likes.
Yan Yuzhen's traffic is dropping.
We need to do something about it.
Most of
her fans are male,
and they get bored very easily.
Posting videos of dancing
in front of peonies every day—
no matter how beautiful you are,
they'll eventually get tired of it.
Men are always like that.
It's the same everywhere.
Let's shoot a few videos
with this makeup look as well.
Wang Fang, you write the script.
Don't always copy and paste from AI.
Add some of your own thoughts.
Although my appearance
filled the blank
in your life,
buying me dinner
is a bit too fancy.
There's no need for this.
Don't worry, you don't have to pay.
That's a relief.
This is the table Ms. Huang reserved,
but she hasn't arrived yet.
Please wait here for a moment, gentlemen.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Hello.
This way, Ms. Huang.
Ms. Huang.
I'm Xia Dongqing.
Hello, I'm Huang Shang.
Hello.
Why are there two of you?
This... This is my friend,
Zhao Hengzhi.
Hello.
Have a seat.
I already ordered.
Surely you two grown men
don't have any
dietary restrictions, right?
I don't eat...
Hold on.
Cilantro...
I don't eat garlic.
I...
Useless bunch.
It's been 3 months,
and you still can't get it done?
I've heard enough. Save it.
Hand in your resignation this afternoon.
Pardon her.
My daughter has always been like this.
Work comes before everything else,
and her temper
is even worse than her workaholic nature.
Please don't take it to heart.
That's why her love life
has been put on hold until now?
Yes.
For a woman, instead of struggling so hard
to earn so much money,
wouldn't it be better
to have someone who understands
and cares for her?
Don't you agree?
That's not necessarily true.
Is this a blind date?
In your dreams.
The dishes have been served.
Let's start eating.
I'm not worried
that you're scammers.
At worst, you just scam me out of a meal.
Anyway,
I haven't been to this place
in a long time.
These were all my favorite dishes
when I was young.
So,
what did my mother,
who passed away 2 years ago,
ask you to tell me?
"After thousands of years of evolution,
women have become wiser,
more elegant,
and more powerful.
They are the Athenas walking through
the concrete jungle."
This copy is good.
What woman
would want to be Athena?
If there's a choice,
of course we'd rather be Yan Yuzhen.
It's too objectifying toward women—
reducing everything to
romance and indulgent pleasure.
Yan Yuzhen is
quite similar to
Marie Antoinette.
Neither of them ended well.
They were both the epitome of femininity—
beautiful, wealthy, enjoying life,
and backed by powerful men.
Seriously,
what woman
wouldn't want that kind of life?
Nonsense.
Your view is
too male-centric.
Yan Yuzhen's fans
are also male.
We need to get female fans.
She who wins female fans wins the world.
I agree.
All the gifts from destiny
have secretly
been priced.
Relying on men has never been
a good thing for women.
Why should I get married?
If you don't get married,
your mom won't be able to
rest in peace.
Easy for you to say.
Who am I supposed to marry?
I've got no time for a boyfriend.
I'm swamped every single day.
At least you have friends, right?
You can ask your friends
to introduce you to someone.
I don't have friends.
In business,
there are only opponents and allies.
And depending on the circumstances,
those roles can change.
Are you married?
He's not.
I'm not.
You don't look annoying.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
I guess not, right?
No, I don't.
Occupation?
Teacher.
College professor.
Full professor.
Ask my mom what she thinks.
Actually, you're pretty decent.
Your occupation
is quite nice,
and you look like a good guy.
Why don't you try dating first?
Well...
Your mom said
you two could try dating first.
I don't have time to try dating.
My mom's demand
is for me to get married.
Then what are we waiting for?
Why not make it quick?
That won't work. We haven't even...
You're not willing?
How do I look?
Beautiful.
Really beautiful.
My company
develops real estate,
and I'm the CEO.
In every first-tier city,
I have properties.
So,
are you satisfied with my conditions?
I am.
Marrying her would be like
getting a city thrown in with the deal.
My mom is sitting right here, right?
Mom.
I'm beautiful and rich,
and I'm doing perfectly fine on my own.
Why would I need a boyfriend?
To come and share the fruits
of my success?
But you can't just
be alone for your whole life.
It's not like I refuse to date.
I wouldn't mind having a baby,
but I'd rather keep the child
and leave the father out of the picture.
That won't do.
I have to get back to the company.
So annoying.
You guys keep eating.
I...
Tell my mom to relax.
Instead of stressing over
pointless things,
she should wish me success
with my project.
If she's still worried,
I'll just burn her
a son-in-law as an offering in a few days.
I'm leaving.
Madam, please don't be anxious.
Rushing things won't help.
Marriage
indeed depends on fate.
Actually,
there's something else
I want to talk to her about.
But she won't listen.
Director,
see you at the office tomorrow.
Okay. Good work today.
Ya, you've worked hard today too.
What do you want to eat? My treat.
There's no one watching the café today.
I want to wait for Dongqing to come back,
so we can make a few more sales.
Ya,
you've got a pimple.
How can a Heavenly Maiden get pimples?
Have you noticed
that your strength
is getting weaker and weaker lately?
That's because you've been human
for too long.
Your body
is gradually turning into a human's.
In ancient times,
300 Chang'es came to the human world.
But now,
not a single surviving Heavenly Maiden
can be found in the mortal world.
According to Kunlun,
if a Heavenly Maiden lives with humans,
she'll fall ill.
But never being able to return to Kunlun
isn't truly a punishment,
It's because they
have all become humans—
weak, short-lived humans.
You will age,
get sick,
wither,
die,
and vanish.
You will become an ordinary woman.
Are you willing to accept that?
I don't know.
I'll become a human?
This
is the consequence of pursuing love.
Love is a palace built by humanity,
decorated with
language,
literature,
and art.
It's magnificent and breathtaking,
dazzling beyond measure,
drawing people to it
like moths to a flame.
People pour their hearts and souls
into entering it,
only to find
that inside lies
an even more brutal forest.
There, people battle one another
in the name of love.
Beauty,
wealth,
manipulation—
these are the weapons of lovers.
Congratulations,
my dear princess.
Your Affection Level
has reached 1 million.
Please make your choice:
would you like to summon Yuanji
to your side?
What am I thinking?
Those with weak weapons—
especially women—
are often the victims in love.
Be careful.
In the forest of love,
smiling beasts lie in wait.
Wait,
why could her mother appear
during the day?
What's so strange?
Huang Shang's attitude
was very strange.
If an ordinary person found out
their mother's spirit was there,
they wouldn't react like that, would they?
She's the strange kind.
You can tell at a glance she's not
the ordinary type.
You're right.
Could it be like
the situation with Dapeng last time?
My wife's calling me.
I'll hang up now.
Honey.
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
There was no one in the café,
so I forgot to turn them on.
I've been running around all day.
I'm so tired.
What did you do today?
First, I went to run some errands
with Zhao Hengzhi.
After we finished,
I went with him to the market
to pick out fish.
Zhao Hengzhi really likes keeping fish.
Then,
I drove him back to school.
We bumped into 2 acquaintances
who insisted on playing ping-pong.
Don't look at other men.
I'll get jealous.
You're exactly the way
I imagined you in my dreams.
Then your dream has come true,
my princess.
By getting my Affection Level
up to 1 million,
would my game character
really come to me?
You're not
dreaming right now.
I spent money on you in the game—
a lot of money—
just to get our Affection Level
to 1 million.
Thank you.
But that's not what matters.
What matters is your love for me.
Will you
disappear tomorrow?
That depends on you,
my princess.
If you wish,
I'll stay by your side forever.
Stay by my side forever?
Do I need to keep topping up?
You have to believe
that there are miracles in life.
Money
can create miracles.
The choice is yours.
Then,
are you willing to do anything for me?
That's a promise.
I want a diamond ring.
Can you
give it to me tomorrow?
Y-You already had it prepared?
However,
keeping the ring
comes with a small price.
What price?
Stay with me tonight,
okay?
Let's do everything
we did in the game
all over again.
Let's go, baby.
I didn't expect it to integrate so well.
It can be used right away.
[Chapter 4: Strange Things]
Be careful
when you go take a leak.
Don't go bumping into anything.
This town isn't very big,
but once it gets dark,
every house is empty.
With just the two of us here,
it's really creepy.
This place has been here
for hundreds of years.
Who knows how many people have died here.
What are you afraid of?
I've been in property development
for so many years,
and I'll tell you this—
there's no place in this world
where people haven't died.
According to the records,
there should be
another well nearby.
Let's go take a look tomorrow.
It smells so good.
What's that smell?
It smells like cosmetics.
Watch out!
♪ Green willows cover my boudoir ♪
♪ I adorn myself before the mirror ♪
♪ I put on a red dress every day ♪
♪ Year after year,
my love never comes home ♪
♪ In the yellow earth mound,
I shall lie alone ♪
♪ When will the grass turn green again? ♪
Ghosts!