[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 6]
Let me see.
We really can't complete the task.
This town...
is haunted.
I strongly advise you
to steer away from it.
Even if you can build villas there,
you won't be able to sell them.
I'll pay you in full
and waive the penalty,
since you didn't deliberately
breach the contract.
Great.
-Thank you, Ms. Huang.
-Thanks, Ms. Huang.
Remember
to keep your mouths shut.
Let's go.
Hello.
Is it Xia Dongqing?
Fancy making some money?
You're looking to develop a town,
but there exist some dirty things
that need to be cleared out.
You believe in
all that supernatural stuff?
Many people can't see those beings,
but that
doesn't mean they don't exist.
Can you see them?
No, I can't.
You go beyond merely believing they exist.
Last time, when your mother's soul
appeared there,
you seemed to have...
Grown accustomed to it.
Right, accustomed to it.
"I command the green demon of pestilence
from the east—
the spirit of rotten wood;
the red demon of pestilence
from the south—
the spirit of flame;
the blood demon of pestilence—
the spirit of vile gold;
and the black demon of pestilence
from the north."
One of my family legacies is a book.
I read it when I was little.
There are all sorts of spells in it.
What is your mother's surname?
Huang.
So you took your mother's surname?
I see.
You are a witch then.
The role of a witch is passed down
through the female line.
You carry your mother's surname.
In each generation of your family,
a girl would be born
with special powers.
I have no special powers.
Now, back to the topic.
My family's ancestral home
is in that town.
However,
no one has ever gone back there
since my great-grandmother's
generation left that place.
If your ancestral home is demolished,
won't it be a huge pity?
Her mother has asked her
for a word about another issue.
By that, she means to stop me
from developing the town.
You won't listen to her anyway.
Right, I won't.
Starting from
my great-grandmother's generation,
my entire family has been living
in Nanyang.
My mother didn't
return here until several years ago.
She only visits that place occasionally
to reminisce.
Jiangnan towns like it are a dime a dozen.
That place isn't worth
developing for tourism at all.
Nonetheless,
all will be different
when villas are built.
They'll be surrounded by hills and rivers
that provide perfect scenery.
Immense value will be created.
It'll be much better this way
than lying wasted.
You are a witch.
That place doesn't scare you.
Why not check out the town on your own?
Come on,
my time is rather precious.
So much money?
It's for you two to split.
Let me make it clear.
Evil spirits are causing
trouble in that town.
When I was a child, I vaguely heard
that a powerful demon
was sealed there.
A powerful demon?
The world
is full of strange things.
Dongqing.
What took you so long?
Open the trunk.
What's in it?
Tools.
Get in the car.
How amazing.
My followers
now amount to nine million.
Congratulations.
Now, ninety-eight percent
of your followers
are female.
Thank you so much, Ya.
I can feel energy
surging through my body now.
I am getting closer and closer
to reaching my goal.
I'm truly happy for you.
Why are you being such a good boy?
Because
I want to please you.
Because I love you.
Love me for what?
For your beauty.
Your demon core...
It was made with a human life.
Quite formidable.
That woman doesn't trust me.
So what?
Will she ever resist your temptation?
She will obey my every word.
Let's go.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You seem completely different.
Different how?
I'm not like a nerd anymore?
You resemble Zhao Li even more now.
Wipe that off.
You talk about Zhao Li all the time.
Does he owe you a lot of money or what?
Do I really
resemble him that much?
No, there's a difference.
What kind of difference?
If Zhao Li were here,
I'd feel very secure.
Cut it out, you.
I'm highly capable too, alright?
I'm can also protect you.
What beautiful sunset glow today.
Stop with all this sighing and blabbing.
Let's just go.
Hold on.
What now?
Take this.
You bought me a bracelet? I won't wear it.
I didn't buy it.
It's Zhao Li's bracelet.
I think it suits you well.
Then I definitely won't wear it,
since it's Zhao Li's.
Just give it a try.
You'll look cool with it on.
Don't throw it away,
now that you've put it on.
What Zhao Li used to wear
will keep you safe.
It's like he's everywhere, isn't it?
Let's go.
Something feels wrong.
But I don't find anything unusual.
There aren't any human sounds around.
Few people
reside in this town, right?
There's flowing water.
Flowers and trees, too.
There should be
sounds of birds and insects.
It really is very quiet here.
So quiet that it doesn't seem like
a human habitat.
You know how to read this?
No.
Is everything fine?
What a lovely scent.
Be careful.
It doesn't seem
like a normal butterfly.
It's okay.
This is an illusion.
Let's follow it to see what's going on.
This tune...
actually sounds familiar.
Let's go up there.
♪ Green willows cover my boudoir ♪
♪ I adorn myself before the mirror ♪
♪ I put on a red dress every day ♪
There are demons producing illusions.
♪ When will the grass turn green again? ♪
I have a good idea
to conceal our presence from them.
What's your plan?
Off you go.
Let's move.
After we get in there,
follow me closely.
Don't touch anything.
If they find you
and catch you,
you'll have to spend the rest of your life
keeping them company in this town.
Even if they catch me,
you will come to my rescue.
It depends.
I'll make an effort,
but if there's grave danger,
my priority will be keeping myself safe.
I don't buy it.
Suit yourself then.
Let me show you
what a night watchman
is capable of.
Shall I prepare background music
for you?
Stay quiet and move ahead.
Make no noise as we tread.
Understood.
♪ Green willows cover my boudoir ♪
♪ I adorn myself before the mirror ♪
♪ I put on a red dress every day ♪
♪ Year after year,
my love never comes home ♪
♪ In the yellow earth mound,
I shall lie alone ♪
♪ When will the grass turn green again? ♪
This is all an illusion.
The demon that created it
is quite a character.
My love,
you promised
to come back for me.
Why have you never returned?
What are you doing?
Breaking a spell is like curing a disease.
The key is using the right charm
on the demon,
like applying the right medicine.
Something's wrong.
Zhao Li. Zhao Li!
Don't call me that.
Zhao Hengzhi, look.
It's that butterfly again.