( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I was really happy when we
joined the company at the same time.
That's why...
I never want to let you go again.
Zen, to me...
you've always been someone special.
"Fake Fact Lips"
(Episode 4: Are You a Demon?!)
Shido-san?
Whoa!
Is everything okay?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Your desk is a total mess.
I've never seen it like this before.
I was just about to clean it up.
So cold!
Good work today.
Zen, to me...
you've always been someone special.
Sorry.
I think I'll head home first.
Huh?
What the hell...
Shido-san.
Shido-san?
Yeah?
You dropped something.
What?
Don't be silly, I didn't drop anything.
No, you really did.
I told you I didn't.
But...
Look.
Ah...
Are you sure you're okay?
You looked totally spaced out just now.
Just now... well...
I was just thinking about work.
I got a little distracted.
Hey, isn't this Kiritani-san's business
card from the Secretarial department?
Why do you have this?
None of your business.
Speaking of which,
it just so happens that today,
I'm going out drinking with
the Secretarial department.
Are you free tonight, Shido-san?
One of the seniors had to
cancel at the last minute.
So I'm just a seat filler?
Yeah, pretty much.
But,
Kiritani-san might be there too.
If you're interested in her,
you should definitely come.
Ah, but
someone else is organizing the girls' side,
so I'm not exactly sure who's showing up.
(Secretarial department Kiritani Yuka)
Ah...
- Sorry, I'll just ask someone else...
- I'll go.
Huh?
I said, I'll go.
Really?
Thank you!
Nice to meet you all.
Okay, and the last one.
I'm Kashimura Akari. Even though
I'm in the Secretarial department,
I'm currently just handling small tasks
like pouring tea and making copies.
I'll do my best to learn,
and I hope to stand on my own
two feet soon. Nice to meet you.
Well then, everyone,
- Nice to meet you.
As expected of the Secretarial
department, you all look so glamorous.
By the way, I didn't expect
you to actually show up.
You really surprised me.
Seriously.
Who invited you?
I did.
Good job!
Actually, I've always wanted to join,
but I just never had the chance before.
It's the same for our Kiritani.
I told her, "You should come
to these things once in a while."
I practically had to drag her out here.
I was surprised to see
Kiritani-san here too.
Good job to you too, Matsushita-san.
Thanks for the compliment.
Oh, it was nothing.
Well, I just felt like commuting between
home and work every day wasn't great for me.
So I gathered my courage and came.
Then we definitely need to
get all the juicy details today.
What details?
All sorts of things, of course.
Hey, what exactly are
you trying to find out...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
- Here's the prosciutto pizza. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Um, Kiritani-san.
Even though I got your business card,
I'm really sorry I haven't
reached out to you.
Not at all, I know you're busy.
But to be honest, I was hesitating
all day about whether to come.
But I'm so glad I did when I
saw you were here, Shido-san.
You're too kind.
Also...
I've always wanted a chance
to have a proper chat with you.
Really?
Yes.
You seem so gentle, Shido-san,
and you're so capable at work.
You're basically the embodiment
of every woman's ideal type.
You're quite the smooth talker.
Maybe we should poach
you for the sales department?
I'm not just flattering you.
Is that true?
If so, then I'm flattered.
Do you really mean that?
Of course. Being praised
by you, Kiritani-san,
what guy wouldn't be happy?
Wow, you're such a charmer.
I am a top-tier salesman, after all.
Um, Shido-san.
You usually have a massive workload, right?
Not at all.
I'm just like the rest of them.
No, no.
Wait, how did you know?
Don't underestimate the Secretarial
department's intelligence network.
Because when I look at the monthly reports,
you're always juggling
several projects at once.
And you manage to pull
them all off flawlessly.
Exactly.
This guy isn't even human.
I am human.
So I couldn't help but worry a little.
I was wondering if you were
getting enough rest and relaxation...
You've never been good
at relaxing, even back then.
Ah.
Sleeping so soundly.
No, I do get plenty of rest.
I don't work once I get home.
I see.
That's a relief.
I didn't expect you to
worry about me so much.
Yeah, I worried on my own,
and now I'm relieved on my own.
Hey, Kiritani-san, worry about me too!
- No way, don't joke around like that.
- Are you drunk already?
I'm not drunk.
- I'm perfectly fine.
- Could I get a glass of water, please?
Minamide-san.
Are you okay?
You've had way too much to drink.
- I'm fine~
- How does look like you're fine?
Yotsuya-san is that
famous Yotsuya-san, right?
Yeah, he and Shido-san
went to high school together.
Even though neither of you are locals,
it's such a coincidence
that you ended up together.
What is that supposed to mean?
You two are quite famous.
Everyone says you're the rising
stars of Section 1 and Section 2.
Seriously, because this guy is
around, we're under so much pressure.
Geez, are you okay?
- I'm fine...
- Go throw up.
Stop joking around.
I'm not that amazing.
Yotsuya...
That guy is truly capable.
Huh?
You...
Shido-san
actually praised Yotsuya-san...
Is it that rare?
It's my first time hearing it...
Me too...
What the hell.
Do you two just go
around praising each other
behind each other's backs?
What do you mean by that?
The other day at the office,
Yotsuya-san said the exact same thing.
Yotsuya-san,
you're still here?
Oh, I was about to head out,
but an urgent matter came up, so
I've been dealing with it until now.
You're working hard too, Onishi.
Because Shido-san works so hard,
I want to help out a bit too.
Don't mind that guy.
He's just foolishly
working himself to the bone.
You don't need to drive
yourself crazy with him.
Aren't you the same, Yotsuya-san?
Your workload is about the
same as Shido-san's, right?
At the end of the day, I'm the same.
Because I want to be a man
worthy of being Shido's rival,
that's why I can keep working this hard.
Wow, what the heck. That's so touching.
So you guys don't actually hate each other.
You two are truly great
rivals. It's wonderful.
Yeah...
Ah, what's everyone drinking next?
Shido-san, do you have a favorite wine?
(Red Wines: Cabernet
Sauvignon, Merlot, Pinot Noir...)
You like Cabernet, right?
Ah... I'll pass on the wine.
Hmm, want to switch back to beer then?
Sure, I'll have a beer...
Alright, I win again.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Don't touch me.
Hey, Ryo!
Wait a sec.
He's taking this way too seriously.
Have you decided on your drinks?
I'll just have what
everyone else is having.
So it's the same after all.
- I'll go order then.
- Okay, thanks!
That's so good.
I'm down for another round.
What's everyone doing next?
- Ah, I have to get up early tomorrow...
- Seriously?
- I don't have to get up early tomorrow.
What do you mean by "seriously"?
No, my "seriously" was
directed at Kiritani-san.
- Really?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'll go.
- Awesome!
Shido.
We're going to an after-party.
Ah, I think I'll head home.
Do you have to get up early tomorrow too?
No, I just drank a bit too much.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thank you.
I'm planning to call it a night too.
Perfect, let's walk to
the station together.
Sounds like a plan.
Good work today.
- Good work today.
- Well then, good work everyone.
Good work today.
Are they together?
Nah, let's just go by ourselves.
Let's go, right now.
Alright, let's head out.
I had a lot of fun today.
It's really my first time
at a gathering like this.
The guys from our
department are pretty loud, huh?
No, not at all.
Everyone is really fun.
The time just flew by.
The people from the Secretarial
department are really fun too.
I got to see a new side of everyone.
People from the Secretarial department might
give off the impression of being very capable.
But off the clock, they're just like that.
Kiritani-san, you're pretty
much the same as usual.
Yeah.
I'm not used to letting my guard down.
We get along pretty well.
I'm exactly the same.
What about when you're with Yotsuya-san?
Huh?
You guys have known each
other since high school, right?
I was wondering, if
you're with Yotsuya-san,
do you ever let your guard down?
No, not at all.
I've never let my guard down around him.
We've always just been
competing with each other.
You're great rivals.
I wish I had a rival like that too.
Kiritani-san.
What's wrong?
Um...
I...
Hmm?
Shido-san.
Oh my.
This.
Looks like you left this at the restaurant.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Well then, see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
Shido-san.
I'm taking the bus.
Ah...
I see, then I'll take the train.
Well then, goodbye.
Okay, goodbye.
(Yotsuya Ryo)
(Block this caller)
Zen, can you hear me?
Zen?
Ugh!
Um...
What's wrong?
Ah, nothing.
I was just at a place called Break
drinking with the people from
the Secretarial department.
Oh...
Ah, I know that place.
The food is pretty good, right?
Yeah.
Was Kiritani-san there too?
Yeah, she was.
I see.
So,
what's this call about?
Huh?
Ah...
No, um...
The people from the
Secretarial department said
they want to grab a meal with you.
Huh?
Just for that?
Yeah.
That's right.
I'm not going.
Not interested.
Say something at least.
Ah, nothing in particular.
No, um...
Ah, the T-shirt.
T-shirt?
The one I borrowed from you last time.
Oh.
I want to return it.
Come get it now.
Huh?
Why?
What do you mean, why?
Because it's a pain to take it back home.
What does that have to do with me?
Do whatever you want with it.
Hey... wait...
What the hell am I doing?
Zen!
Ryo?!
The T-shirt.
You don't even have it on you, do you?
You almost never call me on your own.
Ah.
You're drunk, aren't you?
Don't tell me you missed me?
As if.
I just thought I brought it with me.
Whatever.
It doesn't matter when
you return that kind of thing.
Since I'm already here,
I'll take a walk with you
to help you sober up.
I didn't bring the
T-shirt, so just go home.
Hey, are you a monster?
You're the one who called me here.
I'm not going back.
Because I want to hang
out with you a little longer.
Let's go.
I see.
Hey.
Have you ever been inside that building?
Never.
I heard there are a lot of
interesting shops inside.
Let's go check it out together next time.
As a date?
What do you mean, a date?
How boring.
You're always like this.
You always forget about our "competition."
I'm not free enough to
go on a date with you.
I heard there's a braised pork
rice place you like there too.
Huh?
I've never told anyone
I like braised pork rice.
When I took you to eat it before,
weren't you really enjoying it?
You even remember something like that?
You're terrifyingly observant.
I've had my eyes on you the whole time.
I can't stand you.
Then next time I win, you're treating me.
Eh.
You mean our competition at work?
Duh.
Braised pork rice is way too cheap
of a reward for that competition.
Why? Braised pork rice is delicious.
I mean, it is delicious, but...
Well, you have a point.
Hey.
Zen.
Hmm?
After this competition is settled,
what... will happen to us?
Who knows...
When that time comes...
we probably won't be able
to be friends anymore, right?
Hey, Zen...
What is it?
Maybe we should just call it off.
This kind of competition.
(Next Episode Preview)
(Episode 5: I Really Don't Get It!)
Shido-san?!
Sorry.
Ah, Shido-san.
Just watching you makes me
feel like you're way too busy.
A stellar subordinate is truly dazzling.
You're really not honest with yourself.