( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Who knows.
I guess we won't be friends anymore.
Hey, Zen...
What is it?
Maybe we should just call it off.
This competition.
Huh?
You're calling it off now, of all times?
I'm kidding.
What?
You take things too seriously.
That's not true... You know that, right?
Backing out means you lose, you know.
This is a contest.
I know.
"Fake Fact Lips"
(Episode 5: I Just Don't Get It!)
Good work, Department Head.
This is for you.
Huh?
- Thank you, sir.
- It's the first time I've ever won.
You know, the slot machine thing
on the vending machine.
Are you sure I can have it?
It's such a special prize.
Shido, how many projects
are you on right now?
Uh...
There's Noken Development
and Relto Resource.
And the new affiliate marketing project I just
started researching the day before yesterday.
Wow, that's impressive.
A top employee is really something else.
- I'm counting on you.
- Yes, sir.
But don't push yourself too hard.
Thank you, sir.
(Yotsuya Ryo: I'm swamped this week. Probably
can't meet. Let's call a truce for now.)
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Is Yotsuya in today?
He just left for a team meeting.
Oh, I see.
He should be back this evening.
Is it urgent?
Should I give him a message?
No, that's okay.
(Shido Zen: I left the
T-shirt on your desk.)
(Are you free sometime next week?)
Yotsuya.
Hey.
- Um...
- I have a dinner to get to.
Let's talk next time.
Oh...
(Shido Zen: I left the T-shirt on your
desk. Are you free sometime next week?)
Yotsuya...!
- Department Head, good work today.
- Oh.
Um...
There's a planning
meeting in Osaka this Friday.
Oh, right. I haven't given
you the materials yet, have I?
Oh, but it's not urgent.
No, I'm afraid I'll forget again.
I'll send them to you right now.
- Just a second.
- Sorry to trouble you.
We hope this service will
benefit many more people.
And at the same time, further
grow your company's business.
It's a pleasure working with you.
We'll take care of this.
Oh, thank you.
Wow, the client signed on the spot.
That's Shido-san for you.
That's because we have an excellent team.
You're too modest.
You have an incredible success rate.
The real work starts now.
We need to adjust the
schedule, confirm the budget...
- Shido-san!
- Shido-san?
I'll go get some water!
Sorry, did I scare you?
Not at all.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Lately, just watching you, I can tell
you've been incredibly busy, Shido-san.
Do I look like I'm struggling?
Not struggling, exactly.
But since this week,
you've seemed a bit down.
I even mentioned it to
Department Head Mishima.
How embarrassing.
Making everyone around me worry.
No, no, it's because
we rely on you so much.
At the last dinner party,
didn't Kiritani-san say something too?
She asked if you were getting enough rest.
Getting rest, huh...
In the end, you have to
take care of your own body.
Well, well, Yotsuya-san.
You really are as good
a salesman as they say.
Right?
You're welcome in Osaka anytime.
I'll go talk to HR.
Hey, if you say that, I
might take you seriously.
Come on, let's go for a drink.
What do you want to eat?
If it's kushikatsu...
- Hey, you.
- Hmm?
We're obviously getting
something with batter first.
No way.
That stuff is a given.
(Incoming call: Yotsuya Ryo)
Huh?
You picked up fast.
- What's up?
- It's nothing, really.
It's just that the project I was busy with
is finally wrapped up.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
Well...
For not replying to
your messages and stuff.
You mean for deliberately avoiding me?
No, that's not it.
You don't have to call
me for every little thing.
But...
I've been swamped
with my presentation, too.
I haven't had time to think about you.
I see.
Since you said you were busy,
does that mean you're
done with your thing, too?
The presentation is over.
But the real work is just beginning.
Oh, so it went well.
- That's just like you.
- Of course it is.
Don't overdo it.
You haven't collapsed, have you?
As if I'd collapse.
Anyway, how about you?
Me?
Same as always.
But I guess I am a little tired.
So for some reason,
I suddenly wanted to hear your voice.
But...
after hearing your voice,
I guess I really do
want to see you after all.
Yotsuya.
- We've decided on a restaurant.
- I'm on my way.
Ryo.
Where are you right now?
Right now?
In Osaka.
Osaka...?
Yeah.
I'm staying another night.
Sorry, I have to go.
I'll call you when I get back.
Oh, Shido-san, excuse me.
You had a phone call just now.
Oh, sorry.
I'm heading home for the day.
There shouldn't be anything urgent.
Could you tell them I'll
handle it on Monday?
Got it.
It's so far.
Do you have plans?
Nothing much. Just going to unwind a bit.
Ryo.
Because you said you wanted to see me.
What is it?
You could at least look a little happier.
I'm super... happy.
You're so cold.
Then you should know what to do, right?
Ryo.
Hmm?
Are you doing all of this just to beat me?
That's...
Zen, aren't you doing the same thing?
I...
Zen.
Why are you crying...?
I'm not crying.
Ryo...
For the sake of winning,
would you do this with anyone?
Huh...?
Do you want to beat me that badly?
- That's not it.
- Then what is it?
Why are we...
doing this?
The truth is...
from the very beginning, I never
cared about the competition.
I just...
wanted to be with you.
I've liked you for a long time.
Ever since high school...
Huh?
So I...
wasn't hitting on
you for the competition.
I genuinely wanted you.
I'm sorry for doing something
that felt like I was tricking you.
From the start,
I was destined to lose this competition...
Zen...
If that's the case,
then be my boyfriend.
Huh...?
You pursued me and won.
Now you have to see it through.
What do you mean, 'won me over'?
The winner's word is law, right?
Aren't you going to say anything?
Sorry...
I'm just so confused.
Confused about what?
No.
We talked about this before, didn't we?
About winning or losing this competition.
You mean that time you said you were
quitting the competition out of the blue?
I already apologized for that.
You said back then...
That we might not be able
to be friends anymore, right?
Huh?
That's because we'd be lovers, obviously.
Why'd you have to say it like that?
Huh?
Do you have any idea
how long I've been agonizing over that?
You took it literally?
How dense can you be?
If it meant I couldn't
be with you anymore...
I would've rather we just stayed friends.
I thought I'd done something irreversible.
I regretted it so much.
If you didn't fall for me, I...
would lose you.
Ryo...
That's why...
If you wanted to date me,
you should've just lost sooner.
Says the one who was
into me from the start.
You've got some nerve.
Sore loser.
Takes one to know one.
By the way, don't get the wrong idea.
I only went easy on you
because you were trying so hard.
You just can't be honest, can you?
But that's what I like about you.
It's really throwing me off
when you're suddenly so direct.
Even so...
I don't want us to miss our chance again
because I didn't tell you how I feel.
Like idiots.
Getting so serious over
such a stupid competition.
Both of us.
Anyone would turn into an idiot
in front of the person they like...
Zen.
I like you.
Me too.
I only want Ryo.
It has to be Ryo.
Sorry.
I can't hold back anymore.
See? Now you really
can't live without me.
No.
I already...
couldn't live without you, Zen.
Being with you is driving me crazy.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Whatever.
Zen.
Only look at me.
Hey, Zen.
After the exams are over...
let's go somewhere.
We're studying for entrance exams.
If we go out and have
fun after just one test...
I'll never catch up to my brother.
I wish I could grow up faster.
What a childish thing to say.
When we're adults, we can go far away.
And be with the person we love.
I should get some rest too.
You told Yotsuya-san something like,
'You're welcome in Osaka anytime, ' right?
Of course. That was
just to set up the surprise.
So, Futami-san...
Are you really planning to go
without telling him anything?
A rival's entrance is always sudden.
As the ace of the Osaka branch...
I'm going to make my mark.
(Next Episode)
How much further do you want me to go?
(Episode 6: There's no need for the word 'Tentatively')
Are you going on a date?
Yotsuya-san?
Stop kidding around. Give it back.
Seriously?
I've been in love with you since college.
Getting first place once has
really gone to your head, hasn't it?
Right. I don't want it.
Huh?
You two are a classic
case of mutual admiration.
You should be careful too, Shido-san.
The time you have to
see each other is precious.