I'm back.
- You're back?
- Yeah.
Was it a rough day? Give me your bag. Come on.
You did great today.
I'm so tired.
I told you we should come back together.
Why did you stay late by yourself?
Because I really want to debut
with you this time.
I'm hungry.
You practiced without eating?
Yeah.
Do you want me to order chicken?
Make me ramen.
- You know what that means, right?
- What?
If you have ramen here,
you can't just leave.
This is my place, so I think you're the one
who might not get to leave.
That's exactly what I was hoping for.
You should dry your hair more.
I'm sleepy.
What was that?
There was something I wanted to do
with you when I got home.
Like this?
No, not that.
Something I wanted to do with you.
We can do it tomorrow.
We've got plenty of time,
so just sleep for now.
Okay.
What is this?
[K-pop Star Il Woo Releases Texts and Call Logs
Behind Stalking Allegations]
Il Woo disclosed the texts and calls,
and they're taking legal action.
These texts were fabricated
[Il Woo, why aren't you answering? I miss you]
and bent to fit their agenda.
Of course they're desperate.
If Il Woo goes down,
the whole group goes down with him.
So what's our plan?
What the hell is Il Woo doing?
Is he out of his mind?
Legal action?
He's completely out of control.
Hey, don't worry.
It's not true.
And our company is a major agency.
They can handle something like this.
Just don't give up like last time.
Are you okay?
Don't worry too much.
This will get worked out.
Right?
Huh?
Yeah.
Who gave that insider interview?
What?
According to a source
close to PNJS's Shin Jae Min,
he had a special relationship
with a key member to secure his debut.
The source said
this kind of practice was wrong,
so they agreed to speak to the reporter.
Who said this?
I'll check if someone on our side leaked it
and get the article pulled.
I told you to keep the trainees in line.
How many times did I tell you
to be careful at times like this?
I put together our response plan.
Call Legal.
Yes.
We should put out our own side of the story
and take legal action...
Manager Park.
Yes.
Why do you think I picked Jae Min?
This was as far as he was meant to go.
What?
Jae Min's role, I mean.
He got us attention through the scandal,
and we got to look like the company
that stood by its trainee.
Then that's all the more reason
to take legal action...
I thought you were sharper than this.
Why waste money on a card we're throwing away?
He did his job, so now he steps aside.
Just tell the press
that we only believed what Jae Min told us.
Still, sir...
Still what?
I already worked it out with Il Woo's CEO.
I mean, let's be honest.
How can we debut someone
caught in a scandal with a male idol?
We're not some outlet store.
Why would we sell damaged goods?
Wrap that up fast.
Have a seat.
Jae Min.
Yes.
You've worked hard.
The company has done everything it can,
so we'll be terminating your contract.
Don't worry about the penalty fee for this.
The company needs you.
We're family.
I appreciate you saying that, but...
You just have to take responsibility.
[The penalty shall be set at 80 million won]
You're an adult.
I was the one who pushed to pick you.
Thank you.
We're backing you this hard,
so give it everything you've got.
We'll be terminating your contract.
Don't worry about the penalty fee here.
I'm sorry.
You haven't been answering my texts.
Is it that good? Are you that happy?
Look at that glow on your face.
Hyun Jae must be treating you right.
Of course he is.
If you're jealous, date someone too.
Stop living in the practice room.
What makes you think I'm not seeing someone?
[CEO Room]
Kim Hyun Jae.
Want to see something funny?
Listen, Hyun Jae.
No one cares about you as much as I do.
So keep doing exactly what I tell you.
Just like you have been.
All our practices got canceled.
Nothing bad is going to happen, right?
I wonder if Jae Min's okay.
We're just taking a break
until things calm down,
so don't worry.
Right. Our company is a major agency.
They'll sort it out.
Hyun Jae.
Let's do that.
Damn it. Failed yet again.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Aren't you going to play?
Did you spend all your money already?
Seriously.
But when you look at me like that,
how can I say no?
Hurry up.
Yeah.
Okay.
I really want to win that one.
Is there anything you want?
That one's not that cute.
Isn't that one better?
I like this one.
It looks like you.
You think I'm that ugly?
You little...
Huh? Hey! Stop it!
Seriously.
You and your stupid strength.
So you hate it?
No.
How about we try to win dolls
that look like us?
Sure.
Why did you press that?
No, it won't grab it.
Hold on.
That was fun.
Let's come back here again.
Is there something on my face?
No. Why?
Because you keep staring at me.
That's not it.
It's just...
because you're ugly.
What did you say? Hey!
[Korean University]
- I heard he really was a stalker.
- He even fooled the company.
- He's basically a criminal.
- I can't believe someone like that goes here.
He has no shame.
That's seriously messed up.
I have nowhere to go.
Jae Min.
Khun.
You shouldn't be seen with me.
Why?
If you're with me,
they'll treat you the same way.
It's fine.
I never should've done this from the start.
I'm sorry.
I really wanted to do it with you.
Jae Min.
It's not your fault.
Jae Min!
Come with me.
Where?
Let's go.
I got through it because of you.
It must be hard for you being here.
You did this for me, didn't you?
Hyun Jae.
- How does this make any sense?
- It doesn't.
There's no way.
This is some hidden camera prank, right?
You never used to be like this.
What's really wrong with you?
Just stop already.