( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream")
(Author: Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 2=
You shouldn't look
at what you shouldn't
be looking at, Young Lady.
Stand still.
Don't move.
The person coming should be
a Lady of Gentleness.
How do you know
it's a Lady of Gentleness?
By the sound.
The jade worn by a Lady of Gentleness
comes from Dongjiang.
The sound is slightly dull,
unlike top-quality jade.
You are a Lady of Gentleness too?
Senior Attendant.
A mere Senior Attendant
actually dares to dream of
competing for the Emperor's bed.
Success depends on effort.
Perhaps His Majesty likes my type.
It's thanks to Father's plea
that I was titled Lady of Gentleness.
I must seize the time to get a chance
to attend to him tonight.
Applying the juice
of this flower to your skin
can make it as supple as jade.
Its fragrance is exquisite,
and
it has aphrodisiac effects.
It can make a man
unable to stop,
lost in ecstasy.
Is it that effective?
Absolutely.
Then, pick more of them.
Attendant Li,
do you know
what flower this is?
Shady tricks.
Of course, I wouldn't know.
Women who enter the palace
must fight for favor.
So what if it's a shady trick?
After all, in the palace,
there's only one man available,
who is the Emperor.
Vulgar.
You're a seller of the art of seduction,
yet you think I'm vulgar?
Besides, it's you men
who liked vulgarity first.
Who?
Who's there?
Do you know who I am?
I am Senior Attendant Rou,
personally titled by the Emperor.
If you dare to scare me,
I'll have His Majesty cut off your head!
We're stopping the search.
Go back.
Hurry, let's go.
It seems Lady Xu
is not as stupid as outsiders say.
She's quite good at framing others.
Let's go.
I'll see you out.
Keep walking straight,
and you will reach
the small gate out of the courtyard.
After you go out,
then take off the blindfold.
But I can't see.
How can I walk?
There are no obstacles ahead.
So, walk with confidence.
(I want to see)
(if you are truly foolish
or just pretending.)
(This is the scent of lake water.)
(Is he trying to silence me?)
(Or is he)
(testing me?)
At the hour of Zi tomorrow night,
see you at the Yuehui Pavilion.
I won't wait if you're late.
She caught Your Majesty
entering the garden at night.
There will be trouble.
It seems we can only kill her.
She doesn't recognize me.
This woman is strange.
I want to see
how she learns
the art of seduction from me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Madam.
Well?
Did you see clearly
who was hiding in the shadows?
It was Senior Attendant Rou.
How could it be her?
And I used her name.
What a wench.
She must have been hiding to set me up.
Then, we'll strike first
to gain the upper hand.
Have you heard?
Someone broke into
the Cold Palace last night.
If it were the Empress
in charge of the harem,
it would be fine.
But now,
it happens to be
the eccentric Lady Liu
of Bright Deportment.
Someone accidentally disturbed her rest,
and they almost lost their life.
Lady Liu of Gentleness, I misspoke.
It is fine.
But the one who
broke into the Cold Palace
is likely in big trouble today.
I know, right?
Today,
the person
will not escape death.
Greetings, Ladies.
(Broadly Learned and Determined)
Lady of Bright Deportment has arrived!
- Greetings, Your Ladyship.
Be seated.
- Thank you, Your Ladyship.
Her Ladyship asks
who went to the Cold Palace last night.
Entering the Cold Palace
without permission
is forbidden by His Majesty's rules.
Whoever dares to violate
the palace rules
is seeking death.
Will no one admit it?
Senior Attendant Rou,
you have a lot of nerve!
Your Majesty, someone sent
a secret report to Lady Liu
stating Shen Zhinian
broke into the Cold Palace.
She is being interrogated
at Yurong Palace right now.
If she confesses to seeing Attendant Li,
it will inevitably involve Your Majesty
and cause suspicion
regarding the Cold Palace.
If she dares to mention me,
then
kill her.
This morning,
I heard from several maids on watch
that last night, someone
claiming to be Senior Attendant Rou
broke into the Cold Palace.
I was passing the Cold Palace
on my watch last night,
and I indeed heard a woman
claiming to be Senior Attendant Rou.
I heard it as well.
Shen Zhinian,
do you admit your guilt?
I did not go to
the Cold Palace last night.
I went to Lady Xu's palace.
You're slandering me.
How could you have come to my palace?
In the main hall,
because of my promotion
to Senior Attendant Rou,
Lady Xu was very displeased.
I felt anxious at night
and could not sleep.
So, I made some pastries myself
and went to Lady Xu's to apologize.
Your Ladyship, please look into this.
I saw with my own eyes...
I saw with my own eyes
the maids on watch say
it was Senior Attendant Rou
who broke into the Cold Palace.
Every bird leaves a trace.
If you went there,
I would find out.
Whoever is lying,
I will have her tongue ripped out.
Your Majesty,
Lady Liu wants to rip out
Senior Attendant Rou's tongue.
Oh?
In Lady Xu's palace,
there are several tuberose plants.
I am allergic to tuberose.
But to seek her forgiveness,
I had to wait at her palace gate.
The passing servants all saw me.
Tonight, Xu Baoqin
used my name at the Cold Palace.
I'm afraid there will
be trouble tomorrow.
Put on my cloak.
Go and return quickly.
Your Ladyship, please look.
She really did have
an allergic reaction.
Perhaps
you caught this somewhere else,
or you're allergic to something else?
Tuberose
was brought from home by Lady Xu.
In the entire palace,
they are only found
at Lady Xu's palace gate.
If you do not believe me, Your Ladyship,
you can bring any other flower.
I can find out with one simple test.
I...
You were upset because His Majesty
named me Senior Attendant Rou,
so you harassed me on the spot.
At night, you went to the garden
and shouted the title
"Senior Attendant Rou" on purpose.
You did it all just to frame me.
No.
I didn't...
Your waist pendant
was dropped in the Cold Palace.
That's impossible.
I clearly double-checked
when I returned last night.
I didn't leave anything behind.
She really went there.
That's a serious crime.
How could she dare?
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, please let me explain.
Your Ladyship, listen to my explanation.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship!
Xu Baoqin,
ten strokes of the cane
and one month of confinement
to serve as a warning to others.
So she is being punished.
As she should be.
Indeed.
An oral decree from the Dowager Consort.
For violating palace rules,
Lady Xu is stripped of her rank,
sentenced to tongue-removal,
and confined to the Cold Palace.
Can she even survive that?
Attendant Wu,
what is the meaning of this?
Bring her in.
Kneel.
Your Ladyship, have mercy.
Who is this?
This is Jing, Lady Xu's maid.
She confessed
that Lady Xu broke into
the Cold Palace last night
to pick forbidden flowers.
Drag her away.
Your Ladyship...
Help me, Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, help me.
Save me.
This is so pitiable.
Your Ladyship!
All of you,
go out and watch her punishment.
Remember
to behave yourselves.
(Within these towering palace walls,)
(one wrong step leads to eternal ruin.)
(If I want to survive,)
(I must secure the Emperor's
favor as soon as possible.)
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪