( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 8=
If it really wanted to eat me,
would Your Majesty
kill me?
♪Moon sets on palace walls,
breeze hits the gates♪
Yes.
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
If there comes a day
when Your Majesty wants my life,
I will offer it to you myself.
Your Majesty, follow me.
I have something to show you.
I was reading
some ancient records last night
and found the insect
the little white snake likes to eat.
It's called the Crimson Butterfly.
It's unique on Mount Tian.
There is only one insect
in the capital similar to it.
Hm.
Your Majesty, don't open it.
♪I walk through the palace
day and night, just for my beloved♪
♪All my tenderness is for you,
I'd stay alone for you♪
♪I don't ask for equality,
only that you hear me♪
♪Years of longing haunt
the palace gates, too deep to hide♪
Your Majesty, don't open your eyes.
The fuzz on its wings is poisonous.
Handan,
bring a basin of fresh water.
Shen Zhinian, did you do this on purpose?
Your Majesty, don't open your mouth.
Be careful,
or your mouth will swell up too.
Young Lady, the water is here.
Alright.
Wait a moment.
Let me wash it with fresh water for you.
Your Majesty, here.
Your Majesty,
do you feel any better?
If you had such a "good thing",
how could you not share it with me?
No,
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, stop it.
Young Lady,
Lady Liu of Gentleness is here.
Your Majesty,
hide yourself first.
You dare to tell me to hide?
Is there a guest in your room, Zhinian?
No, there isn't.
I'll be right out.
Hide in here for a moment.
You dare to make me get into a cabinet?
No.
I'm afraid if she
knows Your Majesty is here,
she will refuse to leave.
So you think I am
someone who can't be seen?
I didn't mean it like that.
Let me just
send her away first, alright?
Hide for a moment.
You'd better think that way.
Ruyan, why do you have
time to visit my Tinglan Palace today?
I've come to congratulate you.
Ruyan, please come in.
Please have a seat.
I wonder what there is to congratulate?
Your elder sister has been
titled County Princess Ning'an.
She's become the favorite
of the Dowager Consort.
Is that not a joyous event?
Although I am from the Liu family,
you saw how Lady Liu
of Bright Deportment
treated me.
Please help me say a few kind words
before the Dowager Consort.
You overestimated me.
In front of the Dowager Consort,
what influence could I have?
You have County Princess Ning'an.
Zhinian,
please just help me.
Is someone in the room?
No.
It might be the cat I'm raising.
We shouldn't let it break your things.
It's better to be careful.
Ruyan.
What are you looking for, Ruyan?
Your clothes are too plain.
I'll send a few outfits over another day.
You should dress up properly.
Don't embarrass County Princess Ning'an.
Ruyan, I'm afraid you've misunderstood.
My elder sister
has always looked down on me.
Regarding your request,
I'm afraid I cannot help.
Never mind.
By the way, the Empress Dowager's
birthday is approaching.
I want to choreograph a dance
and invite you to join me.
If we team up,
we will shine.
Ruyan, I'm afraid
you'll be disappointed.
I am not good at dancing.
I really wish to befriend you, Zhinian.
If you look down on me,
I won't bother you anymore.
(So he escaped through the window.)
Shen Zhinian must be
trying to harm Your Majesty.
She is not.
She didn't.
Your Majesty's eyes are in this state,
yet you still speak for her.
Could it be
that you have fallen for her?
How dare you.
I have not fallen for her.
My apologies, Your Majesty.
But then again,
her catching insects
was indeed to please me.
Yes,
she did it to please Your Majesty.
Then, will Your Majesty still
title her Lady of Beauty?
I am in no rush, so why are you?
Get out.
If there comes a day
when Your Majesty wants my life,
I will offer it to you myself.
Little liar.
If it wanted to eat me,
would Your Majesty
kill me?
I would.
(I have been in the palace for so long,)
(yet I still haven't gained
Nangong Xuanyu's trust.)
(Shen Nanqiao entered
the palace just like in her past life.)
(Lu Jianglin has also gained
the Dowager Consort's favor.)
(Is it possible that everything)
(from my past life will happen again?)
(What should I do?)
- Longevity to the Dowager Consort.
- May your virtue shine forever.
Senior Attendant, you're finally back.
What did she call you?
My surname is Chang.
They call me Eunuch Chang.
Jianglin and Nanqiao brought back
a thousand-year-old
immortal tree from Nanhua Temple
to celebrate my birthday.
(Weeping flowering peach blossoms.)
(There is an immortal tree in Nanhua,)
(its weeping branches
bearing peach blossoms.)
(But once it leaves Mount Nanhua,)
(it can hardly survive.)
This tree is called
the Weeping Peach Tree.
It is a thousand years old.
Not only is it vibrant and beautiful,
but its fruit can also
strengthen the body
and prolong one's life.
Transplanting this tree was difficult.
Fortunately,
Young Master Lu is widely learned,
and Nanqiao is an expert in flora.
Only then could it be
brought to the capital safely.
Lu Jianglin, you've earned
the Dowager Consort's favor.
That was not an easy task.
I have little talent,
but I am willing to serve
Your Majesty like a dog or a horse.
I don't lack dogs or horses.
Besides, if I were to ride you
like a horse,
I'm afraid the Dowager Consort
wouldn't be pleased.
Your Majesty,
Dowager Consort,
I would like to perform
a peach blossom dance.
Ruyan, you're a gifted dancer.
Go ahead and perform a piece.
What does Your Majesty think?
Alright.
Senior Attendant Rou
is also a good dancer.
I would like to invite her
to dance with me.
I am clumsy.
I fear I might ruin your mood,
Dowager Consort.
Zhinian once suffered a leg injury.
She really cannot dance.
Zhinian?
Young Master Lu, you call her
a bit too intimately, don't you?
Young Master Lu came from a poor family.
He once studied
at the Shen family's academy.
He was my father's personal student.
Nanqiao, Young Master Lu, and I
have known each other since childhood.
Lu watched her grow up.
He is like an older brother to her.
In that case,
there is no need to be formal.
Join Ruyan
and dance a piece together.
Yes.
(There is the scent
of Love Potion on her silk.)
(So, she plans to frame Lu Jianglin.)
(Once Lu Jianglin loses control)
(and comes after me...)
The second dance,
The Drunken Concubine.
(This is the drugged cup.)
What is it?
Why did she fall?
What happened?
What a "Mouse Playing
Under the Moon" dance.
I am impressed.
So hot...
It's so hot.
Lady Liu,
what are you doing?
You slut.
How disrespectful.
Drag her out now.
How can such improper behavior
be acceptable before the throne?
The peach tree...
How could this be?
Look, what's going on?
This is an ill omen.
On the peach tree...
Look.
Senior Attendant Rou,
just what have you done?
This is the immortal tree
I prepared for
the Dowager Consort's birthday.
Presumptuous!
How dare you curse me?
Guards,
send Shen Zhinian to the Cold Palace.
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪