( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
(Emperor Xing has passed away.)
(The deposed Crown Prince
Nangong Xuanyu)
(slaughtered the six princes
with swift force)
(and purged the traitorous officials)
(to ascend the throne as Emperor.)
(Even though
the Emperor is a ruthless tyrant,)
(who resembles an Asura,)
(noble families still send
their daughters to the capital.)
(Yet, to this day)
(no one has won his favor.)
(Summon the candidates to the palace!)
(I am the concubine-born
daughter of the Shen family,)
(Shen Zhinian.)
(In my past life,
I married the poor scholar Lu Jianglin)
(and helped him
become the Prime Minister.)
(My legitimate elder sister
entered the palace selection)
(but ended up as a discarded consort.)
(In this life,)
(my sister, who once cried
and pleaded to enter the palace)
(actually changed her mind.)
Father, Mother,
I'm not going to the palace.
I want to marry Lu Jianglin.
Entering the palace is a dead end.
Let Shen Zhinian go instead.
Shen Zhinian,
you'd better hold onto
this fortune.
This harem
is quite "exciting".
(But she doesn't know)
(that Lu Jianglin)
(is an ungrateful man)
(who killed his own wife
with his own hands.)
(Living this life again,)
(rather than helping others to the top,)
(I would rather hold the power myself.)
(I will marry the most
powerful man in the world.)
(I'll use him as a stepping stone)
(to soar to the highest heights.)
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream")
(Author: Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 1=
The flowers you hold
were all chosen by yourselves.
Be sure to hold onto them tightly.
If the flower falls,
(Shen Zhinian)
you are disqualified.
(Concubine-born daughter
of the Shen family in Chizhou)
(Xu Baoqin,
daughter of the Xu family army)
(Liu Ruyan,
relative of Dowager Consort Liu)
You actually chose a Yulan magnolia.
How unlucky.
Well, I am different.
What I chose
is a Rhododendron.
His Majesty loves vibrant colors.
The Rhododendron is vibrant.
I will be selected.
The Rhododendron "cries blood".
It's an ill omen.
Shen Zhinian,
how dare you curse me!
I am the daughter of a Great General.
What do you think you are?
You two, please stop arguing.
Baoqin is innocent and lively.
Sister Zhinian is
exceptionally beautiful.
I'm sure you will
both make it to the end.
Are you trying to say
that I'm not beautiful?
Everyone says
that Shen Zhinian of Chizhou
is the top beauty.
(Liu Ruyan is trying to make me)
(a target for everyone else.)
Drag them all away.
Have mercy, Your Majesty!
Please give me another chance,
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
The backgrounds of
these candidates are complex.
Duke Zhen,
Duke Ding,
and the Princess Manor
have all planted their people.
(Nangong Xuanyu, Emperor of Daliang)
Since they've arranged
everything for me,
let them stand there
until I finish this game of weiqi.
Treating noble daughters
like weiqi pieces
and leaving them out in the sun
might be hard to justify.
Justify?
When they sent these people,
did they ever try to justify it to me?
(This isn't about
testing our endurance at all.)
(Why does he have each of us standing)
(in a specific spot?)
(He is treating us like weiqi pieces.)
(This is a stalemate.)
(No. 1 Beauty of Chizhou?)
(I'm going to turn her into
the No. 1 Cripple of Chizhou.)
(He placed us here as discarded pawns.)
(He cannot solve this game.)
(We will be stuck here forever.)
(This is an ancient endgame.)
(It's unsolvable.)
(If you want to break the deadlock,)
(there is only one way.)
(Clear the board.)
(Start over.)
Shen Zhinian, what are you doing?
Shen Zhinian,
what do you think you're doing?
Shen Zhinian of Chizhou,
failed.
Take her away.
(She actually saw the solution.)
(Interesting.)
This is the Emperor's
Golden Feather Arrow for the selection.
Why did he choose her of all people?
By imperial decree,
Shen Zhinian of Chizhou
is titled Senior Attendant Rou.
She is granted
residence in Tinglan Palace.
- Congratulations, Senior Attendant Rou.
I thank His Majesty.
(I gambled correctly.)
(Receiving a title
so unexpectedly today)
(will surely incite jealousy
among the other candidates.)
(From now on, in the palace,)
(I must be even more careful.)
(Cold Palace)
Please bear it a moment longer,
Your Majesty.
The White Snake
treatment is almost finished.
However, Your Majesty,
the backlash of the poison
is becoming more dangerous.
If this continues,
the consequences will be bad.
Manshu Tears.
Flowers bloom,
but leaves never see them.
Like entering a realm of ice and fire.
First ice, then fire.
It flares up once a month.
I actually quite like it.
It's thanks to Dowager Concubine Qin,
who built this secret room
for your treatment
here in the Cold Palace.
Otherwise, every full moon
when the poison flares up,
(Wen Ling, Imperial Guard)
the Duke Zhen would notice something.
Focus on the main task.
The matter regarding
the Chifeng Army token
must be handled quickly.
Understood, Your Majesty.
Shen Zhinian of Chizhou
could solve a stalemate.
Interesting.
(Tinglan Palace)
Young Lady,
I've made inquiries.
There is indeed a eunuch
named Li Congshan in the Cold Palace.
(Handan, Shen Zhinian's Maid)
He is on duty tonight.
As long as he exists, it's fine.
Bring me my cloak.
I'm going to the Cold Palace.
Young Lady, why are you looking for him?
His Majesty hasn't visited
the harem for a long time.
If I want to win his favor,
I must find another way.
Li Congshan used to be the Emperor's
personal attendant.
Because he offended a favored consort,
he was banished to work
in the Cold Palace.
He knows a lot about
the Emperor's preferences in bed.
I'm going to consult him.
Preferences in bed?
There are as many as 30 beauties
entering the palace this time.
Yet he only gave me a title.
I don't know what he sees in me.
He might summon me to serve at any time.
I must make sure
he remembers me vividly
from the very first night.
Young Lady, how did you become so bold?
Only the bold can carve out a future.
People don't always get
a second chance to start over.
Whitey,
help cover for me.
Then, remember to take
the east side gate, Young Lady.
The area is unguarded.
(Cold Palace)
Go ahead.
(How is there no one
in the Cold Palace?)
Didn't they say the concubines
sent here were too many to fit?
Whitey.
Whitey,
don't run off.
Careful, or you'll be stewed.
You are...
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for my cat.
I mean no harm.
Really.
(Attendant)
Are you...
Are you Attendant Li?
Why are you looking for him?
Actually, I came to find Attendant Li
to buy something.
I'm willing to pay handsomely.
Buy what?
The art of seduction.
I wonder
where you plan
to use this art.
No need to ask questions, Attendant Li.
Just name your price.
Since you've found me,
you must follow my rules.
What rules?
The rule of inspection.
(Inspection?)
I must check
if your hands are soft enough.
(No internal power.)
I also must check
if your waist is flexible enough.
(No hidden weapons.)
Are you done with your inspection?
It's my turn to inspect you.
Shen Zhinian,
it's been so long.
Is the Emperor's portrait restored?
Bring it here quickly.
♪Falling at first sight,
a life of turmoil wasted♪
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
(Nangong Xuanyu?)
♪All the spring colors
lean toward one person♪
You seem quite curious
about my appearance, Young Lady.
(Rumor says Nangong Xuanyu
killed his father and brothers.)
(He is prone to distrust.)
(I can't let him realize)
(that I've recognized him.)
Attendant Li,
you won't even show your true face.
I'm not doing
this deal anymore.
Let go of me.
Madam,
this way.
What should you do?
You can't get away now, can you?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪