( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 6=
(Tinglan Palace)
Handan,
what took you so long?
Did you get the medicine?
Hurry and apply it for me.
Why are you hiding?
Didn't you want to
learn the art of seduction?
I will teach you right now.
(Why would he
suddenly reveal his identity?)
Attendant Li,
what nonsense are you talking about?
Is this part of the lesson too?
Black Zhen Liquor
can make people tell the truth.
You knew who I was all along,
and yet you're still pretending.
(He has been drugged.)
(What did I say?)
(How much does he actually know?)
Your Majesty,
you should summon
the imperial physician now
to avoid any harm to your health.
Don't you want my favor?
You on top,
and I below.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid now?
Your Majesty is mistaken.
I want the heart of a powerful figure
who is decisive
and stands above all,
not a heart controlled by drugs.
Shen Zhinian,
you...
Very well.
(He didn't get angry
at my deception and refusal.)
(It seems this risky move)
(was the right one.)
(Shen Zhinian,)
(playing hard to get with me, are you?)
(Just you wait.)
Young Lady, please stop playing.
Aren't you afraid?
Why would a snake
suddenly appear on your bed?
Fortunately, you weren't bitten.
This is just too dangerous.
Look at this snake.
It's quite interesting.
As soon as I reach out,
it crawls into my hand.
If I don't let it up,
it even hangs its head
as if it's feeling sad.
The Emperor has arrived!
(Oh no.)
(He's here to settle the score?)
Your Majesty
is here to hold me accountable?
You should know very well
what I'm here for.
I am dull-witted
and do not know your intentions.
If you, who could pretend
not to know me to get close,
are dull-witted,
then there is no
clever person in this palace.
I was indeed looking for Attendant Li.
I just didn't expect
Your Majesty to be there.
I was afraid,
so I could only play along
and continue the act
with Your Majesty.
You actually know how to be afraid, huh?
Your Majesty, you can't read!
This is a book for women.
- How bold.
- Your Majesty.
I insist on taking a look.
(Fishing Alone on the Autumn River)
(Cold waves shimmer
in the autumn light.)
(A lone fisherman
in a straw cloak angles in the sunset.)
(Drunk, lying among reed flowers
with wind-filled sleeves.)
(Waking to the setting moon
and a boat covered in frost.)
Go back.
(Investigation Records
of Nangong Xuanyu)
You've investigated thoroughly,
haven't you?
Why are you hiding?
Now, you're scared?
I entered the palace
solely for Your Majesty.
Investigating you
was also because
I wanted to win your favor.
How did you find out?
When I entered the palace,
my father gave me 300 taels of silver.
To investigate
Your Majesty's preferences,
I have spent them all.
Liar.
So it was you who stole
my little white snake.
Speak.
Who put you up to this?
No one put me up to it.
It came here on its own.
It suddenly appeared
on my bed last night.
I couldn't get it to leave.
I didn't know it was yours.
Shen Zhinian,
if I don't get my
little white snake back,
I will sentence you to death.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Where are you?
Come out quickly.
Your master is here.
Two hours have already passed.
If you still can't find it,
beware that I will sentence you
to death by white silk.
Do you like this?
Come out.
I'll give it to you.
You don't actually think
it will listen to you, do you?
It's coming out.
(Nangong Xuanyu,)
(I'm not only going to
make your snake obey me,)
(but I'm also going
to make you obey me.)
(You really have
many tricks up your sleeve.)
(I have no time to
play with you anymore.)
Your Majesty.
I've been kneeling for so long,
I can't stand up.
Could you
give me a hand?
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
♪Flowers wither easily,
but obsession remains♪
(They say emperors
have always been heartless.)
(Nangong Xuanyu,)
(you are no exception.)
♪Time silently scars those left behind♪
♪I walk through the palace
day and night, just for my beloved♪
♪All my tenderness is for you,
I'd stay alone for you♪
♪I don't ask for equality,
only that you hear me♪
♪Years of longing haunt
the palace gates, too deep to hide♪
♪I endured the years,
guarding a single truth♪
♪Spending my youth on deep love,
asking not of right or wrong♪
(Met you first under the moonlight,)
(and my heart began to race.)
(I only wish that when the dream ends,)
(you will still be here.)
(Warmth behind the red curtains,)
(entwined with you.)
(Nangong Xuanyu,)
(your heart)
(is racing for me.)
Your Majesty.
What is it?
Dowager Consort Liu encountered
bandits on her way
back from Nanhua Temple.
Fortunately, she was saved by
scholars traveling for the exams.
She will return to
the palace tomorrow morning.
Will you go to
the palace gate to receive her?
This dynasty is ruled by filial piety.
If I don't go,
Jiang Chen will nag me about it again.
(He mentioned Jiang Chen.)
(I didn't expect that he and Jiang Chen
were on such good terms.)
Your Majesty is not
looking for the snake?
I don't need to look for it.
It will return on its own.
If it dares to run away again,
I'll stew it.
Your Majesty is formidable.
It wouldn't dare run away again.
Regarding the little white snake,
do not speak of it to anyone.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Shen Zhinian,
tomorrow, follow me
to welcome the Dowager Consort back.
I obey Your Majesty's command.
The white snake is finally back.
This snake was born
on the peak of Mount Tian.
It takes a century
to grow as thick as a thumb.
Without it, when the poison
acts up on the full moon,
Your Majesty could never survive it.
Your Majesty was so intimate
with Shen Zhinian today,
and you're letting her follow you
to welcome Dowager Consort Liu tomorrow.
Does this mean you trust her now?
I just feel
that being near her helps alleviate
this scorching pain.
Besides, no matter whose side she's on
or what her goal is,
in the end,
she'll be just like this snake,
staying obediently
in the palm of my hand.
The Dowager Consort
has returned to the palace!
Mount Nanhua has always been peaceful.
How could you encounter bandits there?
Your Majesty may not know,
but this group of bandits
(Dowager Consort Liu, Empress Dowager of Daliang)
used a four-year-old child to get close to me.
Fortunately, two passing heroes
came to my rescue.
That is how I was able to return safely.
Guards,
please invite the two heroes
into the hall.
(Shen Nanqiao, legitimate
daughter of the Shen family in Chizhou)
(Lu Jianglin, husband of Shen Nanqiao)
Shen Zhinian,
you must seize
this fortune.
The harem
is quite an eventful place.
Execute!
(Shen Nanqiao.)
(Lu Jianglin.)
(How did they get into the palace?)
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
You may rise.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Nanqiao and Jianglin
disregarded their own safety
to save me.
They lured the bandits away
and nearly lost their lives.
Nanqiao even injured
her hand because of it.
So, I brought her back
to the palace for medical treatment.
(It seems Shen Nanqiao knew
the Dowager Consort would be in danger,)
(so she rushed to
the rescue ahead of time)
(to win her favor.)
(When it comes to palace affairs,)
(she is more familiar
with them than I am.)
(If she manages to stay,)
(she will be a huge problem for me.)
Miss Shen, you also share
the surname Shen
and come from Chizhou.
Do you happen to know
Senior Attendant Rou?
Zhinian.
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪