( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 7=
Miss Shen,
you are also named Shen
and are from Chizhou.
Do you happen to know
Senior Attendant Rou?
Senior Attendant Rou
is my younger concubine-born sister.
Greetings, Nanqiao.
Zhinian.
Young Master Lu.
Greetings,
Senior Attendant Rou.
Indeed, she has
an extraordinary appearance.
Since we were young,
my sister has always
been prettier than I am.
She is also more ambitious than me.
She only chooses
the most outstanding men to marry.
I have misspoken.
What did you do wrong?
When it comes to marriage,
one should follow parents' orders
and the matchmaker's words.
You have done very well.
Shen Zhinian,
you must learn to be content.
Follow the palace rules
and serve the Emperor well.
I will follow your teachings,
Dowager Consort.
Now that my wishes have come true,
it's all thanks to Nanqiao.
Thank you, Nanqiao.
Zhinian,
we can catch up
on our sisterly bond later.
Emperor,
I wish to adopt
Nanqiao as my goddaughter.
What do you think?
(The younger sister entered the palace)
(and the elder sister
saved the Dowager Consort.)
(What a perfect collaboration.)
Whatever you say, Dowager Consort.
Alright.
Then, you will be granted the title of
County Princess Ning'an,
and you will reside in Qingquan Palace.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Thank you, Dowager Consort.
(I never expected)
(that Shen Nanqiao
would dare to enter the palace.)
The Dowager Consort was
originally going to Mount Ling,
but she changed her route
to Nanhua Temple midway.
Shen Nanqiao came to
the capital from Chizhou.
On the way, there is Babao Temple,
which is most popular with civilians,
but she didn't go there.
Instead, she took a detour
to Nanhua Temple.
Was it a coincidence,
or was it intentional?
I think these two sisters
are both very suspicious.
Keep a close eye on them.
Find out the truth.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(Tinglan Palace)
County Princess Ning'an has arrived!
So, you live in such a remote place.
Life here must be
very difficult for you.
It's still better than being at home.
After all, this is the palace.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have followed me here.
There's no need to pretend.
Without power or influence,
you are less than an ant in this palace.
I am different.
Lu has come to
the capital for the re-examination.
He will surely pass.
When he becomes the top scholar,
I will be both a County Princess
and the top scholar's wife.
We both come from the Shen family.
We are tied together.
If you live well,
it's good for the Shen family and me.
You want to benefit from me?
Likewise,
if you make a mistake,
it will implicate the whole Shen family.
I hope you think clearly
before you do anything.
What do you mean?
I'm busy.
County Princess Ning'an,
Young Master Lu,
please leave.
Let's go.
My father-in-law
asked me to give this to you.
Don't be afraid.
Lu,
let's go.
Stop pretending to be so devoted.
He turned around and
married Shen Nanqiao anyway.
If he were truly noble,
he shouldn't have married anyone.
(Lu Jianglin's loss of composure today)
(must have been noticed
by someone with intent.)
(I must be extra careful.)
County Princess Ning'an
came from Chizhou.
She should have
taken the Xu County route.
Why would she take
a detour to Mount Wei?
(Why does he look even more terrifying
than in my past life?)
I went to Nanhua Temple
to pray for my husband,
hoping he would pass the imperial exam.
Nanqiao is gentle and virtuous.
It's just a pity
that such a beautiful flower
has fallen into an ordinary family.
You are too kind, Dowager Consort.
I am merely of humble appearance.
I cannot compare to Zhinian's beauty.
I heard from Nanqiao's maid
that Nanqiao was originally
the one to enter the palace.
It was Shen Zhinian who made a scene,
insisting on breaking
the engagement with Lu Jianglin
because she wanted to become a consort.
Nanqiao felt
indebted to Jianglin,
which is why she
was willing to marry him.
Your Majesty,
Shen Zhinian
is no saint.
Your Majesty,
my sister's love for wealth and status
is not exactly a sin.
Mm.
County Princess, you're right.
It's not a crime for a woman
to seek a good husband.
Your Majesty,
have you taken a liking to Shen Zhinian?
The County Princess
saved your life, Dowager Consort.
So, I cannot mistreat her family.
I will grant Shen Zhinian the title
of Lady of Beauty
to demonstrate your virtue,
Dowager Consort.
A promotion of four ranks without merit?
That is improper.
What do you think, County Princess?
There is no need for such
generosity.
I heard you once had
an engagement with Lu Jianglin.
Looking at your expression,
Your Majesty,
could I be so bold
as to think you are jealous?
Me, jealous?
You think too highly of yourself, no?
I've always been broad-minded,
so I love thinking highly of myself.
I didn't like the poor scholar
my father chose.
I only love a majestic man
like Your Majesty.
What a blatant gold-digger.
In this world,
which woman wouldn't want her husband
to be handsome, brave,
talented, and capable?
This mouth of yours
is indeed your greatest talent.
So, do you like it, Your Majesty?
I don't.
But I love Your Majesty's mouth.
Your Majesty's mouth is stubborn.
How thick-skinned.
I am only thick-skinned
for Your Majesty.
I would never be
this way with anyone else.
Because Your Majesty
is the finest man in the world.
Shen Zhinian,
you'd better
have never said
these words to another man.
I swear,
I have only said them to you.
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
♪All the spring colors
lean toward one person♪
Do you realize that deceiving
the Emperor is a capital offense?
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
♪Flowers wither easily,
but obsession remains♪
I may love to joke,
but one thing is true.
I really like you very much, Your Majesty.
Shen Zhinian,
you'd better be able
to keep up this act forever.
♪I don't ask for equality,
only that you hear me♪
♪Years of longing haunt
the palace gates, too deep to hide♪
♪I endured the years,
guarding a single truth♪
♪Spending my youth on deep love,
asking not of right or wrong♪
♪Though rumors cover the bed,
my heart is sincere♪
♪Only wishing to stay by your side,
never betraying this bond of fate♪
The Emperor has visited twice
but hasn't stayed the night.
Could he really have
some hidden ailment?
It doesn't seem like it.
I don't understand why either.
Every time it reaches
a critical moment, he stops.
Perhaps,
he still doesn't trust me.
Young Lady, why did you tell His Majesty
about your marriage to Lu Jianglin?
My marriage to him isn't a secret.
His Majesty would
find out sooner or later.
It's better that I tell him myself.
But what if His Majesty really thinks
you're someone who favors
the rich and disdains the poor?
Since it's His Majesty's wealth
that I love,
he will only be happy.
It's a man's nature to enjoy conquest.
Senior Attendant, a pigeon just flew in.
Isn't this Lu Jianglin's pigeon?
Drive it away.
Yes.
Lu Jianglin is so indiscreet.
It will cause trouble.
I must find a way
to send him away.
Could it really be as Nanqiao said
that she favors the rich
and disdains the poor,
so she abandoned me?
Shen Zhinian,
I treated you with sincerity.
How could you betray me?
(Tinglan Palace)
Young Lady,
why do you use a bell to catch insects?
This is an insect-catching bell.
Its sound can trick the insects
into thinking
it's a female's mating call.
Can this really attract the insects
the little white snake likes to eat?
I looked through
ancient records last night.
The insects the little white snake likes
are unique on Mount Tian.
Since it's hiding in the Tinglan Palace
and won't leave,
it means there must be
the insects it likes here.
If you help His Majesty raise the snake,
he will be happy.
Whether he's happy is one thing,
but the little white snake
will be happy.
If I can't win His Majesty's favor,
I'll just kidnap the little white snake.
Selling it for money
would also sustain me.
Come give me the cage.
Your hand...
Why are you here again?
Hadn't I come, you would have
kidnapped my little white snake
without me even knowing.
It's raising, not kidnapping.
Doesn't Your Majesty want to know
what the little white snake
likes to eat?
You should be glad
it doesn't like to eat you.
Otherwise, I would have to kill you
and feed it with your blood.
If it really wanted to eat me,
would Your Majesty
really kill me?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪