( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 12=
You thought entering the palace
would bring you wealth and glory?
So what if you've been granted
the title of Lady of Beauty?
His Majesty values the Liu family.
He won't come save you.
The day you entered the palace,
I already left behind a letter
with one of my trusted people
in the palace.
It says that you and Madam Shen
used witchcraft
to curse His Majesty.
If you dare harm me,
that letter will
be delivered to His Majesty.
The entire Shen family
will be buried alongside you.
How dare you frame me!
It's only a letter.
With Dowager Consort Liu backing me,
you can't do a thing.
Tell me,
whose will arrive first?
Your letter,
or His Majesty's secret agents?
How dare you harm me!
Give it to me!
Back then, my mother and I
had Father's favor all to ourselves.
It was your mother,
with no sense of shame,
who seduced Father.
That was because he
himself was fickle and unfaithful.
How can you blame my mother for that?
You still dare talk back?
Do you really think
His Majesty cares about you?
You've been locked up here
for an entire day,
yet His Majesty hasn't even
asked about you once.
Shen Zhinian, just accept your fate.
No one cares whether you live or die.
To me,
you will always be nothing
more than an ant beneath my feet.
Bah!
Carry out the tattoo punishment.
♪Moon sets on palace walls,
breeze hits the gates♪
♪One glance led me
astray for half a lifetime♪
Your Majesty!
Shen Zhinian seduced another man
and behaved immorally.
I acted under
the Dowager Consort's decree.
Shen Nanqiao,
receive the tattoo punishment
and be expelled from the palace.
Your Majesty, spare me!
Your Majesty!
♪Time silently scars those left behind♪
♪I walk through the palace
day and night, just for my beloved♪
♪All my tenderness is for you,
I'd stay alone for you♪
Your Majesty, spare me!
Your Majesty!
Young Lady only left
the Cold Palace to save me.
She happened to run into Lady Liu
and begged Her Ladyship to save me.
Luckily, I tasted that dish first.
Otherwise, the one poisoned
would've been Young Lady.
Go back and rest first.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Weren't you quite capable?
They hit you, yet you didn't fight back?
I'm already injured like this.
Besides, how many people
could I fight alone?
I don't have anyone
powerful enough to protect me.
That sharp tongue of yours
is only used against me.
Today, you saved me.
I'll remember it.
What do you mean "you" and "me"?
How impudent.
Your Majesty treats me well,
so naturally I dare to be bold.
Your Majesty,
come a little closer.
I have something to say.
I...
wish to ask Your Majesty for something.
What is it?
The people in this palace
are treacherous.
I'm afraid
that one day I may offend someone again.
Your Majesty cannot stay
by my side at all times.
So I wish
to ask Your Majesty
for a death-exemption medal.
Do you know who
death-exemption medals are given to?
They're awarded to those who rendered
great service in supporting the ruler,
or saved the ruler's life.
I know.
In the future,
I will surely
risk life and limb for Your Majesty,
shield you from blades and swords,
and brave any danger for you.
Let's wait until you've recovered first.
Yes.
How could His Majesty leave so suddenly?
Now that the treatment's
been interrupted,
who knows whether it can
still be cured properly?
The situation was urgent.
There was truly no other choice.
Just do your best, Physician Lu.
Your Majesty, those words are mistaken.
I accepted the late Consort's
request to care for Your Majesty.
If I fail to cure Your Majesty,
then I can only
repay my crime with death.
With all the time you're wasting talking,
the needles could already be in place.
Who would've thought that one day,
Your Majesty would risk your own life
for the sake of a mere beauty.
She's just a defenseless woman.
If she were to die in my harem,
wouldn't that only make me
seem incompetent?
It's over.
Everything's over.
Now both His Majesty
and Dowager Consort Liu have abandoned us.
My future is ruined.
All because of you.
Lu,
I still have a way.
I know where the thing
Duke Zhen wants most is hidden.
We can seek refuge with him.
What did you say?
Then I'll trust you one more time.
Your Majesty,
the shadow guards discovered
the whereabouts of the Chifeng Army token
at Jinsong Pavilion.
Would Your Majesty like to investigate?
Jinsong Pavilion?
Mm.
But Jinsong Pavilion
is a famous male escort house.
They only receive female guests.
It'll be difficult for us to get in.
What are we going there for?
Why are we dressed like this?
It's just an auction house.
Help me accomplish this,
and I'll grant you
a death-exemption medal.
I will do everything in my power.
- Good.
- Wonderful!
There's actually
a dragon deity parade tonight.
I heard if you touch the dragon's head,
your wishes will come true.
I want to touch it.
Business first.
Yes.
Fine.
I'll indulge you this once.
Mm.
♪Longing turns to yearning,
twining into a red string♪
♪Drawing your face before my eyes♪
Not playing anymore.
♪How many twists of fate
before we finally meet♪
♪The melody drifts
across rivers and mountains♪
♪Rowing a small boat
with you through passing years♪
♪If the scenery is beautiful,
spring won't feel far away♪
♪I only wish to dance with you
among fluttering flowers and butterflies♪
♪Picking an orchid,
pledging our love forever♪
♪Even if the road to the horizon is long,
may we still share the same moon♪
Please, Dragon Deity, protect Handan.
Protect my maternal family
and keep them safe and well.
♪Then together we'll listen
to the endless wind and snow♪
Wait a moment.
♪As time plays like strings,
youth fades from our faces♪
Please, Dragon Deity, bless His Majesty
with peace and safety,
and may all his wishes come true.
Boss, give me a carp lantern.
Alright.
Thank you.
Offering this in your name.
Thank you for bringing me
to see the lanterns.
♪You do not know♪
♪The partridge's cry
is full of resentment♪
Look!
The sky lanterns are rising.
They're flying so high.
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪
Your Majesty,
why are you late?
I've been here
for quite some time already.
But seeing how happy Your Majesty
and Miss Shen were together,
I didn't wish to interrupt.
Miss Shen,
are your injuries any better?
Much better.
Thank you.
Why did this lantern go out?
It was never lit to begin with.
Your Majesty, today's outfit
is certainly unique.
You sure talk a lot.
Let's go.
(Jin)
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪