( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 10=
Be careful, Young Master.
Who's there?
There's no one?
Could it be a wild cat?
There's firelight.
A wild cat shouldn't be coming here.
I hope it doesn't come back.
Zhinian,
did you know I was coming,
so you left a light on for me?
I know I'm in your heart.
Zhinian.
Where did this wild cat come from?
Annoying!
Where did you go?
I...
Just walked around.
This is the harem.
You're an outside male wandering around.
If you're discovered,
I won't be able to save you.
You can't save me?
Then, why did you bring me in?
(If you weren't going
to be the top scholar,)
(who would bother coaxing you?)
Lu,
what do you mean?
If I didn't want Dowager Consort
to recommend you,
why would I come
all the way to the capital?
But the peach tree withered.
Dowager Consort is displeased.
Duke Zhen and Duke Ding
are at each other's throats.
To deal with Duke Zhen,
the Emperor is vigorously
supporting the Liu family.
You should just turn to the Liu family.
They need manpower.
You're from a sheltered home.
How do you know all this?
Of course, it's because my last...
I heard it from Dowager Consort
a while ago.
I hope it's as you say.
Otherwise, never mind my future,
even my life will be lost here.
Lu, why must you be so cowardly?
You are the man who
will be the top scholar.
Top scholar?
It's not that easy to
become the top scholar.
(So overcautious.)
(Looking all weak and useless.)
(How did he pass
the exams in my past life?)
What happened to my hand?
What...
What did you touch?
What could I have touched?
Forget it.
Go get me some medicine.
Tomorrow, I still have to copy scriptures
for Dowager Consort.
Go.
(Letter to Lu Jianglin)
You are heartless to me.
Why did you come to find me
time and again
after entering the Cold Palace?
Could there really be a hidden reason
for you entering the palace?
Your Majesty,
while investigating Lu Jianglin,
we discovered these past letters
between him and Shen Zhinian.
(Hand in hand beneath the moon,
together till white hair and frost)
What a display of deep affection,
with such constant correspondence.
Your Majesty, your hand has
been itching all night without relief.
What exactly is wrong?
Should we summon the imperial physician
again to take a look?
Go to the Cold Palace.
Miss, I went to deliver
medicine to Xu Baoqin today.
The eunuch told me that Great General Xu
used a death-exemption medal
to get her out.
The Xu family's death-exemption medal?
(If I could also obtain
a death-exemption medal,)
(my maternal family and I)
(would escape the fate of my past life.)
Lord Jiang, you're here.
Lord Jiang.
Miss Shen, you said
an orchid has withered.
I've come to take a look.
Thank you, Lord Jiang.
Lord Jiang, please come in.
Please look, sir.
These orchids need to see some sunlight.
The window is broken.
Be careful not to hurt your hand, sir...
I'll find someone to fix it later.
The night is cold.
It won't do if the window won't close.
It's more than just the cold.
There are wild cats making trouble.
I'll go see the Empress.
I'll ask her to find
a way to get you out.
If that can really happen,
I thank you on behalf
of the Young Lady, Lord Jiang.
Handan,
don't trouble Lord Jiang.
Her Highness is unwell.
How can we trouble her
with such trivial matters?
Why do I have a rash on my hand?
The window might have grown mold.
You're having an allergic reaction.
You should go to the Imperial Hospital.
His Majesty has arrived!
Jiang Chen?
Why are you here too?
I came to see
the orchids Miss Shen planted.
Since when did you two become so close?
We aren't close at all.
I've always cherished
orchids like my own life.
I couldn't bear to see them ruined,
so I made a special trip.
What happened to your hand?
I'm not sure what happened.
I only stayed at
Miss Shen's for a while,
and a rash broke out for no reason.
The Cold Palace hasn't
been cared for in years.
There are many insects.
I must have been bitten.
County Princess, you can't go in.
This is the Dowager Consort's token.
Step aside.
What are you afraid of?
If you're bold enough
to exchange love poems,
then write them in front of me.
Write them a hundred times
if once isn't enough.
Your Majesty.
Long live Your Majesty.
What are you doing here?
I...
I know
my sister likes writing poems,
so I brought her brush and ink
to help her pass the time.
Bring them here.
Did I give you permission to rise?
(He has a red rash on his hand too.)
(He was also here last night.)
(It seems I wasn't
the only one here last night.)
(Every one of them is so bold.)
It seems this Cold Palace
is even livelier than Shanglin Garden.
Since you all like it so much,
you should all move in.
I beg for forgiveness.
I'll never come here again.
All of you, dismissed.
I take my leave.
What should your punishment be
for plotting against me?
Oh?
What happened to your hand,
Your Majesty?
Stop pretending.
You sent me to
the Cold Palace for no reason.
Can't I even fix my own window
to hide from wild cats?
You're guarding against me?
You're not a wild cat.
You are a true dragon,
the Son of Heaven.
Even in the Cold Palace,
your tongue is still as sharp as ever.
I'll use some mint water
to wipe your hand,
so your imperial hand feels better.
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
♪Flowers wither easily,
but obsession remains♪
Shen Zhinian.
Yes?
You're hiding something from me.
I'm hiding many things from you.
Which one are you asking about?
You certainly are bold.
In one's life,
how can one not tell a few lies?
Lies can be
well-intentioned or malicious.
I have no malice toward you.
Only admiration.
I just want to win your favor.
You want to win my favor?
Yes.
Every woman in the harem wants that.
But I
want it most.
Since you want my favor so badly,
I'll give you a chance.
Before dawn,
write one hundred love poems.
And you'll let me
out of the Cold Palace?
Depends on your performance.
Your Majesty,
I won't close the window tonight.
What does His Majesty mean by this?
To keep out wild cats.
It's good that they nailed it shut.
I don't know where all these wild cats
in the Cold Palace come from.
They've been here three times already.
They even broke the windows.
Luckily, they didn't get
into your room, Young Lady.
Those three "wild cats" who came by
were actually
His Majesty,
Jiang Chen,
and Lu Jianglin.
They all had red rashes on their hands.
What?
Young Lady, you must be mistaken.
Why would Lord Jiang
climb over a wall?
Besides, the rash on his hand
might have happened during the day.
Didn't you smell the ointment
on Lord Jiang's palm?
And judging by how severe the rash was,
it didn't look like it started today.
To think a refined gentleman
would actually
resort to climbing walls.
As expected,
not a single man is any good.
Never mind him for now.
Let's go back and prepare the ink.
The Emperor ordered me
to write a hundred poems.
I have to get them done quickly.
A hundred poems?
How can you finish that in one night?
If he wants a hundred,
he'll get a hundred.
He wants to make
things difficult for me,
so I'm going to show him I can do it.
Let's go.
Your Majesty,
I've brought all the anti-itch ointments
from the Imperial Hospital.
Let Lu itch to death.
It's not just Lu Jianglin.
Jiang Chen also has a rash on his hands.
Well played, Shen Zhinian.
Seeing three men in a single night, huh?
Could it be that Jiang Chen
was also bewitched by her?
(Could it be)
(that she coaxed him
the same way she coaxed me?)
Your Majesty,
Lady Shen's hundred poems
are here.
(On the high cliff, strong wings rest.
The wind curls, the gaze is cold)
She finished so quickly?
(Not playing with the common sparrows,
spreading wings toward the clouds)
What a fine way to
express her ambitions.
A whole hundred poems of it.
Did I even ask her to
express her ambitions?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪