( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 11=
They composed a full hundred poems.
What has Your Majesty discovered?
Hmm.
Interesting.
One person wrote only of love,
while the other wrote only
of lofty ambition.
Women are easily consumed by love.
Naturally, their poems
are filled with tenderness.
Men are different.
Their hearts are always
set on greater ambitions.
The poems about ambition
were written by Shen Zhinian.
These love poems
were written by Lu Jianglin.
So Lu Jianglin
is quite the hopeless romantic.
If he truly were devoted,
he would've stopped Shen Zhinian
before she ever entered the palace.
That's true.
If he really were so lovestruck,
he wouldn't have married Shen Nanqiao.
Lu Jianglin is no threat.
But this Jiang Chen...
Why has he suddenly
become so attentive to Shen Zhinian?
Keep an eye on him.
Understood.
Your Majesty should visit Physician Lu
to change your medicine.
Physician Lu specifically warned
that it must not be delayed.
Mm.
Let's go.
Luckily, I got the medicine last night.
Today, Wen Ling went
to the Imperial Hospital
and took away every ointment for itching.
Young Master, you explained
that the rash came
from insect bites today.
I wonder
whether His Majesty believed him.
He's far too suspicious.
He won't believe it that easily.
Then what should we do?
He is the ruler,
and I am his subject.
If he refuses to trust me,
there's nothing I can do.
That Shen Zhinian really is capable.
She actually managed
to draw His Majesty to the Cold Palace.
Not only did he go to the Cold Palace,
he even tried climbing in
through the window.
Shen Zhinian truly is special to him.
Spread the news that His Majesty visited
the Cold Palace last night.
Lady Liu,
Liu Ruyan,
Shen Nanqiao...
Don't leave a single one out.
Young Master, you have always
stayed out of harem affairs
and have gotten along well
with His Majesty.
Why are you suddenly
so concerned about Shen Zhinian?
Because His Majesty cares about her.
Lady Liu,
Nanqiao is one of our Liu family.
You should look after her
more in the future.
Dowager Consort, be careful
not to bring trouble upon yourself.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
(May everlasting kindness
and glory remain)
Young Master Lu,
you truly write remarkable poetry.
Lu began studying at the age of four.
By fourteen, his poems were already
renowned throughout Chizhou.
If he's such a gifted poet,
why is he still relying on Shen family?
Young Master Lu simply hasn't
had the right opportunity.
With his talent,
his day will come sooner or later.
What is he, a firework?
"Soaring into the sky"?
Nanqiao and Jianglin
saved my life.
You shouldn't speak so harshly.
Good children.
You've kept me company all day.
Go back and get some rest.
Now that the Emperor
is promoting reforms
and supporting scholars
from humble backgrounds,
Lu Jianglin already enjoys
quite a reputation in Chizhou.
If we can win him over
for the Liu family,
then talented scholars
of humble birth across the realm
will surely flock to us.
If those scholars choose to serve anyone,
they'll serve His Majesty.
The Liu family
are His Majesty's subjects.
How can you think of competing with him?
I can't be bothered arguing with you.
Go back.
Among the women of the Liu clan,
she is by far the most beautiful.
But she's impossible to control.
Dowager Consort,
you still have me.
I will do everything I can
to win His Majesty's favor.
You?
Mm.
You'll already be doing well
if you stop causing trouble.
You were only
just released from confinement.
Behave yourself.
(On the day of Beginning
of Spring in my previous life,)
(the Shen family was executed in full,)
(and my maternal family
was dragged down with them.)
(Now I only have one month left.)
(I must obtain the death-exemption medal
as soon as possible.)
Young Lady,
do you think His Majesty
will release us soon?
Look at tonight's meal. It's so lavish.
We still need to stay careful.
You nearly scared me to death.
Here.
Young Lady, you haven't had a proper meal
since entering the Cold Palace.
These two drumsticks are both for you.
There are two.
We'll each have one.
Eat.
Mm.
Mm, it's delicious.
Young Lady, you should eat too.
The soup is delicious as well.
Handan.
Handan, what's wrong?
Handan!
I'll go fetch an imperial physician.
Hold on.
Wait for me.
How dare you!
Once you've entered the Cold Palace,
without an imperial decree, you are forbidden
from stepping beyond its main gate.
Move aside.
Shen Zhinian,
you really think
His Majesty holds you dear?
If His Majesty truly favored you,
he wouldn't have sent you
to the Cold Palace.
You vile woman!
What are you doing?
Let go!
You madwoman!
Even in the Cold Palace,
you're still this arrogant?
Let me tell you something.
The people sent into the Cold Palace
only leave on stretchers.
Your Highness,
please rest for a while.
Your Highness dreamed
of immortals again last night?
Mm.
I dreamed that my immortal
would descend on seven colored clouds
to save me
and take me home.
The palace is Your Highness's home.
Please don't say such things outside.
True.
Since I'm already here,
I have no choice but to keep living on.
Go on. What does
His Majesty want this time?
Wen Ling said His Majesty has urgent
business and must leave the palace.
He asked Your Ladyship
to watch over the Cold Palace
and make sure nothing goes wrong.
As if he's the only busy one.
Always occupied.
Not only do I have to
work endlessly for him,
I even have to look after his woman.
Forget it.
If it weren't for leaving
this miserable place,
who would bother making a deal with him?
Let's go.
We'll take a look at the Cold Palace.
Zhinian, where are you going?
Move aside.
Didn't you ask me to come see you?
Let go of me.
Nian'er, I know how much
you've suffered since childhood.
Move aside.
You want to rise to a higher position.
Let go of me.
I'm willing to help you.
I only ask that you
look at me once more.
Move aside.
I'm warning you.
Well now.
One devoted lover,
one ambitious schemer.
Even I find the two
of you quite well matched.
Your Ladyship, Handan has been poisoned.
I was on my way
to fetch an imperial physician.
Do you know what happens
to discarded concubines who leave
the Cold Palace without permission?
Take Shen Zhinian to the imperial prison.
Lock her up for a few days.
Lady Liu, you can't arrest her!
I serve Dowager Consort Liu.
Don't use the Dowager Consort
to pressure me.
I answer only to His Majesty.
Take Lu Jianglin
to the imperial prison as well.
You...
Your Ladyship,
you claim to be the fairest of all.
Please,
go to the Cold Palace and check on Handan.
Please save her.
Someone, go inspect the Cold Palace.
If anyone is truly stirring up trouble,
I'll personally make them pay for it.
Yes.
Nian'er,
listen to me.
I serve Dowager Consort Liu.
I can definitely
find a way to get you out.
Don't panic.
Behave yourself.
If you hadn't stopped me,
how would Lady Liu have caught me?
If anything happens to Handan today,
I will never forgive you.
Nian'er,
I was framed too.
Someone came to report
that you had urgent matters
to discuss with me.
That's why I came to see you.
I was only worried about you.
Why are you always so cold toward me?
If I held an official post,
you wouldn't treat me this way.
Shouldn't you take
a good look at yourself first?
Your character is disgraceful.
You're heartless and disloyal.
If you truly held office,
would you still even notice me?
Since when did your words
become so harsh and cutting?
Is that how a proper lady should speak?
And a true gentleman
wouldn't continue courting another woman
after getting married.
I...
Lu!
Are you alright?
Why are you here?
The Dowager Consort ordered your release.
Someone!
By order of Dowager Consort Liu,
Shen Zhinian is to receive
the tattoo punishment.
Yes.
Nanqiao, don't!
Don't touch her!
Let go of me!
None of you touch her!
Duke Zhen,
we've waited all day
and His Majesty still
hasn't ordered her release.
Could it be
that you guessed wrong?
Perhaps His Majesty
never truly intended to favor her.
As expected, I was right all along.
His Majesty
must not be in the palace.
Not in the palace?
His Majesty has been searching
for the military tally lately.
He doesn't even have time
for the woman he favors.
That means he's already found clues
to the tally's whereabouts.
Send people to intercept him immediately.
No matter what,
the military tally must be recovered
before he returns to the palace.
Yes.
Hyah!
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪