( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 3=
That's a brutal beating.
This is far too heavy.
She won't be able to walk after this.
Look at all this blood.
Will she be beaten to death?
I doubt she'll even survive.
How pitiful.
We must never offend
the Lady of Bright Deportment.
Pay attention, Ladies.
Whether you become a Noble Lady
or a useless cripple
depends entirely on your own choices.
Cut out her tongue.
Are you here to watch
your owner's punishment?
Shen Zhinian is terrified.
She surely won't go
to the Cold Palace tonight.
She will certainly go.
Dowager Consort Liu always thought
Your Ladyship wasn't ruthless enough.
She's making a point to Your Ladyship.
The palace rules dictate flogging.
But she's using illegal torture.
I'm going to take
the palace rules to her
and read them to her one by one.
Please don't be angry, Your Ladyship.
She is a Dowager Consort
and the Emperor's nominal foster mother.
Even His Majesty defers to her.
Your Ladyship,
I've investigated everything.
Someone planted forbidden
flowers in the Cold Palace.
A large patch
has bloomed in the palace.
Clear them out now.
Yes.
Wait.
Use the flowers as bait.
Let's see who actually planted them.
Have men watch it.
If anyone dares to go to
the Cold Palace tonight,
report back at once.
Yes.
(Cold Palace)
It's already the hour of Zi.
Your Majesty guessed wrong.
She won't be coming tonight.
She actually dared to come.
She has some courage
for taking such a risk.
But she doesn't seem to be coming over.
She's heading toward
where Xu Baoqin is held.
You go back first.
Yes.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here to bring you medicine.
I mean no harm.
I will bribe the guards here.
I won't let you go hungry.
It's so dark in the Cold Palace.
I'll leave this lantern for you.
There's nothing more
I can do.
Take care.
She framed you like that.
Why do you still want to save her?
She was wrong.
But to suffer such cruel torture
is simply too much.
In this palace,
there is no room for your kind heart.
I'm no saint.
I'm just an ordinary person.
I can be soft-hearted,
but I also know how to survive.
Your Ladyship,
I saw someone enter
the Cold Palace with my own eyes.
They are inside right now.
It's over. Quick, hide.
I'd like to see
who is desecrating the palace grounds.
Follow me in and seize them.
(That's strange.)
(Ever since I was poisoned,)
(my internal organs)
(have felt like they
were on fire every day.)
(But holding her hand)
(actually makes me
feel quite comfortable.)
(Let's test her one more time.)
Didn't you want to
learn the art of seduction?
I wonder
where you would like to begin.
(What is he up to?)
(Never mind.)
(I'll just go along with it.)
If I'm to learn,
I want to learn something different.
I'll be on top,
and he'll be on the bottom.
♪You do not know♪
♪The partridge's cry
is full of resentment♪
Senior Attendant Shen,
you are quite bold.
Attendant Li, you said it yourself.
If I want to be seductive,
I can't afford to be timid.
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
Attendant Li, teach me well.
If you do a good job,
you'll be richly rewarded.
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
You clearly know
the ways of men and women.
Why do you still need me to teach you?
Attendant Li, don't you know
that if one serves with beauty,
as beauty fades,
love withers,
and when love withers,
favor ends?
What I want
is for the moon to shine only on me.
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
Emperors have been fickle
since ancient times.
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
Then, I'll just have
to settle for his body.
If I can hold the moon
in my arms every night,
that would be nice too.
You have grand ambitions, huh?
A small token of appreciation.
(Ten Taels of Silver)
Please accept this, Attendant.
Ten taels?
You want to control a man's heart
for only ten taels?
A heart that doesn't shine solely on me
isn't worth much.
"Isn't worth much," huh?
Fine.
I will teach you right now.
Why did you bring me here?
To know your enemy
is to be victorious in every battle.
First, learn to drink.
Drink?
Black Zhen Liquor.
It goes down like fire,
burning the heart and soul.
It is his favorite.
Half qian of Nine-Steamed Spring,
one qian of Amber Settle.
Gaze at Thousand-Mountain Moon,
and have the winter snow once more.
Finally,
add a little Zhen poison.
Zhen poison?
Won't I die if I drink it?
You must control the amount.
With the right amount, you'll feel like
you're floating to heaven.
But if it's too much...
I'll die on the spot.
Have a taste.
(It can't be real Zhen poison.)
(One drop of Zhen poison is lethal.)
(If he wanted to kill me,)
(he wouldn't go
through all this trouble.)
If I were serving liquor to His Majesty,
should I feed him like this?
He won't drink it.
Oh.
What about this?
Your Ladyship,
someone broke into the liquor cellar.
Hurry up and catch them.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Let's go
take a look.
(Bamboo Dew Spring)
Tell me,
who are you?
Why did you come to the palace?
My name is Shen Zhinian.
I entered the palace
to marry the most powerful man
and attain the highest power.
So, it's power you're after.
It's not power.
It's safety.
It's to live a good life.
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
♪Every step is treacherous,
regardless of the world♪
Then, do you know who I am?
Yes.
♪In the palace, through dawn and dusk,
who keeps a lamp burning♪
Nangong Xuanyu.
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪