( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 4=
(Bamboo Dew Spring)
Then do you know
who I am?
Of course I do.
Nangong Xuanyu.
Nangong Xuanyu is the most
powerful
and formidable man in the world.
Oh, yes.
You treated me to wine today.
I'll treat you next time.
We'll drink
flower wine.
Flower wine?
Mm.
Whatever flower you like,
I'll brew wine from it for you.
Magnolia.
Your Ladyship.
Ahead is the wine cellar.
Don't leave me behind.
I'll teach you another lesson.
A wise man stays away from danger.
Jerk.
Didn't you say someone was here?
Where is he?
Your Majesty.
You said touching her
eases the burning pain inside you.
Then why not keep her as a living cure?
That would only worsen the problem.
How did she find out my identity?
Go investigate it thoroughly.
Yes.
I entered the palace
to marry the greatest man
and claim the highest power.
(Shen Zhinian.)
(If you want power,)
(that depends on
whether you have the fate for it.)
(That wine was way too strong.)
(My head hurts so much.)
(What exactly happened last night?)
(Why did I sleep inside a wine vat?)
(Find a eunuch's outfit
for me to change into.)
(I should be able to return
to Tinglan Palace without being noticed.)
Young Master,
there's an injured sparrow over there.
(Jiang Chen,
eldest legitimate son of Duke Zhen)
Let's go.
We'll be late for court.
Take it back and nurse it well.
This young eunuch has a hangover
and caught a chill as well.
I'll prescribe him
some medicine shortly.
Thank you, my lord.
Please, my lord, you mustn't.
It's alright.
Which palace do you serve in?
I'll have someone deliver the medicine
to you later.
There's no need
to trouble yourself, my lord.
I'll come collect it myself.
You're quite fortunate.
Everyone knows
Lord Jiang of the Duke's Manor
has a truly kind heart.
You shouldn't refuse.
Lord Jiang.
(So he's Jiang Chen,
the Duke's eldest son.)
If you're worried about being punished,
I'll escort you back.
That way your mistress
won't make things difficult for you.
Thank you, my lord.
Senior Attendant,
you've finally returned.
What did she call you?
My surname is Chang.
They all call me Eunuch Chang.
Eunuch Chang.
Thank you.
Miss, forget about Lord Jiang for now.
Last night, Fengqi Palace sent word
that you were
to pay respects to the Empress
this morning at chen hour.
Chen hour?
It's already a quarter past chen hour.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Quick.
Prepare the bath and dressing.
(Fengqi Palace)
Greetings, Your Ladyship.
Lady Liu.
Shen Zhinian.
I thought you'd built your own kingdom
and stopped showing up to court.
I would never dare.
I...
I merely caught a chill.
Last night, I already sent word.
If you couldn't come,
why didn't you report it earlier?
On my way here, I became dizzy
and fell.
My clothes were stained with dirt,
so I went back to change.
That's why I arrived late.
The Empress has arrived.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
(Empress Jiang Jin,
eldest legitimate daughter of Duke Zhen)
Be seated.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Senior Attendant Rou is still unwell.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Ladyship oversees the six palaces.
You've worked hard.
His Majesty's
birthday banquet is approaching.
How are the preparations?
Everything has been prepared.
Please review them, Your Majesty.
I'm only worried that
Your Majesty's health is too delicate
to read through so many pages.
All of you may leave.
Senior Attendant Rou stays behind.
Help me
read through this register.
Yes.
Your Ladyship has quite the temper.
Sit for a while before leaving,
lest she makes things difficult for you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Ladyship said
since Senior Attendant Rou is so eager
to ease Her Majesty's burdens,
you are to uproot every flower
in Shanglin Garden
and replace them all
with the peonies Her Majesty favors.
If you fail to finish before sunset,
you will be punished
according to palace rules.
Lord Jiang has arrived.
Your Majesty.
The foreign envoys have all
been settled at Wenhua Inn.
I came to ask whether Your Majesty
wishes to receive them.
You were late today.
I came across a sick young eunuch
in Shanglin Garden
and took him
to the Imperial Medical Bureau.
That's what delayed me.
In this world,
kindness
doesn't always get rewarded.
Since you've chosen to help others,
there's no need to expect gratitude.
Your Majesty.
Duke Zhen requests an audience.
I'll take my leave first.
Otherwise Father will nag at me again.
Greets, Your Majesty.
Rise, Duke.
(Duke Zhen)
Wan Ning entered the palace today
to accompany the Empress.
Your Majesty watched Wan Ning grow up.
I hope you will look after her.
I understand.
More than ten years have flown by.
Back then, Your Majesty
wasn't even as tall as Wan Ning is now.
In those days,
it was me
who personally carried Your Majesty
out of the dog kennel.
Bark like a dog and you'll get food.
No barking, no food.
Hurry and bark.
Duke Zhen saved my life.
I have never forgotten it.
I only hope that Your Majesty and I
will always remain one family.
(Jiang Wanning, Fourth Young Lady
of the Duke's Manor)
(Yuehui Pavilion)
Miss, why don't you rest a bit?
Leave the planting to me.
It's fine.
Let's work faster
and finish before dark.
Sister.
(Whenever Liu Ruyan appears,
nothing good follows.)
Lady Liu.
I heard Your Ladyship punished you
by making you plant flowers.
In the dead of winter,
how can anything grow?
You and I have suffered together before,
so I came to help you.
(Yuehui Pavilion)
Sister.
How do you use this hoe?
Why don't you...
Don't.
Who's there?
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold my heart
into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪