( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Daughter of Fortune=
(Adapted from the novel
"Phoenix Palace Dream" by Lan Jiujiu)
=Episode 5=
(Yuehui Pavilion)
I told you to stop outsiders.
Are you deaf?
Since your ears are so useless,
we might as well cut them off.
Young Lady, have mercy.
Which palace
are you from?
Fourth Young Lady, please calm down.
Ruyan
was just recently bestowed the title
of Lady of Gentleness by His Majesty.
Lady of Gentleness?
You cannot hit me.
My sister is
Lady Liu of Bright Deportment.
So what if she's Lady Liu?
My father is the Duke.
And my sister is the Empress.
Trying to compare status with me?
Who gave you the nerve?
By the Empress's decree,
anyone who disrupts
the grand dance performance
shall be executed immediately.
As for you,
you can add some color
to my green silk.
Hit her harder!
I thought she was something special.
But she can't even
dodge this simple bullying.
Didn't Your Majesty notify the Empress?
Why hasn't Her Majesty arrived yet?
Your Majesty, are you not going
to intervene?
Nangong Xuanyu is the most powerful
and most heroic man
in the world.
I suppose the Empress isn't coming.
Go and tell them to stop.
Lady of Bright Deportment has arrived.
Stop this at once.
It seems I don't need to help.
She can handle the harem on her own.
Jiang Wanning, how dare you use
private torture in the palace?
I...
I have the Jinfeng Token.
How insolent!
You dare to be so arrogant before me?
Today, I'll see exactly
how you plan to hit me.
Forget it.
You aren't worthy of being
handled by me personally.
Someone, come.
Send the Fourth Young Lady Jiang
to the Empress's palace.
What if I refuse to go?
Then I shall invite
the Empress's carriage
here to the Shanglin Garden.
You!
Let's go.
Young Lady...
Thank you, Your Ladyship.
Shen Zhinian,
I saved you this once today.
I might not next time.
Put away your little tricks.
In this palace,
the more schemes you have,
the shorter your life will be.
Liu...
Finally, the planting
is almost finished.
Young Lady,
everyone in this palace is a predator,
ruthless and cruel.
You have such a weak personality.
How are we ever going
to survive in this palace?
It doesn't matter.
These are just superficial wounds.
Come.
There's important
business to take care of.
You're already injured like this.
What else do you need to do?
To vent my anger.
Today's grievance
will be settled today.
Are you alright?
Who is it?
Who's there?
Stop hitting me.
Who is it?
Who's that?
Are you alright, Young Lady?
Why is it always me who gets hurt?
We have no grudge against Liu Ruyan.
Why would she do this?
Women in the palace will
make things difficult for each other
before they gain the Emperor's favor.
If even the Empress
and Lady Liu are like this,
it's even more so for
someone like Liu Ruyan.
Senior Attendant,
a letter was found at the door.
(Jianyue Pavilion,
Shanglin Garden. Zhen.)
(If he hadn't left me alone
in the liquor cellar,)
(none of this would be happening.)
I'm not going.
Your Majesty,
the Empress has removed
her hairpin to plead for mercy.
She brought Jiang Wanning
and has been kneeling for 15 minutes.
Her Majesty's health is already poor.
If she continues to kneel,
I'm afraid her body won't hold up.
If Duke Zhen uses
this to stir up trouble,
Your Majesty might be harassed again.
This kneeling display of hers
isn't meant for me to see.
(Yuehui Pavilion)
I was lenient in disciplining my sister.
She has made a grave mistake.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
I was lenient in disciplining my sister.
She has made a grave mistake.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
His Majesty asks that you return.
This is
Fourth Young Lady Jiang's matter,
and it has nothing to do with you.
I watched her grow up.
If she is at fault,
it means I didn't teach her well.
Your Majesty,
for my sake,
please let Wanning
kowtow and apologize to you.
Your Majesty,
I know my mistake.
I won't dare do it again.
Come in.
Your Majesty...
Whether His Majesty can forgive you
depends on your attitude.
You must apologize sincerely.
Otherwise, even I can't help you,
and you'll have to
return to the Jiang residence.
I can't go back.
Father would beat me to death.
Your Majesty,
I know my mistake.
I beg for Your Majesty's forgiveness.
Your Majesty,
Wanning knows she was wrong.
For my sake and my brother's,
please let Wanning stay by my side.
Let her accompany me
through my final days.
Jiang Wanning,
since the Empress has pleaded for you,
I will forgive you this once.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
It's getting late.
Escort the Empress back to her palace.
I know why Father
wanted you to enter the palace,
but there was no need to be so hasty.
I protected you today,
but I'm afraid His Majesty
won't favor you.
What if
I conceive an imperial child?
With just you?
Without me,
you couldn't even get near him.
You were near him,
yet you haven't given
birth to a single child.
You...
Fourth Young Lady Jiang,
Her Majesty is so ill,
yet she stayed up
this late for your sake.
Instead of being grateful,
you're upsetting Her Majesty.
I can no longer control you.
Shun,
let's go.
(I put a whole bottle
of Love Potion in it.)
(I don't believe)
(the Emperor can resist it.)
The tea is drugged.
What audacity.
I'm here to serve Your Majesty.
Your Majesty...
Jiang Wanning,
for your insubordination,
you are expelled from the palace.
You shall never set foot
in the palace again.
Your Majesty,
come back!
♪Moon sets on palace walls,
breeze hits the gates♪
Your Majesty.
♪Falling at first sight,
a life of turmoil wasted♪
♪Dim lamps, concerns unheard by anyone♪
♪All the spring colors
lean toward one person♪
♪Faint rouge hides
the tenderness in the eyes♪
Your Majesty.
♪Flowers wither easily,
but obsession remains♪
♪The world is gentle
only because of you♪
♪In the palace, through dawn and dusk,
who keeps a lamp burning♪
♪Time silently scars those left behind♪
♪Broken dreams,
listening to the light rain♪
♪Bitter cold, bringing mist to the eyes♪
♪If we don't meet♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall in shame♪
♪If we meet again,
the peaches will be warm♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
dancing through the years♪
♪Brewing longing,
remembering past lives♪
♪Hard to meet, and just as hard to part♪
♪Who planted the beans
that grew into lotuses?♪
♪Spring breeze passes,
composing the fleeting years♪
♪Clouds on Mount Wu,
no sails on the sea♪
♪Wanting to fold
my heart into a paper kite♪
♪But the ties are too tangled to sever♪