[slow-building,
intriguing music]
[reel clicks softly]
[Ben Snow & Voltage's
"Out in the Streets" plays,
a reggae/techno remix]
[reggae beats grow in volume]
♪ Out in the street,
they call it...
[high-octane techno]
[reggae beats] ♪ Out in
the street, they call it--
[high-octane techno]
[reggae beats] ♪ Out
in the street, they call it
[reggae beats
blend into techno]
♪ They call it... ♪
[man shouts,
muffled by the music]
Woah, woah, woah!
- Wait, stop!
- [music stops]
- Get Garry!
- What?
Oh, fuck.
Fucking hell.
[low, intriguing music]
- What's up, Clareese?
- You should see this.
Jeez, where is that?
Building site in
the Paddington Basin.
Ooh.
[tense flourish]
[alarm blares]
[alarm cuts out, gunshot]
[gunshot]
[slow, tense music]
[phone buzzes]
We've got UXO in Westminster.
I'm just sending you
through the pictures now.
World War II,
looks like a thousand pounder.
We'll need an 800
meter radius perimeter.
- SOLDIERS: Morning, sir.
Morning, sir.
- Morning.
And I'll need you
there as liaison, Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
Oh, and by the way,
Norris called in sick,
so we've got
Corporal Hanson standing in.
Aren't we lucky?
Might even learn a thing or two.
Get the police
onto the evacuation right away.
I'll head there now.
I'll see you on the dance floor.
We need to get onto Westminster
City Council Emergency Planning,
Transport Police and TFL.
- Yes.
- And the Mayor.
[slow, tense music continues]
[sirens blare]
POLICEWOMAN [on megaphone]:
Everyone to Hyde Park,
quickly and calmly.
This area is being evacuated.
Please make your
way calmly to Hyde Park.
Ah, ah, ah!
POLICEWOMAN:
This area is being evacuated.
POLICEMAN: You can
take your coats with you.
If you can just make your way
down the stairs for me,
please, guys.
An old bomb's been discovered
on a building site nearby.
We're evacuating.
[knocks]
POLICEMAN [through door]:
This area is being evacuated.
Nice and calm, everybody.
Thank you.
[tense flourish]
POLICEMAN: Please leave
the area as quickly as possible.
Yes, I completely
understand that, sir.
We're shutting down
the whole square mile.
It's nothing personal.
[in Pashto]:
[policewoman continues
orders over megaphone]
Stay in touch, bro.
BOTH: See ya.
- Look after them.
- Yeah.
WOMAN [in Pashto]:
[intriguing music]
Thank you very much, sir.
Corporal.
Hi, I'm Gary, I'm the foreman.
I can show you, mate.
Just over here.
Right. Okay.
Need a better vantage point.
Is that building safe?
Yes, man.
Okay.
Could it, like, blow any minute?
Theoretically, yes.
[slow, tense music]
We'll need to get that drained,
Corporal.
Yes, sir.
Is that your cabin?
- Yeah.
- Mind if we use it?
- Help yourself.
- Thanks, Gary. You can go now.
- Thank Christ.
- Right, we'll make that
our ICP.
So I want to get some protection
built 'round it.
Sappers to go behind there
and we'll meet with the suits
in the ICP.
[chatter]
Hold on, sir. Slow down, slow
down. Where are you off to?
I, erm, I have to get my laptop.
- Straight on, straight on.
- Sorry.
Sir? Sir?
Where are you going?
Come back!
We've got a resident
running down the street.
I said--
Oh, God.
So this is the same size of bomb
as the controlled explosion
in Exeter two years ago.
As you can see, if it
blows before we contain it,
you'll be very glad the cordon
was in place.
Hardeep Gill, Westminster
Council Emergency Planning.
Sorry I'm late, the traffic.
Is this a big bomb,
like, like a biggie?
- Yes, it is.
- Oh, God.
Well, running right under
the building site here,
there's a 400
kilovolt mains cable.
We're going to have to cut off
the power around the whole area
- until the bomb is neutralized.
- Right.
I want the power off
for as short as possible.
- Of course.
- Chief Superintendent.
It'd be good to get access
to relevant police comms
around the cordon.
No problem.
Sergeant Keane
will stay in close contact.
Right. Thank you, Major.
Yeah, I'll try to make things
as smooth as possible.
Break a leg.
Or whatever you guys say.
Don't be shit.
That's what we say.
[chatter]
[slow, tense music continues]
[on megaphone]:
This area has been evacuated.
If you can hear
this announcement,
please make yourself known
to us immediately.
[police announcements
continue outside]
[engine rattles]
[chatter, phone ringing]
[selection tone]
[music intensifies]
WILL: It's definitely a 500.
Can't tell from here
if it's an SD or an SC, so...
- Hanson, Wardy.
- Yeah?
Let's get the fucking
water out, can we?
BOTH: Sir.
- Here you are, take that.
- What fucking good
would that do?
Protect your ego.
[she chuckles]
- Right. You ready?
- Sir.
Well go on, then.
And don't be shit.
On my way, sir.
[tense music continues]
[engine rattles]
[music fades into silence]
[electrical fizz]
[distant alarms]
Right, that'll be
the mains shut down.
[alarms blare loudly]
[slow, tense music resumes]
This is
Sergeant Keane reporting.
We have started pumping water
from around the bomb.
[on radio]: We'll report back
when we make our next step.
Roger that.
Cordon secure.
You are authorized to proceed.
Nothing's moving.
[music intensifies]
[beeps on]
[metal clatters, he grunts]
[engine hums]
We're on.
[beeps on]
[music quickens and intensifies]
Tony, take it a bit lower.
Thanks.
Hold it there, Tony.
Go to thermal.
Switch back.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
It's a fucking fox.
[whistles, they stop hammering]
[he grunts loudly]
[sledgehammer blows continue]
[muffled and distant
hammering continues]
- All right, mate?
- Got alarms going off
in shops on Edgware Road,
- need to check 'em.
- They're going off
everywhere, mate.
The power's been cut.
Whole place has been evacuated
for an old bomb.
What, so I can't
get through at all?
It's shut down everywhere.
There's nothing I can do.
- All right, cheers.
- All right.
BOTH: Thanks, mate. Okay.
[slow, tense music]
That's water drained, sir.
Good.
- [Martin clears his throat]
- All right, don't get your
knickers in a twist.
It's not for now.
It's a little tradition of mine
for when we're done.
I'm not gonna force you.
[Will breathes heavily]
You okay?
Yeah.
I think we might need
that clockstopper.
- Sir.
- Right.
Do you know what that is?
- Yes, I do, sir.
Checked it on Monday.
- Right, yeah.
- Do you know where you put it?
- Yeah.
- All right, go fucking get it,
then.
- Aye, sir.
- [they pant]
- Fucking hell.
G.
[loud scratching]
Alpha Hotel Two Seven,
do a quick sweep
of the cordon, please.
[on radio]:
Roger that, Gold.
I just need your signature
on this please, ma'am.
Thank you.
[on radio]:
Stop the work.
Got a drive by.
Fuck.
- Is there anything out there?
- There's nothing
going on out here.
It looks like the apocalypse.
- You definitely
got everything up, yeah?
- Yes, ma'am.
[tense music continues]
Just a routine check.
Carry on.
[loud scratching continues]
All right, get the stethoscope
- as close as you can.
- Sir.
- Just leave it down
there for me.
- Aye, sir.
Don't be shit, sir.
The Major is at the bomb
and ready to assess
the condition of the fuze.
Checking all clear?
Alpha Hotel Two Seven?
Leave the cordon immediately.
EOD are starting work.
[on radio]: Roger that, Gold,
we're on our way.
All right there,
Doots? Can you hear me?
DOOTS [on radio]:
Just doing
the final check, sir.
Ready when you are.
[airhorn blares]
There we go.
Right, there's the impact fuze.
12 o' clock. Aluminum.
Not rotted away. Transit plug.
Oh, fucking hell.
That's a bit more complicated.
[music intensifies]
Right. Do you hear that, Doots?
Time fuze.
Attaching mic steth.
[metallic ticking]
Fucking hell, it's ticking.
Clear! Hard cover, now!
Hard cover!
Move, move, move!
Unexpected development.
There's a second fuze
and a timer.
And it's active.
These were designed to create
maximum terror and confusion.
It could detonate any minute
for the next 48 hours.
WILL: Deploying clockstopper!
The Major will deploy
a magnetic clockstopper
to inhibit the fuze.
[he grunts and groans]
[music intensifies]
[grunts]
Oh fuck.
Nobody fucking move!
Heads down!
Right, Corporal, green light!
Brace, brace, brace!
Switching on!
[switch clicks; music cuts out]
[magnetic hum]
[ticking stops, they pant]
[she sighs relieved]
Right, all clear!
Corporal, start
building that mitigation wall!
- Jump up, mate.
- Get back to it.
The timer has been stopped and
the bomb made temporarily safe.
So now we're going
to build the mitigation wall
for a controlled explosion.
This can take up to five hours.
So it would be great
if we could get some pizza in.
[radio cuts out]
[loud scratching continues]
[scratching stops]
- X [on radio]: We hit steel.
- Copy.
[they grunt]
[gentle music; horses trot]
[in Pashto]:
[in English]: Beautiful horses.
[machine rattles]
[tense music resumes]
Didn't really know what to get,
so we kind of just got
everything on the menu.
WILL: Ta.
[clicks]
DOOTS: What is Martin doing?
[air horn blares]
Everyone out.
[exasperated]: All right,
what's going on, Corporal?
There's
something weird here, sir.
Go on, then.
There's a shiny bit
on the bomb casing
where the rust came off.
Probably where
the digger hit it.
It's over 80 years old,
so the whole thing
should be rust, right?
Oh, not necessarily.
It's got an active time fuze,
so it's
obviously well preserved.
It's quite the anomaly.
[music fades]
WILL [shouts]: Back to work!
[metal clangs loudly]
[tense music resumes]
[shakes paint cannister]
- X [on radio]: G?
- Yes?
We're in.
[grunts]
Fuck yes!
Too heavy.
Cash and light jewelry, only.
Wardy.
- Like it's brand new.
- That's weird.
[intriguing music]
Sir, I really think you should
come and have a look at this.
MARTIN: Sorry
to keep mentioning this, sir.
[clack]
[metallic ticking]
- [air horn blares]
- Shall we--
It's fucking ticking!
All right, cover, now!
Go, go, go!
Wardy, move it. Kris, let's go!
Go, go! Get your head down.
It just started ticking
about 10 seconds ago.
Clockstopper's malfunctioned.
Power's still working.
Well, something
clearly isn't, is it?
Go get the S-SET, Corporal.
[tense music builds]
WILL: Put it there.
- Right, Method J.
- Are you sure, sir?
What choice have I got, Doots?
- Permission to speak, s--
- No.
Get your fucking head
down.
Control, the timer fuze is
active again
and the bomb is no
longer stable.
The Major will drill the fuze
then apply a solution to clog
the mechanism.
This is our last option.
Understood.
[he grunts]
[he breathes heavily]
Right, Doots.
I'm starting to drill.
- [metallic ticking]
- Right, that's
the drilling commenced.
[he breathes heavily]
Ma'am, look at this.
This is the drone's POV.
This is where the bomb guys are.
They have a generator running
to power their equipment,
so I assume that
hotspot is theirs.
So what's that?
The electricity
is cut in the area.
That-- that shouldn't be there.
[generator hums]
[metallic ticking]
[breathes heavily]
[holds his breath]
[resumes breathing heavily]
[music fades]
[grunts]
[grunts, loud bang]
[tense music resumes]
Ma'am?
EOD! Stop the operation.
Stop? Can you
confirm we are to stop, ma'am?
Confirm stop.
[air horn blasts]
Hold the fucking drilling!
[exasperated]:
Are you fucking kid--
That is a hold on drilling.
Can we have some more
information, please?
We detected a heat signature
inside the cordon.
We need to investigate.
We think people
could still be there.
Right. The police have detected
an unidentified heat source.
[metallic ticking]
Chief Superintendent,
what's going on?
Sorry, Major,
but we've had to send a car in.
We'll relay police radio now
to keep you in the loop.
WILL: I'm in the middle
of a very dangerous procedure.
I haven't even finished
the mitigation wall.
Which means if
the bomb detonates,
I don't even have to tell you
how bad that's gonna be.
I understand, Major, but we
can't risk injury
to the public.
We'll be as quick as we can.
[music intensifies]
[grunts]
[safe deposit box
opens and closes]
[safe deposit boxes swings open]
[drill squeaks]
[man behind grunts]
Got you.
- Is that it?
- Yeah.
Hey, put it on the trolley.
Huh?
All right.
[he grunts]
[metallic ticking]
WILL [shouts]: Corporal!
Get into hard cover now.
Get in!
Right, explain yourself.
Clockstopper malfunctioned,
sir, it's my responsibility.
You're risking your life
next to a live ordinance.
That's fucking ticking.
I mean, what are you thinking?
- Mate, it's a bit of kit,
all right?
- Mhm.
It's not worth your life.
Stay in hard cover, will you?
Please?
[music intensifies]
Cops, cops, cops!
Quiet as fucking mice.
[generator hums]
[generator stops humming]
POLICEMAN:
This is Alpha Hotel Three Two.
We're commencing
the search of Portlea Place.
No suspicious activity so far.
Just checking entrance now.
All right, entrance is locked.
We're going to check
the surrounding area.
[metallic ticking]
Just fucking tick, tick, tick.
All right, boys,
let's get a move on. Quietly.
The heat signature
seems to have disappeared.
[sighs]
ZUZANA: Major, stand by
for clearing the cordon
and then you
can get back to work.
Alpha Hotel Three Two.
Exit the cordon as soon as
you've completed your check.
[metallic ticking continues;
tense music]
Oh, excuse me, sir.
You can't be back here.
The whole area's been evacuated.
It isn't safe, sir, can you come
back towards here please?
Sir? Oi!
Stop!
Cops are here!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
[music intensifies]
Nah, it's all locked.
Get the bolt cutters.
- Yeah.
- Sir!
POLICEMAN [on radio]:
Non-compliant white male
running inside Portlea House.
We're attempting entry.
Dump your tools.
Get the fuck out of there.
- [metallic ticking continues]
- I've got
a bad feeling about this.
Go get your fucking helmet on.
Put it on!
Police cordon's been breached.
There's nothing we can do.
Just get your head down.
Cover your ears.
This thing could go any second.
- Get that, Earl?
- Yes, sir!
Cover your ears!
- Yes.
- Right, watch your hand.
[music intensifies]
[metal snaps]
Doots, get on the deck, now!
POLICEMAN [on radio]: Entering
the back gate now. In pursuit.
[music crescendos;
metallic ticking stops]
[music fades]
Ticking stopped!
[silence]
[loud, rumbling explosion]
Get ba--
[grunts]
- [glass shatters]
- [grunts]
Shit!
[low rumble]
[worried chatter]
[shocked silence]
[animated chatter]
[groans]
- Alright, alright?
- Yeah.
Corporal! Head count!
We're all good, sir!
- Eazzi?
- All right, Boss.
Doots!
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
[intriguing music]
I need to see the bag.
- It's in here, sealed.
- I need to check the gear,
come on.
- The cops are out there!
- What? You don't trust me?
It doesn't matter about
the fucking cops.
They're out back.
The car's empty.
[car alarms blare]
Mate, you okay? Newman?
NEWMAN: I think
I broke my ribs there.
Happy?
Very happy.
Stick to the plan.
X: Yeah, you too, dickhead.
Requesting backup.
This is an active message.
PC Newman is injured.
Get an ambulance there now.
EOD, are you receiving me? Over.
This is Gold.
Are you receiving me? Over.
DOOTS [on radio]:
EOD here. We're all okay.
Just... a bit shaken.
Glad to hear your voice.
Cordon, injuries.
There's n-- no major injuries
to report here.
Wha-- what about
in the cordon?
ZUZANA [on radio]: One
of the officers in the cordon
is injured.
Awaiting confirmation on
any non-compliant individuals.
[tense music]
Hurry up!
[pants]
Ah fuck.
[they breathe heavily]
You alright?
[music intensifies]
[they grunt]
Joel, can you bring that one up
and play it back?
CLAREESE: Maybe they were
working underground and didn't
hear the warnings?
Find the exact location
and send someone out there.
Yes, ma'am.
- Go, go, go!
- It's not working.
- What do you mean?
- That's not working.
What do you mean
it's not working?
What's going on here?
- Fuck. Swap, okay?
- All right.
Sometimes this happens,
all right? The blades stick.
I'll take yours, you take mine.
Right, now box.
- You okay, my friend?
- Yeah.
[drone buzzes]
- Okay, I'm up.
- Good.
[music intensifies]
Okay. Alright.
- [drones buzz overhead]
- ZUZANA: Stay with him.
The ambulance is on its way.
Yeah, soon as you can.
Look. Come on, man.
The bomb's gone off.
- There's no threat.
- Sir, I understand,
but you have to wait
- a little bit longer, okay?
- Oh, fuck.
[dramatic music swells and ebbs]
[he grunts]
[tense, pulsating music]
Going down.
G: Let's go!
Ambulance is on its way, mate.
- Can I go? Can I go after 'em?
- Yeah. Go, go...
Go, go, go!
Run, run, run, run!
[brakes squeal]
[pulsating music intensifies;
sirens sound]
POLICEMAN [on radio]:
This is Alpha Hotel Two Seven.
Men seen running
out of Portlea House.
We're in pursuit.
ZUZANA [on radio]:
Get me SCO19 on the line.
- We need to stand up
some firearms.
- Right away...
[brakes squeal and echo]
Take us back! Take us back!
[pulsating music continues]
[wet, squelching footsteps]
POLICEMAN:
Approaching the tent...
- You good?
- Yeah, we're good
but police turned up.
- We stick to the plan, yeah?
- Yep.
[radio beeps]
Shh, shh! Quiet, quiet!
Torch, radio off.
[wet, squelching footstep]
This way.
POLICEMAN: Follow me.
[splashing footsteps]
G: In here, quick!
POLICEMAN: Check down there.
[music ebbs]
POLICEMAN: Clear!
- G, where are you?
- Two minutes left and we go...
- Last thing we need...
- ...with or without them.
That's what we agreed.
G, come in! Come in,
we've gotta go, G.
[intriguing, foreboding music]
Fuck! Fucking...
Get off me, man!
Get the fuck off me! Fuck!
Thanks, lads! Me water's
back on again. Nice one.
Enjoy the cake.
I made it for ya.
- The cake's for us?
- Meself, yeah.
- Here, take this, alright?
- Thank you. Cheers.
A little something.
It's all good.
It's open. Let's go!
Fuck it. Go.
Clear!
Hate to bang on, sir.
And I don't wanna
step out of line, but...
perhaps they should test the
explosive chemical signature.
They don't test
World War II bombs, Corporal.
'Cause there's
nothing there to test.
That's my point, sir.
I'm not 100% sure it was
a World War II bomb.
When I was down there,
I could see that the level
of corrosion doesn't match up
to anything that
we've seen in training.
Maybe we won't find a taggant
but we might be able
to trace it back to somewhere.
- We might even see
if there's any...
- Okay, okay.
We'll send it up the line for
further investigation. Alright?
That's one for the police.
There's no harm in checking.
[laughs skeptically]
Fucking hell.
[foreboding music; he pants]
- Major Tranter here.
- Go ahead, Major.
One of our team noticed
some possible anomalies
with the bomb
that you might wanna check out.
ZUZANA: I'm sorry,
what anomalies?
Well, we're not really sure,
so forensics should help, but...
it's possible
it may not have been
a genuine 1940s bomb.
I don't understand.
Nor do I to be honest.
So, I recommend
you swab the explosive residue
for any chemical signature.
Post-detonation, our work here
is technically finished,
bar our clean up and debriefing,
so it's over to you guys now.
Right.
Thanks. We'll take it from here.
Disconnecting police comms now.
Be in touch if anything else
comes up.
[foreboding music resumes]
Oh, fuck!
[tense, pulsating music]
Y, are you there? Y?
Alpha Whiskey
Three Four Five Eight, control.
I'm in the basement
at 11 Portlea House.
There's a massive hole been
drilled into the wall
of the cellar,
leading through into the vault
of a bank
next to Portlea House
on Edgware Road.
I think someone robbed the bank
during the evacuation.
Repeat,
I'm reporting a bank robbery.
Excuse me.
Active message.
It appears there's been
a massive bank job
on Edgware Road.
I repeat,
a bank job on Edgware Road.
[sirens blare]
[helicopter whirs]
[in Pashto]:
Checkpoint A:
Westway and Royal Oak.
Checkpoint B: Maida Vale
and Sutherland Avenue.
[sirens blare, police whistles]
Checkpoint C: Edgware Road
and Bayswater Road.
[tense music]
G [on radio]: Come in, copy.
Yes! Yes! Where are you?
Portobello Road and er,
Westbourne Grove.
- Meet 'em by the Westway, yeah?
- You're on, okay, go to the
bottom of Portobello Road...
- Say, "Under the Westway".
- Under the Westway.
[music intensifies]
[train rattles]
Here, here.
- G: Christ.
- X: You stink, man! What did
you do, go for a swim in it?
Open a window.
Fuck I can taste it! Go on!
[panting]: Let's
move the boxes to the back.
[music ebbs]
- There you go.
- What the fuck's that?
X: Cake.
Happy birthday to me,
eh? Come on...
Oh, you mean this one?
You wanna check it again?
I don't want to check it.
I don't want--
If we get pulled over,
I don't want to fucking see
it in the front.
Thank you very much.
[under his breath]:
That was too fucking close.
X: Fuck it.
Slow down, slow down.
Oh, fucking showtime.
Shit. That way's done. Cut off.
Ah, we've just been working in
the sewer, boys.
Got the stench to prove it.
How're you doing?
Where you going to today?
- X: Where's the paperwork?
- I've got the papers here...
Here.
Off you go.
POLICEMAN ON RIGHT: Morning,
sir. Step outside the vehicle.
Thank you very much.
Smells lovely in here, don't it?
It's been a busy day.
[tense music swells]
Excuse me, ma'am.
Look...
London Water logo.
Get that out to all units.
- Go, Clareese...
- Press Office needs something
on new developments.
- No, not yet.
- Okay.
I need to see the crime scene.
[tense, pulsating music]
[power drill whirs]
MAN [on radio]: Be on the
lookout for anything with
a London Water logo on it.
Checkpoint Foxtrot here.
I think we let a water van
through
a couple of minutes ago,
heading west.
[muffled cheers]
- [they cheer loudly]
- Yes, come on!
[muffled cheers;
tense music continues]
Woo!
You fuckin' beauty!
Fuck, yeah!
[tense music fades out]
[cameras click]
Thanks.
Clareese...
I need to know the names
of the owners of all flats
at Portlea House.
I'm especially
interested in flat 79.
Boss!
Afternoon, Colonel.
Thank you, Corporal.
This is CFA General Minton.
Afternoon, General.
[grunts]
Major Tranter. I'm the EOD
operator on site today.
It could be hours
before they let anyone in.
We've got a flight at 6.
Can we just go get our bags?
We're just at Portlea House.
Just round the corner.
Sorry, you live
at Portlea House?
- Yeah.
- Okay, you have
to come with me.
- Why?
- We just need
a witness statement
because of an incident
at your address.
Okay? Under you come.
[in Pashto]:
You can bring your family, sir.
- What flat number
were you again?
- 79.
Okay.
[on radio]: We have someone
who lives at Portlea House.
They live in flat 79.
Why didn't you immediately
report your concerns?
Sir, with respect, they were
more the corporal's concerns.
I was concentrating on trying
to make the bomb safe.
Still, you
should have reported it.
But we know you're reluctant
to involve superiors
when it comes to decision
making, Major Tranter.
I was briefed
about you on the way here.
Your past
insubordination was mentioned,
but also the fact that you lost
some colleagues under difficult
circumstances.
Let's stick to the question,
shall we?
Could you have reported
the anomaly earlier?
I was in a Category A situation
next to a live 500
kilogram bomb.
That was my priority, sir.
Police forensics have arrived.
Let's see what they come
up with.
- Thank you, Major.
- Yes, sir.
- Carry on.
- Thank you, sir.
[intriguing music]
[music fades]
[in Pashto]:
[phone rings]
POLICEWOMAN: We're interviewing
the family whose storage unit
- was used in the robbery.
- Be there in a minute.
Fresh clothes.
Put your radios, your overalls,
all your stinky shit down here
and I'll burn it with the van.
You want us to strip off here?
[chuckles]
Don't be shy!
I like gold,
bro, what can I say?
Just something for me mum.
Cheeky fuck.
There you go, mate.
[low-key tense music]
They don't have a translator
but their son speaks really
good English.
[they argue in Pashto]
Water, anyone?
[she cries]
No thanks.
[in Pashto]:
So, it appears your apartment
may have been connected
to a crime.
Would you know
anything about that?
No.
Sorry, sorry. What keys?
Okay, so these two men,
they showed up at our door.
They were wearing blue overalls
and they had all of these
papers from the landlord.
And they said they wanted
the keys to the cellar.
They wanted to put some building
equipment or something there.
And we-- we gave them the keys.
Mr. Ka-- Kazza-- Mm... Sorry,
I don't know how to say this.
Just call me Rahim, it's fine.
Rahim, did they keep the keys?
Yeah, yeah, they kept the keys.
My dad told me
not to give them the keys...
My dad told me not
to give them the keys,
but, miss, like,
how was I supposed to know it's
anything dodgy?
We're immigrants here.
People come with official
papers and we do what they say.
They asked for the keys,
so I-- I gave them the keys.
I was, I-- I had no idea
it was something...
- [mother sobs]
- I understand. I understand.
[they argue in Pashto]
We've lost the water van,
and no more sightings
and nothing from ANPR.
Okay. Release the cordons
and stand down the VCPs.
Copy that.
You can all go back in now.
[indignant chatter]
Thank you very much.
Okay. Thank you.
[low-key tense music]
What the fuck are these?
These...
are premium uncut diamonds.
How did you know
which box they'd be in?
What does it matter?
X: Well,
he's the diamond guy, right?
It's a family thing.
We've been mining
these fuckers for generations.
So, why are you robbing banks?
Families are complicated, eh?
Y: Looks like
a piece of glass, that.
G: Because they are uncut.
It means they aren't traceable.
But once they're cut,
we could be
looking at 30 million.
- Seriously?
- Mhm.
Even split, yeah?
Would you mind if
I go call my fence?
- I won't be long.
- Okay.
Does anyone want a beer?
- Yeah, definitely bruv.
- Yeah.
[shouts]: Get the fuck down
on the ground!
- Fuck you!
- Get the fuck down!
Come on!
[shouting, commotion]
[shotgun blast, Y whimpers]
[tense music]
[driver yells]
Shit...
Get up.
Fucking piece of shit!
Fuck you! Fucking...
You're a cunt!
You're fucking dead!
G: I can't stay long, Ludo.
[low-key tense music continues]
No rum today then, boss?
Well, Corporal Hanson
doesn't approve.
It's not my call,
sir. It's fine.
Alright, well go and get some
cups before he changes his
mind, yeah.
- Lads, getting a drink.
- You sure? I don't wanna make
you feel uncomfortable.
- MARTIN: No, boss.
- You haven't got
your notebook out?
It's not one for the records?
[Doots laughs]
Cups.
- Let's go.
- Alright.
Sweet.
- There you go.
- Cheers.
Right. Thanks lads.
Thanks everyone.
A little toast,
to absent friends.
ALL: Absent friends.
Good job today.
Wardy.
Cheers, sir.
It was, er, good
to work with you today, sir.
Cheers, Martin.
Yeah, well done, mate.
[in Pashto]:
Here.
My dear cousin. Yamas.
Yamas.
Well done.
[grunts]
[Y pants]
Stay with us.
I fucking never
trusted that guy.
Yeah, you've been cleared
to go up into your apartment.
But just so you know,
there's no electricity in
the whole area.
[in Pashto]:
What about the lift?
You good, yeah?
Yeah. Just one more.
- Do you want to rest here?
- No, no. Keep going. Yeah.
How much are they really worth?
I'm not sure yet.
Maybe, 4.2... I hope.
Come on.
What? You don't believe me?
[low-key tense music]
How did you know
there were diamonds in the bank?
That's my job.
So, you know whose diamonds
you stole, huh?
- Uh-huh.
- Whose?
A man I used to work for.
A man I don't like very much.
Why?
Because he tried to kill me.
Really? Why?
You want to know?
We had a good deal going.
I would fly into conflict zones,
pick up under-the-radar stones.
I would smuggle them out on
my person.
Deposit them in the bank.
And then for some reason...
he decided to fuck me.
So, I'm fucking him back.
So, this one was up in your ass?
Not that one.
So, can I keep it?
Fine. Take it.
Can I have another one?
We had a deal, alright?
You... you paid for the job,
and I pay you back with
a fuck-ton of interest,
alright? Don't get greedy.
Are you going to tell me
how much this is really worth?
What, what do you know
about diamonds, huh? Nothing.
Do you know how to move them?
To cut them? To sell them
on the black market?
No, you don't
know a fucking thing.
So, leave the diamonds to me.
[music intensifies]
I've changed my mind.
I'll take 50% of everything.
That wasn't the arrangement,
alright?
You keep all of this,
and I keep the stones.
That was the agreement.
50% is fair.
- That's not fair, alright.
- This is fair.
- That's not fucking fair!
- Yeah.
- You did fuck-all for this!
- No, no. 50%. 50%!
No 50%!
50%!
The hardest
substance on Earth, huh?
Wait, no...
You fuck!
[pants]
They're fake.
They're all fucking fake.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
[pants]
[tense music continues]
This guy you worked for.
He changed
the real gems with the fakes.
Because he knew
you were coming, right?
They must have fucking...
fucking followed me
or bugged my phone or, or...
got into my fucking emails.
One of those guys
must know something. Alright?
One of those
guys knows something.
You are fucking me somehow,
but I don't know how.
I'm not fucking you, man.
Alright? I swear to you.
You're lying to me.
I'm not lying to you, man.
- Take him.
- I'm not lying to you, man.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait! Wait, wait!
Don't! Listen to me!
Wait! Fuck!
Wait, wait, wait!
Listen to me!
So these... all these are fake?
No, no, no. You've seen it,
man. You've seen it.
This is all real!
No...
Left.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Wait! Wait! You know me, man!
We're family, alright?
You know me!
[pants]
- Please. Please.
- You're fucking me somehow.
No, no, no, no!
I'm not fucking you, man!
No! Fuck!
[G sobs]
- Fuck!
- You're still
not telling the truth.
Look at me.
I swear, man. I swear
on my-- I swear on my life.
I don't know
where the stones are.
- Right.
- No, no! No, you fuck!
You motherfucker! Fuck! No!
No!
Okay.
It's okay.
Let's take him to the workshop.
No, no! Fuck you... Ludo! Ludo!
Fuck! Wait!
Fuck! Ludo!
Ludo! Man,
you don't need to do this!
Z: You're fucking dead, G!
You're dead, you hear me!
Dead!
Ludo, listen to me, man!
I'm not getting in there, man.
Fuck that! Fuck you!
[Z continues
to shout in distance]
G: Fuck!
- Ludo!
- You shouldn't have lied to me.
Ludo! Ludo!
Fucking hell!
- What about the others?
- Z [in distance]:
I'm gonna find you
and fucking kill you!
No, I want
to talk to them later.
- Z: You're fucking dead,
you slag!
- G [in trunk]: Ludo!
I don't know
where they fucking are!
Ludo, man! Listen to me!
- Z: Come back!
- G: Ludo!
Ow!
Colonel Headley?
This is Chief Superintendent
Zuzana Greenfield.
I've just received the results
of the bomb site soil tests.
Right.
Understood.
[phone buzzes]
Fuckin' hell...
- Colonel.
- Major. The police called.
The results
are back from forensics.
It was not a
Second World War bomb.
The chemical signature
is clear and traceable.
- To where, sir?
- To us, to the army.
It's a fucking nightmare.
Report tomorrow
at zero seven hundred.
Sir.
[tense music]
[Y groans]
[snaps, X grunts]
[blood squelches]
- Fuck!
- Help him!
Oh, God...
You alright? Hey...
Jumpstart the van.
Go on.
Fucking losing him, bruv!
[engine starts]
Ah, yes!
Alright.
[bangs door]
[revs furiously]
[van wheels squeal
and bangs door]
Fucking pump it!
You'll be okay, man.
[music turns somber]
I'm sorry, bro.
You put a tracker on him?
Yeah. I put 'em
in all your new clothes.
Don't trust any of you cunts.
[engine starts]
[crows caw]
Ludo, listen to me, man!
I'm not fucking you, alright?
Just pull the fucking car over!
We'll talk, okay?
We'll have a fucking
conversation, alright man?
[G bangs the trunk]
Ludo!
[grunts]
[low-key tense music]
[sawing]
[door opens]
[distant chatter]
All good?
[music intensifies]
CLAREESE: Ma'am.
The owner of flat 79's nephew
was kicked out of the family
firm nine years ago.
And he has previous,
both here and abroad.
I'm sending it through now.
Yes, sir. The company
that has the lease on the flats
is owned
by the uncle of this man,
Giorgos,
AKA George Karalis.
He did six months
in Pentonville.
His previous was in Belgium
for theft and diamond smuggling.
[clicks button,
clockstopper whirs]
That's new.
I'd like to speak to Chief
Superintendent Greenfield.
Our equipment has
been tampered with.
Thank you very much, sir.
Have a great flight.
Thank you.
G: Ludo! You know me!
We're fucking family, alright?!
You remember that shit?
I've known you since you were
fucking ten years old,
- man, alright?
- Put some music.
G: Pull the car over
and we'll talk about it?
[classical song plays]
Ludo! You fucking
greasy motherfucker!
- [loud classical song plays]
- G: Don't fucking
do this to me!
Ludo!
[intense operatic music]
Shit!
Go!
Get in front! Get in front!
X: Get out!
Fuck!
Huh? You!
Z: Fucking hell! Careful!
[music ends abruptly; silence]
[gunshot]
[two gunshots]
Shit... Fuck!
[grunts]
[trunk opens]
How are you, bruv?
- [speaks indistinctly]
- [panting]
Hey, boys!
Am I glad to see you both, hey.
Hey, listen, man.
I'm sorry, alright.
They fucking set me up,
so they could get the diamonds.
Fuck you! Fuck you, man!
Fuck you! Listen, you dumb fuck!
Listen to me!
I don't have the fucking things!
What did you
think was gonna happen?
Listen...
[tense music]
[gasps]
[gunshot]
[gunshot, tire deflates]
[tire deflates]
[music turns intriguing]
[tense music]
Gotcha!
To all airports,
international train terminals,
passport officials:
Giorgos Karalis. 30s. White.
Known to be traveling on
either a Maltese or
South African passport.
To be arrested, immediately.
[jewelry clinks,
driver laughs]
[tense music]
Hi there. Mackenzie, 229.
I'm afraid I forgot my key.
Okay. Of course Mr. Mackenzie.
Do you have any ID at all?
Er, yeah, in my room. Yeah.
[beard trimmer buzzes]
- Hi, Corporal. Sergeant Palmer.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
Could I get
a ticket for Marrakesh,
the next flight, please?
There's my passport.
I know he's got some, er...
He's had some
psychological problems.
PTSD?
Yeah, maybe, or...
Er, disenchantment?
He volunteered to stay
in Afghanistan, apparently.
The lads at the base said
that he was mad for it.
You know this guy?
No, I've never seen him before.
But him...
I recognize.
Rahim.
He was Major Tranter's
interpreter.
The Major managed to get him
and his whole family over here
to safety.
I've seen him at functions.
All roads lead to Afghanistan.
Karalis spent a year there
working in some gemstone mine.
Clareese,
put out a UK border stop
for questioning on Major Tranter
and Rahim Kadedadza.
Yes, ma'am.
[gently intriguing music]
Karalis is at Heathrow.
He booked a flight to Marrakesh.
- [notification music]
- WOMAN [on PA]:
Attention please.
Final call for Air Turkey...
Er, passport
and that's my boarding pass.
- Enjoy your flight,
Mr. Melville.
- Thank you.
Karalis is not on the flight
to Marrakesh.
- He checked in
and then he vanished.
- Right...
And guess who the night
security guard was on
the bomb site?
Payam Kadedadza,
Rahim's brother.
Follow up on that.
We're just arriving
at Major Tranter's house now.
- Police!
Police!
Clear!
Ma'am...
[tense music]
[music intensifies]
[seabirds call; music continues]
[street buzz; music continues]
[music fades into low-key,
traditional Turkish music]
Well, your bomb
went off a little early.
The cops were all over you
like a fucking mash, mate.
- I had to make a decision.
- Yeah, well,
you made the right one.
Thank you.
Did we get what we needed?
I think so, yeah.
Right.
What was that all about?
Things got a... little ugly.
But I owe you my life,
my friend.
It's okay.
So what are you
going to do next, eh?
- I've got some ideas.
- Hm?
Some things I wanna clean up.
Maybe we do this again?
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
Maybe.
[suitcase rolls loudly]
- Salam alaykum, man.
- Alright?
We good?
[sighs]
Thank fuck.
Are we ready?
- Fuck, yeah.
- Let's do it.
[tense music]
Our best price.
For all of them.
[sighs]
There appears to be some
misunderstanding, gentlemen.
We'll take our
business elsewhere.
Okay, okay.
Please wait.
Okay.
Mazal?
Mazal.
Tell me when.
When.
[transaction beeps]
Confirm.
It is done.
[transaction beeps]
It's done indeed.
G: Thank you. Thank you.
Even split.
Huh.
[Rahim chuckles]
G: Right.
[they chuckle]
[they speak in Pashto]
Let's go, boys, eh?
[tense music continues]
RAHIM: Oh, sorry.
Good luck.
Goodbye, my friend.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[intriguing music]
Fuck you, man. Fuck off!
- Eh?
- In the truck, now!
Ah!
Listen to me...
listen to me, boys.
I have money, alright?
I have money.
I can pay you boys.
- Shut up!
- Okay, I can pay you.
Listen... hey, you.
Fuck. Fuck!
[speaks in Pashto]
If we clean up the bombs
they will tell us about
any enemy movement.
I'm gonna do everything I can
in order to clean up the area.
[in Pashto]:
- Salam alaykum.
- And "where is"...?
- "Chairta".
- Chairta. Chairta tor ghar?
- Yeah. It's good.
WILL: Shit... Terry.
Get cover. Now.
Fuck! Stop!
Stop where you're walking.
I just stood on
a pressure plate.
[pants]
Shit.
There's fuckin' IEDs everywhere.
[trucks rev]
Boss...
Who the fuck are they?
Fuck!
[terrorists yell, gunshots]
Stop! Look at me!
Stand there!
Do not move!
We're surrounded by IEDs.
Who the fuck are you?
And what are you doing here?
I work in the mines.
Precious stones.
WILL: Why are you tied up?
My boss is trying
to fucking kill me, man!
His bodyguards
are taking me to him.
I help you, you fucking help me.
I'll help you, man.
I'll help you!
[gunfire continues]
Hope I don't regret this.
Here.
I need you to take these snips.
Make your way around to that
mound and look for a big tub
of explosives.
Why can't you
fucking do it, man?!
My foot's stuck
on a pressure plate.
So if I lift that,
we're all fucking dead.
- Right, right.
- What's your name?
My name's Karalis.
Karalis, step over this wire,
we need to neutralize that IED.
- Understand?
- Alright, alright.
Because on three,
I'm gonna cover ya, alright?
One, two, three.
[Will shoots]
Fuck me, man!
- Rahim!
- Yeah?
I need you to cover
for me, mate.
No, boss, no gun!
Yes, you fucking can!
You've done the training now.
[gunfire continues]
What can you see?
Nothing yet.
Start slowly
digging around that area.
Slowly.
I see a yellow plastic box, huh?
So, round there, there might
be a cable or a detonator.
[gunfire]
WILL: Carefully now!
There's a fucking
grenade here, man!
Alright! Don't
fucking touch that.
Can you see
a cable or a detonator?
Fuck! Yes, I see a cable, man.
WILL: Trace that back to me.
[gunfire; tense music]
G: Gah!
I can't do this!
Look at me.
We can do this together.
Right, just
take your mind off it.
Tell me about your boss.
Fuck that guy, alright?!
He fucking owes me,
and I'm gonna
get fucking payback!
I'll fucking owe you one
after this, mate.
So, let's pay
him back then, yeah?
[bullets whizz past]
Why the fuck are you here, eh?
British Army. Bomb disposal.
Yeah, well, you missed one.
Haha, nice one.
Hey, do
you wanna get us out of here?
- Let's go then.
- Yeah, yeah. Fuck yeah!
WILL: Alright. Rahim!
Cover for him, now!
[gunfire]
I see a plastic
tube covered in tape.
Right, that's the detonator.
Cut both of them wires,
one at a time.
Alright.
Boss!
I need ammo!
[music intensifies]
WILL: Just cut the other one!
- Ah!
- [music ebbs]
[fire crackles]
[sighs]
Oh, fuck, no!
Rahim! We good?
- Fine.
- Karalis?
[Will laughs]
I like you.
I wanna see these
fucking stones now, sexy.
Hahaha! Let's fuck, eh?
[clicks]
[tense music]
Rahim!
[loud explosions]
[explosions fade out]
[The Clash's
"Police and Thieves" plays,
an upbeat rock song]
♪ Police and thieves
in the street ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Fightin' the nation
With their ♪
♪ Guns and ammunition ♪
♪ From Genesis ♪
♪ To Revelation ♪
♪ The next generation ♪
♪ Will be, hear me ♪
♪ From Genesis ♪
♪ To Revelation ♪
♪ The next generation ♪
♪ Hear me ♪
♪ And all the crowd come in ♪
♪ A-day by day ♪
♪ A-no one stops it ♪
♪ Anyway ♪
♪ All the peacemaker ♪
♪ Third world officer ♪
♪ Hear what I say ♪
♪ Police and thieves
in the street ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Scarin' the nation
with their ♪
♪ Guns and ammunition ♪
♪ Police and thieves
in the street ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Fightin' the nation
with their ♪
♪ Guns and ammunition ♪
♪ From Genesis ♪
♪ To Revelation ♪
♪ The next generation ♪
♪ Hear me ♪
[singer vocalizing]
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ And all the crowd come in ♪
♪ Day by day ♪
♪ No one stops it ♪
♪ In anyway ♪
♪ All the peacemaker ♪
♪ Third world officer ♪
♪ Hear what I say ♪
♪ Police, police, police
and thieves ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Police, police, police
and thieves ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
- ♪ From Genesis ♪
- ♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Police, police, police
and thieves ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ And I'm scarin',
I'm fightin' the nation ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Shootin',
shootin' their guns and ♪
- ♪ Guns and ammunition ♪
- ♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Police, police, police and ♪
♪ I'm scarin' ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ I'm scarin' the nation ♪
♪ Police ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ You gotta take a beat ♪
♪ Here come, here come,
here come ♪
♪ The station is bombed ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Get out, get out, get out,
you people ♪
♪ If you don't want
to get blown up ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ The police, the police
and the thieves ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ You gotta lick the ground ♪
♪ But you are trapped
in the middle, punk ♪
♪ Police, police,
police, police ♪
♪ Police,
police, police, police ♪
♪ Police, police,
police, police ♪
♪ Police,
police, police, police ♪
♪ Police, police,
police, police ♪
♪ Police,
police, police, police ♪