[Episode 10]
- Chen Yi.
- Yes?
The college entrance examination is over.
I want to be brave for once.
- Do you even know what you're doing?
- What?
What exactly are you thinking?
Do you like Miao Jing?
I just didn't want to embarrass her.
Stop pretending with me.
You clearly can't let her go.
Chen Yi.
If Miao Jing doesn't leave
for a good university and stays in Teng City,
it's entirely because of you. You know that.
Can you carry that responsibility?
You're only thinking about now.
Have you thought about her future?
Have you thought about your future together?
Have you thought about your own future?
What's wrong?
Something's wrong with the car.
The car broke down.
Let's get out of the rain first.
Cold?
Wen was right.
I want to stay,
not because I'm attached to home.
Don't gamble with your future.
Teng City is too small.
It's just like our home.
You can't live there forever.
Sooner or later,
you'll move into a bigger, better house.
A house isn't a home.
You know what I can't bear to leave most.
Will you wait for me to come back?
Miao Jing.
You're the only family I have left.
No matter when you come back,
I'll be the first person you see.
Done.
It's fixed?
Chen Yi, after we check our scores,
let's go have hot pot.
Okay.
Pick one.
You went downstairs
in the middle of the night to buy popsicles?
Hurry. If you keep dawdling, they'll melt.
I got one. Open the door.
[Yuedong University Admissions
Information Portal]
[Yuedong University
Outstanding Freshman Scholarship]
620.
I should still be able to apply
for a scholarship, right?
[Class One, We Graduated!]
Tomorrow at eleven thirty,
Teng City Restaurant.
Don't forget to show up.
Got it.
What about Miao Jing? Is she in the group?
Don't forget tomorrow.
Why aren't you saying anything?
At least half the group has a crush on her.
They're too scared to confess.
Miao Jing must have plenty
of people chasing her.
Maybe she's already dating someone in secret.
Dating? I'd love to.
[Friends]
[Chen Yi]
[QQ Chat with Chen Yi]
[Aren't you...]
[Chen Yi: Offline. Call if anything comes up.]
[My Profile]
[Miao, Status]
[Status:
Waiting for a downpour I never saw coming.]
[Chen Yi: I'll hold the umbrella for you.]
We don't even know
if wages will be paid as usual.
Let's ask Hu when he gets here.
He's here.
Manager Chen.
It's so hot.
Hu, any news on the schedule?
Xu, I was just about to tell you.
This project is being suspended for now.
As for when work resumes,
we'll talk about that later, okay?
After I finish telling you,
pass it on to everyone.
Manager Chen, what's going on?
Wages will be settled
according to the actual days worked.
Finance will notify you of the exact process.
Come to me if there are any problems.
But this project was going just fine.
How can you just suspend it like that?
Then...
Manager Chen. This isn't fair.
College kid.
Yours isn't the only project being suspended.
All the construction sites
under Mr. Zhai have been suspended.
If you have a problem with it,
go talk to Mr. Zhai.
For you, it's nothing,
but what are the rest of us supposed to do?
Manager Chen. Please help us find a way.
I'll do my best
with the subsidies you applied for. Take care.
Chen Yi, let's go.
What do we do now?
- We haven't been paid in two months.
- What are we supposed to do?
- What do we do with no money?
- Our kids need to eat and go to school.
I don't know!
Mr. Zhai hasn't shown up in so long,
and the police keep coming by.
Is everything really fine?
How is that a big deal? Do you know Green Life?
Green Life?
The Green Life case
that caused such a stir a few years ago?
Yes.
Green Life was one
of Mr. Zhai's businesses too.
With all the trouble back then,
what happened in the end?
Didn't it still land safely?
No matter
what they came to Teng City to investigate,
even if the sky comes crashing down,
Mr. Zhai can handle it.
This time will be the same.
They won't last more than a few days.
Look.
What kind of tea is this?
It smells pretty good.
Good stuff.
This is premium Pu'er tea.
A few days ago, through me,
Zhai Feng Mao ordered a batch of
premium Pu'er tea at a Lingang auction house.
Was it a gift for...
If those inspection guys knew good tea,
this never would've ended up in my hands.
I already told them I worked for Zhai,
and they still wouldn't let me in.
If they hadn't found the tax forms,
Even if God himself showed up,
I'd still show him who's boss.
Hello, please show your identification.
Here we are.
Security here is pretty tight.
Why did your unit transfer you here
for the night shift?
The team on the pyramid scheme case
is holding meetings here.
And someone has to watch those files at night.
Actually, this is the set I wanted to shoot.
Too bad I didn't get to try it on
at the bridal shop.
Our dear Captain Zhou,
when exactly will you be free?
I've already rescheduled
with the photographer twice.
All right, honey.
Once I'm done with this stretch,
I'll go with you for an even better shoot, OK?
You promise?
I promise. I promise with my heart.
Isn't that Zhao from the tax bureau?
Why is he involved in pyramid schemes now?
Pyramid schemes?
That Green Life case was closed years ago,
wasn't it?
Didn't you just say pyramid schemes?
That the inspection team is here
to investigate pyramid schemes.
People keep saying they're here to
investigate Green Life. I mixed it up.
It's not pyramid schemes. It's tax fraud.
Was security this tight before?
Not before. Only in the last couple of days.
They added more patrols.
And now they check identification
on the way in and out. It's pretty strict.
Honey.
Be careful going in and out
these next couple of days.
Call me anytime if anything happens.
What's wrong?
Tax fraud is very different
from pyramid schemes.
If they really start digging,
Teng City may be in for a reckoning.
There you go again.
Come on, how could it be that serious?
I'm going to work.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Chen Yi, I'm going to use the bathroom.
[PRC General Tax Payment Certificate]
Let's go.
There have been a lot of rumors
going around lately.
Zhai's running out of ways
to hold things together.
You came up under me. Don't lose your nerve.
Is it related to the tax forms?
Who told you that?
With so many people handling things
back and forth,
the people below know bits and pieces.
Yi, you're a smart man.
Something like this can't be hidden from you.
But bringing this up to me at a time like this,
what are you trying to say?
Short on money lately?
Bin, I'm not that ambitious.
Opening a billiards hall with my friends,
making a little money on my own,
and giving my family peace of mind
is enough for me.
I can trust you.
I'll take you to see something in a bit.
The security room surveillance is
for outsiders.
This is the real one.
It covers every corner of the night club.
Only you know about it.
Don't tell anyone outside.
Sit down and let's talk.
Since you already know about the tax forms,
I won't hide it from you.
Zhai Feng Mao and I built this
from the ground up together.
But people change.
I've tried to talk him out of it many times.
After all, the people under
him need him to keep them fed too.
In the past, he'd listen to me.
Now...
Yi, do you remember the first time we met?
I do.
After that match ended,
I got cornered in an alley and beaten up.
You happened to pass by and saved me.
This was the first time we met.
Bin, I don't want it.
All these years,
You've done so much for me and the company,
I've seen it all.
I never had the chance to repay you
for saving my life.
This watch was always meant to be yours.
You saved my life too.
Let's not talk about that.
This is between us.
In Teng City, everyone knows this watch.
Whether you want to get out someday
or keep going,
with it on you, things will be easier for you.
Bin.
I did get where I am today because of you.
But I really don't want to stay tied
to Kuangxia anymore.
I get it.
Zhai Feng Mao asked me
to dinner at the restaurant.
I think this is what he wants.
If I really go,
with all these years of brotherhood,
I'm afraid I won't be able to refuse him.
He might drag me back onto the boat.
This is too important.
You're the only one I can trust with it.
- Happy graduation!
Come on. Here's to your graduation, everyone.
- Cheers!
- Happy graduation!
- Drink up!
- Thank you.
Let me tell you some gossip.
A boy at that table wants Miao Jing's contact.
But he's too embarrassed to ask.
This one is the most obedient. You're the best.
- Let's play games over the break!
- Sure, no problem.
- Sing a song! I'm not singing.
- You guys go ahead.
Sing the one you're best at.
We've graduated. Do something meaningful.
- Come on, just one song.
- Come on.
Give us one. Sing one.
Then let's sing one.
Let's all sing a graduation song together.
♪ Beyond the long pavilion ♪
♪ beside the ancient road ♪
♪ green grass stretches to the sky ♪
♪ The evening wind brushes
the willows as the flute fades ♪
♪ Beyond the sunset, mountains lie ♪
♪ At the edge of heaven ♪
♪ at the corner of earth ♪
♪ our old friends have scattered ♪
♪ With a jug of cloudy wine,
we drain what joy remains ♪
♪ Tonight, farewell dreams turn cold ♪
Let's go.
There's something I need to tell you.
Is the class monitor about to confess?
He's doing it right in front of everyone.
Aren't you going to stop him?
You've all graduated.
It wouldn't be right for me to stop it now.
Favoritism.
Exactly.
Miao Jing, I'm serious.
I got into a university in Hai City too.
It's not as good as Jiaohai,
we can be in the same city the next four years.
I like you. Will you be my girlfriend?
- Say yes.
Mr. Zhai.
Are you alone? Where's Bin?
Mr. Zhang had something to handle
and couldn't get away.
Come on.
- I'm good.
- Don't be polite.
That watch is Bin's, isn't it?
There's only one like it in Teng City.
The accounts are here. Let me take a look.
This is serious business.
Mr. Zhai.
The accounts for these companies
of yours are far too obvious.
There is no way
we can move this half of the funds to Lingang.
If you insist on doing this,
our firm will be taking on enormous risk.
When the time comes,
the tax forms and customs declarations...
What do you mean?
Darn it!
Did I invite you here
to run your mouth and embarrass me?
If my accounts were clean,
why would I need you?
I'm warning you.
I have backing in Teng City too.
Backing?
Let me see what watch you're wearing.
This...
This watch doesn't belong at the table.
Here. Take it.
Hu.
I was joking with you just now.
Do the accounts properly
and everyone looks good.
Do it right, and it's all yours.
Mr. Zhai, I'll go get some liquor.
Close it. Come on.
Let's drink.
I was joking. Don't be scared.
Keep drinking. Come on.
Miao Jing, I like you.
Will you be my girlfriend?
- Say yes.
- Calm down.
Stop that!
Miao Jing hasn't even answered yet.
Thank you. The flowers are beautiful.
But I already like someone.
Who do you like?
Miao Jing, who do you like?
Who is it?
Excuse me. Please let me through.
The cake is here.
It's so pretty.
Chen Yi.
Why did you run? I saw you just now.
Why didn't you come in and say hello?
Why are you here?
I'm here with my boss for business.
I didn't know your thank-you banquet was here.
Miao Jing. Why did you come over here?
They're cutting the cake.
This is...
Chen Yi.
- So handsome.
- Brother!
Do you remember me?
We met at the coming-of-age ceremony.
Don't call me that. I'm not your brother.
Sorry. I didn't mean it like that.
Miao Jing, are you free tomorrow?
- We're planning to go hiking.
- Yeah, hiking.
- She's not free.
- Do you want to join us?
Why? Is it because of the person you like?
Chen Yi?
Where did you run off to?
- You brat. Are you here picking up girls?
- Mr. Zhai.
No, they're people I know.
Host a meal for them.
- Here.
- Mr. Zhai. How can I let you pay for this?
That's too generous.
Let me see. Quite a crowd.
No. This isn't enough.
Don't reject it.
- Take it.
- Mr. Zhai.
- No, really, no need.
- Do as I say.
- Mr. Zhai.
Mr. Zhai.
The guests have all been put in their cars.
They're all gone?
- Let's go.
- Forget it then.
Young girls, come find me next time.
I'll treat you to a feast.
Just remember to come find me.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Don't drink so much next time.
Who is he? Were you really here for business?
It's fine. Go back first. I'll see them off.
Will you come back?
[Log: A sense of safety means being
somewhere close to "home."]
[Friends - Family: CY (Chen Yi)]
[Send]
What are you doing?
I'm checking what I'll need for school.
You seem fine.
They were all talking about you today.
What did they say?
They all asked me what exactly you do.
They said Zhai Feng Mao was ruthless
when he fought for business turf years ago.
And Kuangxia would do anything.
Don't worry. It's not what you think.
You mean you're not like that,
or Zhai Feng Mao isn't?
Chen Yi, you can tell me anything.
I'm not a child anymore.
You don't have to keep protecting me.
Don't overthink it.
Bin.
I want to go with my sister
to Hai City for university.
Think it over.
This will definitely need to be arranged.
As for Zhai Feng Mao,
I'll find a chance to talk to him again.
Okay.
Then I'll trouble you with it, Bin.
You didn't wear the watch today?
It's too valuable.
There's no need for it in everyday life.
- Let's go.
- Hello, Captain Zhou.
Take him to the interrogation room.
Yes, Captain Zhou.
Kang An.
Qian.
I remember you've been following
Kuangxia and Zhai Feng Mao's case, right?
Yes.
All right. There's a meeting. Join it.
Make a report on Zhai Feng Mao's situation
over the years.
Why?
Did the inspection team's get results?
It's about time to wrap it up.
Great.
We can finally tear out this cancer
in Teng City by the roots.
And his Kuangxia too.
When you root out evil, leave none behind.
The detention center's going to be busy soon.
All right. I'll prepare properly.
Keep it confidential.
Before the operation, not a word can leak out.
Got it.
Captain Zhou, he's been taken
to the interrogation room. We can begin.
Okay. Go in and wait for me.
Roger.