"Unfold"
(Episode 6)
Bai Che.
I killed your father.
That kid...
He wants to sell the port
the moment he gets back.
If we hadn't
built this empire with
his father back then,
who does he think he is?
By the way, the organ trafficking
is being cracked down on so hard lately.
It must be that kid's doing.
Since we can't make any money,
we won't let him have it easy either.
Next Tuesday,
take a few capable men with you.
Right.
Jufu Farm.
I'm going to ruin that kid.
You're here.
Next Tuesday,
You...
bring Zhao Lingye to Jufu Farm.
He'll never listen to me.
Don't fucking look at me like that.
If it weren't for me,
would your mother have found
a matching kidney so quickly?
It's a pity, though.
She was too weak.
Not long after the transplant,
she still didn't make it.
You owe me this.
Uncle Bai,
you said this kidney was worth 700,000.
But the documents Mr. Zhao showed me
say otherwise.
That kidney...
you harvested it from
a lung cancer patient.
I...
I really thought you were helping me.
It was an accident.
Who could have known?
Now go and get it done.
I don't owe you anything anymore.
Bai Ronghui got what he deserved.
He killed my mother,
and he lied to me.
Even you, his so-called son,
was just a lie.
I killed him.
Consider your vengeance avenged too.
You don't have to thank me.
He stole my life.
But...
if you dare get in my way,
I won't be so polite next time.
My card.
In case you lost the other one.
Why didn't you call me?
Let's go.
How long have you been waiting?
What if I hadn't come back today?
Bai Che,
You coming to find me...
makes me very happy.
But next time,
call me.
I'll come pick you up.
Does it hurt?
No.
Liar.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You have something to tell me.
Are you leaving here later?
I'll leave once the money
from the port comes in.
I was wondering...
if you would leave me behind.
Why would you think that?
Because I'm one of Lao Bai's people.
Are you?
What?
Lao Bai's person?
What do you think?
I don't like guessing.
Cheng Fan,
did you kill Lao Bai
for me,
or for yourself?
Both.
Both?
Which one more?
He wanted me to bring you to the farm.
They were going to hurt you.
So you killed him.
I'm sorry.
After what he did to you,
he deserved to die.
Do you want to take
a plane or a boat?
There's still food in the fridge.
Should I make you something?
How about a drink?
The bottle you had last time is still here.
I even bought
the one you poured for me at the bar.
It's okay.
Zhou Chen...
Why are you so good to me?
Do you really not know?
Can you feel it?
Every time it sees you,
it beats a little faster.
I'm sorry.
I...
It's okay.
We can take it slow.
Zhou Chen,
don't leave me.
I won't.
Never.