We're close.
Ah! Ah...
Aargh!
I'll find a rock.
Ah...
It can't end like this...
It's okay.
Come here.
There's nothing.
Nothing to be done.
Just turn away.
Be still.
I said turn away!
Aaaargh!
♪ Oft in the stilly night ♪
♪ Ere slumber's chain
has bound me ♪
♪ Fond memory
brings the light ♪
♪ Of other days around me ♪
♪ The smiles, the tears ♪
♪ Of boyhood's years ♪
♪ The words of love
then spoken ♪
♪ The eyes that shone ♪
♪ Now dimm'd and gone ♪
♪ The cheerful hearts
now broken ♪
Why'd you shoot it?
They're pests.
They jump up on the cars
and make shit of the paintwork.
Couldn't just shoo it away, huh?
Goats are stubborn.
Spray it with a hose?
No.
I'm telling you now, Fergal,
I'm not dragging that
into the woods.
Shut up.
Fado, fado...
Long, long ago,
deep in the woods,
there was a small stone hut.
And inside the stone hut,
there lived an old Cailleach...
A witch.
Preying upon the lost,
the evil old crone would first
put the doomed travellers
under her spell,
leaving them as dazzled
and vulnerable as lamplit game.
The witch would then shackle
her stunned prey
before taking
the lost travellers
on a tour of the underworld.
And sometimes,
a hand or a claw
would reach out from the dark
and tear a piece from those
at the end of her chain.
Pluck out an eye.
Peel off an ear.
And sometimes,
they took something
from a little boy
that was more valuable to him
than his eyes or ears.
Any guesses which part of you
that might be?
- These your kids?
- No.
Go find your parents.
And don't talk
to strangers again.
There are worse things
than strangers out there, Yank.
Did we wake you?
Uh, Mr Cob, my apologies.
I was on the phone and I thought
Alby was manning...
Don't apologise to me,
you maneen.
Apologise to the guest!
My apologies.
Why don't you mind
your own business?
It is my business.
I'm the owner.
Bauman. I have a reservation.
If you could just sign...
Ah! Mr Bauman.
Mr Ohm Bauman,
Pullman City, Washington.
With us for a week. Welcome.
Lock it up.
Alby's dragging it out
into the woods.
Dining room is down
this corridor here.
Breakfast in the morning
from seven to ten.
Halloween party tomorrow night
with live music,
cocktails, costumes...
Should be a bit of craic.
Oh, um, craic is a word we use
to describe a fun time
here in Ireland.
Yeah, can I get a room
as far away
from the 'craic' as possible?
- I've work to do.
- What do you do?
Writer.
Well...
you shouldn't hear a thing.
Thank you.
Wait... Bauman.
Ah, I know that name.
I think my son
is a fan of yours!
A celebrity.
Well, if there's anything
we can do
to make your stay
more enjoyable,
please dial '0' and let us know.
All right.
Oh, maybe I could bring in
my son's book
and you could sign it for him?
No.
There's nothing
getting through that.
That's built to last.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Are you lost?
What does it look like?
Well, with that attitude,
it looks like you can stay lost.
Okay, sorry, I'm just...
I can't find my room.
It should be right here,
but it's not.
- Oh, yeah. It's this way.
- Thank you.
- First time in Ireland?
- Yeah.
Are you having a nice time?
Yeah.
This is you.
Thank you.
Enjoy your stay.
Thanks. Oh, hey...
Sorry, would you happen to know
with the Big Redwood is?
- Who are those?
- Jesus...
Oh, uh...
My folks.
Sorry for your loss.
You want a drink?
I think I may need something
stronger than milk.
Nothing stronger than that.
- Moonshine?
- Poitín.
Uisce beatha.
Water of life.
Whoo. Yeah, that's moonshine.
If you want something
to defeat the demons,
and not just be
running from them.
Magic mushrooms.
Psilocybin.
It's all natural.
I pick, dry, and grind
the mushrooms myself.
And I like it with goat's milk.
What are you gonna do with it?
- I'll bury her.
- Hm.
Do you know why they climb
on the cars?
Goats like to graze
on the mushrooms as well.
And when they're coming up,
they go looking for reflective
surfaces, 'cause...
staring into your own eyes
on mushrooms
deepens the trip.
But...
it can be dangerous.
Especially if there's an asshole
with a crossbow nearby.
Don't get me started.
I've nearly come to blows
with him over it.
Thanks for the drink.
Don't go climbing up
on any cars.
I won't!
The boy's skull is the only hard
object for, like, miles.
So, the conquistador
hits the boy with the bottle,
killing him,
but the bottle
still doesn't break.
In the end, he wanders out
into the desert to die.
- Why would you write this?
- What do you mean?
I mean, it's so bleak.
Well, you know, it's meant
to be challenging.
Well, I won't be reading it.
Not if that's how it ends.
Well, you know,
a few of my novels
have been turned
into bad movies,
and when they make
the movie for you,
you tag on a happy ending.
Okay, well, they'd better.
You remind me of my mom.
Your mum? How old
do you think I am?
Well, when she was young,
you know.
Yeah, just in the way she...
Hm. She looks happy.
My dad took that.
You know, they came here
for their honeymoon.
Always wanted to come back.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Why didn't they?
Oh, she died a few years
after that.
- She was very young.
- Mm.
- How did she die?
- Murdered.
Shot in the face
as she came home from work.
Did they catch the person
that shot her?
Nah, he's too young
to be punished.
Should have fucking hanged him.
And your dad?
Oh, well, he...
turned into a monster
and drank himself
to an early grave.
You know, I've had
their ashes for years
and never knew
what to do with them.
I knew they were happy
here, so...
Hey, I noticed the honeymoon
suite, it's closed.
I wonder if that's the room
they stayed in.
That has been closed
a long time.
Do you know why?
Because no couple in their right
mind would honeymoon here?
It's haunted.
- Oh.
- By a witch.
Mr Cob says they managed to lock
her in there years ago.
I tried to convince Mal
to sneak the key off Mr Cob
so I could have a look up there,
but... he wouldn't go for it.
I have never known a man to be
so afraid of his father-in-law.
Why do you want to go up there
so bad?
To see if there really is
a witch up there.
What if there is?
I mean, aren't you
afraid she'll,
uh, 'get you'?
- I'd bring some chalk.
- Chalk?
If you ever find yourself
being chased by a witch,
draw a circle around you.
Keep you safe.
If I ever think I'm being chased
by a witch,
I will look for a psychiatrist,
not a piece of chalk.
Oh, perfect. Alby...
Tell Ohm here about
your encounter
with the witch upstairs.
Well, um...
Hello?
And that's what happened.
Hokum.
Don't worry, Alby.
I believe you.
Fiona?
Delivery to sign for.
Back in a sec.
Are you enjoying your stay,
Mr Bauman?
Yeah, I guess.
When I saw the name, I didn't
think it would actually be you.
Uh, what are you doing here?
Who knows?
I don't mean to bother you,
but I wanted to tell you
how much your books
have meant to me.
I really relate
to your characters.
Well, that's troubling,
seeing as those pages
are populated
by deeply disturbed,
desperate people.
Oh, is that what you use to keep
track of all your ideas?
It is, yeah.
And in fact, I just had one
speaking with you.
Idea for a character,
uh, oblivious charisma vacuum.
Is completely incapable
of reading a room.
Ah...
Is it true, I read
that you're finally writing
the end of the Conquistador
trilogy?
How fuck do I know
what you read?
No, I mean, is it true you're
finally writing the ending?
I'm starting to think
it's gonna be open-ended.
And are you happy
with how it's going?
I'm a writer too.
And some nights it's hard
to face that blank page.
Yeah.
So that's a Halloween costume
you're wearing?
Oh, uh, no.
I-I just work here
to pay the bills.
Oh. Oh, okay. So you're not
a writer, you're a bellboy.
No, I am a writer. I just
don't get paid for it yet.
- Ah.
- You know, it can be hard
to get publishers or agents
or anybody to read anything.
Sure.
And actually, um, I've got
a manuscript in my locker.
Do you mind if I ask you
to take a look at it?
Nope.
Why not?
Ah! Jesus...
You need thicker skin than that
if you wanna make it
as a writer.
What happened to you?
What happened there?
Never meet your heroes.
I'll take another.
And that'll be his last one.
To bleak endings.
Alby?
Can you open this?
I know, I'm just getting
a weird feeling.
He's not answering.
- By the way he was drinking,
he's probably passed out
in a pool of his own piss.
He burnt my hand...
Would you just open it!
Your funeral.
Mr Bauman?
It's Fiona.
You left your things in the bar.
Mr Bauman?
Jesus Christ! Alby!
Thanks very much for your time,
Guards.
Mr Bauman...
Are you closing?
End of season.
How, uh...
- How are you feeling?
- I'm sorry.
I just, uh,
came to get my stuff.
Of course.
It's just, uh, back here,
safe and sound.
Thank you.
Hey, uh...
Who found me?
One of, uh,
the members of staff, Fiona.
She was working in the bar
that night.
Christ... Is she around?
No.
Well, I'd like to talk
to her. Apologise.
Could I get her number?
Uh, Mr Bauman, um,
Fiona's missing.
What do you mean?
She hasn't been seen
since Halloween,
and that's weeks ago.
What?
We thought maybe
she just wanted some time
and didn't let
anybody know, but...
What do they think
happened to her?
They don't know.
Well...
Okay, but she couldn't
have just disappeared.
I mean, they searched the hotel?
- Of course.
And the woods.
Could she have been taken?
By who?
Well, how the fuck
should I know?
I mean... local weirdo,
a guest, someone who works here?
I mean, I don't know
if you've noticed
but there are some oddballs
walking around this place.
Okay.
Those men...
they were police.
And there is a man
that they wanna speak with
who lives in the woods.
His name is Jerry.
Fergal saw Fiona outside talking
to him earlier that night.
He hasn't been seen since.
Now, we always just considered
him a pest around here.
He comes into the hotel,
sits by the fire,
bothers the guests.
- Right.
Since his disappearance,
the Guards have learned
who Jerry is, and...
it turns out Jerry disappeared
after his wife died
under suspicious circumstances
ten years ago.
Mr Bauman, I think
you've been through enough.
Go home. Heal.
I promise I'll call you myself
if there's any updates.
I bet you have a whole
new appreciation
for a woman's intuition.
Alby told me that Fiona made him
unlock your door
because she had a bad feeling.
Lucky boy.
You saw Fiona talking
to the man in the woods
before she disappeared?
Jerry. I warned her before
to stay away from him.
Yeah, Mal said his wife died
under suspicious circumstances?
Well, he obviously killed her,
didn't he?
Why else would he be down here
hiding in the woods for years,
living out of an old van.
Oh, well, now he's gone.
He'll be back.
And I'll be waiting for him.
Did you talk to her that night?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Wh... How'd she seem?
Well, not herself.
Distracted.
Sad.
I think she was still in shock
from having to cut you down.
Okay, what about
the honeymoon suite?
What about it?
Well, was it searched?
I mean, Fiona mentioned
wanting to go up there.
Impossible.
The gate is always locked.
Mr Cob has the key on him
at all times.
So it wasn't searched?
It's always locked.
It's locked now.
Mr Cob has me
check the gate every day.
There's no way she could have
possibly got up there,
so you might as well suggest
that we search the moon.
Police talk to you?
I talk to the Guards every day.
My first cousins.
Guarda Sergeant is my uncle.
Why do you ask?
See, the best thing
you could do now,
is get into your car
and fuck off back to the airport
while you still look like
your passport picture.
Safe home now.
Come on!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Fiona'd be glad to know
you woke up.
Okay, well, she's missing.
Do you have anything
to do with that?
No.
Well, the police
are looking for you.
You're the last one
seen talking to her.
I don't think it's
the only reason
they're looking for me now.
Huh?
Yeah, that's right.
They said you killed your wife.
Yeah, that's true.
She was very ill.
She was in a lot of pain.
You know...
this is Fiona's.
- We were friends.
She let me borrow it.
Oh, she did?
Okay, well, why don't you
come with me
and we'll talk to the police.
No, it's pointless.
They-they wouldn't
believe me anyway.
Oh yeah?
Why? What do you think
happened to her?
I don't know.
But I know she's dead.
Why do you say that?
There's a cupboard
in Mal's office
full of medicine
left behind by guests.
Two nights ago,
I went there to stock up...
I-I saw her.
What?
And-and the bell
she was pointing to,
it's an old mechanical call bell
connected to the honeymoon
suite.
I think she was trying
to tell me to go up there.
I'm waiting till
the hotel's empty
and then I'm going up there
to check.
Okay, but unless you have a key,
then how the hell...
Ah, right. Of course.
Cob lives on the other side
of the woods. I broke in.
But if he had the key,
then she couldn't be up there.
No, unless someone stole it,
took her up there and then put
it back without him noticing.
Right, but who would do that?
I don't know!
Okay. Why don't you
give it to me?
I'll go back and I'll check.
- No, you-you...
You wouldn't even
get near the gate
with Fergal or Mal still there.
No. It has to be at night.
Tonight...
when the hotel is empty.
Would you come with me?
I don't know what I'm gonna find
when I get up there.
I'd rather not go alone.
You know all these things
do exist?
It is just people
with closed minds can't see 'em.
There's one more car
to pass by my count,
then the hotel is empty.
You really think that was
Fiona's ghost that you saw?
Yeah.
Were you drinking your magic
milk when you saw this ghost?
That's how I saw her.
My mind was open.
What the fuck am I doing here?
My wife's spirit
visited me once on a trip.
She thanked me
for ending her suffering.
Said we'd be together
again someday.
Whatever you say, man.
She said we'd be together again.
Believe what you want.
When we go up there, yeah,
and we find Fiona...
you'll believe it too.
And what if we don't find her?
Does that mean all of this
is just in your head?
Okay.
Hey, she-she was kind
of like this.
- Come on.
- Just getting the crossbow.
What? Don't go get that!
We don't need that!
Shit.
Ugh...
Is there someone there?
- Garda Station?
- Áine? It's Fergal.
I have Jerry.
Tell my cousins
I'm bringing him in.
What do you mean,
'you have him'?
- I have to get on the road.
- What? Fergal, no...
Jesus...
Uh...
It's all right, it's all right.
What are you doing here?
You're asking me?
I got a phone call from Mr Cob
in a panic
saying the honeymoon key
was missing.
How'd you even get this?
- Jerry?
- Jerry.
Yeah, he's convinced
Fiona was up here.
Where is he?
Fergal, the fuckhead,
took him to the police.
He didn't see me.
What were you thinking?
Uh, she saved me.
I wanted to help find her.
I don't know.
Okay.
Why don't we just go downstairs?
We'll get in trouble
if we're caught up here.
Alright.
Can you gimme a ride
back to my car?
Yeah.
You're lucky
you didn't get locked in here.
Mr Cob told me a story
about a young bride
locking herself in here once.
Oh no, Mr Bauman...
Mr Bauman, would you please?
You're not supposed
to be up here!
Mr Cob is very strict
on people not coming up here!
I could lose my job!
Where does this go?
There was a basement down there
before it was a hotel.
Uh-huh.
The entrance was lost
during the renovations.
There's nothing down there.
Oh, look at that.
There is nothing down there.
No! Okay, okay.
We need to move, move.
We need to leave!
Mr Bauman, I am going to have
you arrested for trespassing
if you do not leave
right this minute!
Oh...
Hey!
Idea for a character.
Uh, oblivious charisma vacuum.
Completely incapable
of reading a room.
Hi, girls.
Looking well.
I thought you were gonna
hand that in to the hospital.
He's, uh, famous, you know?
I bet you he'll dedicate his new
book to you if he wakes up.
Don't say 'if', Mal.
Drink your tea
while it's still hot.
- Uh...
- You all right?
I feel...
I feel off.
I'm grateful for it, you know,
it looks awesome.
I can't see a thing
in it, man.
It's absolutely sweating...
It's alright.
Ah...
I know I'm gonna be okay.
I'm gonna leave this message
here just in case.
My name is Fiona Crotty.
I think I'm in the basement
of the hotel, but...
I don't know.
I'm pregnant.
Mal, the manager,
is the father.
He wasn't happy with me
for keeping the baby.
I wasn't gonna tell anyone
it was his,
but he was just so terrified
his wife or father-in-law,
Mr Cob, would find out.
I can't believe
he'd go this far.
Put us down here.
Get rid of us.
It's dark,
but I'm gonna see
if I can find a way out.
If I don't and someone
finds this message,
tell my parents I love them.
Fuckin' Fergal...
Shit...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck!
Hello?
Hey!
Who's there?
Aargh!
Okay, kids, we're gonna read
our next letter!
Yay!
"Dear Jack..."
That's me!
"My name is Ohm Bauman."
Ohm? Okay.
"I am ten years old
and my mom died last year."
- What dies, kids?
- Everything!
"I was playing with my dad's
gun and it went off."
What are the two things
we don't ever play with, kids?
- Fire!
- And?
- Guns!
- That's right!
"My dad hates me now."
"I miss my mom."
"I'm scared all the time."
"Can you help me? Ohm."
Well, Ohm, it's pretty simple.
Your dad told you
not to go near his gun,
but you did anyway.
And his wife got her brains
blown out.
You want help?
There's none coming.
You're scared? You should be.
You fucking should be!
There's no way back up.
The dumbwaiter button's broken.
I can't use it to get back up.
I can't find a way out.
I'm stuck down here.
Yes!
Right...
Oh! Ah...
Oh, fuckin' Jesus.
Ah...
I think there's someone
down here!
I keep hearing something.
Is someone there?
Oh God! Oh...
Three, two...
Come on! Come on...
Come on...
Hello?
Aah...
Uh...
- Jesus...
- Ah, Mal.
I need your help.
Jesus, Jerry.
What happened to you?
Oh, Fergal. It doesn't matter.
I need to get up here.
I need to get this open.
- What for?
- The American.
Ohm, he went up there.
- Ugh!
- Stop! Stop, stop.
He's gone.
What?
Mr Cob sent me out here
to look for the key,
and when I got here,
the gate was unlocked,
so I went up.
- And?
- What did you find?
- Mr Bauman.
- Drunk.
- What?
- Where is he?
- He's on his way to the airport.
Well, he was too drunk to drive,
so I took him down to town,
stuffed him in a taxi
and sent him off.
And Fiona?
No.
Hey...
So, you just jumped?
I mean, you could
have been killed.
Are you sure
you checked that room?
I mean, you looked everywhere?
The room's not that big.
She's not there.
I swear to you, I looked.
I need to see it for myself.
Fiona wants me to go up there.
I'm going to have to call
the guards
to tell them you're here.
They know about your wife.
I saw her...
I saw her.
Just go, Jerry.
Take Bauman's car
and don't come back.
I'll tell them
that you were already gone.
Just go.
No, no, no! Jerry!
Jerry!
Aah...
Uh!
Ah!
I left the keys.
Motherfucker...
Are you all right, Mal?
No, I'm-I'm actually
not feeling the best.
I think I might need to lock up
and go home.
Hey, why don't I get the keys
and I'll bring them out to you?
God damn it!
♪ Oft, in the stilly night ♪
♪ Ere slumber's chain
has bound me ♪
♪ Fond memory
brings the light ♪
- Jerry.
- Fiona used to say,
never ignore when something
feels off.
Something feels off here, Mal.
Jerry...
You have to leave.
If you dropped Ohm into town,
why did you come back out here?
To get this...
reframed for my wife.
You drove all the way back out
here for that?
Can't a man do something
nice for his wife
without having
something to hide?
- Uh...
- Jerry...
Jerry, what the fuck
are you doing?
- Key!
- I don't have it.
I gave it back to Mr Cob.
Give it to me!
Okay. Okay, okay.
Jerry, please.
It was a mistake.
You don't know Fiona like I did.
She wasn't a good person!
You know, she was threatening
to tell Mr Cob!
And he hates me!
He's threatened to have me
killed for less over the years!
Just leave him!
He was gonna
kill himself anyway!
♪ I've seen
around me fall ♪
♪ Like leaves
in wintry weather ♪
♪ I feel like one ♪
♪ Who treads alone ♪
♪ Some banquet-hall deserted ♪
- Ohm!
- Hey! Jerry!
I'm in here! Get me
the fuck out of here, man!
There's a small door here!
I can bust it open.
Yeah.
Stay back, stay back.
Uh!
- Fiona?
- No, she's dead.
Mal fucking killed her.
Are you okay?
I'll live.
Uh!
Don't try and leave!
I mean it!
Oh, fuck!
Aaargh!
God! Fuck!
Bauman?
Fuck...
Bauman!
Bauman, listen to me.
The hotel is on fire.
There's no way out down there.
I'll bring you back up
with the key
and we can both leave.
You can go home.
Bauman!
Can you hear me?
Ohm...
Bauman?
Ah!
Uh!
It was an accident.
I'm sorry, it was an accident.
I know.
You can't stay here.
It was an accident.
What's happening?
Help!
Please! No!
Aaaargh!
Mal!
Can you hear me?
Ohm's Mum: Fergal!
Is there someone there?
Jesus...
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Come on, we have to go! Up!
Come on! We have to go!
How are you feeling, Mr Bauman?
You're that bellboy.
My name's Alby.
I didn't think you'd have
anybody visiting you,
being away from home.
I'm not sure I'd have anybody
visiting me there either.
Sit down, sorry.
Okay. Uh, I guess I'll just get
two scoops of vanilla.
Yeah, I work in the ice cream
parlour next door as well, yeah.
Ah.
Oh, this is from Fergal.
He's pretty devastated
about Fiona.
He said if you needed anything
to let him know.
Yeah, I spoke to him
on the phone.
Oh.
You been to the hotel?
What's left of it.
They found remains.
Fiona and Jerry.
Mal?
His car was found outside.
They're looking for him.
Mr Bauman, I need
to tell you something.
I don't what happened, um,
but I'm worried it might have
been my fault in some way.
How?
There was a flask of whiskey
in your room.
- Did you drink it?
- Yeah.
Much of it?
Well, it's whiskey.
I drink all of it. Why?
I spiked it.
With what?
I had some of Jerry's
mushroom powder.
I snuck into your room
and I put it in the flask.
Why would you do that?
Well, it was after
I tried to speak to you
at the bar that night.
You burnt my hand.
That hurt.
You know, all these
things do exist.
It's just people with closed
minds can't see 'em.
I'm sorry.
You were really rude.
I'd better go
before they kick me out.
One of the firemen
found this at the hotel.
Hey, um...
you can take that, too.
I didn't touch it.
Yeah, no, just, just take it.
If you wanted something
to pass the time,
I could bring in my manuscript.
I mean, I've been
through enough already, Alby.
I'll do a quick polish tonight
and drop it in tomorrow.
All right.
I said turn away!
Aaargh!
Here.
Hit me here.
As hard as you can.
You understand?
You don't stop for blood.
You don't stop for bone
and you keep hitting
until it breaks.
Follows the map and you claim it
all as yours.
It's nothing I don't deserve.
Do it before I change my mind.
No.
No...
♪ Farewell vain world
I'm going home ♪
♪ My saviour smiles
and bids me come ♪
♪ And I don't care
to stay here long ♪
♪ Sweet angels
beckon me away ♪
♪ To sing God's praise
in endless day ♪
♪ And I don't care
to stay here long ♪
♪ Right up yonder ♪
♪ Christians away up yonder ♪
♪ Oh yes, my Lord ♪
♪ For I don't care
to stay here long ♪
♪ I'm glad that I am
born to die ♪
♪ From grief and woe
my soul shall fly ♪
♪ And I don't care
to stay here long ♪
♪ Bright angels
shall convey me home ♪
♪ Away to New Jerusalem ♪
♪ And I don't care
to stay here long ♪
♪ Right up yonder ♪
♪ Christians away up yonder ♪
♪ Oh yes, my Lord ♪
♪ For I don't care
to stay here long ♪
♪ Right up yonder ♪
♪ Christians away up yonder ♪
♪ Oh yes, my Lord ♪
♪ For I don't care
to stay here long ♪