Jesus Christ.
Crown is there. He knows.
Get out. Now.
Go.
I said get out.
No can do, sir.
Listen to me. You're in danger.
No hesitation.
Clear.
Shit.
Crown's on the way up.
You don't have much time.
Contact front!
Come on.
Got it!
Is he listening?
Oh, goddamn it.
Sorry, Nigel.
Hey.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Are you kidding me?
Of course you would choose a bookstore.
And a restaurant.
- You saw the restaurant.
- Yeah.
You're deputy director of the CIA.
You can't just call?
- Where's the fun in that?
- You owe me a coffee.
Ah, you got it.
- It's good to see you.
- Yeah.
Good to see you, too.
Just letting the office know
I've been kidnapped.
Thank you.
What time is your flight?
Four hours.
So, this is Wall Street, huh?
Well, technically, it's Broadway, but--
Mm. Which building is yours?
The tall one.
This the part of the conversation
where you ask if I like my new gig?
Well, do you?
You leave the CIA for a nice civilian job.
Uh, I was just checking in on you.
Yeah. You like your new gig?
Ugh, it's shit.
See? We feel about the same way.
Listen, I just couldn't keep doing
what I was doing and have a normal life.
Normal life.
Is that what you were going for?
Come on. You said it yourself: civilian.
Black and white. I don't know, man.
I don't know if I was cut out
for all this gray area stuff.
So, have you seen her?
No. Not since Christmas.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
We gave it a real shot, you know?
And that's all you can ask for.
Cathy's doing
what she was meant to be doing.
And you?
And me?
Well, see, I haven't been
out of the agency long enough
to forget what it was like to be baited.
Bait? There's no bait.
- Oh.
- You said it yourself.
You gave it a shot.
Yeah? And this? All this?
It's never gonna be
good enough for you.
That's a good speech.
Whatever it is, I'm not doing it.
Look, I'm not asking you to come back.
I just need you to meet a guy.
No.
Oh, Jack, you're flying to Dubai.
He's in Dubai.
He'll come to you. It's just a pickup.
- Oh, it's just a pickup.
- Yeah.
Oh, okay. Pickup of what?
Information. Surveillance.
Well, which one is it?
Goddamn it, Jack. He's a friend.
- So he'd do the same for you?
- Hell no.
Yeah, Nigel is
the twitchiest spook I know.
But I'm the better man.
You always are.
So, what is it?
It's housekeeping.
It's an old joint op with MI6.
MI6?
Jesus. You surveilling
one of them or one of us?
- Bit of both.
- Well, that doesn't sound good.
Well, shit.
For someone who wants nothing to do
with it, you sure ask a lot of questions.
Well, it's 'cause I know
what happens when I get caught
doing one of your errands
out in the private sector.
- Oh, no one's gonna know.
- Really?
- Nah.
- You sound pretty confident.
What, you think I would
send you out there all alone?
Oh, wow. Are you sending backup?
Hmm.
Oh, shit. Look who it is.
Oh.
Oh, so you're trying to get me killed.
-  No offense taken.
- This is it?
This is the kind of crackerjack officer
you're going for at the agency now?
Just trying to fill your shoes, buddy.
- On a contract basis.
- Ouch.
But you know what?
We'll always have Dubrovnik, right, Mike?
Call me when it's done.
- You got it.
- Whoa, where are you going?
Welcome back.
I said I wasn't doing it.
Don't do that.
You're better than that.
He's good, isn't he?
- Upgraded.
- I already have my ticket.
- First class, man. I upgraded both of us.
- Oh. You really never change.
It's like a disease.
Hey, are you checking a bag?
Yeah. Short trip.
You know, I can fit it in my carry-on.
We're good.
Hey.
Do you mind if I leave this down?
I'm an anxious flyer.
Are you? Oh, boy.
I knew he'd call you.
- Greer says you're meeting a guy.
- No. No, no, no.
I'm not meeting a guy.
No, you and I both know
that it's never just meeting a guy.
He said it is not a big deal. All right?
- Guy's gonna come to you.
- Is he? 'Cause we're on a plane.
Well, first we got to go to him. Fine.
But he's gonna come to you. You get it.
I don't get it, no.
In fact, why don't you just do it?
Because I got to make sure nobody follows.
But why would somebody follow me?
- Because it's never just meeting a guy.
I know. That's what I was saying.
That's cute.
Think Emirati Intelligence is buying
your old hedge fund cover?
- This isn't a cover. This is real life.
- Mm-hmm.
- No, no. I know.
- I'm actually the senior vice president
- of a risk management--
- Just keep talking, buddy.
- You're gonna help me sleep.
- Hi. Can I offer you champagne?
Is that an angel?
It's my first time in first.
She never would've guessed.
-  Thank you.
-  That's for someone else.
- Come on, man.
- They don't usually give out two.
Uh-huh.
- One per.
- Mm-hmm. Cheers.
The Jakartan trade market
is not only back,
but it's never been stronger.
Dr. Ryan, do you have anything
that you'd like to add?
Jack?
Oh, um, no.
Don't let me be the one to bring down
the optimism in the room.
I think we can all agree, the new regime
has certainly bolstered the market.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Um, I think the question we need
to be asking ourselves is: Why?
Because this new regime has also
brought back old-world standards.
And these days,
it's becoming increasingly convenient
to overlook the political ramifications
of something
in order to track
the financial ramifications.
What I mean is,
in my unique experience,
the kind of minds
that want to bring back the past,
well, they often bring back
a whole lot of volatility with them.
I thought that went well.
I think you're being kind.
I think you're worried about your job,
which you should be,
because honesty is clearly not
the best policy.
Well, it probably feels weird when
global events don't hang in the balance.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry, was that a spy joke?
- It was.
- Oh. Took you long enough.
- Oh, you know.
-  Hey, listen,
don't knock imminent nuclear threat
until you've tried it.
- Oh.
- It's a thing.
So, I guess SLJ made reservations
for our team tonight at Shiro's.
Oh. What's, uh, what's Shiro's?
The kind of upscale restaurant
they make documentaries about.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Oh, boy.
- Hmm.
I, uh...
I'm not quite sure I can tonight.
-  Hmm.
- And listen,
I'm not usually one to complain.
You're really gonna use
the "jet lag" excuse.
With you? Never.
I use "global imminent threat"
with you.
I'll see you tomorrow. Hmm?
I hope so.
- Let's go meet a guy.
- No.
It's never about just meeting a guy.
We talked about that.
And this is what I was talking about.
♪ One night in Dubai ♪
All right, so what am I picking up?
I don't know.
What?
What are you even doing here?
Honestly.
You and I both know that
Emirati Intelligence is not following me.
Greer just asked me to make sure
that everything went well.
Why does that make me more nervous?
Look, you're doing Greer a favor,
he's doing one for me.
How's that?
I need the money.
Don't you own a house
on the coast of everywhere?
Well, remember when you had me
bring a known arms dealer
to a party and use him as bait?
- Maybe.
- That got out.
- Yeah.
- All right.
This is where I leave you, buddy.
Wow. Dinner and a show.
Think you were just meeting a guy?
- So, how do I get to you after the--
- I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Earpiece.
God, I missed this.
Missed what?
This.
Being out in the field,
being part of a team.
Don't look directly at me.
That's a dead giveaway.
Might as well just touch your earpiece.
Sorry.
Looks like we found our man.
Got him.
Hi.
Thank you.
- Keep moving.
- All right.
Where are you going, buddy?
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Easy. Greer sent me.
You're supposed to be Greer.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hang on.
Who are you?
- Just a courier.
- Courier?
Do you have it?
Have what?
What do you think this is, huh?
What has he told you?
He said that you had a package
and that you were a friend.
"A friend."
Is that what he told you?
Jack!
You got a tail!
Oh, Jesus Christ. You're one of them.
Wait, wait. Wait.
Just... wait.
Where the fuck is Greer?
Well, I'm here now. All right?
So, clearly he sent me for a reason.
And why do you think that is?
I assume because he wants me to help you.
Help me?
He's the one who needs the help.
Stop!
Shit.
Your friend sent you
because he's scared, and...
...he's right to be.
Jack.
Get off the boat!
Put your fucking hands up.
Put them up!
Jesus.
What are you doing, man? Hey!
Who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck are you?!
Jack!
-  He's got to have something.
- We got to go!
Get in.
Fuck.
You'd already be dead.
Drive.
Fucking drive!
Goddamn it, Jack.
Yes?
- Anything?
- Not yet, sir.
- What's that?
- Oh, for you.
Not sure why it got mixed up.
They're probably not used to
the deputy director getting regular mail.
Keep trying.
Yes, sir.
Greer.
Good to hear
your voice.
How the hell did you get this number?
Oh, come on, Jim.
I've got friends everywhere.
You told me that.
You know all these calls are recorded.
No fun if they're not.
I need you to find your boy
and tell him to give back
what Nigel took from me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Jim, the only reason
he's still alive is because
you and I both know
he shouldn't have been there at all.
This call is a courtesy.
Nigel tried to shut us down.
Don't make the same mistake.
Listen to me.
Find your boy, Jim. Or I will.
You know, I got to be honest with you.
Coming all the way from the States,
I thought I'd be wrecked, but...
-  I feel pretty great.
- Please stop talking.
Come on, man.
He said this was gonna be easy.
Same thing Greer told you.
You know, maybe your new gig will be like,
"Hey, look, our guy's still a spy.
That's cool."
You know, that kind of thing?
No.
Because that's not a thing.
That's a thing.
Sit.
So who was he?
Oh, we'll find out, as soon as
the police have time with the body.
Your friend in there, Mike November,
he has people looking for him
in Dubrovnik,
the kind of people
I wouldn't mind owing me a favor.
I can get him a jet
chartered there in an hour.
And you, Jack Ryan, I'm sure you're
about to tell me that you're a civilian.
- It's 'cause I am.
- That's good.
Make things easier
for Emirati Intelligence,
because you're their prime suspect
in a double homicide.
Really? Even though
you're the one who pulled the trigger.
From what angle?
You heard the shot, and you saw me
appear from the opposite side.
Come on.
I heard you were smarter than this.
Well, if you think you know me,
then you know I have friends.
Uh-huh.
Same friend in that photograph?
The same friend who put your life at risk
instead of his own?
And the same friend
who killed a man in Karachi.
Did he ever tell you that story?
The way I heard it, Greer stabbed an asset
that was gonna get him killed
but instead got him demoted
and transferred back to Langley.
Did you ever hear
anything different to that?
- Don't think so.
- No?
I didn't think so.
So, this...
...this is the man Greer killed.
I don't see any stab wounds.
I mean, stab wounds are messy.
But torture done right?
That's... that's pretty clean.
You're trying to tell me that James Greer
tortured this man to death?
No, not personally,
but he trained the men who did.
What do you know about Starling?
- Starling?
- Yes.
I hear it's a bird.
By the look on your face,
he really told you absolutely nothing.
Greer and Nigel were handpicked to create
an interagency task force days after 9/11.
It was a black ops unit,
it was created out of pure rage,
and their rules, or their lack of them,
reflected that sentiment.
They racked up a hell of a body count
in the early days of the war.
But then, you know, councils
and committees came into fashion,
and, well, in Karachi,
James Greer took the fall for
the entire program without naming names.
Names like Nigel.
Names like Crown.
Liam Crown.
- Did Greer ever mention that name?
- No.
Nothing?
Last night, all I was there to do
was pick something up from Nigel,
- and I didn't get anything.
- There was nothing to get.
Last night wasn't a drop. It was a meet.
Anything Nigel had,
he would only tell Greer.
Well, then I'm seeing
very little use for me.
Answers.
I wanted them from Nigel.
Now I want them from Greer.
Well, you've very clearly proven
that I don't work for Greer.
You're absolutely right.
Unless you want things to continue
going poorly for you in Dubai...
...you work for me.
You're not really gonna make me
go to this thing alone, are you?
You don't need me to charm
a room full of politicians.
Jack.
Jesus Christ. What the hell is going on?
Wait.
Emma.
Andrew.
Aren't you going to introduce me
to your new friends?
I'm not sure that I'd actually call them--
No. You're right.
Let's make sure I don't have to arrest you
before we get all chummy.
Shall we?
Where the fuck have you been?
Dubai.
I would've thought that was clear.
- Apologies if I was difficult to reach.
- Ah.
That's bullshit.
You were working with Nigel
behind our back.
On the contrary.
Nigel didn't know I was shadowing him.
So you questioned his motives as well?
Never his motives.
Only his safety.
Marlow, we have
an international incident on our hands.
A decorated officer is dead.
And he won't be the last.
What did you find on his killer?
How do you know we found anything?
Because if you hadn't, I'd be in cuffs.
You need me to analyze it for you.
All of this.
And does this analysis hinge on
the two Americans trailing this vehicle?
One of them.
Nigel was supposed to meet
Deputy Director Greer on that boat.
With Nigel gone, Greer is the only one
with direct intel on Starling.
What the hell's Starling?
Well, you have to ask Greer, sir.
You expect me to extract intel
from the deputy director of the CIA?
No.
Not you.
Officer Marlow, can you show Dr. Ryan
to one of the conference rooms
to meet the deputy director?
This way.
And you, Mr. November?
Right. How's the coffee?
Listen, I know
what you're bringing into that room.
- I don't think you have any idea.
- Just remember,
you burn Greer, we have no way in.
Jack, listen.
I'm sorry about what happened.
I think you know me well enough that--
Based on the intel, one can assume
that I don't really know you well at all.
- I imagine Officer Marlow read you in.
- On what?
Starling?
No. Just like you,
Nigel kept her pretty well in the dark.
That was for her protection.
And mine?
The fact that you failed to tell me
about any of the shit
that was going on over there,
was that for my protection, too?
What was she doing in Dubai?
She was probably concerned about Nigel.
See, that's where I'm confused.
Why would she be concerned?
Was sent to me 24 hours ago.
Who are they?
Mark Whitaker and Tobias Wilks.
Jesus. Whitaker. I know him. He was--
Former CIA.
Wilks, MI6.
See, now, how would you know that?
- Because Nigel was running them both.
- But I thought Starling was dead.
- It was. I shut it down.
- When?
Oh, that's right. Just before we met.
When you were demoted
for stabbing a guy in Karachi.
Sorry, do I finally have that story right?
I told you, I shut it down.
Now, two years ago,
Wilks came to Nigel after being recruited
by a secret military contractor.
Let me guess, Crown.
A year in, when Wilks realized
the true scope of what he was a part of--
Do you mean an unsanctioned black ops team
specifically designed for
psychological warfare, assassinations,
the arming and training of
known terrorist groups to wipe out others?
All, of course, with no regard
for rules or consequences?
When he realized what he was a part of,
Wilks reached out to a former officer.
Wow, this Nigel really seems like
a class favorite.
Nigel reached out to me
to let me know
that Crown had resurrected Starling.
What they were doing, what they had done.
Now, he knew he couldn't stop Crown
in short order,
so he did the next best thing.
Which was what?
Monitor the situation.
Till Crown found out.
I-I didn't know.
That's about the time you sent me, right?
I didn't know.
- A civilian.
- I didn't know.
Down to Dubai.
When two rogue agents' covers were blown.
When two operators were killed
- cleaning up some bullshit mess...
- Of course I didn't know--
- Oh, grow the fuck up!
- ...you created 20 years ago!
Civilian my ass!
So don't you stand here in some shit suit
pretending to play Wall Street with me,
after what you've seen,
after what you've done.
It's a goddamn disgrace
to you and your country.
- So that's what this is about?
- Yeah, isn't it?
Walking away from the darkness isn't
the same thing as walking into the light.
So you can save
your holier-than-thou speech.
- I don't have speeches.
- Yes, you do.
You damn near wear it on your chest.
When you walked through that door,
that was the first thing I saw.
You don't care a goddamn about answers.
Except that you want to read me
the fucking riot act!
Twenty years ago,
there was nothing but darkness.
Every minute we lost with red tape,
one of these monsters slipped away.
Starling was created out of
goddamn fucking common sense.
When you're being attacked,
the rules change.
Then, I wonder, why have them at all?
With every strike, with every death,
we saved lives!
Did it come at a cost? Of course it did.
It came at a cost.
And it's only in peacetime
afforded by that cost
that people get to pretend that it didn't.
Is that what you think?
You think I don't realize
that this comes with a cost?
Take a good look. I am the cost.
Every night that I come home
to nothing, to no one,
and every day that I wake up and realize
that that dream that they sent me
out to fight for may not even exist!
Well, find the fucking courage
to fight for it anyway.
Because there are people in this world
that kill the monsters
so you don't have to.
They hold the gates shut
with their bare hands.
They're intelligent. They're dangerous.
And when you tell them
that everything they sacrificed for
wasn't up to your specifications,
that they are the monsters,
well, some might repent,
but others, others will show you
what this world looks like
when the gates are wide open.
What's the difference between you and him?
I don't know.
Maybe nothing.
And maybe it's you.
You and your goddamn moral compass.
You and your unshakable belief
between right and wrong.
Maybe I'm just jealous.
And maybe I'm just wrong.
But somewhere in the middle,
there's a truth.
And if you can't accept the color
of that truth, well, then...
I guess...
you are just a fucking analyst.
Right, let's get started, then.
Dr. Ryan, it's my understanding
that you no longer work for the CIA.
Well, that was my understanding, too.
And now?
Contract basis.
Understood.
Dr. Ryan, Officer Marlow claims
that nothing was recovered by you
during your interaction with Nigel Cooke.
Yes.
That's correct.
Right.
Well, thanks to cooperation
from SIGINT in Dubai,
we uncovered a hard drive
from Nigel's assassin.
Yusuf Bajwa.
No doubt the intel intended
for Deputy Greer.
It was partially damaged, but
Claudia managed to recover a few elements.
Claudia?
As Deputy Spear mentioned,
most of the drive was damaged by water.
However, we were able
to uncover the following.
What are we looking at?
These are surveillance images
of the Karakoram mountain range,
due east of Kabul and overlapping into
the northern territories
of Pakistan and China.
Uh, the companion file, however--
Is that London?
Yes, sir.
The other file appears to be
from a much more recent surveillance op
with photos, along with encoded schematics
and several bank statements.
What was the last transaction?
A withdrawal.
Taken four days ago from an ATM
at the corner of Middlesex Street
and Harrow Place.
Aldgate.
How would you possibly know that?
Because I know this plan.
I stopped it 20 years ago.
The plot was organized by the PMN,
a radicalized military group
we infiltrated under Starling.
The objective?
They were gonna bomb Tower Bridge.
- Greer?
- Elizabeth, we have a problem.
What kind of problem?
Important enough for you to get to London.
Okay. Thank you, everyone.
I suggest that you shut down
the bridge immediately.
I'm-I'm sorry, b-based on what?
Fractured intel referencing a plot
you say you've already prevented?
Nigel died for that intel.
He knew what it would mean to me.
And what would it mean?
That Starling has been resurrected.
Resurrected by who?
Liam Crown.
Liam Crown?
National hero Liam Crown?
Recipient of the Victoria Cross?
We were getting there, sir.
I'd say we're fucking there!
Tell me everything
you know about Crown.
Elizabeth.
For your own protection--
In case you've forgotten,
I'm not the one who needs protection.
I met Crown and Nigel
on our way to Karachi.
We were following
the Pakistani Militant Nexus.
The PMN were planning strikes
all over the world,
- but their primary target...
- Let's go.
...was London.
Our methods were brutal.
Sometimes
all we extracted was poison.
A confession led us to
Karachi's wealthiest neighborhood.
Crown managed to get one of the PMN alive.
A deputy chief of staff
within the Pakistani army.
It was my job to interrogate him.
What that man gave us led our people
to a safe house in Aldgate.
The bombing was stopped
three hours before it was meant to go off.
And the man you interrogated?
He suffered a heart attack,
extracting the information.
So you took the fall.
Yes.
And that's when Starling was shut down?
Or so we thought.
Nigel discovered that Crown never stopped
running Starling's operations.
Jesus.
To what end?
Crown is the kind of soldier who believes
we'll never be able to protect ourselves
with politics and diplomacy.
And after 9/11, he learned firsthand
that the only way to make a difference
is to be willing to do the things
no one else will.
So why put us at risk?
Because now he feels betrayed.
We were trying to put him down.
He's sending a message.
He wants us to know
he'll do exactly
what we trained him to do.
Which is what?
Whatever it takes.
This better be worth it.
Nigel risked everything he had
going over there alone to get this.
Emma, listen, I'm very sorry that--
Did you mean what you said?
Did I say something?
About realizing the dream you fought for
may never exist.
Oh, my God.
Didn't know that MI6
bugs their conference rooms.
That would be unethical.
I bugged your jacket.
How long?
A lady never tells.
Nigel was left out in the open.
I had to be sure
Greer wasn't working with Crown.
Learning more about you...
was a fringe benefit.
Well, you don't make it easy to trust you.
I make it impossible.
Unless our loyalties temporarily align.
What do you care about my dreams, anyway?
They sound familiar.
Hey.
You two seeing this,
or your shitty camera footage
better than my eyes?
All right. Stay on him.
Yeah, yeah.
Every time.
Welcome back, Colonel.
Or I guess it's Director now.
You've come a long way
since our time at CENTCOM.
Yes, we both have.
But I miss it every day.
It's good to see you.
Elizabeth.
Thank you for coming.
- I know the circumstances are--
- You did your job, James.
Nothing to apologize for.
And for you? Always.
Go.
Green light! Green light!
Go in, back in.
- Chief.
- Director.
Thank you for seeing us
on such short notice.
Of course.
Deputy Director Greer.
Chief.
Right this way, please.
Oh!
Goddamn it!
Hey!
- Move!
- Go, go!
-  Armed police!
Go, go, go!
Armed police!
I don't know about you,
but even with experience,
I find it difficult
to express the weight
these situations carry.
-  Move, move, move!
-  The simple fact
that one person can have
such a concrete perspective
that there is nothing left in this world
to offer but darkness.
And that they would come to the conclusion
that there is no light left to fight for.
Jesus.
Suspect's in custody.
Well, I'd say we better get him
the fuck up here, wouldn't you?
We rely on our soldiers
holding a spear to poke holes in the dark.
As a soldier,
this man sitting next to me...
...he is the tip of that spear.
And as a mentor...
...my assurance of hope.
Yeah.
Jack, what do you got?
It's exactly what you said.
He's got everything
but a model of Tower Bridge.
Enough explosives to blow the foundation.
Fuck me.
You talk to him?
Well, right now,
his story is it's not his.
Yeah, these assholes will never learn.
He's a courier.
He was paid to accept a package.
That's it.
- Somebody sent him the equipment?
-  It's bullshit.
Forensics are turning the place over now.
No way he does this on his own.
His story might be bullshit,
but the dots connect.
Okay, listen, the meeting just finished.
I'll take Wright back to the embassy.
I'm riding with him.
Is that Jack?
If that's him,
you're not taking me anywhere just yet.
Look, clearly,
the intel is good. It just doesn't--
It just doesn't add up.
And why leave him out in the open?
All this firepower, and
they just leave him out here all alone?
- It makes no sense.
-  Come on, Jack.
I'm risking more than my ass on this shit.
- You go in there and get me something.
- Holy shit.
What?
"Out in the open."
- Where are you?
-  What? What is it?
Jesus.
What if Crown's trying to set us up?
Took all our firepower
to look the other way?
Look the other way from what?
From you.
Elizabeth!
Greer!
- He's down.
-  What?
- Greer's down!
- Shit.
This is Officer Two Zero Juliet Lima.
Heading southwest
towards Leadenhall.
ETA to GOGGS: less than ten.
Copy,
Officer Marlow.
Getting the coordinates now.
Get out of the way! Goddamn it.
Get out of the way!
Come on, pick up.
Shit.
Come on!
Pursuit heading east
on Horse Guards.
L-Left, left! Go left!
Take the tunnel. Go!
Go, go, go, go.
You got a key for this?
Jack!
Fucker.
Move.
Crown!
Turn around!
Goddamn it!
You good?
Hey, look at me, look at me.
You all right?
You hurt? Huh?
- She's gone.
- Who is?
Wright.
She's gone.
Overwatch has us.
Local police arriving.
- We got to get him out of here.
- Jack, it's over. We got to bring him in.
You're looking at
the acting director of the CIA,
and someone's trying to kill him.
We need to make him disappear.
Now, get up.
- Then we got to move. Go!
- Come on, come on, come on. All right.
Move, move, move!
Turn.
Lower.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
Thank you, sir.
When do they want you back?
If they think I'm leaving
after what he just did, what she just--
Nothing you could do.
You know that, right?
No way you could've known.
She was the light.
In the darkness.
Yes, sir.
Ready.
Whenever you are.
I think it's clear nobody inside or out
can be trusted.
So, if you're asking yourselves
what we are doing here
or why I have invited this gentleman--
Yeah, I am. To both.
Colonel Jones, at your service.
Welcome to Abingdon,
a once great training station
for the RAF Bomber Command,
now closed and used as a satellite
airstrip for military helicopter training.
I grew up with the Colonel.
He still sweeps
my family's steps on holidays
and has made his affections
known to me twice.
- Three times.
- Regardless,
we need someone to help interface
with operations moving forward.
He has not been read in.
He has excused all personnel
that were not handpicked.
It's not foolproof, but it's something.
Thank you, Colonel.
All right. Well, after today,
I think it's clear that
Crown planned this from the beginning.
He planted that hard drive on Bajwa.
He knew that Emirati Intelligence
would share it with MI6,
and he knew that you would recognize
the PMN plot attack.
He also knew how MI6 would respond.
He knew about the meeting,
and he knew where it would be.
He knew all that
because he planned everything.
So how do we find him?
Who were the shooters at Saint Paul's?
We identified two of the bodies.
But they weren't PMN.
Not even remotely.
Both had ties to an obscure Russian
paramilitary group called the Otomstits.
- "Otomstits."
- They were formed in the '80s,
but were effectively eliminated
in the mid-2000s.
Starling.
Jesus Christ.
So Crown is reactivating terrorist groups?
No.
Crown is reactivating terrorist groups
that Starling shut down.
What does he want?
- To prove a point.
-  Prove a point?
Prove the point.
That if it weren't for operations
like Starling to stop them,
these terrorist groups would be free
to carry out attacks just like today
all around the world, anytime.
Because that is what happens
when you leave the gates open.
So that's why Nigel was in Dubai,
to kill Crown.
No. He was in Dubai for me.
What was his objective?
He had infiltrated Crown's operation
to supply the necessary intel
so our agency could take him down.
He was trying to warn you.
Yeah, well, given how today played out,
I would say that Crown was
trying to kill you.
- I wish he had.
- Yeah, well, guess what.
Now you're the director
of the goddamn CIA.
Let's see where this son of a bitch
pops his head up.
You're the director of the CIA.
He got more than he planned for.
- What?
- When Wright got in that car, he pivoted.
He realized he had an opportunity.
You said it yourself: It's our agency
that was gonna shut him down.
Well, what if he had a director
that would let him go free?
- He knows I would kill him.
- No.
I think he'd have
a contingency plan for that.
Sorry to interrupt.
We've got a bit of a situation.
He said it was for James Greer.
How the fuck did he find us?
Check it.
Clear!
I know where he is.
Keep your eyes open.
He'll be here.
Got him.
What do you want?
You know, as the story goes,
they brought in dirt
all the way from Virginia
so their virtuous hero's feet
never again had to touch British soil.
Amazing, the things we do for honor.
Or at least the appearance of it, anyway.
Please.
We all know what happens
when you go waving that around.
There's gonna be no heroics today, Jim,
not from you,
not from your arms dealer waiting in line.
Fuck.
And not even from your wonder boy
standing over there with Blonde Ambition.
Which I've got to be honest with you, Jim,
I'm... I'm not so sure about him.
What do you want?
You know what I want.
I want to know what you know.
You knew that Nigel had betrayed us.
He was gathering intel to use against us.
What I knew was our dog had gone
off his fucking leash.
Intel you were gonna use against my men.
Your men.
The same men that fought your ghost wars
to keep your country safe.
Only one man needs to be put down.
You think you're the man to do it, Jim?
Because now it's you
that has to live with ghosts.
You motherfucker.
Don't!
No hesitation.
Remember?
What do you want?
I want you to go home.
Continue the great work
that you started all those years ago.
Before the power shifted.
Before your... your country woke up
with a fucking conscience.
We held the world in balance.
I want you to give my men--
your men-- the chance to do that again.
And you can start by giving me back
what Nigel stole from me.
I don't, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Jim, the longer we wait,
the more people are gonna die.
I don't have anything.
Jesus Christ.
He doesn't have it.
I do.
Well, look at you.
I'd like that back now, please.
You really think I'd bring
something like that out in the open?
Well, don't tell me you gave it to MI6.
After what happened to Nigel?
How could I possibly trust MI6?
There's hope for your boy yet, Jim.
Oh.
You didn't know?
Just beautiful.
Where is it?
I left it in Dubai.
Okay, then.
Dubai it is.
Where would you like me to bring it?
I think it became pretty clear today.
I'll find you.
What the fuck was he talking about?
Nigel handed something off
and you didn't tell me?
- No, I lied.
- You what?
I bought us some time.
I promise you,
he handed me nothing but this.
You can check it. It's clean.
There has to be something.
Crown said that he saw it
with his own eyes.
Which is exactly why Nigel gave it to me.
If you thought I was there
to pick something up, then Crown did, too.
Nigel knew Crown was watching,
so he had to give me something.
So, what the hell
are we looking for?
The night Nigel's agents were killed,
were there any transmissions?
Any communication at all?
- I have no idea. I was in the dark.
- Shit!
There had to be.
The urgency to find me,
those guys giving their lives.
Well, good news is
we got a whole 24 hours to find it.
I mean, depending how deep they got,
they could have had access to anything--
files, plans, financials.
Whatever it was, he would've left it
for someone he trusted.
Can you get us into his office at MI6?
MI6?
How could he possibly trust them?
Ah, well, thank fuck.
Hello, Arthur.
I was starting to get worried.
He's fine. He's traveling.
There's no need to worry.
Him? I couldn't give two shits
about your father.
It's the 400 quid he owes me
had my heart all aflutter.
That's why I'm here,
to settle his account.
You got the key?
Fine.
Tell him we miss him.
Will do.
So this is what I have to look forward to.
No one knows about this place?
No.
Except his daughter, of course.
When you can't actually get close, pretend.
Yikes.
Does that thing even still work?
Pre-Internet.
No built-in search engines.
- Well, that's smart.
- Yeah.
So, save your judgments.
Huh.
-  What?
-  Ah, he kept photos.
And watched them fade.
I just always thought,
if I was to meet someone, that--
Ha.
I'd have to keep her
as far away from this world as possible.
Mm-hmm?
How'd that go for you?
- Really well, thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
- How about you?
- Yeah, the same.
They're probably together right now.
Then he did really well for himself.
She did not.
Nothing.
No emails, no texts.
Even last opened files are
all time-stamped a week before Dubai.
- Any open websites, programs...
- No.
...chat rooms?
Chat rooms?
Still on AOL, are you?
Maybe.
You mind if I...?
Sure, yeah.
But good luck, because if you think
his apartment's a mess,
you should see his hard drive.
Oh, boy.
Wouldn't make sense, anyway.
If he did send something,
it would be too high risk.
It would just be sitting out
for all to see.
But why would it be a risk
if no one knows he's here?
♪ Ooh, baby...
Whoa! What was that? Oh.
All right, well, listen,
I may still have AOL,
but even I gave up on music torrents.
And you're okay with
saying words like that out loud?
- Torrents?
- Yes. Those words.
- Didn't you go to college?
- No.
- Yeah. Torrents are, like, a music site.
- Thank you.
- Like, downloadable. Napster.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I've got you.
You were an Internet chess player?
Now look who's being judgy.
No, it's not like that.
It's just, any site that has an active...
With an off-site server.
Cheeky bastard.
Holy shit. You were right.
He didn't upload anything.
He was monitoring transmissions live.
From where?
Yello.
Wh-- No, we don't say "yello."
Jack.
Listen, I need your help, all right?
Need you to help me find the source
of this network connection.
Sending it to you now.
Okay. Yeah.
- You're a civilian now.
- Yep.
And you swore a very long and wordy oath
to protect said civilian, me.
So that is your job.
As long as I have a job.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
Eat your heart out, Madonna.
Okay, I'm ready.
"Blonde Ambition."
- Hmm?
- Jack?
Trafalgar Square,
Crown called you Blonde Ambition.
He's been here.
You're sure no one else knows
about this place?
Yes.
Not even Spear?
Got a lot of bad options.
We don't find the intel,
another strike comes.
If we do?
The director of the CIA is
negotiating with a terrorist.
The president's sort of got a thing
about that.
Third option is we kill him.
Only way this ends, the way I see it.
You know, Mike,
I appreciate you being here.
But you don't have to be.
I know that.
Y-You know what's funny?
You and Jack, you guys are always going
at each other, what's right, what's wrong.
Both just struggling
to accept the real fucking truth.
Me? I came to terms with it
a long time ago.
And what truth is that?
The three of us?
The only family we're ever gonna have.
Once you know that, you know
exactly where you're supposed to be.
Huh. The missus as we speak.
Hey. You find anything?
You bet your ass I can do that.
Hang on.
Got ourselves another option.
Jack.
Where the hell are you?
With Ryan, tracking down a lead.
A lead?
Well, what kind of a lead?
He thought he'd found a way
to decrypt the hard drive Nigel gave him,
so I brought him to the Flagon.
- Do you know it?
- His apartment? Yeah.
And?
Was there anything there?
No.
Dead end.
He didn't have a hard drive.
It was a server.
Server?
What server?
You said you needed Nigel to provide you
with enough intel to take Crown down.
Well, what if he found the source
of Crown's entire operation,
and that's what he was trying
to transmit live that night from Dubai?
Dubai.
Crown must have stopped him
before he could.
Jesus.
And your plan is?
We're gonna try again.
All right, here we go.
This is never going to work.
Just keep your head down.
They're leaving.
-  Who is?
- Greer and November.
They're headed home.
What about Ryan?
He never came back to rendezvous.
Maybe he's already on his way
to retrieve the package?
Well, we'd know.
Move out with Greer.
Mm-kay.
Were you expecting
an agency escort?
No, it's just, you know,
first unexpected thing today.
Well, it won't be the last.
They should be inbound to you
in less than 20.
Copy that. Yes, sir.
And hey, you're still on the clock.
What, you mean, like, today, or are you
talking a more permanent kind of thing?
Well, let's see how today goes.
All right. Great.
I don't even look like him.
Ryan and Marlow are in play.
Say cheese.
No.
Oh, today's gonna be a long day.
Folks, if I could have your
attention for a quick safety briefing.
- Oh, come on, man.
- Hey.
FAA regulations there, tough guy.
Are we ready?
I mean, that's a bigger question than
we probably have time for, but--
- The plane.
- Oh, shit, yeah.
All right. Then let's go.
James.
Chief.
I appreciate the ride home.
Anytime.
Stocked it myself.
Now, if there's anything else
I can do for you, just let me know.
You've done more than enough.
And, Director.
I very much look forward
to working with you again.
Talk to me.
I got a full house.
I'm heading to the party.
Time.
You ready?
We're on our way.
We're meeting the team on the other side.
What team?
Called in a favor
from Emirati Intelligence.
Are you
out of your goddamn mind?
We can't operate in Dubai.
Oh, not operating.
Escorting.
What?
They've gone and contacted
fucking Emirati Intelligence.
Well, that won't do them much good.
I sure as hell hope not.
Officer Marlow.
I'm Jamal Ali.
Thank you for taking the call.
An honor.
I worked closely with your mentor...
I was very saddened by the news.
Well, I'm sure he would appreciate that.
So, you need a ride?
Please say Bentley. Please say Bentley.
Sure that one
would be pretty good in traffic.
Sadly, that one is already spoken for.
This way.
Hi, Mom.
Hi, honey. Where are we going?
Right. Okay.
The outgoing signal
to the modem was pinged
at two-four-point-zero-six-zero-six.
Is that a longitude?
'Cause I know you're not reading me
longitude, latitude right now, right?
Sorry. Sorry.
Uh, okay.
You're heading towards Dubai Marina.
Yeah.
Lovely.
Let's find out where they're going.
I don't give a shit what SIGINT says.
I want satellite footage
of Dubai right now.
Now!
That's why Dubai has no crime?
No, no.
We have no crime because
we never need to use them.
How's that?
The eye in the sky.
Dubai is one of the most technologically
advanced cities in the world.
We'll see you commit a crime
almost before you do it.
That's comforting.
I'm genuinely comforted.
We've begun our descent, sir.
Not long now.
Can I get you anything?
No, thank you.
You can hold on to this.
How many do you think?
I assume we're dealing with
a more localized security team.
So, what, like, five, ten?
Sure.
Let's go with that.
Sir.
Cheeky fucking bastards.
We really appreciate your help.
Please. I-I only wish we could do more.
As you know, we cannot legally assist
in any foreign intelligence operation.
Unless, of course, it became
an incident of national security.
Well... let's go cause an incident.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Okay, here we go.
We're really doing this.
We can hear you.
Sorry.
Just breathe.
Thank you.
Contact left!
- Move!
- Contact what?
Holy shit.
Four up top!
Move!
Glass!
Clear!
Shit.
That's on me.
We're clear now.
All right. Last stop.
Where are we going?
Uh, take a right down the corridor.
On the other side, gentlemen.
No hesitation.
Split up!
It looks like the signal is
on a floor higher up.
Stairs.
Race you to the top.
All right. Where are we going?
The network that originated the signal
is on that floor.
Shit.
-  What?
- Security door.
You're welcome.
Let's go, gentlemen.
Hey, Mike, I hate to bother,
but you are...?
Looking for the back door.
Yeah, see, I'm not even gonna guess
what that means.
Move.
That's all you, Napster.
Wow. Really never gonna live
that one down, am I?
All right, Patrick.
Let's make some magic here.
Yeah.
He would've accessed the port
through the back of the server rack.
Got it. Okay.
All right, here we go.
Connecting you to the server... now.
Patrick, you getting this?
Yes, sir.
What am I looking at?
It's his entire network.
Emma.
Ryan!
Jack?
How long?
Uh, 45%.
Not you.
How long?
We're in the air.
What now, Jack?
Move.
Patrick, how long?
We're almost there.
Mike?
On it.
Anytime.
Very, very good, Jack.
You were supposed to pick up a package.
And now you have it.
Grenade!
Patrick!
Done!
Back fucking door, baby!
Yes!
Time to go.
Okay. Okay, okay.
All right, all right.
I thought you said it was time to go.
You're all right. You're all right.
Let's check. Let's check in here.
Move here, move here.
Okay, I got you.
You just breathe.
Breathe, breathe.
Breathe for me. Breathe.
Okay. Okay.
- You're all right.
-  Hey, Jack?
Relax, it's all right.
You're okay. I'll be right back.
Did we get her?
Are you really willing to die for this?
For Greer?
Brother, I could've told you
you can't trust him.
He'll just leave you.
Is this it?
Go out in a blaze of glory?
Is that the plan?
No.
Ghost 1 has arrived.
But this was.
Light him up.
I'll begin by saying
I'm not proud of what I've done.
Pride shouldn't enter
into affairs of state.
But part of our job is
to give our nation pride,
to uphold the ideal of who we are
and who we wish to be,
at any cost.
But if that ideal is based on lies,
then our institutions begin to crumble,
making us susceptible to division.
Even infiltration.
When I returned home, I was broken.
But then I met someone
who brought me back.
Did we get you?
I will always have faith
in the light.
Faith in the men and women
who hold the spears,
the ones who are brave enough
to poke holes in the dark.
I think I got you wrong.
You know exactly what it takes.
Go ahead.
Do it.
Tip of the spear.
Let me show you how.
No hesitation.
His name is Jack Ryan.
And it's my recommendation, Mr. President,
that he serve as my deputy director.
Andrew.
A word.
You know, you really should quit.
So should you.
You good?
Alive.
Hey, remember when you said
that it was impossible to trust you?
Unless our loyalties temporarily align?
- Yeah.
I was just wondering
what that criteria might look like.
Our loyalties aligning?
Yeah.
Start smoking.
You all right?
Yeah.
Other than being angry
that you're always right?
Civilian my ass.
I'm fine, by the way.
Thanks for asking.
I know.
You nervous?
What?
Well, you just seem a bit nervous.
Why the hell would I be nervous?
You're in this shit with me.
Thanks for coming.
For you?
Always.