( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Imperial Brother asked you
to change into the clothes
of us Central Plains people.
Yet you disobeyed him.
You're truly a barbarian.
Unable to understand human language.
This time, your father
is taking Concubine Chen
and her son on the autumn hunt.
If you can't take this opportunity
to trample Yin Qi,
you might as well stay in the palace
and save yourself the embarrassment.
Concubine Chen must have used some tricks
to seduce Father.
Father has never taken them
on the autumn hunt before.
So.
You must demonstrate
your unparalleled strength as the candidate
for the crown prince
and let your father see it.
Otherwise
the little bit of favor he has for you
will be taken away by the other princes.
These things are of no benefit to you.
Don't let me see them again in the future.
Fu'an.
What orders does Your Highness have?
This tea has lost its flavor.
How did you serve it?
Your Highness, please forgive me
I'll bring you fresh tea right away.
Your Highness, please rest for a while
I've brought you your
favorite persimmon cakes.
The persimmon cakes from the fruit
shop on West street are the sweetest.
You'll definitely like them.
Are they sweet?
"Journey With You"
(Episode 4)
The Emperor has ordered General Zhang
to go and guard the border.
He has set off today.
Also, the manager of
Yunshang Pavilion has escaped.
Father has ultimately
followed the advice of Yin Qi.
Recently, Father hasn't just
taken the Imperial City Guard from me
and given it to him
but he has also weakened
Uncle's power considerably.
What else?
Your Highness.
The male concubine Lu wasn't rescued.
Just a male concubine.
If he's gone, he's gone.
Do you need to report
such trivial matters to me?
Understood.
As for the owner of Yunshang Pavilion.
Send someone to chase him
and execute him immediately.
Yes.
Yin Qi.
The price you've made me pay...
I'll make you repay it all.
Imperial Brother
really is something else.
He won't even let us
celebrate Mid-Autumn Festival.
If you want to fight, do it quickly.
Don't delay my important matters.
Why hasn't he come yet?
A Qi is never late
especially on such an important day.
I know... I know there's
poison on this knife.
A Qi.
A Qi, are you alright?
Don't scare me.
A Qi.
A Qi, don't scare me, A Qi.
My lord.
You encountered assassins.
Were they sent by Yin Zhou?
My lord, are you hurt?
Go and call Doctor Hu quickly.
Go.
Okay, okay.
Am I going to die again?
I haven't changed the
outcome for Yanzhi and me yet.
I can't die.
I'm afraid before the doctor arrives
the poison in A Qi's body
will take his life.
No.
Yanzhi.
No, Yanzhi.
I don't want you to get
hurt again because of me.
At a time like this
don't say such things.
If I don't suck out the poison
you'll die.
My lord.
The doctor is here.
Quickly, examine His Highness.
Doctor Hu, please.
How is he?
My lord.
The poison His Highness has is
called One-Day Drunkenness.
It's extremely fast-acting.
It reaches the heart and
lungs within three hours.
Fortunately, His Highness
is blessed with good fortune
and my lord treated him in time.
So.
His life is not in danger?
I'll administer acupuncture to His Highness
to clear the remaining
poison from his body.
It will clear the residual poison from his body
and he should be fine.
But His Highness has
suffered severe injuries
and the poison has
reached his heart and lungs.
He'll need time to recover.
He won't be able to use
martial arts for a while.
Thank you, Doctor Hu.
My lord.
Where are you going?
I know
you want to seek revenge on Yin Zhou.
But think about it
turning against him at this time
will ruin all the plans
we've been making for so long.
My lord.
Think twice.
Don't stop me.
My lord.
I know it's presumptuous of me to say this
but your growing feelings for the Fifth Prince
are becoming harder and harder to control
and will only drag him into this.
Ask yourself honestly.
Is this what you want?
If I hadn't rescued him today
no matter how flawless my plans were,
what good would they do?
Wenjie.
I know what I'm doing.
Take care of A Qi for me.
My Lord,
without my order,
you actually dared to leave the palace
and assassinate a prince?
If any clues are left behind
and Father finds out about me,
what will we do?
Yin Qi has been very active recently,
causing Your Highness
to suffer heavy losses.
I must eliminate him
to vent Your Highness's anger.
Whoever opposes Your Highness
is my enemy.
The first rule for someone who has
pledged their life is to obey my orders.
You dare to disobey this order?
It seems
you cannot be kept.
In consideration of your
years of loyalty to me,
I will not kill you.
Your Highness...
Go!
Don't let me see you again.
Your Highness,
This subordinate is willing
to accept any punishment.
Please, Your Highness,
do not drive me away.
This subordinate has fought
on the battlefield for many years
to have the chance to
protect Your Highness.
If you drive me away,
it would be better to just kill me.
Your Highness,
this subordinate knows he was wrong.
Please, Your Highness,
do not drive me away.
Oh, Young Master,
you've come at an inconvenient time.
Your Highness has given orders
to close the doors and not
receive any guests today.
Please, Young Master, go back.
I want to see Yin Zhou.
Didn't Young Master hear?
Your Highness is not
receiving any guests today.
Pei Yanzhi,
why is he here?
It's all for his Fifth Prince.
Go hide in the study.
If you act on your own again,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Yes, sir.
Fu'an,
let him in.
Do you know
that just by forcing your way
into Mingde Palace with a blade,
I can have your family
executed for your crime?
Why did you go back on your word
and send someone to assassinate A Qi?
How can I explain something.
I have never done?
You've tried every means
to drive A Qi to the border,
and when that failed,
you developed murderous intentions,
wanting to eliminate A Qi completely.
If you have no sincerity,
it seems our alliance
does not need to continue.
If you dare to give up halfway,
I will show you.
Yin Qi's fate
will be a hundred times worse than this.
Your Highness actually
has an alliance with him?
I shouldn't have been so reckless.
I actually made Your Highness cover for me.
Next time,
I must not fail.
Other than you,
who else wants to kill A Qi?
Don't forget
that Yin Qi caused Yunshang Pavilion
to be emptied overnight.
Do you think
they might
come back to take revenge on Yin Qi?
Just think about it,
if I am determined
to assassinate Yin Qi when he is
alone outside the palace,
how could it possibly fail?
I came here today to tell Your Highness.
A Qi
is my bottom line.
Your Highness should be clear
that you and I are on the same boat.
If I overturn this boat,
Your Highness
will be in danger yourself.
Why did Your Highness
become an ally with Pei Yanzhi?
It's because of you useless people.
If you could help me solve my problems,
would I still need to form
an alliance with a hostage?
This subordinate is useless.
Please, Your Highness, forgive me.
Does it hurt?
This subordinate never thought
Your Highness would defend me.
Just now,
this subordinate saw Your
Highness come to my rescue.
Does it also mean...
that in Your Highness's heart,
there is a trace of care for me?
This subordinate has overstepped.
Please, Your Highness, forgive me.
What is Pei Yanzhi worth?
He actually wants to hold
my people accountable.
In this world,
no one can punish you
except me.
You're right.
If even you are not by my side,
in this vast imperial city,
who else can understand my feelings?
Just being able to stay
by Your Highness's side
is a great favor
for this subordinate.
Where am I?
Your Highness was injured by
an assassin and was poisoned.
My lord was worried that
you wouldn't make it back to the palace,
so he brought you to Piaoxiang Pavilion.
Where's Yanzhi?
Where is he?
Your Highness, do you know
that your repeated investigations
into what my lord has done
will only bring him endless trouble?
Can you do something about you and
your lord's stubborness and bad temper?
If I don't stop Yanzhi,
I'll be pushing him to his doom.
Do you have to see his corpse
before you believe me?
Your Highness has grown up in the palace,
living a life of luxury.
How can you understand my lord's situation?
He has worked tirelessly for you,
and what do you do?
Instead of being grateful to him,
you come here and meddle.
If you really care about your lord,
then tell me
what he is planning.
My lord...!
Give us the room.
Why did you come to save me?
How did you leave the room?
Is this how you talk
to the person who saved you?
Did Heshu let you out?
Besides her,
no one else has the courage.
Even if you saved me,
I won't let you
carry out your plan.
A Qi,
I just don't understand
why do you always think
that I will definitely fail?
Brother,
I heard from Yanzhi that you were injured.
I was so worried.
Let me see where you're hurt.
If you keep shouting like this,
the whole palace
will know that I'm injured.
Don't worry,
your brother is fine.
Fortunately, the poison in my body
has been neutralized.
But it has still injured
your internal organs.
You still need to rest and recuperate.
This minister will go get the medicine now.
Thank you, Young Master.
Please come with this official to the
Imperial Hospital to get the medicine.
The Fifth Prince is by your side,
living in fear every day,
either getting injured or poisoned.
How are you taking care of him?
I thought you would
protect and take care of him,
but it turns out you're just a jinx.
It's all because of you
that he almost died.
People like you don't deserve
to stay by his side.
Whether I deserve to stay by his
side or not is not up to you to decide.
The matters between A Qi and me
are none of your business.
So,
last night, you didn't
clear things up at all.
And you got stabbed.
Yanzhi has always been
like this since he was a child.
If he doesn't want to say something,
no one can force him.
It seems
we need to use some special methods
to pry his mouth open.
Last night,
was it you
who secretly let Yanzhi out?
So what if it was?
If I hadn't been clever
and let Yanzhi out,
you might have already...
Anyway,
I can be considered your half-savior.
If you don't appreciate me, that's fine,
but hitting me...?
I was afraid that Yanzhi
would leave the room
and go work for Su He and Yin Zhou again.
What if
one day, everything is exposed?
Today, when you hadn't
returned to the palace yet,
Yanzhi caused a commotion in Mingde Palace
and turned everything upside down.
It might have been
to seek revenge for your
assassination last night
by going after Yin Zhou.
You're saying...
Yanzhi caused a commotion in Mingde Palace?
What?
Do you know how important
you are to Yanzhi now?
You must be overjoyed.
Don't be so disrespectful.
Your growing feelings for the Fifth
Prince will only drag him into this,
and make you lose your judgment.
Don't be so disrespectful.
People like you
simply don't deserve to stay by his side.
They were right.
No matter what,
A Qi must not be dragged
into this matter again.
Your wound hasn't healed yet.
Why did you come out?
Doctor Bai said I'm fine.
Today...
did you go to Mingde Palace
and make a scene with Yinzhou?
Even if I level Mingde
Palace to the ground,
it still can't make up for
the harm Yinzhou has done to you.
You said you wanted to
clear away all obstacles for me.
I know you care about me.
But what I want
is not constant concealment and protection.
Moreover
your so-called protection
is very likely to become a
blade that drives us apart.
That day...
you...
Your Highness.
This matter goes against the rules.
Have you not done things
that go against the rules?
You risked your life to secretly
escort my mother back to Jiangnan.
Do you dare to say
it wasn't for me?
Imperial Concubine Chen
treated me extremely well
I sent her back to Jiangnan
to repay her kindness.
Your Highness.
You'd better not think too much.
What about today?
Today.
Why did you go after Yinzhou?
If you really follow the rules so strictly
why did you allow yourself
to fall in love with me?
I didn't.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, please
take good care of yourself.
I won't come to Yunhe Palace for a while if
there's nothing important during this period.
Your Highness should rest now.
The wound is a bit deep.
It will take some time to heal.
This little wound
means nothing to me.
Your Highness
I've had something in
my heart for a long time.
If Your Highness turns back now
and stays away from all these disputes
you can still be a
carefree prince for life.
Am I so useless in your eyes
that you think in such a way?
That's not what I mean.
I'm willing to take care of Your Highness
for the rest of my life.
Even if the person in Your Highness's heart
is not me.
But
given time,
Your Highness might forget the one
who hurt you.
Nanxing.
Thank you for your kindness.
But
to make me forget Yanzhi...
I'm afraid...
I cannot.
I thought since we grew up together...
your Highness would
have a place for me in your heart.
Your Highness.
Are you really so deeply in
love with the young master
that you feel this way?
I only know
at the moment I was hurt
he was the one I most wanted to see.
However
it's all just my wishful thinking.
Yanzhi only regards me
as a brother.
Although I don't like the young noble
but in this matter.
I still have to speak
up for the young noble.
If your Highness thinks the young
noble doesn't care about you,
then you're really wronging him.
As bystanders
we can see clearly
what kind of feelings the
young noble has for you.
But sometimes
even I can't see it clearly myself.
Since the young noble cares
so much about Your Highness
but doesn't want Your Highness
to realize this care
that means in the young noble's view,
this affection
might bring danger to Your Highness.
Yanzhi fought with Yinzhou for me.
It shows that he hasn't
completely betrayed the Emperor
and become Yin Zhou's ally.
I must do everything in my power
to keep him by my side.
In this way
he won't go astray.
Heshu
I just heard from the servants
that A Qi is missing.
What does that mean?
What do they mean by missing?
At noon today
a guard saw him leave the palace
but he hasn't come back yet.
If he can't return to the
palace before curfew
it will be trouble if
the Emperor finds out.
Brother Yanzhi.
Do you know where my brother would go?
I think.
I can find him.
I hope my journey goes smoothly
to protect Yanzhi's family and clan
and to resolve the border
disputes for our country.
Yanzhi.
What wish did you make?
A Qi.
I hope that in this life
you will be safe, happy
free and fearless.
Yanzhi.
When you made this wish in your past life,
were you sincere?
How did you know I was here?
You put so much effort
into making the sky
lantern for Concubine Chen
you must want her to see it.
We fly sky lanterns every year.
Especially in the first year
after my mother passed away,
we must fly them,
otherwise she would worry.
Do you think
my mother can see this lantern?
This sky lantern
is the letter you wrote to Concubine Chen.
She will receive it.
Yanzhi.
I want to hear an
answer from you.
How do you feel about me?
A Qi.
You're confused because of your illness.
Why are you talking nonsense?
It's getting late.
Let's hurry back to the palace.
When will you finally admit
your feelings for me?
A Qi.
What nonsense are you talking about?
We...
are just good brothers.
There's no such thing as like or dislike.
You...
I once asked you
why you treated me so well.
You said that's how brothers should be.
I asked you again
why you risked your life to help me.
You said you had to
repay my mother's kindness.
You always talk about
righteousness, morality, loyalty,
and responsibility towards me.
Is there nothing else?
Do you still dare to say now
that we're just brothers?
Your hands are so cold.
Treating me like this.
Is it really worth it?
Your Highness.
If you do this,
the Crown Prince
will surely cause trouble for you.
Imperial Brother is always
good at using this trick.
I'm just using his own methods
to deal with him.
Let him make his move.
Only then can I find his flaws.
We know what to do.
You can go and attend
to your business first.
We shall take our leave.
Your wound hasn't healed yet.
Why did you come out again?
Because I know
you'll come to bring me a cloak.
I just saw
you giving instructions
to the Duan brothers.
Is it for this trip
to accompany His Majesty to Jiangnan?
This is the first time Heshu and I
are accompanying Father on a long journey.
There are still many things to arrange.
His Majesty taking you two
siblings to Jiangnan this time
is telling the court and the harem
that the Fifth Prince and Sixth Princess
are highly favored.
I'm worried
that your sharpness
will draw jealousy from others.
Other than Imperial
Brother, who else could it be?
I'm not afraid of his jealousy.
I'm more afraid he'll restrain himself
and I won't be able to catch his flaws.
A Qi,
why have you seemed like a different person
since Concubine Chen passed away?
From everything that has happened recently,
your appearance and attitude
are completely different from before.
A Qi,
can you tell me
why?
Is it because
you only like
the naive Yin Qi from before,
and the calculating Yin Qi
in front of you now
doesn't appeal to you anymore?
No matter how you change,
you'll always be my A Qi.
Then you must protect your A Qi well.
My lord,
the whole city is now talking about
the Fifth Prince becoming the Crown Prince.
If that's really the case,
our plan will be ruined.
Whether it His Majesty's intention
or is someone spreading rumors...
it is still unclear.
Yin Zhou must have also heard about
A Qi becoming the Crown Prince.
Given his personality,
he must be burning with anxiety.
Just now, Su He sent someone to report
that he's also going to Jiangnan.
Give the order to send an elite
force from Talhan to Jiangnan.
Let them pretend to be merchants
and divide into two teams.
Remember,
don't take it lightly.
With so many people
converging in Jiangnan at the same time,
I always feel
something will happen.
This subordinate understands.
Yin Zhou and the Fifth Prince
are at odds with each other,
and the one who suffers the most
is still My lord.
In any case,
for this trip to Jiangnan,
we must not take it lightly.
Make sure that the people secretly
protecting A Qi exercise caution.
Don't worry, my lord.
Senior,
why are you here?
For this trip to Jiangnan,
Xianyue and I will be accompanying.
Really?
With the senior's help,
we have nothing to worry about.
Brother Yanzhi,
look,
I've bought a lot of things
that will be useful for
our trip to Jiangnan.
The things in Jiangnan
are much more exquisite
than those in the capital.
You won't need any of these things.
Why is it you again?
I know better than you
what good things Jiangnan has.
You probably don't know
whose territory Jiangnan belongs to.
What do you mean by that?
Brother Yanzhi,
is she also going to Jiangnan?
Dear young master,
if you encounter any
difficulties in Jiangnan,
remember to come find me.
You...
Why does she get to go to Jiangnan too?
It infuriates me!
She's the richest merchant in Jiangnan.
Why do you think?
What?
She? A rich merchant? Looking like that?
Brother Yanzhi, you must be joking.
This princess wants to see
what she can do in Jiangnan.
Yin Zhou sent assassins
after me on Mid-Autumn Night,
showing that he wants to get rid of me
even more desperately
than in my previous life.
This time,
I won't let Jiangnan
become our grave again.
A Qi,
Aren't you on duty today?
Why did you come here?
I thought the weather was nice today
and wanted to accompany you for a walk.
You just arrived here
and aren't familiar with the terrain.
It's better to have someone with you.
I'm couldn't be more
familiar with this palace.
I don't just want to
walk around the palace.
I want to walk around
the entire city of Jiangnan
and see the place where my mother grew up.
Will you accompany me?
Don't even mention going to Jiangnan.
I'm willing to go anywhere in the world.
By the way, A Qi,
Recently, the ministers in the palace
have all been talking,
saying that His Majesty intends to
pass the crown prince position to you.
Do you...
really want to be the crown prince?
Yanzhi,
If I'm not mistaken,
Su He threatened you
to work for him earlier,
he wanted to form an alliance with Yinzhou,
and after Yinzhou ascended the throne,
he would give him benefits.
And you,
the condition for you to
agree to work for Yinzhou
was my life, right?
Is that correct?
Yes.
But I can't let someone like Yinzhou
take the crown prince position.
Yanzhi,
He only takes advantage of you.
After the matter is accomplished,
and regardless of me,
he won't even spare you.
Trust me.
Are there any clues as to who thoe
spy is that Yin Zhou planted by your side?
That day when I went to Mingde Palace,
I smelled the fragrance that
the late Concubine Chen loved the most.
That was what I deliberately
applied to the sky lanterns.
It must be the assassin
who failed to succeed
and immediately went
back to report to Yinzhou.
Your Highness,
I saw that.
Pei entered Mingde Palace late at night
and stayed for a long time before leaving.
After I found out,
I immediately came to report to you.
It's him.
Who is it?
A few days ago,
I smelled it on Wei Ziming,
and he lied to me,
saying that you went to
Mingde Palace late at night.
The spy sent by Yinzhou
is him.
It's actually Wei Ziming.
He has been by your side
even earlier than Duan Yi and Duan Yong.
So it turns out that at that time,
Yinzhou was already on guard against you.
Now you should know
how terrifying my eldest
imperial brother's scheming is.
What do you plan to do with Wei Ziming?
Dispose of him?
I don't plan to dispose of him.
Since my eldest royal
brother sent him to me,
of course I'll cherish him well.
Mother,
you've also seen that Father
is increasingly favoring Yin Qi.
Everyone in the court
and the harem knows that
it won't be long before he
moves into the Eastern Palace.
Taking advantage of this trip to Jiangnan,
if we can't find a chance to
eliminate him once and for all,
it will be even harder when
he returns to the palace.
It's not that Mother doesn't support you,
but it's not as easy to
kill Yin Qi now as before.
If it's difficult to
kill Yin Qi alone...
Well then,
just kill Father too.
How dare you!
Such treasonous words,
how dare you speak?
After all these years,
I've grown tired of
the struggle for power.
Mother,
do you think.
I have a better choice?
Khan,
Jiangnan is not far ahead.
Judging by the pace,
the Emperor of Daxing and his entourage
have already entered the city.
Such a great country
will eventually be mine.
Giddyup!
Your Highness ordered me
to come here late at night,
is it because of the rumors
that have been causing a stir recently?
If it's for that,
Your Highness can just give up.
A Qi has no interest in power.
This rumor
seems to have been deliberately
spread by someone with ulterior motives.
Whether it's a rumor
or Yin Qi is playing tricks,
I'll make my own judgment.
My uncle
will arrive in Jiangnan soon.
At that time,
I'd like to invite Your Highness
to meet and have a talk.
You and your uncle,
I don't trust either of you.
I wonder if you
can give me a guarantee
to make me believe
that you are sincerely
working to fulfill my wishes.