( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Their fried dough sticks are pretty good.
Freshly fried, right?
Listen to me.
I just brushed right past that guy.
He was just buying some buns.
According to intel from the bureau,
one, he's not staying at any hotel here.
Two, he's not renting any place here.
Three, he has no residence permit.
Four, he's never worked here.
So him showing up in this area
is highly suspicious.
Captain Zhang, Captain Ma.
The short guy headed into the east-west alley.
Copy that.
Tell the boys,
we're at a critical stage now.
Don't give anything away.
The streets here are a tangled maze.
Don't make a move unless absolutely necessary.
Acknowledge.
Copy that.
Hey...
What's up?
What is it?
Soy milk.
I forgot the soy milk. The soy milk.
Right, right, right.
The soy milk.
Tomorrow we go our separate ways.
So tonight,
have a nice meal with everyone.
Godfather,
aren't you joining us?
You won't relax with me around.
Thanks.
Director Wang.
Based on our undercover surveillance these past few days,
we've basically locked onto a
southern man who regularly frequents
the alley behind the market.
Based on the background audio we have,
we can essentially conclude
this underground bank
is located in a residence in that back alley.
Old Street Junction is a maze of alleys
with heavy foot traffic.
Daytime isn't suitable
for a large-scale formal raid.
I know.
A night operation is best.
From the initial Xin Qili case,
to the current financial crimes case,
even the earlier 0301 dismemberment case,
the key to cracking them all
lies in tonight's arrest operation.
It absolutely must
go off without a hitch.
Old Street Junction Market starts closing
gradually from 8 PM each night.
So after 8 PM,
we'll deploy on the perimeter,
guarding these key entry and exit points.
At 1 AM,
once all resident activity has died down,
we'll move in through these alleys,
gradually closing in on the target area.
The breach team will be led by Zhao Dian,
striking from the front, side, and back.
Ma, your team handles the outer cordon.
Every possible exit point
must be locked down tight.
Yes, sir.
Zhang Da, what about us?
You follow behind Ma's team.
Once the breach team succeeds,
wait for my signal, then move in at once
to secure and collect evidence.
Understood.
Everyone, remember one thing.
The targets of this operation
are a major financial crime ring,
but we can't rule out violent resistance.
So we absolutely cannot let our guard down.
Any slip-up
will cost us dearly.
Copy that.
Stop overthinking it.
There's bound to be a resolution.
Don't worry.
From evening till closing time,
only Shorty came in and out
of the alley with a few men.
They only bought beer
and some food.
No one else came in or out.
I figure they're pretty drunk by now.
It's about time.
Move out.
Yes, sir.
Dian.
Come on.
Thanks, Uncle Ma.
Let's go.
Come on, drink up!
Come on, come on.
Cops! Run!
Freeze! Don't move!
Run!
Open the door!
Don't move!
Get down!
On your knees!
Don't move!
Sarge.
The scene is secured.
Evidence team can move in.
Team Two, light up the perimeter.
Lock it down. No one gets out.
Move!
Ma.
You okay?
None got away, right?
Good work.
Good.
Don't move.
It's really over now.
Zhang Da, it's over.
We've got it under control.
Okay.
All good.
Where's the money?
There's still someone inside, right?
Yes.
How's it going?
Shorty deleted everything.
We're trying to recover it.
Deleted?
Zhao Dian.
Did anyone slip out?
They're all here.
Every one of them.
All accounted for.
Excuse me, coming through.
What happened to you?
Your eyes are worse than mine.
Catching crooks, you know.
Come on, step aside.
Officer Gao.
We've already verified this.
Okay, thanks.
Good.
Sis, it's all printed out.
Go on.
I heard Luo Xiao took over
Brother Mao's position.
But I don't know the details.
What was A-Xin's connection to you?
A-Xin used to be our money runner,
in charge of splitting the cash.
He was the one who handed over
the cash to Fengmao.
You were close with A-Xin.
Why kill him and his sister?
I didn't kill them.
His sister was killed by two outsiders.
How do you know it was two outsiders?
I also know the next one
to be taken out is Luo Xiao.
Why didn't you say so sooner?
Locate Luo Xiao immediately.
And everyone at Fengmao Company,
not one gets away.
Detain them all.
Sarge, where are you going?
Luo Xiao's place.
Zhang Da.
We just got a call from the nursing home.
Your daughter, Paopao,
is in my hands.
Listen carefully.
Within half an hour,
get to the old harbor pier.
Ruan Chen!
I don't know what you're up to,
but don't you touch my daughter.
Remember,
no calling the cops.
Airport.
Sir, get in and we'll go.
Go, go, go, go!
Come on, let's go.
Hey, driver.
How much to the airport?
Seventy.
Seventy? No way, that's too expensive.
Fifty. Will you take fifty?
Sarge.
Why did Luo Xiao U-turn to the airport?
Where's he going?
Something's not right.
This route makes him take a huge detour.
At the next intersection,
we can turn around and catch up.
No, no, no. Take a look.
Before he turned around,
wasn't he heading toward the coast?
Wasn't he?
Yes, he was heading to the outskirts.
The endpoint is the docks.
Two hundred meters to the U-turn.
No, no.
No, one hundred meters now.
Turn around, Sarge!
Let's take a gamble.
Mobilize all units to the docks.
Move!
Copy that.
Daddy!
A lawyer, as expected.
Right on time.
Daddy!
Paopao, don't be afraid.
Daddy's right here.
I had no choice but to resort to this.
Forgive me.
What the hell do you want?
I've done everything you asked.
You wanted a billion laundered,
and I worked my ass off to do it.
Why would you go after my daughter?
Seems you don't know yet.
A few hours ago,
my people got rounded up by the cops.
What's that got to do with me?
I wasn't the one who tipped them off.
Would I ever call the police?
Hasn't Zhang Heng come for you yet?
I guarantee this won't be a problem.
Luo Xiao.
In you,
I see a shadow of my younger self.
But you endure more than I did.
That's why
you have a whole family,
while I
am just a lonely man.
I really admire your abilities.
But that ability
must serve me cleanly and decisively.
Otherwise, it becomes dangerous.
Tomorrow morning at eight,
the moment the money arrives,
once the money's in,
I'll wire it straight to your fund account.
Excellent.
Then we'll just
quietly wait for dawn.