( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I'm sorry.
The victim's head was struck hard with a hammer,
causing severe cranial injury.
Actually, within just a few minutes,
she lost all vital signs.
But we still did
everything we could to save her.
But unfortunately,
there was nothing more we could do.
In the surveillance room, I pulled up
the facial images of the two suspects.
Both their identities were completely fake.
Then I also pulled up the files from
the 0301 Dismemberment Case to compare.
These two match closely with what
the previous witnesses described.
It's highly likely that the killers from
the 0301 Dismemberment Case struck again.
Sir.
There's one more thing.
Before these two made their move,
they ran into Luo Xiao in the hallway.
We can't tell what they said on camera.
Come on, get out here.
Get out.
Zhang Heng.
Zhang Heng, calm down.
Let's talk this out.
It's fine, it's fine.
Tell me everything you know.
Talk! Say something!
From Chen Yongjiang to Xin Youna,
why is every single thing connected to you?
Why?
Is this what you wanted to happen?
Is it?
Didn't I warn you a long time ago
not to hide anything from me?
You're finished. You're done for.
You hear me?
Zhang Heng.
If you have evidence he's a criminal,
you can arrest him right now.
No one will stop you.
But if you don't have evidence,
you're just making baseless accusations.
That's not how a cop acts.
Zhang Heng.
Hey, both of you, calm down.
I'll go see what's actually going on.
Ma'am.
Grown in my own garden, no pesticides.
Good for the little one's health.
Did I come at a bad time?
Luo Xiao.
Luo Xiao, are you really
not going to tell me anything?
From when Paopao got sick until now,
all these things, one after another,
I've had my suspicions, Luo Xiao.
Why did you give up being a good lawyer
to run an auto repair shop?
And then out of nowhere,
all this money showed up at home?
Then Zhang Heng kept bringing you to the station,
only to let you go in the end.
Luo Xiao, the reason I didn't ask
is because I didn't need a good husband.
But today, you saw it too.
Xin Youna died right next door.
She asked me yesterday,
she said, she said,
"What... what kind of person are you?"
I thought it was strange then, I thought,
I...
Luo Xiao, can you tell me what you're doing?
Are you safe, Luo Xiao?
I can do without a good husband,
but...
think about Paopao.
Paopao needs a good father.
Haven't you always wanted a divorce?
Let's get one.
I'll give you custody of Paopao.
And all the marital assets too.
Tomorrow I'll have the firm draw up the papers.
Bro.
How did it go?
There you are, Xiao.
The last batch of overseas money
just got wired in.
I'm guessing
it'll clear by tomorrow morning.
Then we just transfer it
into the underground bank's fund account.
And it'll be a breeze.
It's crazy when you think about it.
Just us,
we laundered a full billion.
What about Feng Zhan?
How's his cut looking?
I didn't do the exact math for him,
but his losses
are probably around ten percent.
But don't worry, bro.
We made at least fifteen percent.
That's 150 million.
Right.
Insane.
And Feng Zhan?
Let him make more.
The more he makes,
the more blame he takes.
And the safer we'll be.
Once the money clears tomorrow,
book flights for the boys right away.
Get as far away as possible.
Convert it all to crypto.
And scatter it all.
What happened, bro?
Why do we have to leave?
Aren't we doing this completely legally?
The police already got their hands
on Xin Youna's recording.
The fact they haven't questioned me yet
means they must've found bigger leads.
Besides,
even if the cops aren't an issue,
you think once the money clears,
Ruan Chen will just let me go?
But we laundered a billion for him!
He... he wouldn't go that far, right?
Useless people
are nothing but weeds to him.
You're back.
Where's Paopao?
Yaping's watching her at the hospital.
You haven't eaten, have you?
I've drawn up the divorce papers.
All you need to do is sign.
Let's get this over with.
Didn't we say
we'd wait until Paopao got better?
You've already crawled into Feng Zhan's bed.
There's no need to play the happy couple.
I can accept a lot of things,
even you cheating.
But I don't understand why Feng Zhan.
Did you think I wasn't humiliated enough?
I watched the video of you two.
Rolling in the sheets.
Quite the show.
Luo Xiao, it hurts, doesn't it?
Let me tell you,
every single day since Paopao was born,
that's how I've felt.
Now you've got something on me, right?
So you take the moral high ground to judge me?
Have you ever cared about me?
Have you ever cared about this family?
Have you ever cared about Paopao?
You don't even know what class she's in.
You don't care about us at all.
The only one you care about is yourself.
And Luo Xiao, I'm warning you,
whatever it is you're doing,
don't drag Paopao into it.
Sir.
Sorry for the trouble.
Make sure it's completely crushed.