( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Things are going smoothly on Luo Xiao's end.
The final overseas transfer
should clear and post by tomorrow morning.
Kids,
pack everything up today.
After tonight, we ring the opening bell
and head off to a new life.
Got it.
Get in touch with Briefcase.
I want to see them.
Hurry up!
Is this Officer Zhang?
We're from the county train station.
Based on the wanted notice
you put out online,
we just caught a suspect
involved in a money laundering case.
His name's Chen Guang.
That's exactly how it happened.
Two guys
suddenly showed up at my fishing pond,
saying they wanted to make a deal.
They'd give me money
to pay off all my bank debts.
The catch was I transfer that abandoned
fish raft over to them.
And these two are supposedly brothers.
Quite a story you're telling.
That's exactly what I thought at the time.
But they really did
pull out a huge bag of money,
all cash inside.
They made me go to the bank to pay it off.
Right after, my credit record was cleared.
They were waiting for me at the door,
even set off fireworks to celebrate.
One of them said
to print a fish raft transfer agreement.
And I started thinking,
could it be that this fish raft
has something valuable I never noticed?
Otherwise why would they be so generous,
insisting on a deal that loses them money?
Right?
The more I thought about it,
I just gritted my teeth,
and while they weren't looking,
I bolted.
Two guys with a car,
and they let you get away?
I run pretty fast.
All these years dodging creditors,
I've had plenty of practice.
Are these the two guys you mentioned?
Recognize them?
Yes, yes, yes!
That's them, that's them!
I'd know them if they turned to ash.
Datou.
This...
is where our dream began.
Bro,
my head's spinning a bit right now.
Datou,
after tomorrow,
you'll see a whole different world.
Bro,
I'm doing just fine in this world.
You've got quite the sense of humor.
Datou.
Do you know,
for the past thirty years,
I always thought
I knew exactly what I wanted.
I just wanted a respectable life.
As if just by following that template,
that respectability would get
a little closer to me.
But it's not like that.
Reality isn't like that.
You all look down on me.
No, Bro.
My colleagues shun me too.
And Bro Mao?
He treats me like a doormat.
Uses me to wipe his dirt off.
All those shady things
you all do,
I'm the one cleaning them up.
And you?
You treat me like the biggest loser.
Even to catch my cheating wife,
I had to beg you guys.
No, Bro.
That's because they don't know you.
But I do.
You're 1,000 times better than Bro Mao.
Ten thousand times, even.
Is he even worthy?
Does Bro Mao even compare to me?
You tell me,
what does Bro Mao have that I don't?
What gives him the right?
He's just got a thug's brute strength.
He bullies people.
He bullies people!
I'm not like that, Datou.
I'm not.
I built myself
bit by bit,
step by step,
I climbed up here on my own.
Datou,
you don't know.
Back then,
I...
I'd lock myself in the bathroom.
Guess why the bathroom?
Because it's filthy there.
It stinks.
A person...
only...
only in that kind of environment
will it constantly remind you,
you have to get out of here.
You can't stay here.
You can't live like this.
So,
I studied day and night.
I clawed my way up.
I went to college, became a lawyer,
just for a chance to slave for Bro Mao.
So I'm asking you,
does he deserve it?
Bro,
don't say any more.
Brother,
after Bro Mao's death,
he's set us on
a completely different path.
On this path,
no right or wrong,
no morality,
no rules.
Only a game.
You watch closely.
Let's see who dares look down on me now.
No one will dare look down on me.
For our incoming funds this time,
are we still doing those three transfers?
Yes, those three channels.
First, move the cash into the accounts
of Feng Mao's two trading companies.
Ship out the rest,
labeled as payment for goods.
Payment for goods.
Can Ruisitai handle it on their end?
That small order they had last time
nearly got flagged.
Don't worry.
Everything's been prepared.
The accounts are under new names.
The transactions will be split up.
How's it going?
How are their transactions
this time around?
We can now fully confirm
the audio on Xin Youna's phone
involves financial crimes.
But to verify its authenticity,
voice ID isn't like facial recognition.
Finding the person isn't that easy.
We ran a comparison.
For the 0301 Dismemberment Case,
the suspect's sketch
closely matches the hospital footage.
We never had a clear shot of the killer,
plus the witness descriptions were vague,
so these two bastards got away.
Time to settle both old and new scores.
So these two are professional hitmen.
We checked both victims' connections.
No links to the killers at all.
But Xin Youna's death
was clearly because of
those recordings she had.
If it's a contract killing,
then the employer is very likely
someone from the underground bank.
Criminal cases born from financial crimes.
Should we question Luo Xiao again?
Arresting him now
would tip them off, wouldn't it?
Come listen.
What's this voice saying?
"Sun's roast duck still smells the best."
That's a dialect, right?
That's a Shannan accent.
'Sun's roast duck still smells the best.'
How do you know Shannan dialect?
I once detained a guy from Shannan.
Spent days wearing him down.
Sun's Roast Duck.
There's one by Shuangshi Kindergarten.
But those chain stores,
there's more than one.
Three in total.
So where would this Shannan guy buy from?
If our theory leans toward
the shop being near the underground bank,
then we can rule out the kindergarten.
That area's all government offices.
The bank wouldn't be that bold.
So the community shop and the market,
those are very likely.
Heavy foot traffic there,
and the private areas have walls.
Zhang Da.
How about we set up surveillance all over?
This is just our speculation.
That's a huge area.
If we really set up surveillance,
let alone if we have the manpower,
with students and commuters around,
once things blow up,
the bank would just slip away.
My guess is the Old Street Market.
Shannan people who come here
mostly run small businesses.
Tobacco, liquor, tea, oil.
Only the market is convenient for trading.
Now that Xin Youna is dead,
the market is the only lead we have
to find evidence of the underground bank.
Whether the guess is right or not,
given the situation, we have to try.
Roast duck! Fresh out of the oven!
What'll it be?
I'll take one of these.
Pig ears, please.
Right.
Old Street Market.
Crowded, with many alleys and exits.
Our objective
isn't a surprise raid,
but to move like shadows,
quietly tracking every point of movement.
Stay close and observe.
Note the regulars and the cash flow.
Don't provoke anyone.
We're buyers, we're customers.
Use your eyes as your weapon first.
Takeaway Team, cover the exits and alleys.
Remember, your eyes follow the targets,
your feet remember where they go.
Cleanup Team,
trash is the best witness.
Receipts, flyers, scraps of paper,
don't overlook a single folded invoice.
Stay calm.
Stay composed.
Be patient.
Understood?
Understood.
Gentlemen, the boat is arranged.
Early Thursday morning.
Departing from Ma Dao.
On the boat, you'll have to bear with it,
hiding out in the cargo hold.
Boss,
don't worry.
The two of us are professionals.
Look,
no fingerprints even.
I burned them off myself with hot tongs.
The cops can't catch us.
We were born for this line of work.
Come on.
A toast to you both.
Sorry, we don't drink.
Gotta keep our heads clear at all times.
Boss,
didn't you say there's one more job?
Where's the target?
Smells great.
No problem.
When do we make the move?
Soon.