( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 35=
The book is finished.
And Zhanqiao's mother
has finally found peace too.
I'm going to say goodbye to Mrs. Lin.
You asked me
to think about going abroad with you.
Now that your mom is gone,
I'll tell you that I'm not going.
But don't start saying things like
if I'm not going,
you won't go either.
You're my daughter.
I want you to be free.
I hope you can have
the freedom I never had.
Of course,
you can also see it as selfishness.
Maybe I just want you
to fulfill the dreams I never could.
You're not young anymore.
And we don't even live together.
I thought that if we stayed
in the same city,
no matter what happened,
at least we'd still be able
to look out for each other.
It's really not that big of a deal.
After seeing so many births,
deaths, and illnesses,
life is just like this.
Your dad and I already talked about it.
After you go abroad,
if anything happens to him,
he can always come to me.
(Tofato Tea Cafe)
When are you planning to leave?
Originally, I planned
to leave in the summer.
I thought my mom
could hold on a little longer.
But now that she's gone,
I probably
won't stay much longer either.
Before I leave,
I should tell you
something.
What is it?
Your mother...
I think I may have found her.
Where is she?
She's in Shanghai.
I never told you before
because...
she said...
She said I found the wrong person.
You know our family
doesn't even have a single photo
of the three of us together?
What?
You want to kill me?
Someone like you
doesn't deserve to live.
I...
Divorce!
I want a divorce from you!
I'm pregnant.
You can't bring up divorce right now.
Where's my phone?
You took my phone, right?
You checked my phone, didn't you?
Give me back my phone.
I just wanted to see
who you've been messaging every day.
Just because of that?
Every night you're messaging
Xiaoxue after midnight.
I've put up with this
for a long time already!
Everything I sent her
was work-related! It was work materials!
Sending her those things
is good for the company,
good for you, and good for me too.
I didn't even send a single emoji.
Because all these chat records
were deliberately edited by you.
You prepared all this in advance
just to disgust me.
You even changed your phone password
to my birthday
so I'd conveniently check your phone.
Zhao Lanxin, why...
Why can't you see
that this is my way of loving you?
Every day, no matter where you go,
I pick you up and drive you around.
At night, when you say you're hungry,
I get up and cook for you too.
I'm afraid you'll fall,
so wherever you walk, I support you.
Everyone in the company knows
that I treat you perfectly.
If you still tell people
I treat you badly,
then you're really just
being unreasonable.
And most importantly, you know what?
You have
always been cold
and selfish with others.
No one would ever believe your kindness.
Say something.
Say something. Aren't you supposed
to have everything under control?
Take me to the hospital.
What?
My stomach hurts.
(Emergency)
What are you doing, Ling Yikai?
The doctor told you to stay in bed more
and protect the pregnancy.
I believe my children
will be just as resilient as I am.
Right. You and your children
are all resilient.
I'm not that resilient.
Since we can't get divorced right now,
we'll talk about it
after the children are born.
Starting today,
I'm sleeping in this room.
Your lives and
the children's lives matter,
but my life matters too.
I need to learn how to
protect my own safety.
I never really wanted your life.
Zhao Lanxin,
whether that's true or not,
I don't care, and I don't want to know.
You can keep
playing this game by yourself.
I don't want to play anymore.
You can keep using the company, money,
Grandma, or the future to manipulate me.
I don't want any of it anymore.
As long as I can leave you,
I'm willing to pay any price.
I thought after we had children,
you would change.
I really did hold onto a tiny
bit of hope
for your humanity, Ling Yikai.
Anyone who stays with you
will eventually become like this!
Zhao Lanxin,
I honestly don't have the confidence
that we can raise
a healthy and normal child together.
Hello?
I brought San Mei over.
From now on, you don't need to deal
with San Mei and Er Jiu's
matters anymore.
You said your place was big,
but I didn't expect it to be this big.
You really live alone
in such a big house, huh?
It's a bit too big.
I booked a room next door for you.
Move over there and stay for now.
This place must cost
several thousand a night.
I can't keep spending
your money staying here.
Come on.
There's no need to separate
things so clearly between us.
As for Er Jiu,
if you want a divorce,
I'll handle the rest.
She and Er Jiu are
getting divorced by agreement.
She's staying with me now.
I'm marrying her.
You're marrying her?
Are you joking?
I'm not joking.
Didn't expect that, did you?
Your little act of driving
a wedge between San Mei and Er Jiu
while pretending to be
the hero who saves the day
is over.
Zhao Lanxin,
I never really liked you from the start.
But I believed you could
protect me from hardship.
What I didn't expect
was that the storm itself
came from you all along.
I'm not some morally perfect person.
But compared to me,
you're even worse.
Did you go look for her?
Did you see her?
Not yet.
So what now?
You're planning
to just wait there forever?
People in clothing wholesale
usually start work quite late.
And those doing retail
mostly come by after work.
(End of Season Sale.
Special Prices Storewide)
Make way...
Careful.
Sir,
what are you looking for?
Everything in here today
is 20 percent off.
Feel free to look around.
If you see something you like,
I'll give you a discount.
What did you buy? That's so much.
It's heavy.
Wow, this is really heavy.
Well, wholesale shopping
means buying more.
Clothes?
Who are you buying all this for?
Taking them back for the neighbors.
The key, please.
Come on.
One, two, three.
Okay.
The moment I saw her,
I knew it was my mom.
It was her for sure.
Even though we hadn't
seen each other in decades,
I could
still recognize her face.
Is she doing okay?
Pretty well.
As long as she's doing well,
that's enough.
If I miss her in the future,
I'll just go buy more clothes again.
I'll drive.
No need.
I'm fine.
(Lingqi Reading Platform)
These are
Lingqi's current
top ten bestselling titles.
Do you know
what their online
readership numbers are?
Every single one
has over a million readers.
Lingqi's average daily active users
have already hit
one hundred million.
And now, let's look
at our user data
and the situation with our authors.
Wenliu, you tell everyone.
I'm afraid I'll die
from anger halfway through.
At the moment,
about one-third of our authors
have already
been privately approached by Lingqi.
For SS-tier authors,
their minimum guarantee is over 200,
plus backend profit sharing
on top of the 3,000 base guarantee.
They only want SS-tier
and S-tier star authors.
What about the rest?
They don't want them.
What do you mean?
It means they look down on them.
They only want the very best.
Mr. Fan,
Ms. Zhao is waiting
for you in the office.
Mr. Fan.
I have been hearing
bad news all this morning,
and judging from your face,
I don't think
you're bringing good news either.
Go ahead.
How did Lingqi Platform
disgust you this time?
Gu Yan wants to leave.
It's Lingqi Platform.
You know how our writing model works.
Yeah.
AI collaborative writing, right?
Can you accept big data-driven creation?
As long as you can keep me
where I am now,
there's nothing I can't accept.
Did Dai Shan approach him?
Are they still talking,
or has he already decided?
Didn't you say you
had Gu Yan under control?
I'm worried he'll leave.
I'm worried Dai Shan
promised him something bigger.
AI co-writing is the trend now.
From the way things are developing...
Don't give me that.
Do you think I don't know who Gu Yan is?
Prospects?
Trends?
If he really thought
about things that way,
would he have left
Lin Zhanqiao back then
and signed with you instead?
All along the way,
people have said
that I relied on Lin Zhanqiao,
(Gu Yan)
copied He Han,
and rode on Phantom Knight's fame.
But so what?
Aren't I still the most valuable
online fiction author right now?
So, relying on AI
isn't anything special to me.
Smooth.
Clear-headed.
So that's why
you made it this far?
No need to compliment me.
I know all of you
actually look down on me.
But that's fine.
It lets me negotiate with
you without any burden.
Let's hear what
conditions you still have.
First,
a five-million advance.
Pay me within three days.
Second,
I want your car.
The Lotus?
Yes.
Why?
He Han used to have not only this suite,
but that car too.
Well, I also need to see
your contract with Zhao Lanxin.
My contract with Zhao Lanxin
is based on word count.
I still owe 500,000 words.
Including the drafts I already have,
I can finish it in a week.
I remember when I first came to you,
you weren't particularly
interested in Lingqi.
What exactly
made you change your mind?
You said it yourself.
A wise man knows when to adapt.
What else?
And Zhao Lanxin
isn't worth standing with.
What if it were Lin Zhanqiao?
She might actually be able
to put up a fight against you.
That's what you want.
Here.
Take a look at this.
This is the future positioning
for your writing and personal brand.
As long as you follow it step by step,
you'll surpass your current peak.
(Analysis of Similar Works)
(Shattered Six States,
Fantasy/Eastern Fantasy, by He Han)
Using He Han as the benchmark?
Surpass He Han completely.
Surpassing him isn't difficult at all.
Haven't I already surpassed him?
I've never taken He Han seriously.
Neither have my readers.
He's nothing more
than a comparison target.
But He Han
was already at his peak.
The real peak was not him
but Phantom Knight.
I want the publicity plan revised.
Use Phantom Knight as the benchmark.
If Phantom Knight
created the Online Fiction 1.0 era,
then starting from me,
this will be the 2.0 era.
There's no need for He Han's name.
Didn't expect
that the car would be so popular, huh?
I've already finalized
the deal with Dai Shan.
I never liked Zhao Lanxin to begin with.
Dai Shan offered me
a better opportunity,
so I left.
You don't need to
explain any of this to me.
Whether you work with
Zhao Lanxin or Dai Shan,
I honestly don't care.
Even now,
aside from San Mei and Er Jiu,
you're still the only person I trust.
Only you
treated me like an equal partner.
You cared about my future well-being.
Zhao Lanxin and Dai Shan never did.
To them, I was just a tool.
All they wanted was to squeeze
my value out as quickly as possible.
They don't care what kind of problems
I'll face a year from now,
let alone three or five years later.
All they need
is to find the next Gu Yan.
So what?
What you wanted was never equality
or healthy long-term growth.
I wanted to feel valued.
I wanted to be treated like I mattered.
I wanted someone around me at all times,
praising me.
Even if I knew all of it was fake,
all calculated,
and all just people using me,
I still wanted it.
If you could treat me that way,
I would've never gone to Zhao Lanxin.
I would've kept trying
to maintain my value
just to keep you by my side.
I can't do that.
I can't do that for anyone.
I can lose everything. I can fail.
But I can never
betray my own judgment and feelings.
I know.
That's why I came here
to say goodbye.
I heard you're going abroad.
I never planned to convince you to stay.
Even though I resent you
for not keeping me,
I still respect you.
Zhao Lanxin and Dai Shan went all out
to give me everything I wanted.
But I still look down on them.
How much we've gained
and how much we've lost
isn't something
we should settle right now.
But that day
won't stay far away forever.
Whether this trade was worth it or not,
if we ever meet again in the future,
we can talk about it then.
There's one more thing.
Whether you're Phantom Knight or not,
this time,
I'm going to crush
that name beneath my feet.
I'm the one standing at the top now.
The dullest thing
about a game built on winning and losing
is when your rival
doesn't even want to play.
Mr. Fan.
He replied to you?
(Lingqi Reading. Gu Yan continues
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui)
(How did the sequel
surpass the original work?)
Dai Shan has already signed Gu Yan.
I just came back from Lingqi Platform.
What were you doing there?
Curious. Wanted to see
things for myself.
Know your enemy
and know yourself, you know?
So, what did you learn?
Lingqi Platform
is going to give Gu Yan's
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui
a big promotional push.
They're going all out,
building hype around it.
So Gu Yan signed with them too?
And their marketing strategy
directly targets Phantom Knight.
They want to shape Gu Yan
into No. 1 in online fiction.
Because Dai Shan knows
Gu Yan loves this kind of attention.
I wonder if Phantom Knight would be
furious seeing articles like this.
The original author worked so hard
to build the novel's foundation,
yet Gu Yan gained fame
just by continuing it.
Not only is he ungrateful instead
of respecting the original author,
but he's now also stepping on their name
to promote himself.
Don't worry.
Phantom Knight would never
take a clown like that
seriously.
Can't take it anymore?
We came from the same roots.
Why destroy each other like this?
Beg me.
Please,
I'm begging you.
Please.
Of course,
it's also about giving
those outstanding writers
who are still diligently typing away
a way to make a living.
Back then, you were just like me.
We...
We all walked this road together.
At the beginning,
hardly anyone chose this path.
And now, after all this effort,
it's finally become
a real industry.
Right?
I don't believe it.
I don't believe
you can really bear
to watch a large-scale purge
where low-quality
content drives out the good work.
I don't believe it.
But Fan,
expansion is always
rough in the beginning.
AI co-writing is the same.
I know where the problems are right now.
But my top priority is grabbing
users and market share.
It's about scale.
The low-quality content is temporary.
Once things stabilize gradually,
we'll still move toward premium content.
I'm afraid these talented authors
won't have the patience
to wait until that day comes.
There will be another generation
of talented authors.
This generation's top authors
may not necessarily
remain at the top once
AI collaboration fully takes over.
Their thinking is too rigid.
They can't let go of themselves.
The things they write
aren't as effective
as what the newer writers produce.
So why sign them at all?
Why waste their time?
To make room
for my new writers to rise.
So you'd rather sacrifice them.
That's the real reason
you paid to sign them,
isn't it?
Walk me out?
Sorry.
We're not heading the same way.
Let's go our separate ways.
(Once I finish continuing
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui,)
(that will also mark
my final farewell to Phantom Knight.)
(And I must admit,)
(the Online Fiction 1.0 era)
(represented by Phantom Knight
has already come to an end.)
(I also acknowledge)
(that AI technology is progressing,)
(a gift this era has given to writers.)
(Lingqi's AI co-writing)
(has brought me entirely
new excitement and challenges.)
(AI co-writing
combines technology and innovation,)
(while pushing beyond the boundaries
of traditional storytelling.)
(I'm not someone
who clings to old ways.)
(I'm willing to embrace)
(everything this era has brought.)
(Using AI-assisted writing,)
(I will create
the Online Fiction 2.0 era)
(represented by me, Gu Yan.)
The dullest thing
about a game built on winning and losing
is when your rival
doesn't even want to play.
(A small country threatened by war...)
Are you asleep?
What's wrong?
If you're still awake,
let's talk for a bit.
Er Jiu agreed.
He'll take the money,
sign the divorce papers with you,
and leave Shanghai.
You know this.
Domestic violence can't be forgiven.
I never said I was going to forgive him.
What did he say?
(Temporarily Closed)
This is all I can give you right now.
If you think it's not enough,
I'll figure out another way.
(5,000,000 yuan)
So much money?
I couldn't make that in 10 or 20 years.
I was just thinking,
why should I take
this much money from you?
I owe you.
We once swore
to share blessings and hardships.
You don't owe me.
If anyone owes someone,
it's me who owes San Mei.
I loved her,
but I also hurt her.
When I married her, I already knew
her heart only had room for you.
I thought I could accept that.
But after we got married, I realized
it was too hard.
At one point I even thought,
if it were anyone else,
maybe I wouldn't have been this jealous.
But because it was you,
it tortured me even more.
Take it back.
I'm going to travel around a bit.
See if there's
some business that suits me.
If I ever need money, I'll let you know.
Where are you going?
Northeast China.
The lady at the orphanage said
I'm originally from there, right?
I'm going to take a look.
Will you still stay in touch with me?
Come on.
I've got a famous
and wealthy buddy like you.
You think I'd let that go?
Take care of yourself.
And help me take care of San Mei too.
I should've stopped you
from marrying Er Jiu.
I should have been the one
who married you.
Then, I probably would've
been even more unhappy.
Because I know
you would've only been
with me out of responsibility.
But I don't want
to marry someone
out of responsibility ever again.
If none of this
had ever happened,
the three of us
would probably still be friends today.
Things wouldn't
have turned out like this,
right?
Sometimes,
we try so hard
that we lose what
we once cared about most.
I won't do that anymore.
When I said I wanted to marry you,
it wasn't because of responsibility.
Then, what was it?
Because...
you're the only person left
I can still trust.
You don't need to marry me.
We don't have to get married.
You can still trust me all the same.
I want to keep you by my side.
I'm not like you.
I'm not used to living in hotels.
Where are you going?
Back to the internet cafe.
Er Jiu may be gone,
but the cafe is still there.
But staying at the cafe
won't be as comfortable as here.
I think it's more comfortable there.
What else can I do?
Maybe doing nothing at all
would be better.
♪Slowly drift away♪
♪Died a little inside last night♪
♪Cause I'll never see you again♪
♪I'm waking up to silence around me♪
♪Heal, can I heal?♪
♪All I want is nothing more♪
♪Than to see your face someday♪
♪I don't wanna leave the memories♪
♪My mind's not over you♪
♪Girl don't ask me♪
♪Why I cannot find♪
♪The way to forget you♪
♪We were lovers♪
♪Till that very day♪
♪I'll remember♪
♪Us this way♪
♪How I wish♪
♪That you could hear my voice♪
♪And know I won't forget you♪
♪Never Forget you♪
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪