( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 37=
Hello, everyone.
To all our book lovers,
our fans,
and all our readers here at Dingqi,
hello, everyone!
I'm Fan Shu from Dingqi.
(In today's livestream,)
(I'm here to prove something to you.)
(Since "My Life Envies No Immortal")
(was released,)
(there has been)
(Is Phantom Knight's return fake?)
(a lot of debate and speculation)
(regarding whether the author
is actually Phantom Knight himself.)
(It's been fermenting)
(since early this morning,)
(so I have no choice
but to use this livestream)
(to prove the truth to everyone.)
(First, let me show you something.)
These are Phantom Knight's
original manuscripts from years ago,
which he recently sent to me.
(Here, let's take a look)
(at his own handwriting.)
(This has never been publicly released.)
(Even I am seeing it for the first time.)
(However,)
(anyone who has read)
(Phantom Knight's previous works)
(can easily see)
(that "My Life Envies No Immortal")
still carries
his signature writing style.
Even after all these years,
their writing is just
as good as it was then.
And their style has become
increasingly mature and seasoned.
(Please note,)
(Dingqi Livestream)
(what I just said was)
("they,")
(not "him,")
(nor "her,")
(but "them.")
(I'm now going to announce some data,)
(which are the performance metrics)
(for "My Life Envies No Immortal"
since its launch.)
(Within 24 hours,)
(it garnered over one million bookmarks,)
(donations from over 10,000 people,)
(and over 30,000 comments.)
(It took the No. 1 spot)
(on the charts on release day.)
(On release day,)
(it was No. 1 on Weibo's trending list.)
Not bad.
(No. 1 on Douyin's trending list.)
(In short, it's No. 1 across the board.)
(Phantom Knight Design Studio)
("Heaven's Fall VIII: Eternal Void"
by Phantom Knight)
Ms. Cai,
you're the closest with them.
You mean you had no idea before this?
I'm so stupid.
I never would have guessed
that Phantom Knight was two people.
This has to be the most
romantic thing in the world.
I'm so envious.
I really am a fool.
Hello, Mr. Cai.
Zhanqiao,
you haven't left Shanghai, right?
If you aren't leaving,
call me anytime you want to see houses.
(Phantom Knight)
Thank you.
Okay, thanks.
Thanks.
Hello.
Quick, let's see.
Why is it
that no one could ever mimic
Phantom Knight's signature?
Because it was two people
signing all along.
Two different handwritings.
Why did no one ever think of that?
It's beautiful.
Sign here.
Thank you.
(Phantom Knight Design Studio)
(Year 2014)
So, which of us is Phantom
and which is Knight?
Which one do you want to be?
Well, since I'm a man,
I'll be the Knight.
Who says only men can be knights?
Why can't I be the Knight
just because I'm a woman?
(Phantom Knight Design Studio)
(Exit)
Mei,
what are you doing?
I'm near your office.
Today is my birthday.
Are you free to have a meal together?
Just for an hour.
In an hour, I have to go
back to Haining for a meeting.
How about
I find a restaurant nearby?
I'm not at the office.
Where are you?
You're not at the office?
I said I'm near your office.
Taojiang Road.
By the Pushkin Statue.
How about you tell me
where you are and I'll come to you?
No need.
Wait for me there.
Five minutes.
Okay.
See you in a bit.
Hello.
Are you Lawyer Zhang?
I am.
Ms. Mei asked me to come
wish you a happy birthday.
Thank you.
Where is Ms. Mei?
Ms. Mei went to
Pudong to see a client today.
I'm sorry.
I think I see you also have a cake.
Yes.
Cake is my absolute favorite.
Alright.
Then, I'll get back to work.
Happy Birthday!
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Okay, bye-bye.
(Bei Wenqi, Business Achievement Award)
(Wanna share my honor with you.)
(I booked a seat.
Let's have a meal together to celebrate it.)
That's enough.
Just these.
♪After giving everything,
I couldn't wait any longer♪
♪The verdict was
already waiting in the future♪
♪Why bother confessing♪
♪Or thinking about what to say♪
♪It's none of my concern♪
♪Even if it's unraveled♪
Sir, here's the wine you ordered.
♪Endless dependence♪
♪I really miss♪
♪All the beautiful moments together♪
♪I may seem to be alone♪
♪But I'm still waiting♪
♪Happiness feels like an accident♪
♪Why be overly generous♪
♪Beyond the limits of endurance♪
♪Living in humble silence♪
♪Who is it within the crowd♪
♪Gathering strength beneath the waves♪
♪Who wasted their time
waiting for the wrong person♪
♪In despair♪
♪Saving the love you once gave me♪
♪I don't need your pity♪
Here, please.
Thanks.
You stayed at He Han's last night?
Made up again?
It was for work.
I pulled an all-nighter
to finish the draft.
I haven't even asked you yet.
Why didn't you tell me you hadn't left?
You even pretended
to be abroad and messaged me,
calculating the time difference.
Do you distrust me that much?
It's not that I don't trust you.
It's just that I had to calculate
the time difference for everyone.
So during that time,
I had already adjusted my own schedule
to Los Angeles time.
Why keep everyone in the dark?
To make a big move.
Because I didn't want
Lingqi Platform to be prepared.
I wanted to catch them off guard.
But didn't you already board the plane?
It was destiny.
I'm sorry.
Alright, I got it.
I'm about to take off now.
I won't talk more.
I'll message you when I arrive.
(Ms. Lin,)
(we, the Brain-on-Paper Team,
wish you...)
(- A safe journey)
(- and a boundless future!)
(Come back soon.)
(Okay, thank you.
I'll tell you when I arrive.)
Ladies and gentlemen,
our flight is about to take off.
Please fasten your seatbelts,
straighten your seat backs,
stow your tray tables,
and keep your window shades open.
Hello.
The subscriber you have dialed
is powered off.
Please try again later.
The subscriber you have dialed...
("My Life Envies No Immortal" Outline)
(Select a chat: Zhanqiao)
(Send to Zhanqiao:
"My Life Envies No Immortal" Outline)
(Zhanqiao, if you haven't boarded yet,
please take a look at this.)
(I'm not asking you to stay, but I hope
you'll decide after reading it.)
(Will you take one last gamble with me?)
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're very sorry to inform you
that due to a mechanical failure,
the plane cannot take off at this time.
Please take all your carry-on items
and wait in the departure lounge.
If there is any further news,
ground staff
will notify you immediately.
Departure time will be
announced separately. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we regret to inform you
that it will be a very long time
before we are able to depart
due to a mechanical problem.
(He Han's messages)
Please take all your belongings
and follow our ground staff
to the waiting lounge.
("My Life Envies No Immortal" Outline)
Further information will be given there.
(Zhanqiao, if you haven't boarded...)
We will inform you immediately.
(The Phantom Knight
has had many story ideas.)
(The most mature ones
were developed into novels,)
(but many more were
filed away for a long time.)
("My Life Envies No Immortal"
was the one we couldn't let go of.)
(It had a perfect start,)
(but we couldn't find
an unconventional way)
(to complete the story's structure.)
(It hasn't been
mentioned for so many years,)
(but it turns out
we were both silently solving it.)
(Solving the story's problem,)
(and solving the one between us.)
When did you write this?
I thought you'd forgotten about it.
When did you write it?
When Chenxing disbanded.
I wrote it a long time ago.
But to be fair,
it's actually written quite well.
Your approach is a bit better.
Are you being serious?
You're suddenly so humble.
It feels a bit strange.
The first half of yours is good,
but my ending is still a bit better.
Tell me,
why did we
spend two months back then feeling like
we couldn't keep the story going?
We were young.
Back then, everything we wrote
was about never looking back,
being cold and heartless.
Now that we're older,
we know.
When it's time to turn back,
you can still turn back.
Is this realization a bit too late?
It's not.
Your plane hasn't even taken off.
What?
I mean, in this era
of rapid AI creation,
is the Phantom Knight's
realization too late?
Actually, I'm not interested
in competing with robots.
I just feel that,
in the face of massive AI creation,
the Phantom Knight
should have his own stance.
The Phantom Knight's standard
is to create good stories,
original stories.
These aren't stories
that can be pieced together
by those familiar-looking
big data algorithms.
AI co-writing
will be the absolute trend
of the future.
But He Han refuses to accept it.
Anyway, I'll just stop writing by then.
If it's just to make a living,
I can do anything.
I choose to stay in the past.
Because humans make mistakes
and get lazy.
Even the Phantom Knight
has times when they can't go on,
right?
But AI won't.
That's so boring.
And you?
I'll say it again.
The Phantom Knight's
standard is to create good stories.
If AI can do that,
I won't reject it.
It's just that at that point,
it might be time for us,
the Phantom Knight,
to retire from the scene again.
Actually, besides Ma,
you're the only one who knew
that we were Phantom Knight.
I never understood why
you just suddenly disbanded.
I thought it was because
of that unfinished novel,
that you had a disagreement.
I just remember back then,
you were always fighting and making up.
Actually, Phantom Knight didn't disband
because of our arguments,
disagreements, or a breakup.
It was to stop
the fighting and disagreements,
so we could be together in peace.
Because one day, we suddenly realized
that if we wrote a novel together,
things were great when they were good,
but when they weren't, we'd fight.
And when we were stuck,
we'd get anxious together.
With a job that relies on inspiration,
there was simply no way
for us to give each other
a stable future.
(Year 2018)
What's with the silence?
Can you just let me think?
If you feel something is wrong,
you can say it.
We can discuss and talk about it.
Yes, I think it's wrong.
What's wrong?
Tell me.
I think it's rigid,
predictable, and boring.
Well, give me something lively.
Give me something interesting.
Isn't that what I'm thinking about?
Anyway, yours won't work.
Too conservative.
What conservative?
If I weren't being conservative
and backing you up every time,
this would never
have made it this far, okay?
- How is that possible?
- Also,
all creation needs
to follow its own rules,
doesn't it?
Rules? What the heck
is the point of rules?
Rules are meant to be broken.
Unless you want to be
a second-rate writer forever.
And then what? After they're broken,
I have to clean up the mess?
No problem.
So what if you have to clean up a mess?
At least we would have taken that step.
If you write a novel
by the book like this,
nobody's going to read it.
- Don't you understand it yet?
- You're just being cryptic, you know?
What's wrong with being cryptic?
People read Phantom Knight
exactly because our novel is different.
Let me do it.
I'll show you how to be cryptic.
If I do it well, I'll write
this chapter. Just stay out of it.
What do you mean?
Don't you dare post it on your own!
- We must reach a consensus!
- We can't reach a consensus!
Why can't we?
You're just giving me a flat "no."
You didn't even ask me.
This is creation.
Creation is a chaotic mess.
Nobody cares about being
polite and courteous, okay?
Who's being polite and courteous?
This is called mutual respect.
Do I not respect you?
If anyone else said that to me today,
I would have walked out long ago.
Then, go ahead and walk!
And back then, we were considering
whether or not we should get married.
So I was the one who proposed it.
Either we don't get married
and keep being Phantom Knight together,
fighting until things
become irreconcilable
and unbearable,
and then we just disband
right then and there.
Or we get married,
but one of us
must step back to be an editor
to provide support for the other.
As for the creative side,
it would center on one person.
Between two people who were equals,
how did you decide
who would give up writing?
(Year 2018)
(Phantom Knight)
You first.
Go ahead and draw.
You do it.
(Phantom Knight)
You got it.
No.
(Actually, I knew)
(she had drawn Phantom Knight that day.)
(Phantom Knight Design Studio)
So you drew Phantom Knight.
Of course I knew
that He Han wanted
to write novels forever.
That's what I thought at the time.
Maybe that's what love is,
being able to
give up part of your dreams
for the other person.
So later, I started Chenxing
with Zhao Lanxin and Ling Yikai.
We thought
that we had found the right solution,
that we could be like everyone else,
dating steadily,
and then moving into married life.
But who could have guessed?
We became editor and author,
but we didn't fight
any less than before.
The marriage never happened,
and the romance...
Well, we broke up.
The thing that stopped
you from being together
wasn't Phantom Knight.
Phantom Knight just
took the blame for you.
It was ourselves.
He Han.
Lin Zhanqiao.
Two beautiful ladies,
stay a while longer.
My shop is about to close.
Closing again?
I thought you weren't going to.
Just for a while.
My son
is taking me on a trip abroad.
That's wonderful.
You're really enjoying life.
Let He Han know.
I will.
I'll miss you guys.
Remember to
take lots of photos for us to see.
That's really kind of funny.
Cheers.
Come on.
How do you think
a villain should be
written to be convincing?
You have to make him believe
that he's the protagonist.
that he's the one in the right?
Of course,
a truly great villain
is never evil just for the sake of it.
He has his own worldview.
He feels the world owes him,
or he's more awake than everyone else,
but nobody understands him.
What if he wasn't
a villain to begin with?
Then, it's even more interesting.
Maybe he just wants to
prove his worth too much.
He's afraid of being replaced.
He's afraid of not being loved.
Then, how can
a villain get the love he wants?
Is love really what he wants?
What else?
Maybe it's recognition.
Maybe it's control.
Maybe he just wants to prove
he's worthy of love.
And if he never gets it?
He won't give up
until he's trapped himself in this game.
That doesn't sound
like a good ending.
But he himself
might not accept that ending.
(AI Co-Writing)
Hello, Ms. Zhao.
(Chenxing Culture)
Mr. Fan sent me here
(Copyright Agreement)
to sign the agreements with you.
Once you have finished signing,
the work will be handed over to me.
Thank you, Ms. Zhao!
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Thank you so much.
Colleagues of the Brain-on-Paper Team,
are you happy?
Yes!
From now on, we have our lucky star.
- I can make a living writing novels.
- Everyone says it's great!
The first one who sells their copyrights
- must treat the whole team!
- I'll give you the contract today.
- Let's eat lobster!
- Ms. Zhao?
Ms. Zhao.
What's wrong?
Ms. Zhao!
- Are you okay?
- What's happening?
Call 120.
(So what do we do next?)
(First,)
(when chasing Fan Sizhe...)
(Second...)
Why aren't you answering your phone?
What are you doing here?
I didn't hear it.
Zhao Lanxin is in premature labor.
Come with me to the hospital.
Your children are about to be born.
I'm not going.
I had an agreement with Zhao Lanxin.
We'll get a divorce
once the children are born.
She will take the children away.
So when I see them,
it also means I'm about to lose them.
What's the point?
Just go.
Let me know
when the children are born. Thanks.
I've revised it exactly as you said.
Let me pass this time, Ms. Lin.
I still have to go drive later.
Not bad.
Our current progress
is significantly ahead of schedule.
In another two or three months,
the novel will be finished.
Isn't that great?
Yeah.
But what do we do when it's finished?
Start another one?
We'll see then.
This doesn't sound like you,
Lin Zhanqiao.
How about this?
After the novel is finished,
let's go get married.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Look,
we have been
bickering like this,
breaking up and making up.
We disbanded Phantom Knight back then
because we
wanted to get closer to each other.
Now, we've reformed Phantom Knight
also because
we want to get closer to each other.
But is it possible
that the distance of this collaboration
is actually
the most suitable distance
between us?
One step further and it's too far,
then we'll miss each other.
One step closer and it's too near,
then we'll hurt each other.
It's my fault.
It's our fault.
Lin Zhanqiao,
I love you very much.
Me too.
Even more than very much.
(He Han and I have come full circle.)
(We seem to have returned to
how we first loved each other.)
(But I know,)
(this time)
(is different from the past.)
(Phantom Knight Design Studio)
Lin Zhanqiao!
Is Phantom Knight still continuing?
Of course.
(I'm more certain about
my choices and my stance.)
(I see my future self more clearly.)
(We love each other deeply,)
(but we're willing to
give each other freedom)
(and give ourselves space.)
(We dare to promise)
(to be each other's
first responder in times of need,)
(no matter the distance)
(and at any cost.)
(I didn't leave.)
(Zhou Mei, however, did.)
(She only told me
she was gone afterward.)
(She said it was revenge
for me not telling her I stayed.)
(Actually, I think)
(it's because she didn't want to
face the sorrow of parting so often.)
(She finally let go of the past)
(and cleared the thorns from her life.)
(A brand-new Zhou Mei)
(will go and bravely embrace)
(the person truly worthy of her love.)
Thank you, everyone.
I'll keep working hard.
(Zhangzhu terminated
her contract with Lingqi Platform)
(and signed with Dingqi Platform.)
(And she won)
(the New Creator Award.)
("Han" Overdose)
(After the babies were born,)
(Zhao Lanxin and Ling Yikai's
relationship softened.)
(They moved their battleground)
(to the trivialities of
domestic life and parenting.)
(Zhao Lanxin)
(still holds high the banner
with her own name on it.)
(She doesn't complain,)
(and she doesn't give up.)
(Then, there's San Mei.)
(Of the original trio,)
(the other two drifted away.)
(Even without any other advantages,)
(as long as a woman)
(is diligent and brave,)
(she can always find a way)
(to make a living and find her place.)
(Minors Not Allowed)
(We've each found our own path.)
(In family,)
(friendship,)
(romance,)
(and marriage,)
(we've each found our rightful place.)
(There are no myths in love.)
(The prince-and-princess script
isn't in our hands.)
(And we certainly can't
write a happily ever after ending.)
(In an ordinary life,)
(if it's destined to be
a mix of joy and sorrow,)
(then in moments of joy,)
(I hope there's someone to
share a glass of sweet wine with.)
(And in times of distress,)
(we shall surely)
(stand together, side by side.)
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪