( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 36=
First of all,
I've gathered the requests
from this group of students.
They hope to increase
the proportion of AI co-writing.
They believe
it's the trend of the future.
I can't do that.
I'm teaching people how to write novels,
not how to use AI.
Besides, I don't even
know how to use it myself.
How can I teach it?
Second,
Dai Shan wants you
to visit Lingqi Platform.
Not going.
Third,
Zhangzhu has also signed with Dai Shan.
What?
Mr. He Han,
don't worry
about hurting my self-esteem.
Just tell it like it is.
Am I any good at writing novels?
You're okay.
But I'm not the particularly
talented type, right?
It's fine. Just tell me the truth.
I...
can't become you,
can't become Lin Zhanqiao,
and I can't
even become
someone like Gu Yan
or Hong Qigong, right?
No, you can't say that.
- Everyone...
- Anyway, I'm just
not the gifted type, right?
No.
You're right. I know it myself.
But I still want to be
someone a bit different.
I want you
to look at me in a new light
for just a moment.
Wait, what does that have to do
with you going to Lingqi Platform?
I'm going as an undercover agent.
If I go, won't I find out
what they're actually up to?
We will know whether
they're truly capable
or just all talk.
Who asked you to go?
No one asked me to go.
I decided to go on my own.
Then, who do you plan to share
the information you gather with?
A lot of people.
For example, Prefrontal Cortex,
Mustard Salad, Zhugan Dalang,
and some you don't know,
the writers from our
Brain-on-Paper Team.
- What team?
- Let me analyze your zodiac sign.
- We've formed a "Brain-on-Paper" team.
- I don't follow.
It's just a team of
young writers who
weren't recruited by Dai Shan.
There are new writers from Chenxing
and some writers
from your training class.
Let me state this clearly.
It's not that we're rejecting AI.
We're rejecting
having our aesthetics and tastes
tightly controlled by AI big data.
And we're talking about
daily updates from everyone.
A serious daily check-in
of at least 5,000 words.
This team of yours...
It is still growing.
Mimi has been a huge help.
She's the one who gave me
your students' contact info.
Hello! Good work, everyone.
I bought some food and drinks
to fuel your brains.
- Thanks.
- Much appreciated.
- Thanks for the milk.
- Thank you, Mimi.
- There's enough for everyone.
- Take a look at
- our detailed outline for this chapter.
- Okay.
Does your boss know about this?
No.
But I think I still need to tell her.
Because...
I want to ask her to let us
use the Chenxing office.
The lease for that place
hasn't expired yet, right?
Besides,
every meeting we had before
was at my place.
But now that I'm an undercover agent,
we can't keep meeting at my house.
It would be too easy
to blow my cover, right?
Not bad, Cai Zhangzhu.
I already see you in a new light.
You've grown quite capable now.
The fate of the industry
is every woman's responsibility.
Thanks.
Enjoy your meal.
I have two paths before me now.
First,
I go to Hong Kong, China.
In a few years, I'll be successful,
and then I'll return home in glory.
The other one,
I stay.
But I'll lose all
my clients and connections.
I'll lose Catherine.
I'll have to start over as a nobody.
But I can keep pursuing you.
Even if the odds are against me.
Only a fool would
choose the second path.
So you made the right choice.
Maybe I'm just that fool.
What do you mean?
I've already chosen the second path.
Aren't you going
to Hong Kong, China, tomorrow?
Before coming here,
I already told Catherine
I'm not going to Hong Kong, China.
Even though I still hoped
to hear you ask me to stay,
I've made this decision,
and it won't change.
Are you serious?
I don't want this decision
to affect your future.
It won't.
I'm the one who chose to pursue love.
I might lose some opportunities,
but I'll earn back
what I've lost myself.
If I can't,
then I'm simply not worthy.
Of course, years from now,
if you see a down-and-out me,
I hope you won't look
down on me too much.
Just give me some time.
That's all.
I won't look down on you.
When you first saw me at the hospital,
you were quite dismissive.
I was dismissive then,
but I won't be in the future.
Dinner is on me today.
I was thinking of coming to see you
since you were leaving tomorrow.
But you got here first.
I happened to have some things
I needed your help with,
so I came by to see you.
I've already made plans with your dad.
I'll go play chess with him every week.
I know. He told me.
So, he even went out
and bought a new chessboard.
Don't worry.
There's one more thing.
Go on.
The lease for Chenxing's office
still has a month left.
So I've left it to Zhangzhu
and her Brain-on-Paper Team.
It doesn't feel like
I've been away long,
but it seems like
a lot of time has passed.
I've already spoken to
the property management.
The cleaning lady
is coming this afternoon.
After that, you all can come
and use the place anytime.
Thanks, Ms. Lin.
This is great.
I feel like we're part of
the regular army now.
Good luck to you.
In the future,
if they need any help
and you happen to be free,
please give them a hand.
They're a bunch of young people,
just like we used to be.
Full of passion.
No problem.
These are some outlines and directions
I wanted to work on,
but never got around to.
They're quite suitable
as entry-level choices
for the current market.
I think they might be
useful for Zhangzhu and her team.
At least it can help
broaden their thinking.
Got it.
And about Gu Yan...
If they continue to
challenge Phantom Knight
or spread malicious rumors,
I've already consulted Ma.
We can gather evidence and sue.
What do you think?
He's not worth it.
Agreed.
What time is your flight tomorrow?
Let me drive you to the airport.
No need.
Then, take care of yourself.
Don't worry.
I'm off then.
Did you call a car?
Yes, I did.
It should be here soon.
Let me walk you to the car.
No need.
This is far enough.
Okay.
Lin Zhanqiao.
(Year 2015)
(Heaven's Fall by Phantom Knight)
Lin Zhanqiao, look!
He Han!
He Han, look.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday,
(Heaven's Fall by Phantom Knight)
Phantom Knight!
(Phantom Knight Design Studio)
If you had come ten minutes earlier,
He Han would still be here.
Today, he broke his rule
and had a beer here.
He said he's seeing off a friend.
(Sandalwood Beer)
Why are you drinking?
The person I like is leaving.
Is that
a good enough reason for a drink?
When he comes by next time,
thank him for me.
Even though you two didn't meet,
you were both here drinking a beer
at the same time.
I guess you could call that
a connection.
Thanks.
(Zhanqiao: Mei, I'm leaving tomorrow.
Let's skip the goodbyes)
(to avoid the sadness.
I'll call you when I arrive.)
(May: Worlds apart, yet close at heart.
Safe travels.)
♪I keep asking myself♪
♪What it is I should become♪
♪To follow what my heart truly wants♪
♪Like a drifting dandelion♪
♪Turning where it drifts♪
♪Into soil where it can grow♪
♪When the rain comes, I hide♪
♪In a flower shop at the corner♪
♪Even spring borrows its fragrance♪
♪Moonlight keeps me company
on lonely roads♪
♪Across fields of blooms,
a boat awaits me♪
♪Swaying in the shape of the wind♪
I have an announcement to make.
Today, Mustard Salad's "Original Seal"
is signed with Dingqi Platform
as an S-tier work.
Based on their resource schedule
and our current backlog,
it will be released in two weeks.
Here, this is for you two.
Mr. He Han.
Mr. He Han, you're here.
- Welcome, Mr. He Han.
- Hello, Mr. He Han.
So lively here.
Of course.
Keep it up, Brain-on-Paper Team.
- The legend is here.
- Welcome, Mr. He Han.
- I invited Mr. He Han
to be your consultant.
Good, please.
Mr. He Han,
look, what we have here
are our existing works
and recent backlogs.
Not bad.
If you have any questions,
feel free to ask me.
Besides, Lin Zhanqiao asked me to come,
so you should thank her.
These are some high-potential
outlines she left for everyone.
If you want to start
a new work but lack inspiration,
you can refer to these anytime. Alright?
Thank you so much, Mr. He Han.
You can use Ms. Lin's old office.
Is that okay?
That's perfect.
Good. Ms. Lin left something for you.
I'll go get it for you.
Sure.
Li, come down and take a look.
Mr. He Han,
here.
I'll head out now.
Okay.
(Author. Novel Type. One-Sentence
Outline: My Life, Envies No Immortal)
Hello.
The number you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
Hello.
The subscriber you
dialed is powered off.
Please redial later.
The subscriber you
dialed is powered off.
Mr. Fan.
("The Yin-Dragon Decree")
Hello, Mr. Fan.
Mr. Fan.
We received a novel from Phantom Knight.
I've put it on your desk.
Who?
Phantom Knight.
Still joking at a time like this?
Hello?
Hello.
I'm from Dingqi. My last name is Fan.
I just received
a novel signed by Phantom Knight titled
"My Life Envies No Immortal."
You sent this, right?
Excuse me, who is this?
It's me, Mr. Fan.
He Han.
Why are you making this kind of joke?
I wouldn't choose
a time like this to joke around.
Do you know
how many people I have
to deal with every month
who claim to be Phantom Knight?
If you don't believe me,
you can call Ma yourself.
He's Phantom Knight's editor.
He can prove it.
Have some tea.
So,
Zhanqiao isn't Phantom Knight.
Since you are Phantom Knight,
why did you suddenly stop writing
and switch back to your real name?
Personal reasons.
So that time,
your "Shattered Six States"
plagiarized Phantom Knight's
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui."
Essentially, you were copying yourself.
Is that why you
didn't come forward to clarify things?
How could I? Under those circumstances,
if I had explained everything,
wouldn't I have exposed myself?
Then, what about now?
Are you no longer afraid?
Instead, you've come out
to reveal your identity.
Right now,
at the old Chenxing office,
there are over a dozen young authors
who are persisting with their novels.
They are full of passion and
want to challenge Lingqi Platform.
But their influence is limited
if they're on their own.
If Phantom Knight takes the lead,
this confrontation
might actually be worth a shot.
Even if I believe what you've said,
on what basis should I believe
that you can still produce
work of the same
high standard as before?
Zhanqiao is gone.
You don't even have a decent editor.
Because you have no choice.
You have to believe me.
(Phantom Knight's stunning comeback,
real identity shocks the internet.)
(A new work created by
He Han and Lin Zhanqiao.)
(Phantom Knight returns.
Dingqi invites you to a literary feast.)
(Phantom Knight)
Fan,
where did you
find another Phantom Knight from?
No comment.
Did you ask Mr. Fan?
What did he say?
I couldn't get anything out of him.
What do you mean by that?
It means
I don't know what he's up to either.
Usually when I ask him things,
he'll give me a mix of truth and lies.
But this time, no matter what I ask,
he has no reaction.
He's not hiding anything,
but he's not bragging either.
What does that mean?
Don't you know him well?
Has the real Phantom Knight returned?
Didn't you also suspect
that Lin Zhanqiao was Phantom Knight?
But she's already gone abroad.
What's really going on here?
Even if Lin Zhanqiao
isn't Phantom Knight,
the author who Fan has
can't possibly be
the real Phantom Knight either.
Who could it be, then?
The title of the new novel
has been released,
which means there's content.
If the content wasn't good enough,
Mr. Fan wouldn't
dare to launch it so rashly.
This shows that,
to some extent,
he is very confident.
It's also possible
he's just making a last-ditch effort.
I don't care what the reason is.
I want you to tell me
as quickly as possible
who this Phantom Knight really is.
Also,
no matter who he is,
after the novel goes online,
none of his data can exceed mine.
Don't worry.
This project is nothing more than
using the Phantom Knight name
as a gimmick.
It just has a bit better traffic.
It won't be a good project.
If it were a good project,
Fan would have brought it out long ago.
He wouldn't have waited until now.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you getting nervous?
Me, nervous?
I see you've been
drinking water constantly.
When did this happen?
It...
It's been so many years that he...
I entered this industry because of him.
Hello, Mr. He Han.
Did you see the news?
Phantom Knight is going
to serialize a new novel.
It's the real Phantom Knight himself.
I saw it.
Let's wait and see.
(Chapter 52: Luoshui Overflows,
No Fish in Sight)
(Phantom Knight's latest work)
Now is the time
for each of us
to bring out our best resources
and give it our all.
We'll see who has the real skill.
No problem.
So, who exactly is Phantom Knight?
He's here.
He Han?
It's He Han.
He Han has been frequenting
Dingqi Platform lately,
having closed-door meetings with Fan.
I checked.
He has stopped all his
online and offline classes.
The writer behind Phantom Knight
must be He Han.
That's why Fan
dared to say the work wouldn't be bad.
Why is it him again?
Mr. He Han,
Dai Shan found out it's you.
What did she say?
As soon as she returned to the company,
she told everyone
that the person behind
Phantom Knight's return
is you, Mr. He Han.
And then,
she said you were
impersonating him
and deceiving the public.
She told everyone to get ready,
and as soon as the new novel is live,
they will launch attacks from all sides.
She wants to...
Make sure I never recover.
That's pretty much what she meant.
What should we do, Mr. He Han?
We all know
that you chose to step up
and pose as Phantom Knight
just to lead the way
for us young authors.
But we
can't just watch the bullets hit you
and not defend you.
Didn't you say it yourself?
Whoever holds
the banner for the dreamers
is the Phantom Knight.
Right?
What?
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Come on in.
Sit.
Go ahead.
What do you want to ask?
Regarding the Phantom Knight novel
that Dingqi Platform
is about to release,
you ghostwrote it, didn't you?
I wrote it.
Don't you look down on yourself?
Why?
The name "He Han"
already has enough
weight in the industry,
but you're still not satisfied.
You want more.
You want to surpass yourself
by standing at Phantom Knight's height
to enjoy even more success.
But have you ever thought
that once all of this is exposed,
the halo that the name "He Han"
brought you
might disappear along with it?
What are you laughing at?
Why does no one believe
that I am the Phantom Knight?
Have you ever heard the saying?
The person you see in yourself
is not you.
The person others see in you
is not you, either.
But the way you see others,
that's who you are.
The things you cherish as treasures
might not even matter to anyone else.
You make it sound so simple.
Don't you want to return
to the top of the charts
and to live in those
massive hotel suites again?
I don't believe you at all.
We're all just ordinary people.
Ordinary people say they don't care,
but their actions are honest.
I agree.
The action is honest.
And mine is telling me
that apartment was too big.
One person doesn't need that much space.
The extra space
is just called emptiness.
You might be No. 1
on the charts right now,
but you have no one by your side
to share that joy and achievement with.
Is it worth it?
Besides, you know
that this top spot
is something you'll lose eventually.
Be smart.
An ordinary person should
understand what I'm saying.
You're saying
it's a case
of sour grapes.
I've tasted them.
They weren't that good.
How do I know
you're not just finding
another excuse to tie me down?
Mr. Fan has already called you
and explained the situation.
Helping the company
is helping me,
and it's helping yourself.
I know you're making other plans,
but you haven't found
anything yet, right?
For this current wave,
if we team up with Mr. Fan
and Phantom Knight,
we might not fully stage a comeback,
but at least we can
get some breathing room.
At that point,
when we liquidate the company,
what's left might actually be profit.
You won't talk now
because of the company's debt, right?
What do you mean?
Are you saying
you'd agree to dissolve the company?
Yes.
Let's set a timeframe.
What timeframe?
From now
until the babies are born,
we start the liquidation process.
Why the babies' birth?
Because I can't divorce you yet.
Once our babies are born
and the one-year nursing period is over,
we can get a divorce.
One year is just enough time
to finish the liquidation.
What's wrong, Zhao Lanxin?
You don't seriously think
that the only thing
I want to split up with you
is the company, do you?
If you can agree to this,
I can immediately go
find interested companies
to negotiate copyright pre-sales.
With a name like Phantom Knight,
even without a specific work yet,
it won't be hard to negotiate.
The real challenge will be
how to negotiate an even higher price.
Of course,
you could choose to
cooperate with someone else.
But first,
it takes time for
someone new to get involved.
Second, and most importantly,
you don't trust anyone,
let alone someone new.
I promise you.
Write it down.
Write what?
Write that after the children are born,
we will have a divorce by agreement.
And after the company's
assets are liquidated,
we will split them fifty-fifty.
I won't write it.
(Letter of Commitment: Divorce
by agreement after the babies are born.)
(Assets after company liquidation to be
split 50/50. Guarantor: Zhao Lanxin.)
Come with me to see
Mr. Fan tomorrow morning.
(Phantom Knight's Return.
Dingqi invites you to a literary feast.)
(Phantom Knight's Return.)
(Dingqi invites you
to a literary feast.)
(New work in preparation and creation.)
(Phantom Knight's Return.
Dingqi invites you to a literary feast.)
("My Life Envies No Immortal",
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui")
(Rankings)
("Demon Emperor: Nine-Tailed Fox",
"Fate Reset: Divine Doctor's Daughter")
("My Life Envies No Immortal"
Author: Phantom Knight)
I support him.
Well, for Gu Yan,
good will triumph over evil.
Yes, I know genres are popping up.
Like daily check-in
or immortality styles
and Eastern fantasy.
But we can agree
that good work
isn't just a stack
of these new elements, right?
Right.
A classic is a classic.
If we innovate in
structure and core themes,
that's enough.
Staring at the screen like this
is completely useless.
Our data won't go up just
because you're staring at it!
You should be doing something right now.
Whether it's spending money
or asking for favors,
that's what works.
You can express your anxiety,
but you can't treat me like an idiot.
You were the one who said
big data can simulate
reader interest and pacing
with perfect accuracy.
And you also said
that He Han is at his wits' end
and can't write anything good anymore.
If big data could have told me
that your emotions are so unstable
and you're so fond of shifting blame,
I might not have cooperated with you.
This is my work.
This is my honor!
This is our work.
It's a work of Lingqi Platform.
It doesn't belong to you alone.
Success or failure,
it all belongs to Lingqi Platform.
Tomorrow, He Han will face
the readers' judgment
for his impersonation.
Not only will his readers
look down on him,
but Phantom Knight's
readers will also tear him apart.
Bye.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪