♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 2=
(Could my contract wife)
(be my cousin's first love?)
(Four Years Ago, Linhai Medical University)
Stop following me.
Xu Nange,
that pipette won't stop me.
Please stop following me.
Not until you say yes.
I'm not giving up.
I'm not into dating.
Got it?
Xu Nange.
So it's dating you hate, not me.
Trust me.
I'll give you an amazing life.
I think
you should work
on your own life first.
Your family must be rich.
But all I see
is a spoiled rich kid wasting his life.
Sorry.
I was pretty awful back then.
When I come back this time,
I hope you'll accept me.
Mr. Huo.
What's wrong, Mr. Huo?
How much did Xu Nange pay you?
Huh?
I don't know what you mean.
She's the senior
Zichen loved for years.
Don't tell me you didn't know.
I...
I really didn't, Mr. Huo.
Then you botched the background check.
I...
Xu Nange
broke Zichen's heart,
then signed the marriage contract.
Are you two in this together?
I'm innocent!
Mr. Huo...
Here's what happened.
I only did what you asked.
Out of all the candidates,
she seemed like a fit,
so I gave you her file.
Right?
You made the final call.
You chose her.
You liked
her research skills, medical background,
and thought
she might help
with Old Mrs. Huo's condition.
So...
Besides,
if I had an agenda,
why would I bring more resumes
yesterday for you to review? Right?
Mr. Huo,
you tricked me?
Then tell me.
Why would she agree
to a temporary marriage?
Her file says
family and school reasons.
I'm not sure about the family part.
As for school,
she probably needs
three more months for her thesis.
The current rules say
married PhD and master's students
can take marriage leave.
She must be
out of options.
Get the car.
Find her.
What will you do?
I'll teach her
where the line is.
So you do answer calls.
Busy as always, Dr. Big Shot?
Say it,
or I'm hanging up.
Fine.
I'll make it quick.
Just letting you know,
your room is becoming
a walk-in closet.
Come get
all your junk,
or I'm throwing it out.
I'll come tomorrow.
Don't touch anything.
Who wants your trash?
You know what?
Just marry someone already
and stop showing up here.
You're annoying.
Fine.
Then wait for my good news.
Why are you here?
House calls weren't in the contract.
You live here?
Yeah.
Don't come in if you're judging.
I wasn't planning to.
I...
Not inviting me up?
I came to ask you something.
Why go through all this
to get close to the Huo family?
Get close to the Huo family?
Huo Zichen.
Explain that.
Who's Huo Zichen?
Your junior,
and my cousin.
I sort of remember him.
Seriously?
Are you Huo men
all here to make my life harder?
He chased me years ago,
and I made it clear
that I didn't like him.
So you rejected him
to get to me?
Huo Beiyan,
are you that narcissistic?
You asked me to marry you.
Maybe you should
get your head checked.
Is that so?
You were testing me?
Just being careful.
I can ignore many things,
but family is my line.
Zichen will be back in a week.
So
the deal is off.
We're divorcing.
Here's extra compensation.
(Huo Trust Bank, 200,000 to Xu Nange)
Works for me.
I was worried
this would get messy.
Good deal.
Let's divorce.
Shen Yan,
arrange the divorce tomorrow.
What?
Divorce?
Mr. Huo, you're kidding, right?
That's not possible.
Why?
There's a cooling-off period.
How long?
One month.
You won't be divorced
before your cousin gets back.
My money!
Deal's off. The contract stays.
You...
Aren't you afraid he'll snap?
There's a cooling-off period.
Use your brain.
Yin,
listen to me.
Getting an interview at Huo Group
is only step one.
What if he doesn't remember me?
We only met once.
Most women never even
get that chance with Huo Beiyan.
Besides,
with that face of yours,
you'll win him over.
I'll make sure
everything is perfect
so you look your best.
Is he really getting married?
What if the source is wrong?
Family first, career second.
That's the Huo family rule.
Everyone knows that.
Huo Beiyan has officially
taken over the family.
Our Xu family
has to seize this chance.
Mom,
just wait for my good news.
Xu Nange,
keep it down.
You're so annoying.
Is everything packed?
Don't leave anything,
or I'll throw it straight in the trash.
Don't worry.
I won't set foot here again.
Came back for junk?
How pathetic.
Mom,
I need a whole new look.
Of course.
Use my card.
You have to win
Huo Beiyan's heart.
(Huo Beiyan?)
He's mine.
Absolutely.
What are you laughing at, Xu Nange?
I'm not laughing.
I'm not the smiling type.
Then go cry
in your crappy rental.
I'm sick of seeing you.
Xu Yin,
haven't you heard?
Huo Beiyan is already married.
That's impossible.
With the Huo family's status,
if he got married,
the whole city would know.
Wait.
What's that?
A marriage certificate?
(Marriage Certificate)
Xu Nange, you're married?
You told me to get married,
so I did.
(Marriage Certificate)
Let me see
what broke loser you married.
Why'd you snatch it?
Embarrassed?
Honestly?
A little.
I'm out.
Good. Go.
Don't ever come back.
Same suitcase as mine?
Wait.
(Graduation Certificate)
Isn't that mine?
Please move, Mrs. Huo.
Wait.
Who told you to move this?
I did.
Huo Beiyan,
you again?
Turns out
you're the real schemer.
Can't deal
with your cousin,
so you take it out on my stuff?
Very funny.
What do you want?
Starting today,
you're moving in with me.
What?
Come on, Dad.
That's not even a family rule.
I'm doing this for your grandma's peace of mind.
Besides,
you're already legally married.
Why can't she live with us?
Her family is more traditional.
We'll talk after the wedding.
Then come to the board dinner in two days,
dressed properly.
That shouldn't be a problem, right?
She's...
pretty busy lately.
She has no time.
As the Huo family's
daughter-in-law,
she should be there.
Anyway, I... I'll listen to Grandma.
Yes, listen to Grandma.
Listen to her? You're taking advantage
of her not being able...
- Come home. Good.
- I...
Come home.
Home will be livelier.
That's my mom.
When it matters,
you never miss.
Still got it.
My grandson...
No, you brat.
You heard your grandma.
I get that you want
to be a good grandson.
But why move my things?
I'm not moving.
Xu Nange,
this isn't up for debate.
Huo Beiyan, I'm not asking
for your permission either.
All we signed was...
Keep it down.
I know.
All we signed
was a fake marriage contract,
not a slave contract.
Where does it say
I have to move in with you?
That's unreasonable.
And honestly, not safe for me.
Not safe?
What are you scared of?
That I'll eat you?
Huo Beiyan,
do you really think
every woman wants you?
Why should I go along with this?
Because you signed it.
If divorce didn't take a month,
I'd already be gone.
Besides, Zichen finding out doesn't scare me.
It scares you.
Then what exactly
will make you cooperate?
Now that's a better attitude.
Let's be honest.
You need my help
to reassure your grandma
and answer to the Huo family.
Fine.
I get all that.
But I, Xu Nange,
respond to kindness, not threats.
I want you to show some real sincerity
and beg me nicely,
instead of using that arrogant CEO tone
to micromanage my life.
You think you look cool?
You want me to beg you?
I...
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪