♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 6=
Without air conditioning,
aren't you hot?
This is an old apartment complex.
A powerful AC unit
would drive up the electric bill.
What if I reimburse the bill?
Then sure.
Just eat.
Don't be shy.
Make yourself
at home.
♪How did you stay close to me?♪
This is seriously so good.
How are you this good at cooking?
If you like it, eat more.
♪Even though I still believe♪
Is it really that good?
It's amazing.
Have some more.
♪Doesn't mean to say♪
(Product Development Schedule)
Boss,
why are you still here this late?
It's me.
Mr. Zichen?
You…
Didn't Beiyan go on a trip?
I just figured
I'd help lighten his workload.
I see.
You know,
why doesn't Beiyan set his wallpaper
to a picture of his wife?
Mr. Huo's a total workaholic.
He's the type
who keeps work and emotions
completely separate.
That makes sense.
Oh right.
I remember Beiyan used to have
a marriage arrangement with the Ye family.
Before I went abroad, both families
were already discussing it.
But now that he's married,
what happened to them?
Mr. Huo and Miss Ye's engagement
was called off a long time ago.
Probably not long
after you left the country.
The Ye family didn't say much at the time.
Though I heard
Miss Ye was pretty upset.
But after that,
she never caused Mr. Huo any trouble.
In that case,
I'll go make you some coffee.
This AI setup of yours
looks way too fake.
Look at us standing by the ocean.
Our expressions are stiff as boards.
And look at your smile. It's like someone
pulled up the corners of your mouth.
One glance and you can tell it's fake.
I'll tweak it a bit more.
♪Sometimes we roll the dice♪
,♪To see what the future hides♪
♪Spinning us round and round
like a never-ending ride♪
♪But I gave you everything♪
You've actually got a pretty cute face.
What did you say?
Your AI controls
are actually really good.
It feels natural.
Here, look.
Anything else look off?
This snowy mountain looks so real.
Almost... too real.
You like snowy mountains?
Back when I was
at the Linhai research lab,
there was a study trip to Europe.
The location was the Alps.
The mountains there
looked exactly like this picture.
Too bad I never got to go.
If you want to go,
you can just tell me.
You...
I...
There are discounted tickets
and a free upgrade.
Not going.
I'm busy.
I'm serious. Miss this chance
and it's gone for good.
I'm serious too.
I'm really busy.
Alright then, Nange.
Don't forget to wash the dishes.
Why am I washing dishes again?
I cook, you wash.
Fine.
What do you want to eat?
Braised pork.
Alright, I'll go buy groceries.
Wash the dishes properly.
Xu Nange, open the door!
Who is it?
Who told you to come here?
Didn't I already say not
to contact me unless necessary?
Living in a dump like this,
and you still dare claim
you married Mr. Huo?
Xu Nange,
have you become a scam artist now?
Where's the marriage certificate?
You wouldn't let me see it before.
Take it out.
I'm exposing your lies right now.
What's wrong with you two?
Get out.
Why are you nervous?
Show us the marriage certificate.
Not only
did you fool people at Huo Group,
you even lied
to your university advisor.
Let me tell you.
I've already figured you out, Xu Nange.
If you really are Mrs. Huo,
then call Huo Beiyan over
and let him save you from this mess.
Right?
Why should I call him?
We have visitors?
Mr... Mr. Huo?
Mr. Huo.
They are my stepmother and my sister.
Then sit.
I bought enough groceries
for four people anyway.
Wait, what?
When did I say
I was keeping them for dinner?
That really is Mr. Huo?
Mr. Huo,
why are you living
in a place this rundown?
Did Xu Nange force you?
Just tell me.
I'll teach her a lesson for you.
Where my wife and I live
is none of your business.
Nange, dear,
have some water.
Calm down a little.
You two carry on.
I'm going back to eating.
Xu Yin,
watch your manners.
Mom!
What "Mom"?
Learn something from Nange.
When you eat,
focus on eating properly.
Right, Nange?
Eat more.
Look at you.
You've gotten thinner.
Maybe I've been...
This braised pork is really good.
...a little too strict with you before.
Then eat more.
You're all so loud.
Just eat.
Mom, I feel wronged.
Wronged about what?
Shut up and eat.
I already said you're too noisy.
I...
I have huge news for you.
Our Nange
married the eldest son
of the Huo family,
Huo Beiyan.
What other Huo family could there be?
How many people in Hai City
dare carry the surname Huo?
Why would I lie to you?
What would I gain from it?
They are very lovey-dovey.
They're perfectly happy living together
in that tiny apartment downtown.
Where's that?
That's where our Nange
used to lock herself away for research,
studying day and night like
those old scholars burning midnight oil.
Very admirable, really.
Do you even realize
they never actually left Hai City?
Answer my question.
Understood.
I'm giving you three hours.
Bring the two of them back.
If they don't return,
then neither should you.
But sir, three hours...
Go!
Yes,
right away.
Mr. Huo, ma'am,
please just come back with me.
The old master specifically ordered it.
I...
I'm not going back.
I'm perfectly comfortable here.
Why go back?
Mr. Huo, you don't understand
how angry the old master is right now.
If you don't return,
I won't be able to explain myself.
How about you head back first?
I'll go home after my dad cools down.
Not a chance.
You think I'm going back alone
while you stay here?
Absolutely not.
Either we both go back,
or neither of us does.
- Let's talk this through.
- I was just...
What are you two doing?
Old Master!
Why are you here?
Didn't you say three hours?
It hasn't been three hours yet.
You're hopeless, kid.
I had to come personally.
Dad.
Nange.
Beiyan.
Look at this place.
Why make yourselves suffer
living somewhere like this?
What are you standing around for?
Pack your things
and come home with me.
Did you even suffer?
There's not even a proper bed here.
Come on, start packing.
I know. If you hate it so much, don't stay.
Who asked you to stay anyway?
Mind your own business.
You're still worried about Zichen?
Leave it to time.
Accepting our marriage
will take time.
Accepting the way we live together
will also take time.
And when we eventually divorce,
it'll tear open his wounds
all over again.
Those three blows combined
will need a long time to soften
if we want to minimize the damage.
So...
I want you
to promise me something first.
Until the timing is right,
maintain things as they are
for as long as possible.
How long are we talking?
What's the longest you could accept?
Mr. Huo, the old madam's condition
is acting up again.
Please hurry and check on her.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪