♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 3=
I want you to show some real sincerity
and beg me nicely,
instead of using that arrogant CEO tone
to micromanage my life.
You think you look cool?
You want me to beg you? I...
Hello?
You want me to move my car?
Got it. I'm on my way.
I'll be right there.
Isn't the car right here?
Xu Nange,
could you please move into my place?
Do me a favor, please?
What did you say? I didn't catch that.
Xu Nange, I...
Alright, let's move.
Get in. Hurry up.
Shen Yan.
Let's go.
Dad,
let me introduce you.
This is Xu Nange.
This is my father,
and this is my grandma.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Huo.
Nice to meet you, Grandma.
Nange,
nice to meet you.
don't mind her.
She's our family matriarch.
She's in her 70s now.
She has dementia, so she doesn't
remember people or past events anymore.
Mom,
this is your granddaughter-in-law,
Xu Nange.
What's wrong, Nange?
Low blood sugar?
I'll be fine as long as I get
an early night tonight.
Don't worry about it, Mr. Huo.
Come on.
You two are already married.
Why are you still calling me Mr. Huo?
Well, we haven't had the wedding yet.
She should go through the tea ceremony
before changing how she addresses you.
Yeah.
You really know
your traditional etiquette. Very well.
My mom is definitely going to love you.
Right, Mom?
Nange,
you seem really ill.
Yeah.
I am actually feeling a bit
under the weather today.
In that case,
let's catch up another day.
Nange isn't feeling well today.
Alright.
Head over to the apartment
and get some rest.
That apartment
will be your marital home from now on.
It's just
a three-minute walk from here.
That way, I won't disturb you,
but we can still look out for each other.
Go on over.
Okay, let's head out then.
Alright.
Hurry up.
Mom,
your granddaughter-in-law
is really great.
Wonderful.
Read this.
What's this?
Since you just launched
a harsh personal attack on me,
I think
we should
sign a supplementary agreement.
Here's the first clause.
Since this move
was completely unplanned,
(Clause 1: Disruption Compensation)
it poses a potential risk of disrupting
the progress
of Party B's research papers.
For instance,
disrupting Party B's
physical balance in any shape or form.
Including, but not limited to,
fabricating clinical symptoms induced
by tripping, bumping, or shoving.
Party A, meaning you,
will need to cover all time-related costs
that Party B, meaning me,
might incur as a result.
The compensation will be
calculated at 300% of my hourly rate.
Hourly rate?
Dr. Xu,
what exactly is your labor
valued at on the open market?
As a PhD student
at Linhai Medical University,
my monthly stipend
averages about 2,800 yuan.
Based on the legal 40-hour work week,
that breaks down to 24.10 per hour.
300% of that
would be 72.30 yuan.
But given your status,
which is incredibly high-profile,
this could cause me
additional mental distress.
So,
I think we should round it up
to an even 100 yuan per hour.
Keep the pocket change.
No need to thank me.
You...
Clause two.
My experimental data
and research materials
require the highest level
of security clearance.
Without my biometric authentication,
(Clause 2: Data Security)
no one is allowed to touch anything.
That includes you, Mr. Huo.
No one at all?
What if there's a fire?
Not even firefighters?
In case of emergency,
I need to be
on-site to authorize access.
Dr. Xu.
We are signing
a cohabitation agreement here.
It's not some nuclear launch code.
Mr. Huo,
my research is more important
than nuclear weapons.
It could determine the future
treatment path
for certain mental disorders.
Are you done?
My turn.
Clause one.
Party B must, in all settings
outside the lab,
concede that Party A holds
all superficial rights
of a legal spouse.
Including, but not limited to,
holding hands, hugging,
and intimate interaction when necessary.
Yes.
That's exactly the face.
Don't look
as sharp as you did just now.
Wait,
that's your own demand.
You can't include that.
Clause two.
In front of Party A's family,
Party B must proactively display
a stable, loving marriage
at least once a day.
Within a week, you must complete
all background reading required
to act as the wife of Huo Group's CEO.
That's absolutely impossible.
Even my lab data doesn't run
that smoothly every time.
Clause three
is about my brother, Huo Zichen.
No need to explain.
I get it. We need to
get our story straight.
Our marriage was totally unexpected,
and we...
Fell hopelessly in love.
It was love...
at first sight.
Can we change the wording a bit?
We are
the optimal match
based on a rational evaluation.
Dr. Xu,
Zichen isn't stupid.
A story that's too logical
won't fool him.
Besides,
you're just putting on
a little irrational performance
in exchange for my full backing
on your upcoming research papers,
along with...
this entire house
that can hold
those nuclear weapons of yours.
Isn't that enough?
Deal.
Well, I hope you
can strictly stick
to the terms of this agreement.
Don't worry, Mr. Huo.
Since this is a contract marriage,
I'll definitely show
some professional integrity.
What do you mean, contract marriage?
Dad.
What are you doing here?
I came over
to have Nange
pick out a car she likes,
so she has something
to drive for her daily commute.
But I just heard something
about a contract marriage.
What's that about?
Contract marriage?
What contract marriage?
Please, have a seat first.
This is on you.
Why did you have to use
such a cold term?
The contract we were talking about
is just an interdisciplinary
research project Beiyan and I built
around our marriage.
An interdisciplinary research project?
Right.
Interdisciplinary.
Interdisciplinary is great.
That sounds pretty interesting.
Tell me more.
As you know, I'm a medical student.
I'm used to using data
and models to understand everything.
Before I met Beiyan,
marriage to me
was just this massive,
highly unpredictable, unknown system.
Beiyan hoped that by treating it
like a research project,
I could adapt to my new role
as quickly as possible
and stop stressing out.
So I defined this KPI
as the initialization contract
of our marital relationship,
which is exactly
what you just overheard.
Don't stress out, okay?
I pretty much get the gist of it.
Alright.
I won't keep you guys, then.
You two
can get back to your project.
Dad.
I'll walk you out.
I didn't understand a single word.
Alright.
Pick one.
Not like you can take it with you
when the contract ends anyway.
No thanks.
I don't even have a driver's license.
Why do you sound so proud
of not having a license?
You're a grown adult.
And you
call yourself a PhD student?
Mr. Huo,
we're at the campus.
Can we keep it low-key?
Let's go.
Where to now?
Shopping
for a new outfit
to get ready for the dinner party.
Come on.
Just buy whatever you want.
Is there a budget limit?
If I don't spend it all,
can I cash out the rest?
Not a chance.
Get in. Come on.
Cheapskate. Can we negotiate?
The party starts at 7:00 p.m.
It's rude to be late.
What on earth is that noise?
Are you doing makeup
or running lab tests?
If you stopped rushing me,
my efficiency would shoot up
by at least 20%.
♪Sometimes we roll the dice♪
♪To see what the future hides♪
♪Spinning us round and round
like a never-ending ride♪
♪But I gave you everything♪
♪Even the songs I loved to sing♪
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪