♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 5=
We only got married not long ago.
I only just found out
he's your cousin too.
I accept it.
Maybe it's just coincidence.
Or fate.
You never used to believe in fate.
But I believe saying that
makes you feel better.
I understand.
Zichen,
I'm sorry.
I didn't know
the person you loved was...
was...
Xu Nange.
Nange,
from now on,
please take good care of my cousin.
He only looks cold and arrogant,
but he's actually very caring.
Beiyan,
Nange is a good girl.
Don't let her down.
I'm going back
to say hello to the others.
You two talk.
(That's impossible.)
(From what I know about Xu Nange,)
(there's no way she and Beiyan)
(could've had
some romantic chance encounter.)
(Something's definitely off.)
You're seriously still eating?
What else am I supposed to do?
Him liking me is his business.
What's that got to do with me?
I'm hungry.
I still need to eat.
I'm starving.
Besides,
skipping meals solves nothing.
It'll just ruin my experiments tomorrow.
You don't seriously still think
I came after you and Huo Zichen, do you?
Fine.
I believe you.
Good.
I don't like people talking
behind my back.
From now on,
we live our own lives.
Once the three-month agreement ends,
we part ways peacefully.
Zichen.
Beiyan.
Are you cold?
It's much warmer than overseas.
Actually, I know
you still haven't moved on.
You were only keeping up
appearances for the Huo family.
- That's why you...
- Beiyan.
I originally thought that once
I made something of myself abroad
and came back,
I'd finally be able to catch up to you.
But I never expected
I couldn't even beat you in love.
I didn't even realize
you were my rival.
Zichen,
actually...
Beiyan,
let's not talk about this anymore.
It's been four years.
It's time to move on.
After tonight, it's all behind us.
Nange was right.
Some things are just fate.
Zichen...
Ma'am, your VIP card
will be ready within five minutes.
Mr. Huo specifically instructed us
to prioritize
your requests.
Thank you.
I'll stay here by myself.
Go ahead and continue with your work.
Well, well.
Isn't this my dear sister, Xu Nange?
You came to apply for work too?
Just passing by.
Oh please.
Don't tell me you're here trying
to corner Mr. Huo too?
Didn't expect the genius PhD
to still have some brains left.
Miss,
without an appointment,
you'll need to leave.
Then what's she doing here?
A broke student
trying to fish for opportunities?
I'm here for an interview.
I want to see Mr. Huo.
This is Mr. Huo's wife.
If you refuse to leave,
I'll have security escort you out.
What?
Mr. Huo's wife?
Impossible.
There's no way she's Mr. Huo's wife.
She's a liar.
Ma'am,
your VIP card is ready.
Thank you.
(VIP Access Pass)
Please use the executive elevator.
I'll handle the trouble here for you.
Wait.
Security.
I...
Xu Nange...
Why did you call me here?
Some things
are safer to discuss here.
Come, sit first.
This
can't keep going.
I'm really worried about Zichen.
I talked with him last night.
I could clearly tell
he still hasn't moved on from you.
Living so close to each other
isn't helping.
Seeing each other
every day will only
keep reopening his wounds.
Besides,
there are too many eyes
in the Huo family.
Our agreement
could easily be exposed.
So,
the only solution is...
we go on a honeymoon.
You mean, running away?
Will that actually work?
Like you said,
things have already come to this.
The only thing we can do now
is let time cool things down
and help Zichen slowly move on.
Until he accepts reality,
we also need to be careful
about ending our agreement marriage.
Fine.
It's not like we have a better option.
Then,
we leave tonight.
Wait.
If it's a honeymoon,
I can't go too far.
It's in the supplementary agreement.
My research can't be delayed.
We'll stay in Hai City.
Stay in Hai City?
Huo Beiyan,
you do know who you are, right?
If we hide in Hai City,
your father's going
to find us sooner or later.
That apartment you used to rent,
nobody knows about it, right?
Not really.
But,
can you even live there?
It's a little rundown,
but for Zichen,
I can manage.
Alright.
I'll head back tonight
and get ready to move.
My room really isn't that bad.
Oh really?
You really saw Xu Nange
at the Huo Group?
I'm asking you.
I saw her with my own eyes.
I find it impossible to believe
that Xu Nange could become Mrs. Huo.
Mom,
I'm not over this.
That Xu Nange!
Acting all innocent is one thing,
but she even humiliated me
in front of everyone at Huo Group.
Mom,
I feel awful.
Something's suspicious
about this.
I will get to the bottom of it for you.
Don't be upset anymore.
How are you going to do that?
We start by going to where she lives
and questioning her properly.
There's only one bed in my place.
You take the couch,
and I'll take the bed.
This couch is practically collapsing.
Can anyone even sleep on that?
The door's over there.
If you don't want to sleep here,
you can leave.
Fine. I'll sleep here.
But we need ground rules.
First,
no noise after 10 p.m.
I need my sleep.
Second,
don't enter my space without permission.
This is my space.
Third,
we take turns cooking.
I can't stand takeout.
Deal.
Then I have three rules too.
First...
Get out.
First,
from 8 a.m. to 4 p.m. is my thesis time.
You are not allowed to disturb me.
Second, the fan stays
on medium speed only.
High speed affects my concentration.
You don't have air conditioning?
A fan?
You can leave if you want.
Third, you are not allowed to touch
any of my research materials,
especially the stack on my desk.
Then make yourself at home, Mr. Huo.
I'm eating.
That's what you eat?
Do you have some kind
of self-destructive tendency?
I think this
maintains vital functions
and fills my stomach.
Seems perfectly fine to me.
If you want something else,
feel free to order takeout.
Fine.
I'll cook from now on.
You can cook?
What's so surprising about that?
Honestly, the real miracle
is that you've survived this long.
I...
Come on.
Dinner's ready.
How did you make so many dishes?
This shredded potato is amazing.
Really?
The onion beef is even better.
How did you make it?
I used pearl onions.
First, you finely chop the butter
and cook it until fully melted.
That way,
it doesn't overpower the flavor
of the Chinese dish,
while still preserving the richness
of the beef.
This is seriously delicious.
Eat.
Without air conditioning, aren't you hot?
This is an old apartment complex.
A powerful AC unit
would drive up the electric bill.
What if I reimburse the bill?
Then sure.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪