♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 1=
Our marriage will last for three months.
During this period,
both parties must cooperate fully
and face the risks together.
Add a clause. The marriage
ends automatically upon expiration,
and both parties
must cooperate to finalize the divorce.
(Temporary Marriage Agreement)
(Marriage Registry, Civil Affairs Bureau
of Nanhai District, Hai City)
Any income earned by either party
before or during the marriage
(Temporary Marriage Agreement)
belong solely to that individual
and will not be treated
as marital property.
Once the agreement ends,
neither party can claim
any rights or demand any compensation.
Add another clause. During the marriage,
both parties
must respect each other's private lives
and treat one another
like total strangers.
Any more questions?
Nope, that's it.
Let's proceed, then.
(Marriage Registry, Civil Affairs Bureau
of Nanhai District, Hai City)
(Holder: Huo Beiyan)
Mr. Huo.
Morning, Mr. Huo.
Here are the seven candidates
I've picked for you today.
First up,
He Hua.
24 years old.
Has a background
in business management. Height...
(Personal Profile: He Hua)
Six-foot-one?
Don't bother.
I'm already married.
Wait, who did you pick?
We had a medical student
(Holder: Huo Beiyan)
in the applicants two days ago.
She seemed alright.
Well, that officially checks off
the family rule of getting married
before focusing on your career.
Isn't this a bit rushed, though?
What about her personality or character?
- Are you guys compatible?
- Doesn't matter.
I don't really care.
Get back to work.
(Zichen)
Hello, Zichen?
Beiyan,
I'm planning to head back home.
- That's awesome. Are you...
- By the way, Mr. Huo,
where should I
put this marriage certificate?
Beiyan,
you're getting married?
This is huge. Why didn't you tell me?
Who's my sister-in-law?
Just a regular woman.
Her name is, uh...
You'll find out when you get back.
Beiyan,
since you're getting married,
I guess I really need to step up my game
with my own love life too.
Beiyan,
do you remember
that woman I was crazy about
when I was an undergrad?
I feel like I'm in her league now.
You never mentioned her to me.
That's on me.
I'll introduce you to her when I'm back.
Why don't you give me a quick breakdown
of what my future sister-in-law is like?
How should I put it?
She has
a very sexy mind.
♪You brought the cold in with you♪
♪You fill the room♪
♪Is it darkness in you♪
♪If we talk this over♪
♪Will you tell the truth♪
♪Can you picture forever♪
Hey.
- It's you?
You just knocked over my research data.
What are you scowling at?
I was just wondering
if this whole thing
is part of your scheme.
What scheme?
Staging a chance encounter
just to get my attention
and then
trying to get a piece of my fortune.
(Authorized Personnel Only)
Can't you see
that massive sign on the door?
Authorized personnel only.
Well, I'm authorized, am I?
I...
Yes.
You're my legally wedded husband now.
But this lab is a...
(Linhai Medical University, Xu Nange)
Xu Nange?
Listen up.
This trick of yours
isn't going to work on me.
Listen up.
Get out of here right now.
Why should I leave?
Get out.
Get out now.
You're filthy.
I'm filthy?
- Me? I take two showers a day.
- You didn't sanitize. You...
Xu Nange,
why are you yelling
at our university trustee?
He's...
Mr. Huo, what brings you here?
Professor Liang,
did you just say he's a trustee?
Yes.
I'll deal with you later.
Mr. Huo, our main lab
is in the East Building.
I'll show you the way.
I saw the sign,
authorized personnel.
This way.
After you.
I now have a good grasp
of our school's research progress,
so I've decided
to increase my funding.
However,
I personally
happen to be more interested
in research related
to Alzheimer's disease.
This topic
is currently one of the most challenging
and cutting-edge fields
in medicine.
On top of that,
the leading expert in this field
happens to be right here in our country.
Dr. X?
Yes.
They're an absolute
legend in the industry.
and their identity is a mystery.
Their papers
are only occasionally
published on preprint servers.
(A Novel Pathway
to Cognitive Reconstruction)
(By: X (Ph.D.))
How about this?
(Department of Experimental Neurology)
I'll have the team focus on keeping up
with the progress
of Dr. X's research papers.
Alright.
Oh, by the way,
about my student just now,
I'm incredibly sorry.
Don't worry.
She's actually my wife.
We were just bickering.
However, I'd prefer to keep
our marriage private.
I hope you can keep this to yourselves.
I understand.
Rest assured, Mr. Huo.
Absolutely.
Remember, everyone.
Keep it a secret.
- Got it.
- Don't worry.
Mr. Huo,
if you didn't want them to know,
don't tell them in the first place.
Wow, you're so right.
Why didn't I think of that?
Care to enlighten me?
My marriage is a massive deal,
and secrets always find a way
of getting out.
By asking them to keep it quiet,
I'm just laying the groundwork
to prove I'm really married.
Otherwise,
if my dad finds something fishy,
I'll be in trouble.
Brilliant.
Cut out the flattery.
Mr. Huo.
Huo Beiyan, the eldest son
of Hai City's richest man, Huo Baoxiang,
has been appearing frequently.
Word is he's about to take the helm
of the Huo Group empire.
Will this multi-billion dollar
family fortune
spark a new power struggle?
This is shaping up to be
Huo Beiyan's most critical challenge.
(Marriage Registry)
Get out.
Get out now. You're filthy.
No wonder he wanted
to sign an agreement.
Wait, didn't I just
land myself a massive headache?
Xu Nange,
how did you get mixed up
with someone like that?
This won't do.
The risk is way too high.
(Temporary Marriage Agreement)
Wait, this isn't right either.
If I piss him off,
won't I just end up
in even bigger trouble?
I...
(Temporary Marriage Agreement)
Grandma,
I'll definitely find a way to cure you.
You won't keep losing your memory.
All your memories
will come flooding back.
I promise you.
Huo Beiyan.
Dad,
don't yell like that.
You'll scare Grandma.
What is wrong with you?
You secretly found
some random woman
and just went and married her?
What do you mean random woman?
She's your daughter-in-law.
Watch how you talk about her.
You actually remember she's your wife?
When are you bringing her to see me?
Dad, stop worrying about my stuff.
Zichen is coming back soon.
Shouldn't we get things ready?
Don't change the subject.
I'll handle the airport pickup.
Just tell me...
Dad,
I'll go get the room ready.
What room?
Zichen's room, obviously.
The warmth of home
means more
than a flashy airport reception.
The warmth of home means more
You brat,
you're lecturing me?
Beiyan,
do you remember
that woman I was crazy about
when I was an undergrad?
I feel like I'm in her league now.
(Could my contract wife)
(be my cousin's first love?)
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪