♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 4=
♪Sometimes we roll the dice♪
,♪To see what the future hides♪
♪Spinning us round and round
like a never-ending ride♪
So?
What do you think?
Is your face
a little
asymmetrical?
Here's a fun fact for you.
No one's face is perfectly symmetrical.
I meant
your eye makeup.
Is it?
Oh, some touchups?
Mr. Huo.
Mr. Huo. Mrs. Huo.
You must be Mrs. Huo.
You really are young and beautiful.
Mr. Huo sure is
a lucky man.
You flatter us.
This is my wife.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
You know who I am?
Of course.
I often hear Beiyan mention you.
The group's efficiency division
has achieved today's success
thanks to your years of leadership.
Mr. Huo is usually so stern.
I didn't expect him to praise me.
Of course.
What's going on?
I have no idea.
She probably read the company's profile
on the way here.
The drive was only ten minutes.
She memorized the whole thing?
Ask her. Why are you asking me?
How would I know?
Is she that amazing?
I just memorized it on the way here.
Just like how people
end up reading the shampoo labels
in the bathroom
if they forgot their phone.
Curiosity for knowledge
can help pass the time.
Do you do that?
No. I don't.
Me neither.
Mrs. Huo,
you must be very supportive
of Beiyan's career,
right?
The group is expecting major changes.
Beiyan has decided to go back
into pharmaceutical business.
But the water runs deep,
and the risks are high.
What do you think, Mrs. Huo?
Nange and I...
You're too kind, Mr. Li.
Beiyan and the experts
will weigh the group's strategy.
Though I do know
a little about pharmaceuticals.
The industry's landscape
has already changed.
Small biotech companies
have made a huge impact
on traditional giants
through cutting-edge
innovative drug licensing partnerships.
If Huo Group wants to break through,
catching up alone isn't enough.
Your insights into Huo Group
have truly opened my eyes.
Just some humble opinions.
A toast to you.
Here's to a successful partnership
tonight.
When can we end this?
I feel like this dress
is about to crush my ribs.
Hand in there a little longer.
My dad's way too cunning.
It'll be bad if we slip up later.
What do you mean?
Don't scare me.
Mr. Huo.
Hello, everyone.
Congratulations, Mr. Huo.
Congratulations.
Congrats.
Good everyone,
honored guests
and directors.
My son, Beiyan, has always been
impulsive in everything he does.
Well then.
Let's have him tell us
how they fell in love.
How about it?
Sure.
Beiyan!
Beiyan.
Hang on.
What love story
do we even have to tell?
Make one up.
You do it.
You were making things up
with my dad yesterday? You do it.
That was different. I used a formula.
I had a logical framework for it.
How am I supposed to apply that today?
Just use another formula.
How am I supposed to do that?
I've been single since birth.
What formula do I have?
Then
I'll control the flow later.
Just follow my lead.
Be careful.
Don't let anything slip.
Beiyan!
I'm here.
Coming.
Beiyan,
hurry and tell everyone
the juicy story
of how you two
fell in love.
I want
to be the first to hear it.
That's right.
Tell us, Beiyan.
Since everyone here
is so interested
in our love story,
I'll tell everyone
how Nange and I
first met.
Sure.
Tell us.
It was on a sunny day
after autumn.
Sunny day.
I ran into her outside the lab
at Linhai Medical University.
She was carrying a stack
of research papers and almost fell.
Careful!
I caught her in my arms.
And then?
What a cliche plot.
It's making my toes curl.
Right, Nange?
Yeah.
I was about
to return
the neuroanatomy atlas
and "The New Modern Medicine".
What's that?
My...
No need to brag about your reading list.
I just didn't expect
the guy who caught me
to turn out to be the trustee.
Are you alright?
I... I'm fine.
I'm Huo Beiyan.
(Huo Group, Huo Beiyan)
You are...
I also didn't expect
that the trustee came to campus
just to borrow a meal card.
Mr. Huo, what brings you to the campus
on a weekend?
Since fate brought us together,
I'll just be direct.
Can you
lend me your meal card?
Meal card?
Yes. Meal card.
I didn't expect that.
This is too funny.
Meal card?
Am I that hungry?
Right, Beiyan?
Y... Yeah. Exactly.
Here's the thing.
Actually before that,
we met once
in the university's cafeteria.
When I saw her then,
my heart instantly
skipped a beat for her.
So to see her again,
I kept
wandering around the university lab.
And I really did meet her again.
I guess
it was fated.
Not bad.
You patched the story back together.
And after that,
Nange and I gradually got closer.
She may usually
seem gentle and adorable,
but in private, she likes...
to play Monopoly.
Monopoly?
- Didn't see that coming.
- Monopoly?
I just happen to know a thing about it,
so it became one
of the ways
we spent time together.
Huo Beiyan,
let's settle this once
and for all today.
Xu Nange,
today
I'll make you admit defeat.
Yes.
I'm from a science
and engineering background.
My fascination with probability
made me absolutely obsessed
with the game.
But I didn't expect
the university trustee
to use underhanded tricks
and cheat during the game.
Cheat?
He shouldn't have done that.
Ms. Xu,
don't push it.
You started it first.
We're doomed if this falls apart.
I'm not scared.
Nange.
Zichen's back.
Boy.
You just got back
and already causing a scene.
Zichen's back.
He just got back.
You got back earlier
without telling me.
I wanted to give you...
and her a surprise.
Too bad it shattered.
Apologies, everyone.
I was in a hurry
to give Beiyan a surprise.
I didn't mean
to ruin the mood.
I'm sorry for the shock.
Don't stop the music.
Carry on.
Alright.
Come on.
Let's continue.
Zichen,
I only realized something
recently myself.
I want to talk to her first.
♪All of my dreams, leading me here♪
♪Fueling the fire
that help me fight all the fear♪
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪