( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 19=
Tighten it.
Pull harder.
Why stop now?
It was so tight.
Surely, she'd black out.
Back then,
who didn't go through this?
To stand center stage,
this is the hurdle you must clear.
Kid.
You're awake.
- You're awake.
- There you are.
You're awake.
Master Gou.
Sorry.
I couldn't hold on.
You held on, kid.
The initiation is done.
You made it.
(That night,)
(Yi Qing'e tasted what it's like to be)
(the lead for the first time.)
(She's never)
(felt like this before.)
(But she was also afraid.)
(She recalled the day
of her uncle's incident.)
(There were just as many people.)
(The more people, the tenser she felt.)
(Plus,)
(the pain from the head wrap
still lingered,)
(making her more nervous
than before the show.)
Alright.
Here, two slices of meat.
Okay.
Shredded pork noodles.
Eat as much as you want today.
Master Song,
your kitchen has hidden talents.
You really wowed us today.
You deserve praise.
You bet.
People always look down on us,
complaining about taste
and anything else.
Look at you guys.
Which one of you
is better than our kitchen maid?
Look at you.
Look how arrogant you are.
Arrogant? I'm being modest now.
Modest? Come on.
If anyone complains
about our cooking again,
you can do the cooking,
and we'll go perform on stage.
- Deal!
- I'm so proud!
- I'm starving!
- Come on!
Eat up. It's really good.
Why aren't those girls eating?
Girls are just complicated.
Hurry up! Come on over!
- Here.
- More meat.
Can I have a second bowl?
Why are you all just sitting here?
Aren't you getting food?
These noodles are really good.
Shredded pork.
Brat.
Why is he so annoying?
You always looked down on her.
Now, she's a success.
Are you jealous?
What? Are you fine with it?
We wasted all these years.
So what?
Should I act like you guys?
Do I have to cry about it?
Listen.
She's suffered so much over the years.
Do you even know? Seriously.
She just got lucky.
Right. She got lucky.
Would you trade your life for hers?
Would you?
You little suck-up.
What's it got to do with you?
She's insulting me.
Listen to me.
Every single one of you.
You have one thing, eyeing another.
You want rice and noodles too.
You can't eat all the delicacies.
Exactly.
You can't take every good thing.
That's right.
Try to let it go.
Let it go, okay?
What's it to you if she succeeded?
Why are you so excited?
Exactly.
These noodles lack vinegar.
Not sour enough. I'll add some vinegar.
- Eat up.
- Yeah.
Eat yourselves to death.
I hope you choke.
I'd gladly choke on shredded pork.
Celebration banquet!
Pour it. Pour some more.
Let's celebrate.
Cheers!
- Come on.
- Okay, pour it.
Kid,
today
was the best drink
I've had in a long time
and the best show I've seen.
Kid,
pour Mr. Qin some wine.
- No, no.
- A toast to Mr. Qin.
No, no.
Without Mr. Qin,
you'd have no debut performance today.
All right. I wouldn't dare.
- Easy.
- Fill it up.
Just a little. Good.
- Fill it.
- What little?
Oh, kid,
you should toast all your masters.
They
taught you real skills
to make your own way.
And, kid,
thank your uncle most of all.
He's the one who changed your life.
Too bad he isn't here.
Kid,
drink this chicken soup.
I heard you fainted
after leaving the stage.
Drink this to nurture yourself.
- I was worried.
- Come on.
- Thanks, Aunt.
- Drink.
- But I still feel sick.
I'm afraid I'll throw up.
She's not feeling well.
She just fainted.
Why not just keep it warm?
She'll ask for it when she needs it.
Okay, I'll keep it warm in the pot.
If you want it later, just drink up.
Thanks, Aunt.
It's nothing. Sit down.
Sit down. Look at you.
Master Gou, I have to head back.
Where are you going?
I'm heading back to help
Master Song clean up.
No need. Stay here.
Today, you're an actress.
Right.
Sit here.
Aunt Mi Lan.
Why are you crying?
When did you learn opera
from Master Gou?
Since I was little.
Have you been practicing
all these years?
I haven't skipped a single day.
Master Gou
wouldn't even let me go home.
And I had no idea.
Master Gou wouldn't let me tell anyone.
You had enough on your plate back then.
You grew up in the blink of an eye.
I feel like I barely know you.
My head is still spinning.
I knew nothing.
I was unprepared,
and Master Gou and the guys
pushed me on stage.
I was just confused too.
You'd been preparing all along.
You just didn't know it.
Today, when I saw you onstage,
I was happy for you.
I felt sorry for myself.
It was hard enough
to outlast Hua Caixiang.
Now, you've grown up too.
I could still compete with Hua Caixiang.
But with you, I never had a chance.
Still, I have to thank you.
Now, I know
what to do next.
Aunt Mi Lan.
Don't call me Aunt.
I'm not that old. Call me Sis.
I'm so jealous of you.
After all these years of work,
I still couldn't do it,
but you went onstage
and became the lead.
I don't want the lead.
Why?
I never wanted it since I was a kid.
I'm scared.
Scared of what?
I'm scared of standing on stage.
What were all these years
of hard work and suffering for?
He didn't want me to give up.
Who is he?
My uncle.
What are you doing? What's wrong?
Let's learn from Meng Liang
and Jiao Zan.
Who are Meng Liang and Jiao Zan?
Master Qiu and Master Zhou.
Are you nuts?
It's the middle of the night!
Give me the blanket.
Don't sleep! Get up and chat.
I can't sleep.
Go talk to Chu Jiahe.
Right now,
she's probably awake too.
I'm going home to tell my mom
that I'm done with it.
I'll take over her job.
Then, all these years go to waste.
So what?
Anything's fine.
What else can I do?
How did she make it?
I might as well quit too.
I'll go back.
All of it was pointless anyway.
It's so unfair.
If someone taught us,
we'd act way better than her.
Exactly.
She stole all the spotlight.
Always playing the accordion.
Can he play anything besides this?
That's all he's got.
So annoying.
Can you keep it down?
Idiot, get lost!
♪On the banyan tree by the pond♪
♪Cicadas are singing of summer♪
♪On the swing by the playground♪
♪Only butterflies rest upon it♪
♪The teacher's chalk on the board♪
♪Is still chirping away endlessly♪
♪Going on and on♪
♪Waiting for class and school to end♪
♪Waiting for games in childhood♪
Clothes matter to people.
The girl returns to the kitchen
and becomes a kitchen maid again.
That's not right.
What's wrong?
Didn't they say
the kid
would move to the trainee class?
Why's there still no word?
Exactly.
I even told her she'd marry the stage.
This whole lot.
Won't they give her a trick
and drop her?
Yi Qing'e! Yi Qing'e!
Why aren't you training?
Why wash veg here?
Yeah.
You know what?
You were amazing on stage last time.
We were both stunned watching you.
It was impressive.
That leg lift of yours
totally wowed the audience.
Let me tell you.
You're way better
than those girls who just talk big.
You're much better. I'm telling you.
You have such a big basin.
Can you finish all that?
Feng Xiaoxiao, give her a hand.
Don't let her...
- You should help out too.
- No need.
Let me help.
- It's okay.
- Put it down.
- It's fine.
- It's okay.
- Just leave it there.
- It's fine.
- No need.
Don't touch it.
Okay, okay, I won't.
Well.
We want to talk to you about something.
We want to ask if your masters
are taking apprentices.
We both want to learn opera together.
Yeah, we want to become apprentices too.
Please do us a favor.
Put in a good word for us.
Yeah.
How about this? We'll call you Senior.
Right.
Senior.
Senior, you...
Help us out, Senior.
Senior what? Senior?
Look how smug you are.
Let's go.
We'll go ourselves.
On the troupe's rural tour,
the kid really made us proud.
Even those snobs
praised Cunjia Troupe behind our backs.
Four old men and one kid
brought the troupe back to life.
Amazing.
What's so amazing about that?
You think that was a compliment?
From now on, Cunjia Troupe
can't be thrown around.
What's wrong?
What did we do? Why can't we say it?
I can't control what they say;
I can only control what they eat.
Why isn't Zhu Jiru around?
He's been back for days.
What happens next?
He owes us an explanation.
Zhu Jiru?
Even Huang Zhengjing is missing.
What are you two looking at?
Move along, move along.
Masters above,
please accept this from your apprentice.
What's this? What's this?
Get up, get up.
We want to learn from you.
Please take us in.
What are you doing?
Move, move.
If you don't agree,
we won't get up.
You two little brats.
Let's see if you get up.
Let's see.
You can take Yi Qing'e.
- Why refuse us?
- Exactly.
This is a modern troupe,
not an old-style opera troupe.
No need for formal vows.
Go on back home.
We even kowtowed.
That's another matter. Go.
How is that different?
You only take girls
and not boys?
Exactly.
Listen to yourself.
What nonsense are you spouting?
I'll make you pay. I swear.
I already told you.
Bowing like that won't work.
It's all because of you.
Why bring up girls?
She's our senior.
I was trying to be friendly.
Look at this.
What are you doing?
With moves like that,
you might as well go to sleep.
Hurry up and train. Move.
We'll train.
Get moving. Keep training.
Where are the girls?
They must be sleeping.
Sleeping?
Feng Xiaoxiao.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Go call them.
They won't listen to me.
What can you even do?
What are you doing?
I can't take long shots.
You can't catch anything.
You're done for.
Look at you.
Open the door.
- Hurry!
- Coming, sir.
Hurry, hurry!
What are you doing?
Why take so long to open up?
Look at the time. You have to train.
Move it. To the training ground.
Mr. He,
I'm not feeling well today.
I can't train.
The rest of you, go now.
Mr. He,
I'm not feeling well either.
Mr. He, I'm not up to it either.
What a coincidence.
Your cycles all lined up, huh?
Fine. Fine.
Don't you dare get up.
Stay down. Rest up nice and easy.
Just you wait.
Jiahe,
what do we do now?
Whoever wants to go can go.
I'm not going anyway.
I'm not going either.
Me neither.
Troupe Leader! Troupe Leader!
Troupe Leader!
You're finally back.
We've been back for days.
Where have you been?
I had something to handle.
I wasn't with the troupe.
What's up?
I wanted to brief you on the show.
No need.
You handled that field discretion
extremely well.
I had no other choice.
They were tired of Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui.
They asked for Da Jiao Zan.
Anything else?
Since Da Jiao Zan did so well,
could we bring Yi Qing'e
back to the trainee class?
Let's seize the chance
and stage Yang Pai Feng next.
What if I say no?
I'll still stand by my idea.
Please, Troupe Leader,
report my idea to the higher-ups.
Then report it yourself.
The leaders want a word anyway.
Troupe Leader.
Deputy Troupe Leader.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't be the class teacher anymore.
What happened now?
Since the kids came back
from the village,
they've been so negative and passive.
They won't listen to me
or train properly.
Especially the girls.
Their moods are all over the place.
For example, right now,
the girls all say
they're on their period.
None of them
is training.
What to do?
From now on,
you can go straight
to Troupe Leader Zhu.
It's no longer my call.
Wait.
What do you mean
by that?
I won't be your troupe leader soon.
Then who will?
Once the transfer order comes, I'm gone.
The troupe needs an insider
as the leader.
I'll be the Director
of the Material Bureau.
I can really understand it.
After seeing Yi Qing'e in Da Jiao Zan,
you can't accept it.
Comparing yourself to her is rough.
But in my opinion,
to make it in opera,
there are only two ways.
First,
you're born with the gift.
Second,
it takes hard work.
Yi Qing'e's skills
didn't fall from the sky.
Right?
She didn't get there overnight.
It came from hard training.
Now, you see the gap.
Train hard,
and you can pass her.
We do train hard.
Don't jump in.
If you only blame others,
the gap will only
keep growing.
We always do vocal drills and tumbling
in the morning
and weapon work in the afternoon.
Which of us doesn't have
better conditions?
Why end up worse than a kitchen maid?
We've suffered for so many years.
What have we learned in the end?
Nonsense.
You've learned acting
and life in the troupe.
That's just nonsense.
I'm more anxious than any of you.
I wish all you kids
could get onstage right now
and play the lead.
I wish you could carry our troupe.
But can you?
Our troupe
has ended up like this today.
Are you sure you're not part
of the reason?
When we run into problems,
we have to solve them, right?
Can you look at yourselves for once?
Fine. I do have a problem.
I request a transfer to the kitchen.
That's where I'll learn real skills.
I also request a transfer.
- Me too.
- I want to go too.
Fine.
No need to transfer.
Tomorrow, the trainee class
will become the cooking squad.
You can all cook in the kitchen.
What?
What is he doing?
- Is he threatening us?
- Exactly.
Why so worked up?
Exactly.
How about spear fighting?
Not good.
No.
Then the broadsword routine?
Still no.
Still no?
Then fist fighting?
Even worse.
Whose green pants are these?
Forget green pants.
Let's do staff fighting.
Staff fighting?
What do you think of staff fighting?
Get out.
Idiot!
Why does Yi Qing'e look so pretty?
Prettier than the poster girls.
The old guys did her makeup well.
Exactly, exactly.
Exactly.
Still awake?
I can't fall asleep.
- Let's chat.
- You're still up?
She looks good even without makeup.
Have you noticed?
Yi Qing'e got way prettier.
You've been watching closely.
Exactly.
She was such a goof as a kid.
Who knew she'd grow up so pretty?
You little rascal.
She's getting prettier.
How many have you even seen?
Let me finish.
I'm telling you.
When a girl is little,
she shouldn't be too pretty.
Right.
What time is it? Let us sleep.
So noisy. How long will this go on?
So annoying. Can you shut up?
We have to get up early tomorrow.
- Get out.
- What's wrong with you?
- Nuts.
- Just chatting.
You can sleep. What's the problem?
Exactly.
- Let's find Yi Qing'e. Okay?
- Stop.
Those two are the ugliest.
Come on.
Hurry up.
- The uglier one yells louder.
- Go.
What are you two doing?
You nearly scared me to death!
I...
He wanted to watch you train.
Cut it out.
No.
I...
Don't listen to his nonsense.
I'm hungry.
I came to find two Mo to eat.
Where did she go?
Aren't you hungry?
Nice.
She gave me two Mo.
Share one with me.
Share? She gave them to me.
She gave them to me.
Gross. What a faker.
Yang Paifeng, give me a bigger scoop.
Give me the ladle. I'll do it.
Are you deaf? I said, "Give it to me."
What are you doing?
She's grossing me out.
What's wrong with you?
Chu Jiahe,
she just sang Da Jiao Zan.
Is it because you can't?
Don't take it out on her.
What's it to you?
Mind your own business.
Bullying people is wrong.
Who is she to you anyway?
You care about her, huh?
In that case,
why not just take her home?
What's wrong with you?
You must be looking for trouble.
Don't you have better things to do?
Who told you to serve me?
What are you doing?
- She grosses me out.
- Have you no shame?
- What?
- Apologize to her.
Apologize.
- Don't leave. Apologize now.
- Let go.
Let go of me.
Let go.
What's wrong?
Why is she leaving?
- Come back.
- What a coward.
Don't go. Stop right there.
What happened?
The kid brought her food.
She called her dirty
and dumped it on her.
You've got way too much nerve.
Picking on the kid.
Stop banging, all of you.
Stop it.
Master Song, where are we going?
To get answers from Director Huang. Go.
I'm fine.
How is this fine?
You did nothing wrong. Why be scared?
Don't worry about me, Master Song.
I'm not just worried about you.
Look at the mess.
It makes the kitchen look bad.
How can we work now?
Let's go.
The handover files are all here.
I'll pass them to you in advance.
Okay.
Leave them with me. Don't worry.
(Files)
Since the leadership has spoken to you,
it's basically settled now.
Right, right.
No rush.
Once the transfer order comes,
you'll have the position.
Troupe Leader,
your place in my heart won't change.
- What place?
- Troupe Leader.
Right at the center.
Troupe Leader.
Come here. Stand right there.
Look at this.
What happened?
Chu Jiahe from the trainee class
grabbed the ladle for no reason
and spilled food all over the kid.
For no reason?
No one hates someone for no reason.
So many people saw it.
Go ask around, then.
I've handed this over.
You look into it.
Troupe Leader, you can't just leave.
Master Song.
Take the kid to wash up first.
I'll find out what happened
and decide what to do.
No. Handle this right now.
If not, dinner can't even start.
Why can't it start?
This is just too much.
Qing'e,
I apologize
on behalf of Chu Jiahe first.
Will that do?
I'm fine.
Well...
Hey, this kid...
I'll handle this.
Master, did you call me?
You've been back for days.
You should've calmed down by now.
That night in Da Jiao Zan,
how do you think you did?
I don't know.
I'd give you a sixty. Barely passing.
So many cheered that night,
because they hadn't seen
old opera in years.
To be honest, that night,
your eyes weren't bright enough.
They lacked a spark.
Look.
When a Dan role is onstage,
all the technique
ends up in those two eyes.
If the eyes are dull,
the role has no soul.
When the eyes shine,
the performance comes alive.
Go and light two sticks of incense.
Work on your eyes properly.
All right.
Go on.
Who is it?
It's me, Mi Lan.
What's wrong, Mi Lan?
What happened to you?
Nothing.
What did Liao do to you?
Is what they said true?
What did they say?
They said that Chef Liao
forced himself on you.
Is it true?
Say something.
Tell me.
I don't want to talk about it.
You need to tell me now.
Come on, tell me.
He pinned me to the bed and tried
to undo my belt.
And then?
Then Master Song rushed in and hit him.
Did he get your belt open?
No. It was tied in a tight knot.
Is that all he did to you?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Master Song told me not to.
He said it would hurt me.
Who else knows about this?
Only Master Song.
Then how did Chu Jiahe know?
She said you were taken advantage of.
Mi Lan,
was I really taken advantage of?
Master Song saved you.
Then Chu Jiahe ruined your name.
Let's go find them.
I'm not going.
I'm here. What are you scared of?
I'm scared of everything.
What's wrong with you?
If you don't clear this up with her,
life will only get harder for you.
Do you get that?
You weren't like this as a kid.
You caught snakes and fought Er Laizi.
What happened to you?
You've turned into a lamb.
Anyone can push you around, right?
Silly.
I'm not silly.
Look at them.
Each one looks more real than the last.
They need a master to train them.
Chu Jiahe.
Ms. Mi Lan.
I need to ask you something.
Ms. Mi Lan, what is it?
Come with me.
What's wrong?
Why did you bring me here?
Come over here.
Come here.
Let go of me.
Let go.
Feeling guilty?
What do I have to feel guilty about?
Did you start that rumor of Yi Qing'e
being taken advantage of by Liao?
It's not a rumor.
You saw it?
Yes.
What's your relationship with Liao?
Did he let you watch
how he took advantage of Yi Qing'e?
Tomorrow, I'll tell the whole troupe
that when Liao took advantage
of Yi Qing'e,
you were in it with him.
What did Yi Qing'e ever do to you?
Why did you treat her like this?
Answer me.
I taught you stagecraft.
Not these dirty tricks offstage.
As an opera performer,
if you can't even be decent,
how can you play any role?
She suddenly made it.
It's hard for me too.
But I accept my fate.
If you can't stand her doing well,
work harder onstage.
Compete with her up there.
Don't do it offstage
with such low tactics.
I'm making this clear today.
If you ever hurt Yi Qing'e again,
I'll expose you to the whole troupe.
Try me if you don't believe it.
Qing'e.
Apologize to Yi Qing'e.
Apologize.
Get back here.
Don't chase her, Mi Lan.
I'll go get you something.
Wait here for me.
Jiahe, what did Ms. Mi Lan say?
- What?
- Stop bugging me.
Get back to practice.
These practice outfits are brand-new.
I won't need them anymore.
Take them and wear them.
This scarf is for you.
In my room,
there are lots of things.
If you can use any of them,
go and take them.
This Xinhua Dictionary is for you.
(Xinhua Dictionary)
To be the lead, you have to study.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Where are you going?
To the south.
What for?
To get married.
You're giving up opera?
In this line of work, there's no choice.
There's only one leading role.
Once you're the lead,
attention naturally follows.
You're still a sapling,
yet you've already drawn the storm.
As for stage skills,
you've only learned half.
You need to keep studying hard.
As for life offstage,
I doubt Master Gou and the others
can teach you.
Figure it out yourself.
I'm leaving early tomorrow.
I haven't told anyone.
Come see me off.
(Xinhua Dictionary)
=The Lead=
(Preview)
You've had it hard all these years.
The troupe is back with pros.
Let's do Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
The girls in our trainee class
can all go onstage.
For Mu Guiying,
Yi Qing'e is the first choice.
Chu Jiahe is second.
Roles aren't about importance.
For the opera armor,
we still need 14 sets.
If Chu Jiahe plays Mu Guiying,
will the costume issue be solved?
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪