( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 17=
Why did you pick a fight with him?
What if you actually hurt the old man?
So what if he's old?
He can't just act entitled like that.
He criticizes everyone he sees,
saying no one is good enough,
as if only those four can perform,
and the rest of us are just shouting.
They just know some traditional opera.
Ask them to sing Hong Deng Ji.
Ask them to sing Sha Jia Bang.
See if they can even do it.
What's wrong with you?
Why hassle over this?
Your drumming does have some issues.
We have a better one.
He's locked up in prison now.
Why not get him out?
Can't you be more open-minded?
Can't you be more generous?
What do you mean?
Go and apologize to him.
Why should I?
It's already enough
that I didn't go after Zhou,
and now I have to apologize?
Deputy Troupe Leader,
this isn't over. I'm telling you.
It's not over?
Those four old men
have already got one foot in the grave.
Just give them a way out.
We still have to rehearse the play.
Not a chance. Take it or leave it.
He Dachui, think of the big picture.
Do it for me.
Forget it. I'm not doing it.
He Dachui is a Party member after all.
He's the trainee class teacher
and a model worker every year.
But those old losers broke his bones.
This behavior is extremely vile.
They must be punished, Troupe Leader.
The key is
that it has caused public outrage.
If unpunished,
He Dachui won't let it go.
Nor will the orchestra,
the whole trainee class,
or the masses
of the troupe.
Your wife won't let it go either, right?
My wife is also very angry.
What is going on here?
What's going on?
My wife is mad at me again.
What's the reason this time?
Because of your wife. Why else?
Your wife wants
to play Lin Chong's wife.
She went to my wife and told her
Mi Lan was the one
who seduced me back then.
Now, she's digging up the past again.
I didn't even know about this.
Luckily, she just hurt me to get a part.
If she wanted to be the troupe leader,
she probably would have killed me.
Master,
here, the brazier is ready.
Warm yourself up.
It's freezing.
Situan,
pack your things.
Go back tomorrow. Don't follow me.
Is it because Dachui hated your act?
Master,
who'll take your robe if I leave?
I'll stop shaking the robe, okay?
He Dachui actually did a good thing.
His slap
didn't just knock your tooth out,
but cured your lifelong bad habits.
Master,
don't make me leave.
Master, I'm begging you, Master.
Master.
Master!
(Plead guilty and accept the law
Submit to management and reform)
Hu Sanyuan.
Hu Sanyuan,
stop banging. You're so loud.
Do you know why I can't sew straight?
Why?
My right hand is messed up.
I think your brain is messed up.
You're crazy.
Your hand won't obey you,
but it works fine for that bowl?
Stop it, will you?
Just stop it.
If you're crazy, knock your noggin.
Do you hear me?
Didn't you want to knock?
Come on.
Knock right here.
This is the root of his illness.
Won't this ruin me?
It won't.
Knock.
Wait a sec.
Gently, be gentle.
It won't work if you go light.
Knock harder.
The faster, the better.
Hu Sanyuan.
Are you asleep?
Stop pretending to sleep.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Missing the outside?
How many days have you been in here?
1,750 days.
The fewer days you have left,
the more each one drags.
I actually think time's flying.
Come on, that's nonsense.
I'm telling you.
People who count down every day
never feel that time is flying.
But to someone like me,
who doesn't count at all,
every day feels the same.
Veterinarian.
My back's burning.
Check it. It must be all bruised.
Burning means it's working.
This tapping is like Gua Sha
or Cupping.
It invigorates blood.
Once you're used to it,
you feel tight all over
if you miss a few days.
Wait.
You're a veterinarian.
Did you use the same treatment on me
that you use on donkeys?
It works anyway. What's the difference?
It's been three days already.
He Dachui hasn't apologized,
and Zhu Jiru hasn't shown up.
Are we still rehearsing or what?
What exactly is going on?
Let me go find out.
Don't be desperate. Let them be.
But we're the ones stuck now.
You enjoyed hitting him,
but how do we fix this mess?
Fine, you find a better way then.
Tell He Dachui to break my leg.
An eye for an eye. How about that?
You big fool.
What are you trying to say?
Did you teach the kid the whole play
or an opera excerpt?
An opera excerpt.
Call the kid over.
Cunren, Cunyi.
One of you plays Meng Liang,
and one plays Jiao Zan.
Work with the kid.
Let's perform the excerpt.
Call Zhu Jiru over to watch.
Right.
Let's show those snobs,
that bunch of wimps.
Let them open their eyes and see
if we have what it takes
and how we turn a kitchen maid
into a young Wudan.
Someone's been killed!
The four of you
just rehearsed in secret
so quietly
right under my nose?
Tell me first.
How was the performance?
How was it?
Incredible.
Really incredible.
It's been 20 years,
and I've never been so impressed.
This girl's basics are solid,
her technique is authentic,
and her acting is brilliant.
How did the four of you do it?
You treated such a rare,
gifted talent like dirt.
If Gou Cunzhong hadn't found her,
her whole life
might have been wasted.
She started out as nothing.
Even her own uncle
noticed that she was
a sprout back then.
Qing'e,
do you still remember?
When Hu Sanyuan brought you
to my office,
you had a runny nose.
Hu Sanyuan said
that as long as you had
some commodity grain,
you could be a guard or a cook
or do whatever was needed.
Who would have thought?
You've become such a talented Wudan.
It's truly impressive.
I'd even say that in a few years,
if we're lucky,
our livelihood
might just depend on her.
I called you here
to see this opera excerpt
because I want to discuss something.
Can we stop rehearsing
Bi Shang Liang Shan?
Let's rehearse Yang Pai Feng first.
You've done the full Yang Pai Feng?
We've only done Da Jiao Zan so far.
But as you know,
this opera excerpt
is the core of the play.
Once we nail this,
the full-length play will be easy.
I'll go talk to Huang Zhengjing.
Let's push for Yang Pai Feng.
How sure are you?
If not, don't reveal the kid's talent.
We don't want extra trouble
or anything bad for the kid.
Put your mind at ease.
The kid was overlooked before
because we were blind.
If the kid is buried again now,
we'll never forgive ourselves.
Qinqiang opera performers today
are already facing a talent gap.
Now, this kid has shown up.
On a smaller scale,
our troupe has a future.
On a bigger scale,
Qinqiang opera has a future.
Kid, do you hear that?
Who?
Hu Sanyuan's niece?
We once treated her like nobody
and sent her to the kitchen.
Who knew she'd be that tough?
Those veteran artists noticed
that she had real opera talent.
They taught her while she stoked fires.
And those veteran artists
used traditional opera standards
to train the kid.
Her basic skills are rock solid.
Our trainees can't compare.
Even those big stars in the troupe
are not as good as her.
You're being ridiculous.
How am I being ridiculous?
My dear Troupe Leader!
Our troupe is struggling right now.
We should put aside all our prejudices
and focus on the big picture.
I have no prejudice against anyone.
If you hadn't mentioned her,
I would've forgotten her.
That kid is a treasure.
We absolutely can't let her
go to waste in our hands again.
Go to waste in our hands again?
What do you mean by that?
If I remember correctly,
Hu Sanyuan got that kid in
by messing around, right?
She slacked off here for a year
and failed the exam.
According to the troupe's rules,
she was supposed to be sent home.
I was the one who took pity on her
and let her tend the fire
in the kitchen.
At least she'd get commodity grain.
Why can't she act in Yang Pai Feng?
You do the job your post calls for.
I'm the troupe's leader.
How can I boss around the supply
and marketing cooperative?
It's simple. How do you not get it?
How is this not our troupe's business?
Back then, you took that child
from the trainee class to tend fires.
So, why can't you take her now
from the kitchen back to training...
Deputy Director Zhu!
Watch your tone.
Think about the big picture.
It's fine if the show isn't a success.
If it is,
do you know what it means?
What?
It means telling the world
that the County Troupe
spent several years
training dozens of successors,
and they aren't
as good as an apprentice
trained overnight by veteran artists.
How will you explain that
to the organization, the masses,
and the kids in the trainee class?
Listen, Zhu.
We can't just focus
on these minor gains.
It's not just about one or two plays.
We need to have a broader vision.
With your perspective,
what's there to argue with me
about the bigger picture?
Let me stress this again.
Our reviving traditional opera
isn't about reviving an old-style troupe
or some rotten old hierarchy.
This is about the bigger picture.
It's called having a vision.
Stop waiting.
Zhu Jiru isn't coming.
He should at least give us an answer.
Like a bun tossed to a dog,
it's gone for good.
Isn't that his answer?
He got hotheaded last night,
talking about the future
of the troupe and Qinqiang opera.
He shouted those slogans.
How could he show his face now?
That wimp is hiding again.
Can't we work around Zhu Jiru
and Huang Zhengjing?
Who?
Here they come.
What do you want?
A group fight?
Let's talk inside.
Talk? Not with you.
You...
Don't hit guests who come with gifts.
Dachui,
we four old-timers
came to apologize today.
I was wrong that day.
I shouldn't have talked nonsense.
In front of all those people,
I embarrassed you.
We're here to sincerely apologize.
Bro, here. Take it.
I don't need your apology.
Leave, now.
I'm telling you. This isn't over.
Dachui.
- Here.
- What for?
Take it. Just take it.
Come on. Hit me.
Hit me as much as you want
until you feel better.
Then we can move on, okay?
Knock it off.
Don't give me that routine.
Dachui,
the four of us together
are over 250,
even older than Lian Po
when he apologized.
Let's just drop it.
We've lived together for decades.
We saw you grow from a little kid.
You saw us grow old too.
Conflicts are bound to happen.
Even teeth bite the tongue.
If we don't let this go,
we'll end up suffering.
Dachui,
isn't that right?
Aunt, you head back first.
I'll finish the rest of the work.
Okay.
Alright.
I'm almost done.
Master Song.
Master Song, sit here.
I'll massage your back.
No need, no need.
I'll just go lie down and stretch out.
I banked the fire.
Plump, I'm taking off.
Okay.
Don't forget to turn off the lights.
- Go to bed early.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
Wait, wait a minute.
I'm not done peeing!
You always do this.
No need.
Oh, come on!
Saluting Comrade Lei Feng!
Cut the nonsense!
Yes.
This pig has grown so fat.
Yi Qing'e,
when are we going to kill and eat it?
None of your business. Move.
Let go!
- Move.
- Let go!
Let go!
So much nonsense. Move.
You...
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Zhou Yuzhi, I love you!
Chu Jiahe, I love you!
Chu Jiahe! Chu Jiahe!
What a rare guest.
I'm looking for Chu Jiahe.
Come in, it's cold out there.
Jiahe!
Chu Jiahe!
She's here for you.
She's looking for you.
Chu Jiahe, come out for a second.
I need to talk to you.
Quiet down!
What did you say?
You're whispering like a fly.
Come out. I need to talk to you.
No, just say it here.
I want to buy some clothes,
but I don't know what to get.
You always look so good.
Where do you buy your clothes?
Can you go to the Department Store
and buy some clothes with me?
Helping you?
I don't have time for that.
Besides, my clothes
are from Shanghai
and the provincial capital.
- Mine too!
What nice clothes could they have here?
- So tacky!
- Exactly!
Only bumpkins buy clothes here.
Besides,
you just feed pigs and cook.
Why do you need nice clothes?
Yeah, pigs don't look at you.
Pigs don't care.
Come on, let's continue.
Keep going.
Chu Jiahe! Chu Jiahe!
Zhou Yuzhi! Zhou Yuzhi!
Chu Jiahe!
Chu Jiahe, one more!
Chu Jiahe, I love you!
I love you all too!
I love you!
One more!
One more! One more!
Chu Jiahe, I love you!
Chu Jiahe!
Qing'e.
What's up?
You're not learning opera
with those four old guys today?
They're busy.
Busy picking on people.
I know.
They went begging He Dachui.
Gifts, apologies, the whole act.
Snot and tears were everywhere.
They were a total mess.
He Dachui was kind enough
to agree to drum for them.
Isn't this room cold?
No, it isn't.
Feel the draft down here.
It's blowing through.
How could it not be cold?
I've been
a poor master.
I never came to see you
or looked after you.
Do you have mice here?
I'm not scared.
Well, I'm not a mouse.
So, why are you scared of me?
Look at this pad. It must be cold.
It's so thin.
I'll get an electric blanket.
Once plugged in, it'll be warm.
Is this quilt thick enough?
Yes.
Nonsense.
I can't even reach you.
Why are you standing so far away?
Come over and sit for a while.
Chat with me for a bit.
You're not treating me as your master.
Why are you being so distant?
I still have that rock candy
for you. Here.
Have some rock candy. Take it.
I don't want it.
Take it.
Come here.
- Come here.
- No.
You said you're not cold.
Your little hands are freezing.
Let me warm them for you.
- I'm not cold.
- No need.
- Let me warm you up.
Let me warm you up.
Come on.
I just want to warm you up.
If only the dorm had a restroom.
It's freezing this winter.
Don't move. Don't move.
Master Song!
Don't yell.
Master Song! Master Song!
I just wanted to warm up.
You're young. Just warming up.
What's going on?
I don't know.
- Master Song.
- Don't yell.
Master Song.
Don't yell. Don't yell.
That wimp.
Just warming you up.
You wimp.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
She's just a kid.
How could you touch her?
Have you no conscience?
I didn't do anything!
What did he do to you?
He tried
to untie my belt.
No, she tied a dead knot.
I couldn't get it open.
Let's go to the police.
Master Song, please!
I'm a scumbag. I beg you!
I lost my mind!
In the dead of winter...
I'll hit myself. I'll do it!
Shut up.
You have two choices.
The Public Security Bureau.
Go to prison.
Or just get out.
The farther, the better.
Never let the kid see you again.
Say something.
I'll be the sous-chef.
You'll be the head chef.
I'm begging you.
You whim.
What's wrong with him?
Kid, don't be scared.
Try to steady yourself.
Listen to me, okay?
If we report him to the police,
he'll get eight or ten years
for trying to assault you,
yet even death wouldn't be enough.
But if we report it,
the police will investigate
and question everyone.
Then the whole troupe will know.
Once rumors like this start spreading,
who knows how they'll end up?
His miserable life is worthless,
but you're still young.
Your reputation
for the rest of your life...
Oh, kid.
What should we do?
I want to go home.
You can't go back now.
All your efforts will be for nothing.
All those years of suffering
would be completely wasted.
Be good, okay?
Listen to me. Don't go back.
Stay calm on your own.
Think about it.
All right?
Master Liao, what are you doing?
Master Song! Master Song!
Why did Master Liao
jump the wall and leave?
At least he has some shame.
What happened?
Why bother with that?
Let him go wherever he wants.
Just get back to work.
It's fine, kid. Go to work.
Keep at it. It's nothing.
What's going on?
Why play different things?
Captain,
we haven't played for a long time.
We're all a bit rusty,
and the skill levels vary,
so I'm letting them practice alone.
Once they've improved,
we'll rehearse together.
Okay.
What piece for the competition?
Have you decided yet?
I still want to do Zhan Shan Tong.
- What?
- Zhan Shan Tong.
Why?
I've thought about it.
This part is the most powerful.
It captures the essence
of Qinqiang opera.
What essence?
It's desolate and resonant,
accepting defeat but not fate.
But didn't you say the vocal style
is too hard even for professionals?
Yes. I wanted to report that.
I plan to modify the arrangement.
We'll change the solo into a chorus.
One line per person for the first half.
Then, everyone joins in for the end.
I'd be thankful
if I could find one singer
in this prison,
and now you want a chorus?
A few lines are easy,
but finishing the play
in one breath is hard.
Didn't you run out of breath
near the end that day?
Besides, singing Zhan Shan Tong alone
feels too bleak.
A chorus has real presence.
It hits harder too.
That works.
I agree. Let's do Zhan Shan Tong.
And count me in for the chorus.
Captain,
we're called Rebirth Band.
You may not really fit.
♪From Hancheng County, Shaanxi♪
Is this hard to play?
No.
I watched you rehearse before.
It had so much energy.
It gave me goosebumps.
Can you teach me to play this thing?
Why?
Here's what I think.
Aren't you leaving in a year?
Then, I'll take over your shift
and keep banging this thing.
(Auditorium)
Easy, easy.
Good.
Good, good, good.
Right, good.
Yes, good.
Good.
That branch. Yes, yes.
That one, that one.
Fold them all.
Right.
(Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Fold it this way. Fold it.
(Bi Shang Liang Shan
Lin Chong: Li Gang, Mrs. Lin: Mi Lan)
A little more.
Coming through. Make way, please.
Make way, please.
Coming through.
Excuse me.
Hurry up with the makeup.
We're running out of time.
Please, go easy on me.
During the rehearsal yesterday,
it almost pinched my head off.
Thanks. Thank you.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe
Traditional Opera: Bi Shang Liang Shan)
Too soon. Too soon.
Come back.
What a wimp.
What's this?
Go.
Laidi.
Come here. Give me a hand.
Loosen my headpiece.
Mr. Gou got it way too tight.
I haven't even gone on stage,
and I'm already fainting here.
Hurry, help me loosen this.
♪Endless words to say♪
♪In blood and tears,
the couple can't bear to part♪
This actress is named Mi Lan.
She's our star performer.
She is impressive.
Honey.
Dear.
Is this prearranged?
Go away.
Since no one is speaking,
I'll say a few words.
Since I started leading the troupe,
within the troupe,
and behind my back,
there's been a certain rumor,
saying I don't know anything,
and it's amateurs leading professionals,
disregarding artistic creation,
and suppressing artists.
Some people even went so far
as to write joint letters
to the higher-ups,
claiming the troupe's stagnation
was due to my incompetence
and dictatorial ways.
It got to the point
where I began to doubt myself,
wondering if I was really incompetent.
So,
with the production
of Bi Shang Liang Shan,
I delegated all my authority
to let professionals lead the way.
I stayed out of the creative process.
Deputy Troupe Leader,
I kept my word, right?
Yes.
How did that turn out?
Troupe Leader,
the premiere failed.
I take full responsibility.
You can't carry that blame.
I'm the troupe leader.
The higher-ups will come after me.
Let's be honest.
Back when I was an amateur
leading the troupe,
we never let a show get this bad.
Here's the thing.
I'm the chief director of this show.
For it to end up like this,
I'm to blame.
I wasn't
capable enough.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Be quiet.
This is a troupe meeting.
Who are you to speak here?
How dare you!
Is that how you talk
to a veteran artist?
Who let you get away with that?
Director Gu,
I should thank you.
You helped me get my confidence back.
I won't say anything else.
We all gave it our best.
Thank you, everyone.
That's all.
Troupe Leader.
Troupe Leader, Troupe Leader.
Huang Zhengjing is so ruthless.
He cuts deep without one dirty word.
I can't stay anymore.
I really can't stay
here anymore.
I'm leaving.
If you go, I'm going with you.
I'm done with this crappy troupe.
It's so humiliating.
Yeah.
We can make a living anywhere.
You're leaving?
You shouldn't have come back.
Just leave, then.
Leave right now.
All three of you can leave together.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
All the other prison propaganda teams
get a reward,
except us.
Why is that?
Your plays aren't good.
You have such great veteran artists.
Why don't you use them?
Da Jiao Zan.
An old play. No one can perform it.
Such great skills. A fine Wudan.
Yi Qing'e,
take the lead role.
I'm nervous.
Go!
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪