( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
ظآزOnly after bloom comes fruitظآز
ظآزWho says glory must fade to the pastظآز
ظآزOnly through thunder
do you reach the cloudsظآز
ظآزWho made you the crown of every peakظآز
ظآزI stand at the center of the stageظآز
ظآزMy shadow is pinned against the wallظآز
ظآزFacing the light earns every medalظآز
ظآزLittle birds,
save your needless peckingظآز
ظآزThe open sky rises highظآز
ظآزWhen night falls,
the moon begins to shineظآز
ظآزI stand in the heart of these landsظآز
ظآزMy shadow bears no crown or robeظآز
ظآزThen I know truth needs no disguiseظآز
ظآزThe green hills see me as I amظآز
ظآزLike dew, lightning,
and moon on the riverظآز
ظآزShowing me exactly who I amظآز
=The Lead=
=Episode 21=
What's a Dan role?
A Dan role is a red sun,
rising above the horizon.
Qing'e,
I want to discuss something with you.
Go ahead.
I really want to play Mu Guiying.
You've performed Da Jiao Zan.
Let me have Mu Guiying this time.
You can be the lead
in the next new play.
Let's team up.
One lead role each.
Let them be our supporting cast.
What do you say?
ظآزI'll give you some leewayظآز
Go on.
What are you staring at? Go.
Next.
Yi Qing'e, you're up.
Get ready.
ظآزI'll give you some leewayظآز
Go.
Good.
Bravo.
Bravo, bravo.
Great. That was great.
Yi Qing'e.
Yi Qing'e,
when you were spear-pressing today,
was I standing too far back?
I should move forward a bit.
We can make eye contact side by side.
But today was really great!
It could be even better, though.
I think we can't slack off.
- We need practice.
- Feng Xiaoxiao!
- What is it?
- What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Why did you act like that with me?
Act like what?
Your staring made me so flustered.
You completely threw me off!
Do I have a choice in how I act?
You went too far.
How did I go too far?
You shouldn't have...
What?
What shouldn't I have done?
Drop the coal.
We need to practice more.
We should use the time we have.
- Master Song.
- Look at you.
- Why call him?
- Come to me anytime.
- Master Song.
- Anytime.
I'm always ready.
You...
Alright.
(Main Cast of Yang Men Nyu Jiang:
Mu Guiying)
No one's saying anything, huh?
Then let me say a few words.
Here's what I think.
They both play Mu Guiying
and Yang Qiniang.
One scene each.
They switch for each scene.
How's that?
Talk all you want.
Can you put that lousy blade
of yours down?
How troublesome.
You touched me.
What do you think?
What? You don't agree?
Then, have some tea.
Have some tea. Continue.
This is my salary over the years.
I live alone, with nowhere to spend it.
I can't take it after I die.
It should cover the opera armor, right?
(Current Savings Passbook)
(Mu Guiying)
(Mu Guiying: Yi Qing'e)
Then, it's settled.
Opera comes before everything.
Focus on rehearsing, all of you.
I'll handle the costumes.
Now, I have a major decision
to announce.
The region is planning
a performance showcase to carry on
the tradition and revive Qinqiang opera.
Two shows for each troupe.
Yang Men Nyu Jiang
will count as one.
Next, we'll need the four of you
to do another opera excerpt.
You will perform it
to fulfill your wish.
I can tell.
Feng Xiaoxiao acted totally differently
with you than he did
with that idiot.
He didn't mess with you, did he?
You're the one on purpose.
What do you mean?
Chu Jiahe.
Mr. He.
Well.
The role is decided.
You'll play Qiniang.
This role
is extremely important.
It has singing, speech, acting,
and combat.
To be blunt,
you and Mu Guiying
are co-lead female roles.
Get prepared, okay?
Take it seriously.
Mr. He, what do I play?
You? An extra.
I knew it.
Do your best.
Jiahe, you're amazing.
Yang Qiniang, a co-lead.
Co-lead with me?
Is she even good enough?
It's settled.
You'll play Mu Guiying.
Rehearsals start soon.
Mu Guiying is tough to play.
She has many vocal styles.
Practice the vocal style hard.
Master.
I...
What's wrong?
- Say it.
- I want to play Qiniang.
Why?
No reason.
I don't want to play Mu Guiying.
Did someone say something to you?
No.
Look at me.
Tell me.
What's really going on?
Bread!
Here, take it.
Take care.
Bread!
- Two for yourself?
- Bread, popsicles!
Bread and popsicles!
Come on, let's go in and play too.
Come play. It's on me.
What about ours?
What can you do?
- Good.
- I can do anything.
Can you beat someone?
You haven't even learned the craft.
But you've learned trading roles
for favors.
Is that even your call?
You think I don't know how?
You think I can't flatter Zhu Jiru?
I can't flatter Chu Jiahe?
You think I can't flatter people?
How could you do this?
Come back.
Get back here.
For you
and the opera,
I spent my whole life savings.
And you hand out roles as favors?
Trading roles for favors, huh?
You'd better remember this.
Remember this.
Trading roles for favors, huh?
I'll make you remember.
Don't hit her like this.
- Get away.
- Stop.
You'll hurt her badly like this.
She should know opera comes
before everything.
It's no longer
the era of old opera troupes.
You can't hit her as our master did.
If I don't hit her,
how will she learn my unique skills?
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
See you on Monday.
- Okay.
- See you, Master Gou.
Okay.
Feng Xiaoxiao.
Who let you smoke?
Who said you could smoke? Who?
Always talking nonsense.
- Don't move.
- Talking nonsense.
- What's wrong?
- Don't move.
That's for talking nonsense.
I'll beat you senseless.
Talking nonsense.
Will you smoke again?
- Always talking nonsense.
- Smoking, huh?
- Back off.
- If you smoke again,
I'll beat you.
You too.
- Behave yourselves.
- You two.
Behave yourselves.
(Customer First)
Where did he hit you?
Come on. Get up.
Are you okay?
It's scraped up.
Your head is bleeding.
Come on, let's go to the hospital.
This is called breaking-out.
Breaking-out is
a Qinqiang opera skill.
There's a full-length opera
called Li Hui Niang.
It's about a woman killed by a villain.
She returns as a ghost,
breathes fire, burns him down,
and saves the scholar she once loved.
Breaking-out is a rare skill,
especially the 81 Consecutive Bursts
of Fire.
Not everyone can pull it off.
At that final show of Gui Yuan Sha Sheng
in Beishan,
your master did
the 81 Consecutive Bursts of Fire,
but the last burst failed.
The show fell apart.
It haunted your master ever since.
We're going to the Beishan arts showcase
with two shows.
One is your Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
The other is your master's
Gui Yuan Sha Sheng.
He wants that final burst of fire
to come out.
That's enough. Take a break.
- I'm fine.
- Stop pushing it.
I'm fine. One more.
(Hot water)
What happened to you?
Someone beat me up.
Who was it?
Why would he beat you up?
What happened to your leg?
Training injury.
Did your master hit you?
ظآزI came down from the mountainsظآز
ظآزCarrying orchid grassظآز
ظآزI planted it in my little gardenظآز
ظآزHoping it would bloom soonظآز
ظآزI checked on it three times a dayظآز
ظآزWatching it as the days went byظآز
ظآزYet the orchid stillظآز
ظآزHad not a single budظآز
Who are you here for?
Master Hu.
Qing'e.
Qing'e, come out. Look who's back.
Look, hurry, look.
Why are you living here?
How can anyone live here?
Those people must've bullied you.
They must be bullying you.
How can anyone live here?
This place is so terrible.
Tell me who bullied you.
Those jerks. I'll go sort them out.
(Hot water)
No one's bullying me.
I'm really fine, Uncle.
I'm doing great.
Who was it? Tell me.
Look, I'm doing just fine.
Well...
How can you live here?
This place...
It's okay, Uncle.
I did well in there,
so they cut my time short
and let me out early.
That's good.
Qin Bawa went to see me.
I know a bit about your situation.
Qing'e, it must've been hard on you.
It's nothing.
You can perform opera now.
And you sing so well.
I never saw that coming.
My masters taught me well.
I owe them more than I can repay.
I have to pay it back.
Uncle,
can you come back to the troupe?
I don't know.
Who are you here for?
Hu Sanyuan.
Sit.
I heard you were back two days ago.
The police told me
you behaved well in there,
so you got out early.
Sit down.
I've waited for two days for you.
I went to Nail's hometown
and apologized to his parents.
I burned paper at Nail's grave.
Welcome back to society.
You've lost weight.
In there,
was it hard?
Not really.
How was the food? Was it enough?
Yeah.
Did anyone give you trouble in there?
Not for me.
I knew it.
You can survive anywhere.
Troupe Leader,
I want to return to the troupe.
I hope you return too.
Personal ties aside,
the troupe needs you.
The orchestra needs you even more.
But you have no idea.
After you were caught,
Huang Zhengjing dismissed you.
If we restore your status right now,
that's just impossible.
Letting you back into the orchestra
is even more impossible.
I hope you understand.
I understand.
Here's the thing.
I wanted to start you
as a temporary worker,
helping out in our kitchen,
but now, the kid...
Things are different now.
It's not like it used to be.
She's our leading performer now.
She's vital to our troupe.
What happened back then
hit her really hard.
If you come back now,
I'm worried
that her hard-won confidence
could be shattered again.
You're right.
Okay, okay.
Eat up.
Go on, eat some more.
They don't want you back?
I changed my mind.
I don't want to go back.
Why?
When you first joined the troupe,
you said
that the troupe was like a sheep pen.
I don't remember.
I didn't see it then.
Now, I think you had a point.
I don't want to be penned in there.
Then, what will you do?
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
I'll live well.
Just in a different way.
What are you doing?
Take it back. I don't want it.
Keep it.
You send money home every month?
Consider it a loan to me.
I'll pay you back.
(Restaurant; Ningzhou specialties,
Northern and Southern cuisine)
All right. Go back.
Don't worry about me. Bye.
(Restaurant)
(Department Store)
ظآزI came down from the mountainsظآز
ظآزCarrying orchid grassظآز
ظآزI planted it in my little gardenظآز
ظآزHoping it would bloom soonظآز
ظآزI checked on it three times a dayظآز
ظآزWatching it as the days went byظآز
(Yunnan Baiyao, Mercurochrome)
Take these two bottles.
Use some wherever you're hurt.
Thanks.
Where's your uncle?
He left.
Left?
Where did he go?
I don't know.
Why leave right after coming back?
I was thinking
that maybe he could play drums
for us for the show.
He brought me here, but he left.
So, all these years,
have you missed your uncle?
I don't know.
How can you not know?
I just don't know.
When your uncle left,
were you upset?
No.
Why?
Somehow,
he felt like a stranger to me.
He must've felt the same way.
He doesn't know what to say to me.
Maybe that's why he left.
Then,
do I feel like a stranger to you?
(Yunnan Baiyao, Mercurochrome)
You should get some sleep, too.
What happened to your head?
Why are you looking at me?
You think I did it?
I fell on my own.
Really?
- It doesn't look like it.
- I told you.
He said he fell.
How would I know?
Right, right.
Do you still want to be in this play?
Yes.
Fall again, and you're out.
Okay.
Especially around the warehouse.
It's a key fire-safety area.
Check for aging wiring.
- Inspect it.
- Director Huang.
Got it? Stay alert.
The weather's dry now.
Make sure to watch for fire tonight.
Right.
Who is the leader
who just went by?
The director of our Material Bureau.
Can you pay me after today's work?
Didn't I already tell you?
Wait until the month's end.
Get back to work.
I quit.
You've only been here for two days.
Why quit?
I'm not cut out for this.
Faster.
Give me your hand.
(Promote physical culture;
Improve the people's health)
Hold on to me.
Everyone, follow me.
Be careful.
(Photo Studio)
Sorry.
Shiwu.
It's hard to take photos.
- Shiwu, we're done.
- Don't cry, okay?
Listen to me.
Smile at the camera for photos.
Got it?
No more tears, okay?
The photo is done.
You have to smile for photos.
All right, all right.
Mom, if you won't let me win,
I can't go defend the realm.
Go easy on me, and I'll get through.
Oh, my.
How could I ever beat you, Mom?
- I'll go line up.
- Okay, okay.
- Get the bowls.
- I'll get them.
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
Are you with Feng Xiaoxiao now?
You can't be with him.
Because he and I got together ages ago.
I won't fight you for Mu Guiying.
But Feng Xiaoxiao is not up for grabs.
Even if you try, I won't give him up.
Yi Qing'e.
What are you doing here?
Why are you looking for Yi Qing'e?
What's it to you?
What were you talking about?
Wait. What were you two saying?
What are you two up to?
What do you need?
Master Gou wants us at the gatehouse.
The two of us?
Tell me.
How were Yang Wenguang and Mu Guiying?
I think it's pretty good.
You tell me.
I don't know.
Not great.
Why won't you look at Yang Wenguang?
Why is that?
Say it.
Tell me why you won't look.
I feel embarrassed.
Embarrassed?
You made that little spark
completely flat.
What matters for actors onstage?
The actors' eyes.
You haven't even trained your eyes.
How can you perform opera?
Go.
Find a crowded place.
Stare into Yang Wenguang's eyes.
Don't let your mind wander.
Practice it a hundred times.
If that fails, do it a thousand.
If that fails, do it ten thousand.
What's so funny?
You two, get out.
Why are you
embarrassed?
No reason.
Where should we practice then?
On the dirt mound behind the kitchen.
Master Gou said
to find a crowded place.
You eat first.
We'll practice
at the dorm entrance after.
I'm not going.
If you won't, I'll go find Master Gou.
Stay focused.
- Look at me.
- Feng Xiaoxiao.
Your eyes wandered off.
Lie on the ground; then she'll see you.
What's so funny?
Go back if you want to laugh.
Why did I ask you all here?
Ignore them, okay?
Focus on me. Look at me.
Laughing?
Laugh again, and I'll hit you.
Ignore them, okay?
Your eyes wandered off again.
Jiahe.
Come out.
Look at those silly fools.
Let them watch if they want.
There'll be more people onstage.
Don't mind them.
Excuse me.
Are you Mung Bean?
Hello, Turtle.
Turtle, huh?
You
- You're killing me!
- Hurry!
You're talking nonsense.
Laughing, huh?
I won't laugh. I won't.
Fine, fine.
- Please, stop!
- Say it again.
I won't laugh. I won't.
ظآزI came down from the mountainsظآز
ظآزCarrying orchid grassظآز
ظآزI planted it in my little gardenظآز
ظآزHoping it would bloom soonظآز
ظآزI checked on it three times a dayظآز
ظآزWatching it as the days went byظآز
ظآزYet the orchid stillظآز
ظآزHad not a single budظآز
ظآزAutumn came soonظآز
ظآزI moved the orchid indoorsظآز
ظآزTending it day by dayظآز
ظآزThinking of it night after nightظآز
ظآزHoping it would bloom soonظآز
ظآزTo fulfill my long-cherished wishظآز
ظآزClusters of flowers filled the yardظآز
ظآزAdding fragrance to the airظآز
ظآزI came down from the mountainsظآز
ظآزCarrying orchid grassظآز
ظآزI planted it in my little gardenظآز
ظآزHoping it would bloom soonظآز
ظآزI checked on it three times a dayظآز
ظآزWatching it as the days went byظآز
ظآزYet the orchid stillظآز
ظآزHad not a single budظآز
ظآزAutumn came soonظآز
ظآزI moved the orchid indoorsظآز
ظآزTending it day by dayظآز
ظآزThinking of it night after nightظآز
ظآزHoping it would bloom soonظآز
ظآزTo fulfill my long-cherished wishظآز
ظآزClusters of flowers filled the yardظآز
ظآزAdding fragrance to the airظآز
ظآزI came down from the mountainsظآز
ظآزCarrying orchid grassظآز
ظآزI planted it in my little gardenظآز
ظآزHoping it would bloom soonظآز
ظآزI checked on it three times a dayظآز
ظآزWatching it as the days went byظآز
=The Lead=
(Preview)
About the scene you two did today,
those looks
weren't Mu Guiying and Yang Wenguang's.
I told her that you've long been mine
and that I won't give you up to her.
Since when did I become yours?
Stop!
What's going on?
A few days ago, it was only one.
Now, all three of them have problems.
How would I know?
These are the drum scores I wrote
for Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
What on earth is this?
I can't read it.
What if the orchestra
drags us down too?
ظآزWhen I woke up and turned backظآز
ظآزI wasn't sure where to goظآز
ظآزWe met and brushed pastظآز
ظآزYour shadow drifted out of sightظآز
ظآزThe stove fire blazed in my dreamظآز
ظآزLit up the tracks of pearly tearsظآز
ظآزIn my dream, water sleeves flewظآز
ظآزHiding a lifetime of loveظآز
ظآزThe Qinling Mountains
crossed the stageظآز
ظآزSpring water brewed strong wineظآز
ظآزSheep moved through the valleyظآز
ظآزIt felt like a promise
from another lifeظآز
ظآزWhen I woke up and turned backظآز
ظآزI wasn't sure where to goظآز
ظآزIf I chose again, I'd still roamظآز
ظآزAll over this sunlit plateauظآز
ظآزThe dream ends; the curtain fallsظآز
ظآزMoonlight washes off this stage makeupظآز
ظآزThe one in the mirror wears gray hairظآز
ظآزAlready sang all my joy and sorrowظآز
ظآزAlready shouted across Qinchuan Plainظآز