( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 18=
Leave?
You shouldn't have come back.
Just leave.
Leave right now.
All three of you, leave!
Never come back!
What else can you do besides running away?
Back then, at the slightest
sign of trouble,
you ran faster than anyone else.
You made it sound nice.
Roaming the world, completely free?
You're just a coward!
Teaching opera singing?
A coward like you teaching Qinqiang opera,
can it still be called Qinqiang opera?
That's Coward opera!
Master Gou.
Did you watch tonight's
performance?
I did.
Know why it's a failure?
Pull hard, pull it up.
Pull it higher.
No skills off stage,
nothing on stage.
I tied it myself.
The veil couldn't have pulled it down.
Mr. Gou.
I grew up being trained in modern opera.
I never had head binding before.
You tied it too tight.
I couldn't take it.
If you can't take this little pain,
you shouldn't be in this profession.
Step aside!
Be careful!
You'll draw attention.
What are you doing here?
We're hungry.
Looking for some Mo to eat.
We'll leave right away.
Don't grab me!
Me first!
Let me out first. Me first!
The Mo issue is solved.
Master Song.
Here.
Listen up.
The troupe's going to the countryside
to perform Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui.
- We're all going too.
- Give me more.
Get prepared.
All going?
They haven't done that play in years.
Why bring it back now?
Running out of options, huh?
Bi Shang Liang Shan was a total flop.
What else to perform?
If a troupe doesn't perform, what is it?
They'll mess it up anyway.
What are you talking about?
Don't jinx it.
You should have more hope.
(Performing opera for the people)
(Theater in the country)
Get off. Get off.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
Boys, help the girls out.
Come on.
Hurry up!
Come on. Be careful.
Unload the gear.
Hurry up.
Line up now.
Start stage setup now.
Unload the gear. Stay safe.
Come on.
Okay, okay.
Attention, everyone.
- Line up quickly.
- Attention.
Line up.
The kitchen is on the school playground.
Food will be ready in an hour.
Okay.
Qiu!
In an hour?
The water is too far from the kitchen.
Carrying water is exhausting us.
- How did you plan this?
- Okay, okay.
- I'll fix it now.
- Tell them to wait.
Hurry up.
I'll fix it right away.
Keep your spirits up.
Got it.
Master Song.
What?
Tell everyone it's two meals
a day tomorrow.
Why is that?
They eat at 10 AM tomorrow.
Tough show tonight. Let everyone sleep in.
They eat at 4 PM today.
They'll prep for the show after eating.
You tell them. I don't
want to get yelled at.
I was invited to attend a banquet.
Unload the food. Hurry.
Bye.
So full of yourself.
Old fox.
I always have to play the bad guy.
Only two meals?
The food budget won't last the month?
One meal is even better.
Makes our job easier.
Back then,
they'd call me over from time to time
for meetings and studying.
At least I had something real to do.
And now?
Reform and Opening-up.
Times have changed.
No more endless meetings.
I have plenty of free time.
I can't just do nothing.
So I opened this Xishi Tofu Shop.
Plus, I was recently made
Commune Cultural Station Director.
Director?
How many people do you manage?
Just one.
I
manage myself.
You make magic with tofu.
We should bring Master Song here
- to learn.
- Right.
He makes cabbage and tofu stew all day.
Even pigs wouldn't eat it.
Exactly.
If your troupe's food is terrible,
we can let it slide.
But your troupe's plays are boring.
That's unacceptable.
What era are we in?
Why are you still performing those?
Passing off weeds as seeds
to fool us country folks?
Yeah, we're tired of them.
Right, fooling us farmers.
We don't want to fool you either.
Didn't Bi Shang Liang Shan fail?
We have no plays left.
You have great veteran artists.
Why don't you use them?
They did.
No use.
Did they use you or not?
There's a talent gap.
It's no use whoever comes.
Mr. Qin.
I came here to ask you
to write a modern play for us.
If you asked me to make tofu for you,
I could do that.
But the modern play...
I haven't written anything in years.
With your skills...
How is Hu Sanyuan? Any news on him?
No news.
He won't be out for at least a year.
That's not important.
What's important is
that we urgently need a modern play.
Right.
The tofu is delicious.
You like the tofu?
I'll send you two loads tomorrow.
Great.
(Fourth Qinchuan Provincial
Prison System Art Showcase)
Next, Beishan Prison's
Rebirth Propaganda Team.
Performing Qinqiang opera Zhan Shan Tong.
Quick time, march.
One, two, one.
Sit.
♪With a loud shout♪
♪Tied outside the tent♪
(Rhythm and Arts Showcase)
Laidi.
How are you doing?
Doing great.
Any news about your uncle?
None.
I wonder how he's been
these past few years.
I used to dream about him a lot.
Haven't dreamed of him lately.
Any news about Hua Caixiang?
None either.
I heard she's had a hard time lately.
When they were in the troupe,
I didn't really notice it.
Now that they've left the troupe,
it's gotten so boring.
I remember this area
is near your hometown, right?
When was the last time you went back?
A few years ago.
Ever since Ms. Hua and I
brought you out of your hometown,
you've never gone back?
You must miss home a lot.
Listen.
After the performance,
I'll go back with you.
It's a half-day trek home from here.
A round trip takes a whole day.
We're short-staffed. I can't leave.
Is something on your mind?
No.
If you need anything or have any issues,
you must let me know.
That's right. Careful.
Straighten that curtain out.
Zhu.
Right, tighten it.
Make sure the rope is tight.
- Zhu.
- Right. Careful.
Tighten it.
Zhu.
Zhu, let's go.
Go? Go where?
Come with me.
What is it?
I'm busy here.
Just come.
Come on.
- Go where?
- Follow me.
You'll know.
Why so mysterious?
Her. That kid.
An actress in your troupe?
What actress?
She's a kitchen maid.
Are you kidding?
This...
Such great skills! She's a good Wudan!
The kitchen maid of Tianbo Yang Mansion!
That's right!
What Tianbo Yang Mansion?
Hu Sanyuan's niece!
Gou Cunzhong's apprentice.
Hu Sanyuan's niece?
The one who rushed to eat four of my Mo
and almost choked to death?
Exactly.
She doesn't look like her.
How old was she?
How old is she now?
Girls change as they grow up!
If she were in our troupe,
she'd be even more beautiful.
Who left the tofu here?
Me.
I delivered the tofu.
Kid, remember this.
My name is Qin Bawa.
A playwright.
(Xishi Tofu Shop)
Besides Da Jiao Zan?
We only taught her that opera excerpt.
Then, for tonight,
can we add that excerpt?
The leaders won't agree.
Didn't I explain the situation?
What situation?
We're not allowed to
rehearse Yang Pai Feng.
It is ridiculous.
Just Troupe Leader Huang
shouting slogans.
And you get scared.
Are his words gospel?
You don't know about our troupe.
I may not know the situation.
But I know you, Zhu Jiru.
Just tell me, yes or no?
Straighten up.
Learn from me.
Live with some backbone, okay?
What can one tough Zhu Jiru do?
You can change that kid's fate!
People are eating here, Bawa.
Calm down. Talk nicely.
Go.
Just go.
Nothing.
- I'm telling you, Zhu Jiru.
- Just eat.
If you watch Huang Zhengjing ruin the kid,
and you say nothing,
you're an accomplice.
Can't we eat in peace?
Shut up and eat your food!
Stop blowing things out of proportion!
- Sorry.
- You have no right!
This dish is free.
- Look, look!
- Enjoy.
He slammed the table and yelled.
He spilled my tea.
I've been talking to him calmly.
Watch your tone.
Tough now?
Feeling bold now?
Why are you talking to me so tough?
Is it because I have no power?
Just a solemn reminder
that I'm the Cultural Station Director.
Your troupe's performance fee
is paid by the Station.
You listen,
no Da Jiao Zan today,
then no payment from the Station.
I keep my word.
So?
Meng Liang and Jiao Zan are in town.
We don't have the costumes.
We do.
Those old things
were kept safe by us old folks.
We even performed for you.
How could you forget?
And the drums?
Can He Dachui play?
He played Bi Shang Liang Shan.
The kid and I will run it twice with music.
It shouldn't be a problem.
You would think!
Will he play for you?
Let's go talk to him.
His drumming isn't good,
and neither is his temper.
Master Qiu, keep your temper
- in check later.
- I know.
Watch your tone.
You're asking for a favor.
- Hello, Troupe Leader Zhu.
- Hello.
Okay.
I'll talk to him about our show first.
He Dachui.
I need to discuss something with you.
Go ahead.
Tonight, I want to
add an opera excerpt.
What is it?
Da Jiao Zan.
Da Jiao Zan?
- Yang...
- The excerpt from Yang Pai Feng.
It's an old play. No one can sing it.
Yi Qing'e can.
- Who?
- Yi Qing'e.
The kitchen maid playing a kitchen maid.
Hu Sanyuan's niece?
Exactly.
Total nonsense.
No way. That kid can't sing.
I've seen her skills.
Really good.
Good my foot.
I believe she stokes fires well.
I believe she chops veggies well.
If you say she outcooks Master Song,
I'd be half-convinced.
She sings opera well?
I wouldn't believe it to save my life.
Hey, that one! That one.
A secret for you.
Gou Cunzhong took her as an apprentice
many years ago.
She's been training for years too.
- Who?
- Gou Cunzhong.
I don't trust him!
In Bi Shang Liang Shan,
Hu Sanniang sang so terribly.
I won't play. I just can't.
- Let me.
- Stay out of it.
- Come on.
Dachui.
This play is an easy gig.
The opening,
Shua Hai Er,
and the finale. All right?
You even played for Bi Shang Liang Shan.
And the whole troupe thinks
you're playing better and better.
This play is a piece of cake for you.
Come on.
Dachui.
Stop flattering me like that.
Last time in Bi Shang Liang Shan,
you guys almost ruined me.
The band and actors need to sync up.
Just leave it alone.
It'll take at least half a month.
If you're not embarrassed, I am.
No, here's the thing.
This morning, a Commune official
was strolling around here.
He happened to see Qing'e practicing.
And he happens to be an expert.
He was blown away by her skills.
He insists on adding the show.
If we don't add it,
the troupe won't get a single penny.
What can we do?
What does that have to do with me?
Hang it at position four.
Right, position four.
Dachui.
Let her do a run-through, and take a look.
Watch it first before deciding.
Just watching?
Stop, stop, stop!
Come on, kitchen meeting.
Can't see we're so busy?
Our kitchen is gonna get celebrated!
I'd just be happy
not to get yelled at.
Guess.
No. Just tell us!
Tonight, our kitchen is gonna
play the lead!
What do you mean?
Zhu Jiru and the Commune leaders just agreed
to add a show tonight, Da Jiao Zan.
Yi Qing'e takes the lead!
That's wonderful!
I called two helpers. They'll be here soon.
- Okay.
- Free the kid up.
Let her get ready.
Sure.
Kid.
I already made the call.
Your three masters bring the costumes.
Let's do a run-through
before they arrive.
Why so suddenly?
Not at all!
Hard work pays off!
I knew it!
Our kid will make it eventually!
Laidi, get up.
Stop working.
Let's go wash your face.
Get ready for the run-through.
Nice and clean.
Hey, ignore her.
Come here.
Let's discuss something.
- What is it?
- Just come here.
Any other good news?
Chop your veggies.
Go wash your face.
What's wrong?
I'm nervous.
Don't be afraid, kid.
Anyone would be nervous.
Like a bride on her wedding day,
there's a first time for everything.
Listen to me.
Just sing how you usually practice.
You'll be absolutely fine.
The kid might not sing.
First you say yes, then you say no.
Will the kid sing or not?
If it's a no,
it is because He Dachui
won't play the drums for her.
Why?
No idea.
I think He Dachui doubts the kid can sing.
So, can the kid sing or not?
It's not about whether she can.
If she gets on stage today,
she might never step down.
The lead in our troupe...
Hua Caixiang.
Mi Lan.
Every single one of them.
I guarantee it
from now on,
no one can fight her for the lead.
Isn't that a good thing?
Like heck it is.
What do you mean?
What's wrong? Just tell me.
Go talk to He Dachui.
Why me?
Because he listens to you.
What do you mean?
She didn't even gasp.
You, either.
Good?
Good or bad,
it's not up to me.
Then whom?
She dared to hit him.
You'll know when you grow up.
Men are very easy to handle.
The kid's head got hit.
Not bad.
Hurry up and cook.
Keep it up.
Mo.
What's on your mind?
Alright, okay.
Attention, everyone.
Hurry up and eat, get ready.
We go in at 5:30.
The show starts at 6:00 sharp.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
Where are the band guys?
Eat. No need to worry about it.
Sing a cappella?
That's about enough.
We're going to eat.
Thank you. Thanks, everyone.
Hurry. Go eat.
When will your sidekicks get here?
Soon.
Master Gou!
You and your three ancient relics
better get ready.
See you on stage.
I'm relieved you're here.
Look at me.
Remember today,
the day of your debut.
Great! You are finally here! Great!
Me, the kid, and the band.
We ran through it twice.
Go wash your faces and eat.
Then do the kid's makeup.
- This way. Come.
- Okay.
This way.
- Let's go.
- Laidi. Laidi!
- Quick, quick!
- Come with me.
What is it?
Don't worry about it.
No eating! Head binding is up next!
- You're so fussy.
- This way.
Today,
you are marrying the stage.
The kitchen is your maternal home.
And I am your mother.
You must be washed spotless
before going on stage.
Reporting, Hu Sanyuan is here.
Come in.
Go in.
The competition results are out.
We came up empty.
And got slapped with a label.
I don't get what you mean.
First, second, and third prizes.
Encouragement and hope prizes.
All Prison Propaganda Teams won,
except us.
What label did we get?
(Our track chosen for the event was unfit.)
But why?
Why?
"Executioners, escort the lord here now."
"Waiting at the execution ground."
Then someone asked.
"Who are the executioners?
Who is the lord?"
"Are you mocking someone indirectly?"
They needed me to explain.
We're singing an old opera.
It's about chaos in the
Sui and Tang Dynasties.
How...
No need to explain to me.
What I told them was exactly
what you said.
Sir, lock me up then.
How come it's your fault?
I told you to sing.
What's wrong with these people?
It's the Reform and Opening-up era.
Some people's bodies have moved on,
but their minds are stuck in the past.
In my heart,
our performance
deserves the grand prize.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
♪Honghu waters, wave upon wave♪
♪The shores of Honghu are my home♪
♪Boats set out at dawn
to cast their nets♪
♪Returning in the evening
with holds full of fish♪
Now,
press your ears down.
Bear with it.
It hurts.
Loosen it a bit.
It's too tight. She can't take it.
She has to.
If she passes out, how can she perform?
Shut up.
Head binding is your first test.
You must suffer this to sing opera.
Now,
get up and walk.
Now Yi Qing'e finally understood
why Mi Lan was in unbearable pain.
Head binding is cruelest for a Dan role.
It's like torturing the head.
It's too tight. Loosen it.
Shut your trap!
How is it going?
Almost done.
They're almost done.
How much longer?
How's the band?
We're lucky if they play it all.
Don't expect too much.
Hurry up.
Okay, right away.
Is it okay?
♪As long as we face
the sun like sunflowers♪
♪Holding high♪
♪The red flag raised in Jinggangshan♪
Hurry, hurry up!
♪March towards victory♪
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
On stage,
Master Zhou and Master Qiu will guide you.
They'll set the rhythm for you.
Just follow their rhythm.
Don't follow the rhythm of the drums.
Stick to the rhythm I teach you.
Let the drums follow you.
Don't look at me.
Look at the audience.
What do you see?
People.
Look up at the sky.
What do you see?
Stars.
The highest state of acting
is not performing for people,
but performing for Heaven.
Forget the audience.
Got it?
Got it.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Please enjoy the excerpt, Da Jiao Zan.
Starring Yi Qing'e,
Zhou Cunren, Qiu Cunyi.
Go.
Are you crazy?
Go!
Bravo!
Excellent!
Amazing!
Bravo!
What are you doing?
Excellent!
Bravo!
Kid.
Hang in there.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
Four old men and one little girl
brought the troupe back to life with ease!
With Hua Caixiang, at least
I had a chance to compete.
But with you, I don't even
have the chance to compete.
We wanna be your apprentices!
Masters, please take us in!
Stop fooling around!
Get lost!
This is so unfair!
If someone taught us,
we'd perform even better than her!
Who told you to serve me food?
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪