( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 24=
Checkmate!
Stop for now.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Show your warmth.
- Troupe Leader Zhu.
- Hongbing.
It's a long trip.
Nice to meet you again!
The show was so amazing!
I got stunned!
They are our key members.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Come on.
Those are the training outfits.
- Find people to take them.
- Okay.
- Take them to the rehearsal hall.
- Sure.
Where are the actors?
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Inside. I'll introduce.
Come.
I've been looking forward.
Well, Hongbing...
What a car!
It looks better than the Magistrate's.
Let's welcome our distinguished guest,
Comrade Liu Hongbing.
Why did I call Comrade Liu Hongbing
our distinguished guest?
The costumes for Yang Men Nyu Jiang
and the fine opera armor
were all obtained by him
from various channels
just for us.
If it weren't for him
and his full support,
you wouldn't look so stunning on stage.
Impressive!
Today,
Comrade Liu Hongbing
came all the way from Beishan
to bring you some
brand-new practice outfits
as a reward for your amazing
performance.
Great!
Next up,
let's have Comrade Liu Hongbing
say a few words.
Welcome!
Hello, everyone.
I am a military veteran,
and here I offer you a military salute.
Helping you get these stage costumes,
to me,
is just a tiny matter.
It's not worth mentioning.
I've watched
every single show
of the joint performance.
You guys
deserve the most thumbs up!
- Thumbs up?
- You deserve a thumbs up.
Your speech deserves one too.
Feng Xiaoxiao, Liu Ke.
Both of you, shut up.
Everyone, be serious.
Applause!
Yi Qing'e?
Those are all our...
She's here.
- Qing'e.
- Yi Qing'e.
Liu Hongbing brought you something.
Hello, Comrade Yi Qing'e.
I have something for you.
Give me a hand.
Look.
Every photo in this album
was taken by me.
You were amazing.
This is your first show.
Keep it. It'll be a great memento.
The newspaper.
Look at this newspaper.
I had my friend
write this article just for you.
- Take a look.
- No, thanks.
Just take it.
It's a good keepsake.
Have a look.
Take it.
Just take it.
You made the front page.
Keep it as a souvenir.
Thank you.
So you live here?
Be careful!
How can anyone live here?
I want to live here.
We have dorms.
Right.
Yi Qing'e volunteered to
live here. It's convenient
for practice.
This won't do. I'm telling you,
living here for too long
will wreck her health.
Hongbing, you have no idea
that our troupe's housing conditions
are really tight.
I'll talk to the county leaders
and report this properly.
Such a great Qinqiang opera actress
deserves more attention!
Thank you so much, Hongbing.
You're a huge help.
- Thank you!
- On behalf of the troupe, I thank
Liu Hongbing.
Thank you!
It's the least I could do.
This young man...
Oh my goodness.
Looks young, but he's a big shot.
He carries himself like a soldier.
Really?
He does.
Go serve it.
Okay, okay.
- Careful.
- Coming!
The troupe's own canteen.
Nothing fancy. Have a taste.
Tomato and egg.
How does it taste?
Great!
Listen,
the food here
is amazing. Just like army food.
You have quite the palate.
Our cook, Master Song,
used to serve in the mess squad.
He was a squad leader.
Then I must toast him.
Plump.
Take Hongbing to chat with Master Song.
Hello, Master Song.
He drives for the leaders of
the Administrative Office.
Why drag me to this dinner?
Why? For your own matter, of course.
What matter?
He's got strong connections.
I want to get you back to the troupe.
He's just a driver.
Can he pull that off?
He can.
Do you know what his father does?
What? A county leader?
Administrative Commissioner.
Liu Hongbing may not be highly educated,
but he's a passionate guy who loves to help.
That newspaper article about Qing'e.
He's the one who got someone to write it.
Did you ask him to do it?
He did it on his own.
What does it have to do with him?
Why would he do that?
He values talent and did it for us.
Our girl in "Yang Men Nyu Jiang"...
Wasn't her singing amazing?
Truly remarkable.
Such talent deserves great coverage.
Right?
Just chatted with my buddy.
He served eight years before me.
An old squad leader.
- Close as family.
- Yes indeed.
Wherever you soldiers go,
you're all like one big family.
Absolutely.
True comrades-in-arms.
Aunt Plump just told me that
Qing'e is
a talent raised in this cafeteria.
What's the story?
I guess you could say that.
Qing'e owes where she is today all to him.
Him?
I told you about Hu Sanyuan.
I didn't tell you
about his relationship with Qing'e.
Hu Sanyuan is Yi Qing'e's uncle.
Her real uncle.
Uncle?
So you're the uncle!
Nice to meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
She was amazing on stage.
A truly rare talent.
Hongbing.
Sit, sit.
I've heard so much about you.
That year, Hu Sanyuan went to prison.
Yi Qing'e was implicated.
My predecessor
wanted to fire her.
I tried everything I could
to keep her working in the kitchen.
Qing'e is a tough one.
A few masters in our troupe
saw her talent for opera
and secretly took her in as a student.
She learned while tending the fire.
That's how she got so good today.
It wasn't easy.
It's so touching.
With such a touching story,
why didn't you write it in the paper?
I have an idea.
You'll be going to perform
in Beishan for a month.
I'll ask my friends in the press
to do a proper interview with Qing'e.
We'll put these touching stories
all over the newspapers,
so everyone can read about it.
As for this...
let's not report it.
Why not?
I'll explain it to you later.
Alright.
Then call Qing'e over.
Let's toast her.
The show was such a success.
It's worth celebrating.
Our troupe has rules.
Members are forbidden from drinking.
Especially female members.
They can't drink with guests.
I'll drink with you.
Rules? Understood.
Understood.
To get Hu Sanyuan back to our troupe,
is it difficult?
That's no big deal.
Uncle,
I'm not bragging to you,
but for me, this matter
is just a tiny thing.
But why return to the county troupe?
I can pull some strings
to get you and Qing'e
into the Local Troupe together.
I asked you to bring him back,
and you're poaching my staff?
That's not what I meant.
Qing'e deserves a bigger stage.
That's not gonna happen. Our troupe
just got back on its feet.
The old masters either died or left.
We just trained two girls well.
The Provincial Troupe poached them.
Qing'e is our key trainee now. If she
leaves, we're done for.
Look at the bigger picture.
What bigger picture?
You two stop caring about my business.
I won't go back to the troupe.
Why not?
No reason. I just don't want to.
Then stop worrying about Qing'e.
She's staying put at this troupe.
Hu Sanyuan, why are you so stubborn?
Don't be rash!
Line up, line up!
Come on, line up!
Line up.
Applause!
Farewell! Farewell!
- So annoying!
- A warm farewell!
- Liu Ke!
- Farewell, farewell!
- You're so annoying!
- A warm farewell!
- Help!
- Get my bags!
- Farewell! A warm farewell!
Farewell! Farewell!
A warm farewell!
Farewell! A warm farewell!
Yi Qing'e.
Goodbye.
Really leaving?
Where are you going?
Zhou Yuzhi and I are being transferred
- to the Provincial Troupe.
- I'll be back.
- Shine or whatever at this troupe.
- I'll visit!
No one will compete with you.
Goodbye.
Take care.
- Hold this for me.
- Take care.
Take care!
- Safe travels.
Come back!
- Come back!
- Visit us!
Don't forget about us!
She's really good. A real talent.
Yeah.
Good.
Great.
Really good.
Impressive.
Now, let's welcome County Magistrate Guo.
Women's Federation, you go first.
Okay.
Comrade Yi Qing'e,
due to your outstanding stage performance,
on behalf of the County Women's Federation,
I officially invite you to join us.
Thank you, Federation leaders.
I am incredibly honored.
Look how modest this young comrade is.
Comrade Yi Qing'e.
You are the pride of our county.
You brought our county glory at your age.
And to our county's cultural prosperity,
you've made a huge contribution.
Yes, yes.
Your shining presence on stage
proves our county's Qinqiang opera
has worthy successors.
Thank you, County Magistrate Guo.
I represent the County CPPCC today
to give you some good news.
Following the CPPCC's
serious discussions and deliberations,
and approval at the general meeting,
as a representative for women and artists,
you're elected as a County CPPCC Member.
Good, good.
You've shone bright on the opera stage.
On the political stage,
I hope you'll be a rising star too.
Be active in political affairs
and help build our county.
Good.
Magistrate Guo.
What is it?
Comrade Yi Qing'e is so young.
She just achieved a little...
What's wrong with being young?
Her youth and talent are her strengths.
She's a CPPCC Member now.
Then what about our troupe?
What should we do about it?
The troupe and the CPPCC
are different matters.
Take care, Magistrate Guo.
Became a Member just like that?
The youth, you know.
Is the next title Deputy Troupe Leader?
For that kid,
anything's possible.
Then what about me?
You?
Replace me as Troupe Leader.
That wouldn't be right.
Congratulations, Qing'e,
on becoming a CPPCC Member.
What's a CPPCC Member?
To put it simply,
you help the County Government
by offering advice,
discussing policies,
and promoting the county's
economic and cultural development.
The Members are all
elites from various fields,
who have passed a strict selection.
From now on, I'll be leading you
and also reporting to you.
Don't be nervous.
You are my boss now.
You can always learn.
Okay, the sleeves.
This is...
How much is this?
Measure it again.
Uncle.
Qing'e, what brings you here?
Perfect timing.
Let the tailor take your measurements.
I'll get you two new outfits.
No need. I need to talk to you.
What's wrong?
Sit.
Water.
What is it?
They want me to be a leader.
Leading the trainee class?
No.
Then who are you leading?
They want me to be a CPPCC Member.
What?
A CPPCC Member.
Who's tricking you?
County Magistrate Guo
told me at the Troupe.
He told you in person?
Was Zhu Jiru there?
Uncle, don't look for Troupe Leader Zhu.
Stay out of it. I'll go talk to him.
Then talk nicely.
Don't quarrel.
I know, I know. Don't worry.
Alright, you go back. I'll go.
Talk nicely.
I know. Go back.
Don't quarrel.
Come in.
Sit.
I'll stand.
Come on, sit.
About the CPPCC Member thing,
Qing'e told you, right?
Why are you joking with the kid?
Who's joking?
Is this something to joke about?
Sit!
How is that possible?
Why wouldn't it be?
She didn't even dare to speak back then.
People thought she was mute.
And now?
She's famous all over Beishan.
Little Queen of Qinqiang Opera.
Who recommended her as a CPPCC Member?
Me.
Why did you recommend her?
I was trying to get a spot for myself.
I got the spot, but I didn't pass.
The CPPCC asked me to pick her.
Got it?
Try to fight for yourself again.
Get yourself up there.
What good karma did this kid get?
Good luck just falls right into her lap.
This sudden windfall is too much.
She can't handle it.
Why can't she?
I oppose her becoming a CPPCC Member.
You oppose it? What right do you have?
I'm her uncle. What else do I need?
What rank is an uncle?
Is an uncle above Party Secretary,
or CPPCC Chairman?
Don't give me this nonsense.
I oppose it anyway.
The higher-ups don't know
what she's like.
Can she really be a CPPCC Member?
You'd even have to report to her?
- Do you understand politics?
- No.
Then you have no say in this.
I know you want what's best for her.
She's just a fragile young girl.
The Little Queen of Qinqiang Opera's crown
is already too heavy.
We can't add any more weight to it.
I'm begging you, okay?
I know how you feel
and what you fear.
You believe in fate?
No.
Whether you believe it or not,
this is Yi Qing'e's fate.
What can we do about your fate?
I have no idea.
When I brought you out here,
I just wanted you to have commodity grain.
I could never have imagined
that you could fly so high.
I'm really at a loss.
Next, Trouple Leader Zhu will report.
Hello, leaders.
Over the past year,
our troupe performed the traditional opera
Yang Men Nyu Jiang
and the opera excerpt Da Jiao Zan.
The performances were a huge success.
So far,
our troupe has performed across the region
for nearly a hundred shows.
They are deeply loved by the locals.
We're overwhelmed with show requests.
We're booked for the
second half of the year.
Comrade Yi Qing'e knows that well.
We want to strike while the iron is hot
and stage another classic Qinqiang opera,
You Xi Hu.
The biggest challenge right now is that
our troupe only has four veterans.
Mr. Gou Cunzhong has already passed away.
Zhou Cunren,
Gu Cunxiao,
and Qiu Cunyi
also left the troupe, and went
their separate ways.
How will you rehearse the play then?
That's why
for our next steps,
we need all the leaders
present here to give us
your full support
and help us out of this crisis.
Welcome, County Magistrate Guo and leaders,
to the county's Materials Bureau warehouse
for on-site inspection and guidance.
On behalf of the Materials Bureau,
I'd like to welcome you all here.
A warm welcome.
Comrade Yi Qing'e.
Don't hide.
Come, step forward.
- Come.
- Come on.
No need to be afraid of your old boss.
Hello, Member Yi. Welcome!
Director Huang.
Watch what you call him.
Bureau Chief Huang.
Welcome, welcome everyone.
I'll continue my report now.
County Magistrate Guo.
Currently, our county
is in excellent shape.
All industries are...
All industries are thriving.
To meet our county's construction needs,
the Materials Bureau spares no effort.
We reach out nationwide
for in-demand steel, cement, and timber.
Member Yi.
Hello, ma'am!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
I have no idea.
Ma'am.
Don't go, ma'am!
Cut your nonsense.
Seriously?
You're a big shot now.
On par with the County Magistrate?
Huang Zhengjing and Zhu Jiru report to you.
What's this?
(Veggies, soup, Mo)
I drew it in my free time.
Just to kill time.
(Serving food, making tofu)
Nice sheep drawing.
Of course.
Serving food, making tofu.
An old geezer sits by the pot.
Wants to eat
a bowl
of tofu.
You even know Pinyin.
(Beishan Theater)
The Yang Men Nyu Jiang show
was a massive success.
During the regional showcase,
after taking first place,
the local leaders
had them stationed in Beishan
to perform for half a year.
The name Yi Qing'e in the Beishan area
was recognized everywhere.
Bravo!
Yi Qing'e.
Let's talk about your past.
Maybe your childhood.
Things from my childhood...
I don't really remember.
Have some Kvass. It's refreshing.
Some for our reporter friend too.
No, thanks.
I'll leave it here in case you get thirsty.
Bravo!
- Bravo!
- Your breathtaking,
gorgeous face
pierced through many unreachable,
solid barriers.
You're clearly a Song
dynasty snake spirit,
yet you make...
Bravo!
Yi Qing'e!
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Beishan Regional News.
(Huge success)
Your Yang Men Nyu Jiang photo
takes up half a page.
And also...
Look.
I used color film just for
your photos. They can't
even develop them in Beishan.
I went all the way to Chang'an for this.
Every single one...
- Sorry.
- Watch where you're going.
Didn't notice.
Look.
Look at you...
Hey, buddy!
Watch where you're going!
Why keep doing this? What's your problem?
You're in my way.
In your way? Who are you?
This is a dressing room, not a commune.
Get out.
What? Doing this on purpose?
- I do it on purpose.
- You...
I'll teach you
a lesson!
Stop fighting!
We're not fighting.
We're taking off makeup.
You shouldn't be backstage.
Well...
I just came to hand out photos.
Look.
Photos of everyone. Look.
I got one of you too.
Here, take it.
What are you looking at back there?
Don't be so petty.
He's weird. Come on.
Hand these out to everyone.
Qing'e, you're famous now!
And look at this.
Our local Beishan Evening News.
Everyone gets one.
Take a look.
Beishan's Yang Men Nyu Jiang show
was a huge success!
Here, one for each of you. Look.
- Your play...
- Yi Qing'e.
- Half a page in the news!
- Let me see!
Come look!
Don't fight over it. Stop.
Here, here, I have more!
Come here, hurry!
Looking great.
- Here, take these.
- I gotta say,
he's a pretty good photographer.
This one is great.
His skills aren't bad.
Qing'e.
Come with me.
I just received a notice.
Report to Provincial Qinqiang Troupe ASAP.
Why?
I don't know.
I'm not going.
It's not up to you.
Or me.
A top provincial leader
called the County Party Secretary.
You have to go.
I'm not going anywhere.
Master died right here.
I only sing right here.
I sing for my master.
Even if he were alive, it still
wouldn't be up to you!
I'm not going!
The performance plan has changed.
Pack your bags. Tomorrow,
we'll head back.
What are you whining about?
Go pack your bags!
What are you waiting for?
Go.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
(Boiled water)
Master Song.
Where is she?
In her room.
You...
Work.
I want to go see her.
I'm her uncle. Stay out of it.
Qing'e.
What's wrong?
Zhu Jiru told me everything.
There's nothing we can do, right?
The higher-ups summoned you.
No one can stop them.
I know what you're thinking.
The Opera Troupe trained you.
The Opera Troupe needs your help right now.
If you leave now,
it just doesn't feel right.
But there's no other way now, is there?
Sometimes we just don't have a choice.
But have you thought about it?
If your master were here...
If Master Gou were here,
what would he say?
He'd definitely tell you to go.
The Provincial Qinqiang Troupe is where
Qinqiang opera singers dream of going.
A bigger stage means a bigger show.
You have the talent now.
This county troupe is
too small for you.
Did you hear me?
Are you listening to me?
I'm scared.
Scared of what?
When I first came here as a kid,
I was scared for years.
Actually, my bravery was all an act.
Now I'm finally not scared anymore.
You want me to leave.
I don't want to live in fear anymore.
I... I get it.
Back then
when I was sent away,
I didn't want to go either.
I was scared too.
No use.
I stayed a while and settled down.
Then I wasn't scared anymore.
To tell you the truth,
I was scared again when I got out.
What was I supposed to do?
How to face people?
But I got through it.
We face a lot in this life.
We have to keep moving forward.
Once you get through it and look back,
you'll see it was nothing at all.
Don't worry, I will go with you.
I've cleaned up my act.
I'm not as hot-tempered.
I won't cause trouble for you.
Master Gu is already there.
He can look out for you.
You have to listen to Master Gou.
He definitely wants you to go.
You like Yi Qing'e, don't you?
I do.
I know.
She likes you too.
What do we do now?
Understand?
You could crush me like a bug.
Why would I crush you?
There are two ways to like someone.
One is to hold it tight.
The tighter you hold, the sooner it dies.
And the other?
Just let it go.
Let it fly.
Into the vast sky.
Just let it fly.
Got it?
If not, think it over carefully.
What did my uncle tell you?
He said you're dumb.
I'm not.
People used to say you were dumb.
I didn't think so.
Now I think you're dumb.
Still saying you're not?
Then why skip Provincial Qinqiang Troupe?
I want to go.
I'll get into the Provincial Qinqiang Troupe
and leave this mountain valley.
You head there first.
Settle in and wait for me.
If you leave, they might cancel the play.
Look.
Is it nice?
It is.
For a silkworm to become a butterfly,
it must survive countless hardships.
How bitter it is, what it truly feels like,
only the butterfly itself knows.
I understand that.
I once raised silkworms.
You're raising one again.
So are Gou Cunzhong,
Cunchao, the others…
We're all doing our best to turn this kid
into a beautiful butterfly.
"Fierce the west wind,
wild geese cry beneath
the frost-lit dawn moon.
Beneath that frosty moon,
hoofbeats scatter,
bugles choke in the night.
The mighty pass stretches on, hard as iron."
Chairman Mao's
Yi Qin'e · Loushan Pass.
Fits this moment perfectly.
Yi Qing'e?
Yi Qin'e
is an old ci-poetry tune title.
Li Qingzhao and Li Bai
both wrote
immortal lines under that title.
"Yi" means remembrance.
"Qin", the Qin Mountains.
"E"… the same "E" from Yi Qing'e.
How about we use Yi Qin'e
as the kid's stage name?
Good. You tell her.
Kid!
Kid.
You're about to set off.
Your uncle and I want
to give you a stage name.
It may bring you good luck.
Yi Qin'e is an old ci-poetry tune title.
You can also think of it as meaning
"a woman of Qin who sings opera".
From now on, your name is Yi Qin'e.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
I have your word.
Get into the Provincial Troupe.
Qin'e!
A ghost that won't go away?
"He was the root of disaster."
Watch your accents!
Let her rest for a bit?
I can fill in.
No dormitory?
(Ice Pops, Shuipen Yangrou)
Qin'e!
Opera tickets!
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪