( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 22=
(Castration of pigs, cattle and
donkeys and veterinary care)
I thought breeding meant
taking animals to the breeding station.
But look at you.
Leading bulls and male donkeys around,
looking everywhere for females.
It's the busy farming season.
All the animals are working in the fields.
Who has time for the breeding station?
So we have to make house calls.
Good thing they are animals.
Sanyuan.
Tonight, try my cooking.
Braised pig testicles.
They'll be amazing.
You've never had anything like it.
What are you writing?
A drum score.
What drum score?
Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
The troupe dropped you.
And you still won't give up?
After years inside, I realized
the world outside had changed.
Back when I went in,
people just wanted enough to eat.
So much time has passed.
Now, everyone was shouting,
"Boost business and get rich."
Now, everywhere you look,
people are chasing money.
Stop clinging to those drumsticks.
Find a new way to live, fast.
You can breed donkeys,
do pig castration...
Besides the two drumsticks,
what else do I know?
Then go tap people's backs.
I can't live off that.
These are for fire breathing.
Starting today,
during the day, you do Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
At night, we four do Gui Yuan Sha Sheng.
No one else can watch.
But you must stay right by me.
Fire breathing is the
Dan role's secret skill.
You have to master it.
Remember,
never panic during fire breathing.
Once you hold this in your mouth,
sink your qi to the dantian.
Use abdominal breathing.
Keep your breath under control.
And the plosive sounds.
Watch.
Whatever you do, don't panic.
♪Dear son, you softly beg♪
♪To go to battle♪
♪If you have real skill♪
♪Mother won't worry♪
♪I ponder secretly in my heart♪
♪My mind is made up♪
♪Competing on the training ground♪
♪I hold back a bit for my son♪
Stop, stop.
What do you
think about your performance?
It was okay.
It was bad.
Why was it bad?
I don't know.
Are you seeing someone?
No.
Tell the truth.
I'm not.
Do you have a crush on someone?
No.
You don't like Feng Xiaoxiao?
Why do we call eyes "lamps"?
Through them, I can see into your heart.
What's in your heart
is plain
as day.
You can fool no one.
When you played the scene,
from the look alone
wasn't Mu Guiying and Yang Wenguang.
It was Mu Guiying and Yang Zongbao.
A mother-son bond
was turned into a loving couple by you two.
The eye training
was to clear stray thoughts
and keep your mind on the play alone.
But you
got even more stray thoughts.
You're still young.
You mustn't date.
I'm not dating anyone.
Stop arguing.
Before you become a star performer,
you must only care about acting.
Nothing else is allowed.
Do you hear me?
Answer me.
Know why?
They will hold you back.
♪I came down from the mountains♪
♪Carrying orchid grass♪
♪I planted it in my little garden♪
♪Hoping it would bloom soon♪
♪I checked on it three times a day♪
♪Watching it as the days went by♪
♪Yet the orchid still♪
♪Had not a single bud♪
Looking for me?
Wait...
Why are you ignoring me?
What did I do wrong?
What did Chu Jiahe say to you?
Tell me.
Tell me, or I'll go ask her.
I... I'm going.
She didn't say anything.
I did.
What did you say?
I said I won't fight her for Mu Guiying.
But she can't steal you from me.
Yi Qing'e.
Yi Qing'e!
I also said
that you're already mine.
I won't give you up to her.
Since when am I yours?
Didn't we go roller skating together?
Didn't I sing while you played?
Didn't we watch movies together?
Didn't you eat my candy?
Or meat from my bowl?
Hey!
Being close isn't the same as dating!
What you think and I think differ.
If I say we're dating, we are.
Why are you so unreasonable?
My reasons are all that matter.
You don't have to be with me.
You can be with someone else.
But you can't be with her.
Why?
Who I choose is none of your business.
She wants rice,
and she wants Mo too.
All the good things
can't all go to her alone.
A dog said that.
Dog?
Is that what I meant?
Did I mean it like that?
Was that my point?
Yi Qing'e.
Well, I did say that.
But that's not what I meant.
I meant those girls.
Yi Qing'e.
You should go.
Don't play here anymore.
What's wrong?
Did she scare you?
You were so bold as a kid.
Catching snakes, fighting Er Laizi.
Why have you grown more timid?
It has nothing to do with her.
"Nothing to do with her"?
There's someone else?
My master.
Which master?
Master Gou.
What did he tell you?
Tell me.
How about this?
If you tell me,
I'll never play here again.
He said my heart must hold only opera.
Nothing else is allowed in.
♪Horses race, startled birds cry♪
♪Winding roads fade into empty hills♪
- ♪All the way♪
- Stop!
Yi Qing'e, Feng Xiaoxiao,
and Chu Jiahe!
What's going on with you?
Sleepy?
Everyone else is doing fine.
Except the three of you.
You're flat and totally lifeless.
What's on your mind?
Everyone else, take a break.
You three, stay right there
and get your focus back!
When you do, we'll continue.
If you can't,
you'll keep standing there!
What's going on?
It was just one.
Now all three have issues.
How would I know?
I only taught Yi Qing'e.
I didn't teach the other two.
You taught her that?
What even was that?
Look at you.
Do you have to be so angry?
All right, all right.
Ignore that old coot.
What kind of mess is this?
Just look at them.
No spark inside, none in their eyes.
Hu Sanyuan?
Why are you back?
- What?
- Take it.
What is it?
The Yang Men Nyu Jiang drum score.
Give it a try.
What?
Teaching me the drums?
- Let's eat first.
- Okay.
Come with me.
You needed me, Master Gou?
There's a rule for trainees.
No dating allowed.
You know that, right?
I know.
How serious are you two?
Us two? Me and who?
Yi Qing'e.
We're not dating.
Chu Jiahe likes you, too, right?
You can't fool me.
I'm not fooling anyone.
I don't care if you date Chu Jiahe.
But not Yi Qing'e.
I don't like Chu Jiahe.
You can't like Yi Qing'e either!
Why not?
In Yi Qing'e's heart,
there's no room for two things.
You can tell from her acting
these past few days.
Who says we can only act
and can't date?
It's not that you can't.
Just not right now.
Her heart must stay with the play,
and with the role.
Plump.
Your bowl.
Yeah.
I never imagined that kid
would make it this far.
When I brought her out,
I just wanted her to have food,
and ease my sister's burden.
Who would've thought?
The kid owes you.
I owe you too.
I'll never forget it.
You've got that wrong.
You brought the kid out.
So even at my age,
I finally did something right.
Where's the old Hu Sanyuan?
You're still the same
Master Gu I always looked
up to.
When I heard you came out early,
I wondered where to find you.
Director Gu, look.
Now he's back, no need to worry.
The past few days,
He Dachui's drum
had him too worried to sleep.
I've written the drum score.
I came here
to give He Dachui the drum score.
That won't help at all.
Even if you carve it on the drum,
he still won't play it right.
From now on,
you play the drum for us.
Yeah.
I need to head back soon.
I've got work to do.
What kind of work?
Pig castration.
What?
Mother, if you don't lose,
I won't be able to serve the country.
Please show mercy and let me go.
- Mother...
- Stop.
Yi Qing'e.
What's wrong with you?
We've rehearsed this
for days.
You're drifting further off.
Each take gets worse!
Where are your eyes looking?
Yang Wenguang is right there.
Why look at Yang Qiniang?
Kid, stay focused in rehearsal.
Don't let your eyes wander.
Mr. Dachui.
What?
Could you
play it from this drum score?
Why?
No reason.
Just try it.
See how it feels.
What did you even draw here?
I can't read it.
I can't play this.
I just can't.
I can't.
Rehearsal over!
Since Hu Sanyuan is back,
I want him on drums for this show.
He can't do it.
Just because he went to prison?
For this show, He Dachui has been
practicing really hard
to sharpen his skills.
I heard it.
He's not that far off.
What he lacks isn't skills.
It's not about his hands.
A man who can't accept one drum score
lacks vision and heart.
Let me make this clear.
Even if he drums himself into the ground,
he still can't play the spirit
of Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
If we
only performed in our county,
letting He Dachui play would be fine.
But don't forget,
we're going to the Beishan Showcase.
Experts in the whole region
and the whole province will be there.
And our kids
are just a bunch of rookies anyway.
Even Yi Qing'e
has been really inconsistent lately.
If the band drags them down,
what to do?
Anyway,
this is your first show in charge.
Let's sit down and talk.
Sit down first.
You think I don't want
Hu Sanyuan on drums?
I want him back in the troupe too.
But I can't decide.
You run the troupe
but can't decide?
Are you just a shrine idol?
Only good for prayers and incense?
That's enough. Drop it.
Watch your mouth.
Loose talk brings trouble.
That's true anytime.
You forgot?
Yi Qing'e stars or Hu Sanyuan drums.
You can only have one. Who?
Why only one?
Answer me first.
Yi Qing'e.
Then Hu has to step aside.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Anyone but Yi Qing'e
can play Mu Guiying,
and Hu can still drum.
That's it.
What do you mean?
I don't get it.
Yi Qing'e and Chu Jiahe are competing.
Yi Qing'e already has the upper hand.
Think about it.
Now,
if her uncle, just freed, drums for her,
how can the kid perform later?
Now, even if I ask Hu Sanyuan to drum,
he won't say yes.
Step back to move forward.
That's how we protect Yi Qing'e.
Her uncle
understands that.
(Boys' Dorm)
Master, your breathing sounds worse.
This juice boiled from elm bark
does wonders for the sideburns.
Flat and smooth.
Neat, sleek, and well-shaped.
It slims chubby faces, plumps thin ones.
Mr. Gou.
With the sideburns on,
you'd look gorgeous.
Maybe back then.
Now, even if you stuck
an elm all over my face,
it won't help.
(Restaurant)
(It is a glorious, great cause)
This is all I can afford.
Waiter.
Bring us your best bottle.
Coming right up.
I can't afford it.
Then why treat me?
Come on, talk.
What's the matter?
Did you read the drum score?
I tore it up.
Right, I was reckless.
I shouldn't have given it there.
You get it all wrong.
Try me anywhere you want.
It ends the same. I tear it up.
Don't you get it?
You listen, Hu Sanyuan.
Nail's life
and your years of suffering in prison.
Wasn't that enough
for you to drop the bad habit?
Can't you just change?
You listen,
you're not the old Hu Sanyuan,
and I'm not the old He Dachui either.
Act tough with others if you want,
but not with me.
I'm already being polite.
You're still the same He Dachui.
Not one bit has changed.
Come on.
How is that?
Know why you can never beat me?
Why?
You take me too seriously.
Who takes you seriously?
Can you be
more like Hu Sanyuan than me?
How could you possibly beat me?
Your technique isn't bad at all.
You're just focusing on the wrong thing.
Keep an open mind.
Think long-term.
Now that I've quit playing,
in our county and the Beishan Region,
who can outplay you?
- You're right.
- If you get stuck,
just ask me.
Why would I ask you?
I'll tell you.
I'm not playing anymore.
What are you afraid of?
Listen to you.
You still sound better than me.
You're lecturing me?
Come on, cheers.
Think long-term.
Mother, if you don't lose...
Stop.
That's not on me, right?
I was following your
nose-wiping tissue beat.
Are we rehearsing?
Can we still rehearse?
(Script)
What to do?
Say something.
We've run this scene for days.
The kid's getting worse.
We're running out of time.
We can't stay stuck here.
I want Chu Jiahe as Mu Guiying.
No way.
Why not?
Chu Jiahe isn't Mu Guiying.
With Yi Qing'e's current state,
she's even less like Mu Guiying!
You don't know Dan, so keep quiet.
Fine, you know Dan.
Then get her into the zone!
We can't have the whole crew run it
with her over and over again!
If this keeps up,
everyone will be exhausted and lose
their momentum!
Everyone has off days.
I was in a worse state back then.
Few are as carefree as you,
always so pumped up,
forgetting everything else on stage.
Don't get sidetracked.
Focus!
What to do now?
Go straight to dress rehearsal.
Strapped on
the opera armor, she'll have no choice.
Look at him!
Never seen someone so fiercely protective!
Okay, good.
Holding someone in your heart...
That feeling...
I know it well.
My first time in the opera armor,
I was about your age.
When I was ten,
my family was too poor to feed me.
They sent me to the opera troupe.
I was short and frail.
Master had me learn the Dan role.
When I was about your age,
I also had someone in my heart.
Whether eating or sleeping,
she was all I could
think about.
For a long while,
I couldn't sing a scene right.
Even Master's harsh blows did nothing.
That day,
Master put me in the opera armor too.
Once I wore that costume
and stood near the stage,
I suddenly felt
like I could command the world.
What I carried inside
wasn't just one person.
It held a whole army.
Remember,
you're not Yi Qing'e.
You are Mu Guiying.
Today's meeting
is a pre-battle rally.
After this,
our whole troupe is going to Beishan
for the regional arts showcase.
They call it an arts showcase,
but really, across the whole region,
eleven troupes will
compete in Qinqiang opera.
The County Party Committee and Government
are taking this showcase
very seriously.
They even got us
a big coach just for the trip.
We no longer have to
choke on wind and dust
on the way to our shows.
Our troupe was built
on the old opera company
thirty years ago.
We once had countless glory days.
But for all kinds of reasons,
we once reached a point with no shows.
But today,
under the Party's leadership,
and with our veteran artists' efforts,
our whole troupe has united,
and we're about to leave winter behind
and welcome a new spring!
Liu Ke.
She called you.
Let's switch seats.
Why?
Just switch.
Why asking?
Just do it. Get up.
Please, sit.
Play well.
Why looking at me?
Keep playing.
Master Gou.
Look behind you.
♪Winnow, winnow, winnowing buckwheat♪
♪Winnow, winnow, one, two, hey♪
♪A girl's winnowing buckwheat by the door♪
♪Down the road comes a silly fellow♪
♪He says, "Young girl, go slow"♪
♪"Let me pass by your front door"♪
♪Winnow, winnow, one, two, hey♪
♪A girl's winnowing buckwheat by the door♪
♪Down the road comes a silly fellow♪
♪He says, "Young girl, go slow"♪
♪"Let me pass by your front door"♪
♪Hey-yo, hey-yo♪
♪Hey now, hey now, yo♪
Sanyuan.
I hear the County Troupe's going to Beishan.
Your niece will be onstage.
Why not go to watch?
I'll go.
Then
why hang around with me?
I'll go tomorrow.
Move aside.
That's the troupe's van.
- Master Song!
- Pull over!
Pull over!
Sanyuan? What are you here?
That's Hu Sanyuan.
How's it going?
Heading to Beishan for the show?
Yeah.
Can I come with you?
Sure. Hop in.
- Come here.
- Hop in.
Here, here.
I'm getting in.
Get in from the back.
- Okay, okay.
- Careful.
- Help me up.
- Master Hu, why here?
- Make room.
- Come on.
Sit, sit.
Let's go.
I was thinking,
it's Qing'e's performance,
how could you miss it?
Of course, I'll be there.
Sanyuan!
Get me a ticket!
I'll come find you then.
Here, take this straw hat.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
My last show was right here.
My consecutive fire-breathing
went badly.
Harder!
You're always
the best Dan actor.
Too weak. Stronger, stronger.
Why don't you do it?
Move, move.
Listen to me.
For fire breathing, just take it easy.
Don't push yourself.
Remember that.
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪