( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 20=
Troupe Leader.
Still up this late?
Aren't you the same?
Hard to sleep alone.
Let's chat then.
People are strange creatures.
Before, I wanted to leave
this place, but couldn't.
Now that I can leave,
I suddenly feel lost.
What's there to feel lost about?
The troupe is your home.
Come back and visit at any time.
I won't come back here again.
I'm not welcome here.
Who said that?
You're more than welcome here.
I know where I stand.
Zhu.
You've been through a lot over the years.
What are you talking about?
Not at all.
Do you believe in fate?
Life
is just a game of chess.
And we're just the pieces.
How the pieces move
is all predetermined.
If you play the knight,
you can only move in an L-shape.
If I play the bishop,
I can only move diagonally.
There's no other choice.
Right.
You are right.
Zhu.
All you ever say
to me is just "right".
Right about what?
If I had a notebook, I'd write it down.
(Hongqi)
I'll leave this notebook for you too.
Hope it helps with your work.
Focus on the issue, not the person.
Right.
(Xinhua Dictionary)
(Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Come back and visit when you have time.
I will.
Please take care.
Stay strong.
Keep singing.
Yi Qing'e,
you'll be a big star someday.
Back then, your uncle
entrusted you to my care.
But I can't protect you anymore.
You must protect yourself now.
Mi Lan left.
She went to the distant south.
Watching the car drive away,
Yi Qing'e suddenly realized
the place she found outside Jiuyangou
was the very mountain trapping Mi Lan.
Go.
It's uphill. I'll get off first.
- Okay. Easy now.
- Let me help.
- I'm fine.
- Let's go.
One, two, go!
Come on, lend a hand.
Master Gou.
Thank you!
Goodbye.
Goodbye. Master Gou, goodbye.
Who is it?
(Entrance Guard)
Huang Zhengjing also left.
He left empty-handed.
Not a single thing from the troupe
did he take with him.
A tricycle and a bicycle
carried away all his belongings.
Yi Qing'e just didn't expect that
the one lighting firecrackers
was his most trusted
Head of Security Section.
The higher-ups made me
the acting Troupe Director.
Acting?
Temporarily acting.
The troupe is finally back in our hands.
Nonsense.
What does it have to do with us?
The troupe is back in expert hands.
Trouple Leader Zhu,
congratulations.
Since you're the new boss now,
let's start rehearsing right away
the full play of Yang Pai Feng,
shall we?
We can't.
Why not?
Don't you call the shots in the troupe?
Huang Zhengjing was right.
That Da Jiao Zan was
like a stone stirring up a thousand waves.
The response has been extremely strong.
Especially among the girls
in our trainee class.
Some of
their parents are local officials.
Regarding the kitchen girl Yi Qing'e
being the lead in Da Jiao Zan,
they're demanding answers.
And
they're also seriously questioning
why their girls,
after years of training,
are unable to get on stage.
For what?
What do you mean?
The troupe will keep rotting like this?
What kind of talk is that?
We rot if we don't do Yang Pai Feng?
I want Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
You must be dreaming.
Let Trouple Leader Zhu finish speaking.
Yang Men Nyu Jiang would be
a grand production.
It requires a lot of actors.
Mu Guiying, Eighth Sister, Ninth Sister...
Just the Widow Army alone
would give all the girls a chance
to perform.
First, we can resolve internal conflicts
to give county leaders an explanation.
Second,
all the actors in this play
will be elected from our trainee class.
Taking this opportunity
to train new blood for our troupe,
so these kids
can see new hope for our troupe.
Trouple Leader Zhu,
you are living in a fantasy.
To turn these amateur kids
into true professionals,
how much effort
will that take?
Plus, there is a catch.
These kids must be able
to endure hardship.
You nailed it.
Yi Qing'e didn't suffer for nothing.
And these kids have seen it all.
I'm telling you,
these kids are scrambling right now
to go work in the kitchen.
These kids have been training for years.
They do have some basic skills.
Let's encourage them,
give them a refresher,
and be strict with them.
I think it'll work out.
I agree.
It's settled then.
You four go and think carefully about how
to handle this.
Then report back to me,
so I can report to the county leaders.
Then it's settled.
By the way,
I'll return Yi Qing'e to the trainee class.
She'll live and train with the trainees.
No need to teach her privately anymore.
Most importantly,
don't call each other master and apprentice.
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
Our trainee class has 28 kids.
They are all your students.
Treat them equally
to avoid any new conflicts.
Show off your skills?
Don't make too much.
Or the three of us can't finish it all.
Knife skills are crucial, you know?
Cutting potatoes...
You're cutting so fast.
When did you practice this?
Being fast isn't enough.
Watch your hands
and cut them evenly.
You...
They're actually very even.
I know why you said
you'd show off your skills to us.
The wok is already so hot.
You need to add oil first.
Hot wok, cold oil.
What kind of cooking method is that?
Looking good.
Have a taste.
How is it?
Delicious, huh?
Attention, attention!
I have an announcement!
Shut up.
Open your mouth.
Taste it.
Delicious.
You didn't cook it.
- Laidi cooked it.
- How is it?
I taught her!
Can a lousy master teach a good student?
A lousy master like you
can train such a good apprentice.
What's so strange about that?
You're talking nonsense.
You are talking nonsense.
Kid.
Great cooking.
This is the first dish you cooked,
and it's also your last.
What do you mean?
The troupe has decided,
starting today,
you're back to the trainee class!
Awesome!
Qiu, that's good news!
It's great!
Stop posing there.
Laidi,
what's wrong?
I'm not going.
Why?
I just don't want to.
I'm staying right here.
You'd pass up such a great opportunity
and be stuck in the kitchen forever?
- Why's this kid so silly?
- Exactly.
I'm not silly. I'm not going anywhere.
No. It's the troupe's call, not yours.
Why should I go wherever you tell me to?
Why should I do whatever you say?
I'm not going.
I'd rather die than go.
I won't be bossed around anymore.
Kid, you can't perform if you refuse!
I'm not performing!
I never wanted to!
I was forced!
I'll just tend the kitchen fire forever!
(Boiled water)
What is the kid thinking?
What the kid thinks,
does anyone really care?
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll stay in the kitchen.
The kitchen is my home.
Master Song.
Don't kick me out.
Please.
Please, Master Song.
Kid.
Singing opera
is your true calling.
I don't want to leave.
I don't want to leave
(Men; Boiled water)
Did you talk to the kid?
I did.
She reacted very strongly.
She'd rather quit singing
than leave the kitchen.
Qing'e must return to the trainee class.
This is non-negotiable.
Why?
I told you the reason.
No wiggle room?
Wiggle room for what?
It's for her own good.
More like for your own good.
What good will I get?
What good?
So you can give everyone an explanation.
I'm the acting Troupe Director now.
Of course, I must consider all sides.
What are you scoffing at?
We sent away one Huang Zhengjing,
only to get a Zhu Zhengjing.
- What do you mean?
- What do I mean?
Huang Zhengjing made her leave the class.
Now you insist she go back to the class.
What's the difference between you two?
How is that the same?
How is it different?
You both just want to avoid trouble.
Who ever considered the kid's feelings?
So, why won't she go back to the class?
Why?
She's looked down on in the trainee class.
Always living at the mercy of others.
Who knows how much she has suffered?
She only feels warm in the kitchen.
She only feels safe when sleeping
in that storeroom.
Now you want to take the only
sense of security she has?
How will she survive?
Besides,
we are her masters.
Legitimate masters!
What's there to hide?
Why are you crying?
Don't laugh at me.
I just started
learning guitar.
I dare not play in front of crowds.
Mind if I use your spot?
Who is it?
It's me.
Master.
I've talked to them.
You'll still live here
and stay on the kitchen staff.
But you'll join the other kids
to train and rehearse.
There's a new play.
Your acting and acrobatic skills are okay.
Now focus on your vocal skills.
You can't just be a Wudan forever.
Relax. Sink your breath to the Dantian.
Tighten your
core.
Focus your breath here.
Don't just use your belly.
Breathe from your chest.
Open up.
You know? Open up. Come on.
♪The wind howls♪
♪So bleak♪
Hit that pitch right away.
It falls flat right away, kid.
Your voice falls flat.
♪Horses dash, birds scatter♪
Laidi.
I just learned something.
Watch me do it.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
Don't move!
Let me catch my breath.
Just let me catch my breath.
You can't do flips all by yourself.
That's how Heiwa had his accident.
We were just kids.
We've grown up now.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I've caught my breath now.
You work really hard.
Getting up so early to start the fire.
Practice something else.
Stop doing flips.
Sure.
You... you have to teach me.
Please?
Do you...
Do you take apprentices?
Just stop doing flips.
Come on, teach me.
If you don't teach me, I'll do flips.
I'll do it.
What is Dan?
Dan
is a red sun
rising above the horizon.
Dan
is the heart of the play.
Dan is the finishing touch.
Dan is a beacon on the stage.
Dan
isn't just a pretty face.
Dan also requires acting.
What is acting?
It's your unique essence.
So,
you must practice tirelessly
and train hard
to blend your essence and beauty
seamlessly together.
The bow stance.
The right hand. Make a fist.
- Two, three...
- Go.
- Eyes, eyes.
- Keep this leg straight.
Straighten the left leg.
- Hands higher.
- Not like this!
Use your waist. Your expression.
One, two, one.
One, two, one. One...
- Go.
- Faster.
Good. Come on, go.
Power, power, power.
Good.
Come on.
Three, nod.
Don't lose your position.
Back, back, back.
The footwork.
- It's about finesse.
- With me.
Girl, faster. Faster.
Straighten up. Go.
- Go.
- Good.
- Yes, yes.
- Go.
Go.
Good.
Much better.
My frozen shoulder is acting up.
Feels so good.
What kind of technique is this?
Jijifeng.
I heard the guys in your cell line up
shirtless every night, waiting for you
to tap their backs.
The vet's acupoints plus my technique.
Those guys are used to it.
They ache all over if I skip a few days.
That sounds like a hassle.
If you leave, no one will tap my back.
Ma Wuqi can do it now too.
Really?
Yeah.
Let me tell you something.
Your sentence reduction was approved.
Why did you stop?
(Beishan to Ningzhou)
We're at Erdaoliang.
Take your belongings and get off.
I'm getting off.
Careful.
(Beishan to Ningzhou)
(Entrance Guard)
Morning, Master Gou.
Morning.
I have good news for you.
I talked to the Head of Security Section.
You won't need to guard the gate anymore.
Focus on rehearsing with the other masters.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not going anywhere.
The gatehouse is fine.
Why?
I feel settled here.
Used to living here, huh?
All right.
Do what makes you feel settled.
A few words.
The kids in our troupe
have been rehearsing for a while.
What do you think of Chu Jiahe?
Brain, fast.
Eyes, lively.
Skills, shaky.
What about Yi Qing'e?
Brain, slow.
Eyes, bright.
Skills, solid.
How are their vocal skills?
Chu Jiahe has a good pitch.
Sweet voice, but narrow range.
Yi Qing'e sings crisply.
Broad and loud voice.
For Yang Men Nyu Jiang,
our troupe will start rehearsals soon.
I was thinking,
for the role of Mu Guiying...
Yi Qing'e.
Personal feelings aside,
among the kids in the troupe,
to play Mu Guiying,
Yi Qing'e is number one.
Chu Jiahe is second.
There are no small roles.
Isn't Qi Niang's role also important?
Wouldn't Qing'e fit?
Is it because she's from Cunjia Troupe?
That's not the main reason.
Then what is it?
We'll talk about it
at the meeting.
(Cast for Yang Men Nyu Jiang)
Why isn't Master Qiu here yet?
He went for groceries. No need to wait.
As for the generals' opera
armor, how many sets
are we short of?
Eleven for the female generals.
Two for Meng Liang and Jiao Zan.
One is enough for the enemy general.
I agree that
Yi Qing'e is best suited for Mu Guiying.
We can ignore the Cunjia Troupe issue
and not care about those kids
fighting over roles.
Right now, for
the opera armor,
we are 14 sets short.
We only have two sets, both ruined.
We can't just let the kids
wear modern clothes
to play ancient people on stage, can we?
I don't get what you mean.
If Chu Jiahe plays Mu Guiying,
will the issue be solved?
Chu Jiahe's dad
is the Deputy County Magistrate for finance.
So?
Magistrate Chu said
he'll solve the troupe's costume funding.
As a father,
he also told me very tactfully
to have the troupe value Jiahe more.
I think it's understandable.
Right?
Let me ask you.
Who's greater, the county leader
or Heaven?
I really don't follow you.
On our first day of learning opera,
what the master taught us was that
the play is greater than Heaven.
But without costumes,
how can they perform? Which matters more?
Still, we can't stoop so low
just for costumes.
Here's what I think.
Set a piece for the two kids.
Let them perform, then we'll decide.
Will that work?
I think it will.
Qing'e.
Master Gou is looking for you.
Okay, got it.
♪My lady♪
Master, you wanted to see me?
The troupe is staging Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
Mu Guiying will be you or Chu Jiahe.
Master Gu picked a scene that tests
singing, reciting, acting and acrobatics.
You both act it out.
We all watch.
I've highlighted it for you.
Memorize your lines and lyrics early.
Okay, I got it.
Also,
run lines with Feng Xiaoxiao
and think carefully
about how to perform.
In this scene,
after all the Yang family men died in battle,
Mu Guiying's son, Yang Wenguang, became
the only man left in the family.
He wants to go to battle
with the female generals.
But he's too young.
She Taijun disagrees.
She asks him to duel Mu Guiying.
If he defeats her,
he can go to battle.
Twenty-nine.
Careful.
Look.
What's this?
What?
A script.
(Qinqiang Opera Script
for Yang Men Nyu Jiang)
I know. What about it?
Look.
Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
Yang Wenguang.
Me.
Aren't you smug?
What kind of role is it?
He's Taijun's great-grandson.
Yang Liulang's grandson.
Mu Guiying's son.
That's a complicated family tree.
Is it a major role?
It's alright.
Just the male lead.
Look at you, so smug.
What about me?
You?
I saw it on the board.
Just like before.
One of the crowd.
Still an extra.
Then who plays Mu Guiying?
Yi Qing'e and Chu Jiahe.
Why two Mu Guiyings?
Director Gu chose a scene.
He wants me to act with both of them.
He'll probably choose one of them later.
He's picking a mom for you.
Which mom do you want?
I don't care.
Really?
I don't care!
- Really?
- Really!
Don't lie to me.
I'm not lying to you, really.
Your mom is here.
Feng Xiaoxiao,
let's find a place to run lines.
Run lines!
I'm starting, Laidi.
Mother,
I must avenge Father.
If you don't go easy on me,
how can I fight the enemy?
Mother,
please go easy on your son.
Besides, how could I ever beat you?
♪Dear son, you softly beg to go to war♪
♪If you have real skill, I won't worry♪
Even the pigs are running lines now?
♪We compete on the training ground♪
You can run lines with them.
♪I will go easy on you, son♪
Watch my spear!
It's okay. I've got you.
One more time.
Zhou Yuzhi.
Jiahe.
Stage combat.
Didn't you go practice with Feng Xiaoxiao?
Did he go practice with that dummy?
Did he really fall for that dummy?
No way.
Jiahe! Jiahe!
It's me!
Not that dummy!
Jiahe! Jiahe!
It's me, Zhou Yuzhi!
Let's stop here for today.
Mother!
Your dear son is leaving.
If you get hungry later,
just dig right here
for baked potatoes.
- Here.
- Okay.
Go to bed early.
I'm already hungry.
I saved one for you.
Mother,
the potato got burnt.
What should I do?
It's fine.
It's still edible.
Eat.
But how?
It's good.
It's really good.
You're still up?
Open the door.
Who is it?
It's me, Chu Jiahe.
Open the door.
I need to talk to you.
Wait a second.
What is it?
Can I come in first?
I went too far that day.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong before.
Let's make up, okay?
From now on, we'll be good friends.
We'll shop together,
practice together...
okay?
Okay?
I'll just take that as a yes.
Alright.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
Fire breathing is a signature
skill of Qinqiang opera.
He wants to spit out that very last
mouthful of flame.
Let's join forces.
One lead role for each of us.
Deal?
Trading roles for favors?
Selling the role?
You learn the lesson!
Qing'e!
Hurry out here! Look who's back!
How can you live here?
If anyone's been bullying you, tell me!
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪