( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 23=
Listen up, everyone.
Time for the walk-through.
Let's prep this afternoon.
The show is tomorrow night.
Things are different now.
This isn't the stage we used to know.
It's newly built.
It's so wide and spacious.
It's a beautiful stage to perform on.
But it's still the same play.
We're still the actors.
It's just
that our hair has gone gray,
and our teeth are falling out.
I have a feeling.
The stage will be your lucky place.
Just let me in.
No, no. This is backstage.
No outsiders allowed.
I'm not an outsider.
I'm with the troupe.
Do you have a staff ID?
I used to.
That was the past. Do you have one now?
He Dachui.
Quick, quick.
Tell him to let me in.
Hu Sanyuan, why are you here?
It's my niece's play. I had to come.
You want to go in?
Hurry up and tell him.
What are you going in for?
I promise you I won't touch the drums.
I'll just stand behind you.
I can serve you tea and water, okay?
Is that okay?
Come on, hurry.
One show tomorrow, one the next day.
Which play comes first?
Yang Men Nyu Jiang.
Gui Yuan Sha Sheng.
Are you sure?
Gui Yuan Sha Sheng, then.
Alright.
Gui Yuan Sha Sheng.
(Beishan Theater)
(Beishan opera excerpt:
Gui Yuan Sha Sheng)
Sanyuan is back.
You must be playing today.
Who said that?
I'll play.
Right, right.
Come on, come on.
I just let it cool down.
Okay, I'll put it down.
Come on.
Do you know why
we're doing Gui Yuan Sha Sheng first?
My last show back then was right here.
The last three bursts
of fire didn't come out.
I blew it.
Master Qiu told me that.
Remember:
The fire-breathing powder
must be ground by yourself,
mixed by yourself,
and packed by yourself.
The formula and ratio
must never be shared with anyone.
Got it.
Harder.
Pull harder.
Good.
You look beautiful.
Pat me on the back.
A childhood habit.
You still haven't outgrown it.
Don't be nervous.
No matter when,
you're always the best Dan role.
(Beishan Regional Showcase)
♪So bitter♪
Steady.
Opera isn't sung for people.
It's sung for the heavens.
♪Resentment rises♪
♪Three thousand feet high♪
♪Wronged souls are filled with rage♪
Your master is amazing.
Too weak. Stronger, stronger.
Why are you yelling, water boy?
- You do it then.
- Move.
♪Alas, in my prime♪
♪I lost my life♪
♪Gritting teeth in hate for the culprit♪
Your uncle.
Great.
Bravo.
Gou.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Listen to me.
For fire breathing,
just do what you can.
- Don't force it.
- Okay.
Remember.
Hurry on stage. Don't worry about me.
Go now.
Where are you going!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Twenty.
Twenty-one.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three.
Twenty-four, twenty-five, twenty-six.
Twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine.
(Beishan Theater)
Gou.
That's enough.
Stop it.
Seventy-nine.
Eighty.
Eighty-one!
Excuse me. Please make way.
Close the curtain!
Cunzhong!
Gou!
Cunzhong! Cunzhong!
Cunzhong!
Curtain call!
A chair! Bring a chair!
Hurry! Bring a chair!
Gou!
Cunzhong!
Cunzhong! Gou!
Come on, make way!
(Mortuary)
The doctor said
it was sudden cardiac death.
They found a lot of foreign matter
in his mouth and nose.
It was all sawdust and rosin.
Let's discuss
how to handle this.
So, no one's talking, huh?
Tomorrow,
I'll tell the organizing committee
to delay the show for two days.
Let him rest in peace first.
Tomorrow night's show
will go on as usual.
I agree.
I agree too.
I can't sing tomorrow.
Then let Gou wait.
When you finish this play,
we'll lay him to rest.
(Mortuary)
Why don't you head back to the hotel?
The kid and I'll keep vigil
for Master Gou.
I'll talk to her.
Just head back first.
Alright then.
I'll be heading back.
Come here.
Come burn joss paper for Master Gou.
(Mortuary)
Do you know why Master Gu
had you finish singing
before laying Master Gou to rest?
He wanted Master Gou to listen,
so he'd know his legacy would live on.
For Master Gou's entire life,
nothing mattered more
than Qinqiang opera.
Qinqiang opera was his life.
Do you know why Master Gou
performed first?
It's a warm-up act.
It's to warm up the stage.
In the opera troupes of the past,
when you arrive at a new place,
you first need to warm up the crowd
to build momentum
for the lead
and the finale.
It's an opening act,
like a stepping stone.
If Yang Men Nyu Jiang succeeds,
you'll stand on their shoulders.
They are the ones who lift you up.
In our line of work,
this is the greatest favor.
Never forget it.
(Beishan Theater)
♪The wind howls♪
♪The mist is thick♪
♪The starlight is dim♪
♪Horses gallop; birds are startled♪
♪The winding mountain road is desolate♪
♪On the way here, the sky darkens♪
♪The moon somehow rises in the east♪
Great!
Bravo!
♪The wind blows♪
♪Blowing sand strikes the face♪
♪Fog obscures
the endless withered grass♪
♪Cutting through thorns
to the southeast♪
Your turn.
Come on, hurry.
♪Only after bloom♪
♪Comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder♪
♪Do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪Only by swallowing the rumors♪
♪Do you truly shine♪
♪Who made the raging flames
so scorching♪
♪Only by soaking in bitterness♪
♪Is your life as tough as rock♪
♪After all,
your pure light stings like salt♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪Only those who lead♪
♪Take arrows from behind♪
♪After all, your steps are so light♪
♪Only a broken string♪
♪Can echo through the sky♪
♪After all,
only the echo shakes the roof♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪The moon is so high in the sky♪
♪On a white horse over the stone bridge♪
♪Curved bridge reflects the mountains♪
♪Myriad lights share the reunion♪
♪Yi Qin'e, you'll rise high♪
♪Train with red silk; walk on stilts♪
♪Stilts sway onstage♪
♪Singing joys and sorrows to the skies♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe's
Yang Men Nyu Jiang was a hit)
(Tomb of Gou Cunzhong,
erected by all of Ningzhou County)
Today is your first seventh-day.
We came to see you.
Cunzhong,
we
can only go with you this far.
Don't be afraid.
(Tomb of Gou Cunzhong)
With Master
and the brothers there,
you won't be lonely.
When you see them,
greet them for us.
What should we do?
I'm leaving tomorrow.
It's time for us to bow out.
Master,
where are you going?
To the provincial troupe.
They're rehearsing old plays too.
They asked me to be a consultant.
Will you tell Zhu Jiru?
No.
I'm not telling anyone.
I won't trouble them.
You're always so carefree.
The world is boundless.
Everything has its time.
Those meant to leave have left.
From now on, the stage
is all yours.
You must keep singing.
However hard it gets,
you have to keep singing.
(Tomb of Gou Cunzhong,
erected by all of Ningzhou County)
♪Li Lanying honors the loyal souls♪
♪Witnessed by heaven and earth♪
(Grand Auditorium, Weimin General Store)
(Gu Cunxiao left.)
(Zhou Cunren moved
to the Bureau of Culture.)
(Qiu Cunyi returned to his hometown.)
(Yi Qing'e watched them)
(leave one after another,)
(feeling a deep void in her heart.)
(These four old men)
(rescued her from the kitchen stove)
(and devoted their lives
to teaching her.)
(Weimin General Store)
(Now, with them gone,)
(the Cunjia Troupe
only has the name left.)
(She fears that in this troupe,)
(she'll be the only one left.)
Ningzhou People's Broadcasting Station.
We now bring you
an important report from Beishan.
Warm congratulations
to Yang Men Nyu Jiang,
a newly adapted traditional opera,
from Ningzhou County
Qinqiang Opera Troupe,
on the great success
in the Beishan arts showcase.
It's also won
the Best Traditional Opera Award.
Good for you, Troupe Leader.
- Leaders and regional experts
- Listen!
- who watched the show
- We won!
highly praised the performance
of Yang Men Nyu Jiang
from the Ningzhou County Troupe.
Everyone agreed
that this is a rare, outstanding
Qinqiang opera in our region
and even the province.
Hurry, hurry!
What's the rush?
Stop chopping! Stop!
- What's wrong?
- Listen!
- Yi Qing'e
also won the First Prize
for Young Actors.
The play Yang Men Nyu Jiang
is a very difficult one.
- They mean Laidi!
- Who else?
Where is she?
She's feeding the pigs.
Hurry! Hurry up! Let's go!
- Laidi!
Laidi!
Laidi, hurry!
Stop it!
Stop feeding them! Hurry!
You won an award! You won!
First prize, Laidi!
Stop calling her Laidi.
It's Yi Qing'e now.
You're on the radio!
- Give it to me!
- Let's go!
That's you. Go listen!
I'll do it.
Let's go listen to the radio!
Her showcase after years of training
was a complete success.
You two are so lucky
to be fed by the lead.
We'll kill you to feed the lead.
Eat up now.
(Hot water)
Reports say
that at 11, Yi Qing'e
joined Ningzhou County
Qinqiang Opera Troupe.
Over the years in the trainee class,
she feared no hardship or fatigue,
practicing day after day,
year after year.
- Do you hear that?
- She stayed disciplined
and kept training her basic skills.
Laidi!
Stop working and listen to the radio!
Don't walk away!
Come listen! Stop working!
Laidi!
This silly girl.
Our Ningzhou County
Qinqiang Opera Troupe
trained such an excellent young actress.
That's not fair.
It was everyone's effort.
Why does she get all the credit?
Exactly.
It is also very well executed.
- Awesome!
- Qinqiang opera...
Awesome!
- Awesome.
- represents our heart.
Come here. I need to talk to you.
What's wrong? What is it?
I'm being transferred.
Where to?
The provincial troupe.
They're recruiting young people now.
Zhou Yuzhi's family
pulled strings for her.
She's leaving too.
That's a good thing.
It's the Tian'anmen of Qinqiang opera.
You should go too.
Let's go together.
Me? I...
I don't have the connections.
I'm not going to daydream.
I talked to my dad.
He'll transfer you too.
I'm not going.
Are you going to stay
in this valley forever for her?
I'm not doing this for anyone.
Listen to me.
Or your life will be ruined,
just like Master Gou.
Thank you.
I mean it.
I wish you a bright future.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
I'm representing the County CPPCC today
to share some good news.
They made me a CPPCC Member.
What?
You'll be my boss from now on.
Hey, why are you joking with the kid?
She's now famous all over Beishan
as the Little Queen of Qinqiang Opera.
Yi Qing'e.
I took these photos of you
with color film.
Every single one is...
This is a dressing room, not a commune.
Get out.
You did it on purpose!
- That's right!
- You...
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪