( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
You married my friend.
Why do you still have the nerve
to claim you're dating Preaw?
Why can't I?
Even we have slept together too.
You're just a coward
who won't admit the truth!
You just like Mook better than me.
- Feed him! Feed him!
- Feed him! Yay
Mom said she was going to buy us food.
But… But she never came back.
Tawan, my brother, he's dead.
There, there.
Don't cry.
It's alright, sweetie. Don't cry.
Teacher, what should we do?
Can you help him in any way?
I'd better take him to the police,
in case anyone's reported
the kids as missing.
It's okay.
Don't be scared, sweetie.
Don't cry. You're with her now.
Don't be scared, okay? Stay with me here.
I'll help you find your mom,
alright, sweetie?
- Did you just get back from a flight?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
Early morning flights
always make me so tired.
Does Preaw not have many shifts lately?
How come I rarely see her?
Remember the boyfriend
she revealed at the party?
I heard he's abusive,
and Preaw got beaten.
That Top guy?
He's that horrible?
I'm not sure if it's true, though,
because our flight schedule's
been pretty weird lately,
so I don't know if it's true or not.
Why are you at my house?
What's the matter, Khim?
Can you open the gate for me?
Amp told me you haven't shown up
to work for a while now.
Are you okay?
No, no. I'm fine. I'm just…
a little sick, so I asked
for a schedule change.
If there's nothing else,
I'll be going back to rest now.
Hey.
- Thank you.
- Careful.
Smells so good.
I was just craving coffee, Boss.
So you're done with shooting
for the couple campaign?
Don't tease me, Boss.
I don't even know how long
I have to keep pretending.
There's news to consume daily these days.
Once a new trend comes, it will die down.
What I'm more worried about
is The One's profit evaluation
this quarter
because if it doesn't meet
Mr.Thee's target,
he might end our partnership.
Here.
I'm almost done
with the packages' pricing table.
We should promote it along
with Mr. Thee's wedding campaign.
I want to pump out
lots of online promotions in this period.
Yeah.
Mook, don't work so hard that you forget
about our kids' showcase at school today.
Oh, right.
I'll hurry and finish my work.
Are we going together?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Mook!
Mook, many pages are posting
bad reviews of our company.
I don't know why they suddenly
made a post slandering our tours.
So many pages did.
Their trips suck.
The hotel doesn't match the photos.
Terrible service. Expensive too.
No cancellations, they say.
Well, I'm cancelling them myself.
I'm so done.
I'll give you a hint.
It's called "A Round" something.
Could it be someone
trying to sabotage our company?
Excuse me.
The van rentals that used
to work with us just called.
So many of them cancelled our bookings.
But why?
Mook,
I think we can deal with this
in a meeting tomorrow.
Right now, we have to go,
or we'll be late for school.
Let's go.
Boss, can I leave Kongkwan in your care?
I want to solve these problems first.
Are you sure, Mook?
Kongkwan will be sad
if her mom doesn't go see her work.
It's alright. I'll explain to her
when I pick her up.
Then, call me if you need anything.
I'll take care of the kids.
Thank you, Boss.
- See you later.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- See you later, Boss.
- Yes.
Right.
Can I have the numbers
of the van rentals that cancelled on us?
I'll call them.
I'll make a list and text it to you.
Yes.
I'm sure someone's trying to sabotage us
by damaging our reputation.
But why now, of all times?
Remember the boyfriend
she revealed at the party?
I heard he's abusive,
and Preaw got beaten.
Why are you at my house?
What's the matter, Khim?
Can you open the gate for me?
Did Ploy not tell you two?
She moved out with Top.
We haven't talked since the wedding.
Where did they move to?
I just can't seem
to get hold of her lately.
She's at Top's condo.
She said she's been tied up
with work lately.
She hasn't been home for many days.
It's normal for newly-wed couples.
Top probably can't stay
too far away from her.
It's good, though. It means
I'll have a grandkid very soon.
So, do you know where his condo is?
Actually, Ploy did tell me,
but I can't remember.
Can you try calling her again?
Of course.
Oh, Ploy!
Hello?
I sent you something. Please read it.
Hey, Top!
I really appreciate it, Mr. Chit.
I'll send my company's
entire van rental schedule to you.
We'll pay more than A Round Trip,
and I assure you,
we'll book with you constantly.
Yes, thank you so much, Mr. Chit.
Goodbye.
Usa, are you sure
that this can get A Round Trip
to lose their contract?
Of course I am.
If we keep taking all their good suppliers
and creating pages to slander them,
I'm so sure
it'll affect The One eventually.
What if Mr. Thee looks into this?
Will he find out we did this?
Kuk, there are so many
internet trolls these days.
How could they ever track one down?
These days, this is the way
to survive in business.
Just trust me.
You'll get the big project soon.
My mom told me
she'd take me to the beach more often.
Thank you.
Coming up next is Kongkwan's work.
Kongkwan, you can start now.
I love Mommy a lot.
She loves me a lot too.
Mommy is like my angel.
Thank you.
She didn't even come
to see her kid's work.
Poor girl.
Yeah.
Coming up next is Poonpun's work.
How could you do this, Mr. Chit?
We've worked together many years,
and we've always kept you busy.
You can't just cancel on us
suddenly like this.
Mr. Chit? Mr. Chit!
What the hell?
What should we do, Mook?
It's really weird.
There must be something going on.
But now, we need to find new suppliers.
How many more van rentals
have we hired before?
I want ones with good service.
I only care about good service.
As for the price, we can negotiate.
If it's not too different, we'll be okay.
Okay. I'll find a new supplier
and have them send us a quotation.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Whan?
Can you look into the accounts
that gave us bad reviews?
I want to know who's behind it.
Sure.
Come on in.
What's up?
Kongkwan.
Once your mom's done with work,
she'll be right over.
Okay, Uncle.
She's really busy lately.
Please don't be mad at her.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Here's the early dismissal pass.
Thank you.
Kongkwan, I need to take
Poonpun to the dentist.
I'll take you for pizza later, okay?
Okay.
See you later.
- See you later.
Bye-bye.
- Yes.
Let's go. Here, I'll hold that for you.
Come on.
Kongkwan, let's go
to our classroom together.
Here.
Yes, adding the honeymoon package
to our main campaign is a good idea.
If you're fine with it, we'll prepare
to create an ad to promote it.
It should be able to boost
the hotel's sales.
‪Okay.
Mook!
You've got a nosebleed.
- Hold on.
- Wait, Mr. Thee!
Stay still.
Let me wipe your hand.
- Hey…
- Breathe through your mouth.
I'm okay. It's just a nosebleed.
No, you're not. Stay still.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Sorry, what?
Yes, I'll be right over.
What happened, Mook?
Kongkwan's gone missing.
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
What happened?
Kongkwan's gone missing.
I searched the entire building,
but I couldn't find her, ma'am.
Since when?
It was during PE.
The students were in PE class
down at the field.
When we came back up here,
she went missing.
I'm having everyone search for her now.
She's definitely still on the premises
because the school gates
don't open until it's time.
Kongkwan!
Kongkwan?
Kongkwan, honey!
- Kongkwan, can you hear me?
- Kongkwan!
Did you find her?
- No.
- Let's try that way.
- Kongkwan!
Kongkwan, can you hear me?
- Mook.
- Honey.
- Kongkwan!
Listen to me,
don't think negative thoughts.
I'm sure we'll find her.
But I've searched all over and…
Calm down, Mook.
Stay calm.
Let's keep looking.
She might be around here somewhere.
Okay?
Okay.
You go look that way.
I'll go that way.
Okay.
Kongkwan!
Where the hell did they go?
They're just too fast!
What do we tell our boss now?
God knows where their mom
took them and fled to.
I'll deal with them later.
They'll pay for this!
Don't cry.
Tawan, don't be scared.
Can I hide in here with you?
Who are you?
My name is Thee.
I'm mad at my mom,
so can I hide in here too?
You're mad at your mom too?
Yes.
My mom…
She left me.
Why is your mom so cruel?
She's nothing like my mom.
What's your name?
My name is Kongkwan.
Why are you hiding here?
I'm sad because
my mom loves someone else more than me.
My friends are making fun of me.
They say my mom's going to remarry.
I don't want her to remarry.
But I think
your mom loves you the most,
no matter what,
and she surely won't love
anyone more than you.
You're lucky to have a mom.
You're not like me.
Mine's not with me anymore.
Don't be sad.
I'm sure she'll come back.
It's getting late.
Should we go see your mom?
If she comes here and doesn't see you,
she'll get sad.
I don't want my mom to be sad.
Then I'll take you to her, okay?
You know my mom?
Yes,
I'm a friend of hers.
Let's go.
Okay.
Mommy!
Kongkwan!
Where were you?
I was so worried about you.
I'm sorry for making you sad, Mommy.
What happened, honey?
Today,
everyone's parents were here.
She's probably sad
that you didn't come see her work.
I'm sorry, honey.
It's my fault.
Okay?
You love me, right?
Of course I do.
I love you the most.
I promise I won't make you sad again.
SCUMBAG
You asshole. You're not a real man!
That's not what you said that night.
All you said was how good I was.
Asshole!
The gift I sent you today
was just to warn you
to mind your own damn business.
Today's sex tape
may not be yours yet,
but if you don't stop,
I assure you
there'll be even wilder ones.
Next time, it won't be just you
I send the videos to.
Having all these nice, sexy videos
makes me want to show them off.
I'm so sure
the likes and shares will be crazy.
Just think about it.
Is risking your future
really worth it?
Stay in your lane, Khim.
Stay out of my business,
and stay away from Ploy.
Okay?
Ploy. You're home?
I need to go take care of something.
I'll be home late.
You can go to bed without me.
You're coming home late again?
Ever since we got married,
you never stayed home.
Don't get mad. Come here.
I already told you
I have something to take care of.
What's that thing
you always need to take care of?
You go out every night.
And you're never back
until the morning after.
Come on now.
You're my wife, not my mom.
If you keep being ridiculous
till I can't stand you,
I won't be this nice.
Do you understand?
My good girl.
Keep being a good girl.
You're way sweeter this way.
This Saturday, I'm taking you
to visit your mom and dad,
so we can have dinner with them.
They must've missed you.
When I say something,
you answer.
Understood?
Ploy.
I'm back.
You're home at dawn every day.
Just be honest with me.
Are you seeing someone else?
I already have you.
How could I see someone else?
Top, you reek of booze and cigarettes.
Why don't you go shower first?
Top, you're hurting me!
You're lucky I even married you,
yet you'd play hard to get?
Why are you talking to me that way?
If you didn't want to marry me,
why didn't you just tell Ma and Pa?
Your mom
really loves me.
That's why she gave you to me so easily.
She told me to take good care of you too.
I'd better do what I was told.
Top, Top, that hurts!
Top! Top!
I said it hurt!
Top, I'm sorry.
I won't say anything bad to you again.
Please don't hurt me.
Didn't you want me to come home?
Well, here I am.
So, take care of me.
Top!
Don't hurt me, Top!
Top…
Top!
Don't you dare tell anyone
about what's going on at home,
or you'll regret it.
You're not mad at me anymore, right?
I never was mad at you.
I was the one who broke your promise.
It's okay.
Uncle Thee told me you love me the most,
and I'm luckier than him
to still have my mom.
Unlike me, his mom left him.
Okay.
But you have to promise me
you won't run away from me again.
- Okay?
- Okay, I promise.
And what else?
Let me kiss your forehead.
Come on. Go to sleep.
Good night.
Poor little girl. She must've been tired.
Yeah.
Mr. Pat's here, Mook.
I'm sorry, Mook.
If I'd kept waiting for you,
it wouldn't have happened.
Don't blame yourself, Boss.
It's entirely my fault
for not caring about her feelings.
How's Kongkwan doing?
She's asleep.
She's feeling better now.
What about you? Are you okay?
Not really.
I need better self-management.
I need to rearrange my life's priorities.
I've decided, Boss.
She's the most important thing in my life.
I'll have to trade something
to keep what I value the most in my life.
Are you talking about Mr. Thee?
I'm sad because
my mom loves someone else more than me.
My friends are making fun of me.
They say my mom's going to remarry.
I don't want her to remarry.
I don't want my mom to be sad.
How's Kongkwan doing?
She's doing better now.
Yesterday, she was probably very sad
that I broke my promise.
I wanted to thank you
for helping me find her yesterday
and to thank you
for everything you've done.
You said
you were waiting for my answer.
Please don't reject me just yet.
No matter now or later,
my answer stays the same.
What happened yesterday reminded me
just how important she is to me.
I don't want to make her sad again.
Please don't waste your time with me.
Thank you for understanding.
Is something wrong, Mr. Thee?
Ms. Mook looked stressed.
Is this a sign that we're losing our jobs?
No way!
I just signed up for a facelift.
I'm still paying it off.
I can't go broke now!
Mr. Pitak.
- Yes?
- What happened?
Why is Mr. Thee's stuff being moved out?
It was Mr. Thee's orders.
From now on, he'll be working
at the hotel like before.
Should there be any meetings,
we'll have you attend them at the hotel.
Okay. So, that means
we'll still be working together, right?
Yes.
- If you'll excuse me.
- See you later.
Hey,
I think something must've happened.
Did Mook and Mr. Thee fight?
If they really fought,
what about our story with them
being a couple?
What do we do?
Oh, right.
You've talked to Mr. Thee?
Yes, but don't worry.
I'll make sure it won't affect our work.
If our company is affected in any way,
I'll gladly quit.
Don't say that as if we're strangers.
I'd never leave you just because of this.
And if something happens
because of your decision,
I'm ready to accept it too.
Thank you, Boss.
I'm sure Mr. Thee won't mix his work
with his personal life, Mook.
What I'm more worried about
is the news about you and him.
I'll go talk to that reporter.
It's no use, Mook.
She won't leave us alone for sure.
Also,
I'm partly responsible for this too.
I'll try talking to Prao again.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
I took care of everything as you asked.
I've moved out your belongings
and dealt with the reporter.
I can't help you with that.
I'm a reporter.
It's my duty to present the truth.
Please let Mr. Thee know
no matter what he does,
he can't esape the truth.
You're a reporter.
Of course you have to present
everything as it is.
You covered the wastewater treatment story
in a community, right?
If you stop writing news
about Mr. Thee and Ms. Mook,
no one will know about this.
Are you threatening me?
In my entire time working with Mr. Thee,
he's never threatened anyone.
If your agency found out
you falsified the story
about the corruption
in the project's development,
you might want to start
looking for a new job.
I want the files of the photo
you brought to the conference that day
and also all the photos
taken by the people you sent
to follow Mr. Thee and Ms. Mook.
Thank you.
I don't want there to be any stories
that'll defame me and Mook
because I don't want her daughter
to be sad about things like this again.
You seem to care a lot about Ms. Mook.
I do,
because I got to see
just how great the love
Mook has for her daughter is.
I want to protect their feelings.
Well, I hope you haven't forgotten
that you already have someone.
I'll deal with that myself,
but I want you to handle the issue
at Ms. Mook's daughter's school.
Of course.
CHADCHAI
That's all. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello, Mr. Chadchai.
Khim, something bad happened.
- What's up?
- Did you hear about Preaw?
She's hospitalized?
They say she got beaten so badly,
she was hospitalized.
So the news about her
being abused is true.
I'm sure it was that guy
at the birthday party.
- But the other day, I still--
- What is it?
Did you go see her?
Nothing.
I meant at the party,
they still seemed fine.
Her friend said
she couldn't take it anymore,
so she broke up with him,
but he wouldn't let her.
Then, they had a big fight,
and he hurt her.
You really can't judge a book
by its cover.
Come on in.
Time for you break.
Thank you.
Get it together, Mook.
Come on. Get it together.
Hello.
I bought some desserts for you.
This shop makes the best desserts.
Here you go.
Sorry, I can't accept this.
You shouldn't have.
Please, take it.
We just wanted to spread some kindness.
In the past, if we've done you any wrong,
please forget about it.
After all, our kids are friends.
That's right. From now on,
we'll make sure to zip it.
We won't say or do anything
to make Kongkwan uncomfortable.
What happened?
Last time we met, you two still hated me.
We heard about Kongkwan
going missing the other day,
and we felt bad
that she was upset partly because of us.
If our kids went missing,
it would break our hearts too.
Mommy!
Are you tired?
Thank you for understanding.
If you'll excuse me. Let's go.
Oh, Ms. Mook.
- Please accept it.
- Please.
Please, Ms. Mook.
Please.
Thank you.
Let's go, honey. Did you have fun today?
We really didn't want things
to get this far.
That's right.
We really didn't expect Ms. Prao
to send the photos to that reporter.
Mr. Thee will let you off this time…
but on one condition.
Don't cause any trouble
for Ms. Mook and her daughter again.
I hope we won't have to meet
like this again.
You can keep them.
Keep them as souvenirs.
I have the files already.
We're lucky they're not suing us.
I can't imagine if we had
to take it all the way to court.
But this means Mr. Thee
must really care about Kongkwan's mom.
He loves her, obviously.
Mom!
- Hey, kids!
- Hi!
Guys,
from now on, don't pick a fight
with Kongkwan again, got it?
Well, you're the one
who told us that her mom
is a bad person and to stay away from her.
Let's go home, honey.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on.
You good? Do you want me to hold that?
Good job.
Our hotel's doing very bad right now.
We need to hurry
and do something, Mrs. Narin.
It's true.
We're barely getting any guests.
It'll probably stay this slow
for quite a while.
The other hotels that can't survive
have already started to shut down.
But I don't think our hotel
will need to shut down too.
What do you mean, Mr. Chadchai?
It'll be hard to get
a bank loan right now.
To be honest,
we're already badly overdrawn.
There's an investor
who's interested in our hotel.
I'll go talk to him.
So we'll need a stockholder to help us?
It's still better than shutting down.
Right now, we can still
support our employees,
but if this continues,
we won't be able to sustain them
or even our hotel.
COULDN'T COPE! HOTEL AFFECTED BY COVID
DECIDES TO SHUTDOWN
NARIN BEACH RESORT AFFECTED BY COVID
COULDN'T COPE, SHUTS DOWN
Don't worry, Mr. Thee.
I think you'll get what you want very soon
because the hotel's been doing
very bad lately.
Good. I'll leave it to you, Mr. Chadchai.
Of course.
How many shares
would you like to purchase?
As many as possible.
In fact, I'd like all of it.
You probably saw
that our hotel is a good investment.
I've been waiting for this moment.
I need an answer very soon.
I hope you remember our deal.
Don't worry, I'll reward you
according to the shares I get.
How about that?
You have a meeting
about the couple campaign today, Mr. Thee.
A Round Trip will attend it too.
Will Ms. Mook be attending?
Her name wasn't listed, sir.
Ms. Usa wanted to treat you to lunch.
She said she wanted to speak with you.
You haven't eaten all morning?
I'm not very hungry.
You can have someone take it out.
Mook, are you sure you're fine with this?
I could've come alone, you know.
It wouldn't be right, Whan.
This is about work. I can differentiate.
So, are you and Mr. Thee fighting?
Mook!
I thought you weren't attending.
I'm glad you came.
Hello, Mook. Are you here for a meeting?
I'm just heading to lunch with Mr. Thee.
Go ahead.
There's still time.
Let's have lunch together, Mook.
It's okay.
Please go ahead. I'm not hungry.
But it sounds like
Ms. Whan's hungry, Mook.
Stop thinking about it. Just come with me.
Let's go. Come on, Ms. Whan.
Well…
Wait for me, Mr. Thee!
You wanted to speak with me
about something?
It's nothing, really.
I've read some bad news about you,
so I was worried about you.
About me and Ms. Mook?
There's nothing worrying, really.
You were probably shocked
when the reporter made a scene that day,
so I understand you
for dealing with the situation that way.
Mook, you should be careful as well.
Especially since
you're working with Mr. Thee,
everyone's watching you.
Your public image is very important.
Don't cause Mr. Thee any trouble.
Don't you worry.
I know what I'm doing.
I'm full. If you'll excuse me.
Mook.
If that's all you had to say,
then please excuse me.
Enjoy your food.
Mook!
Mook.
Mook, wait for me.
Mook. Watch out!
I'm so sorry.
Let go of me. Mr. Thee, let go!
If someone sees us,
you'll ruin your image.
I've missed you, Mook.
I think I made myself clear.
I know.
I'll stay out of you
and your daughter's lives.
But that doesn't mean
I'll stop loving you.
You should hurry to the meeting.
Mook!
Wait for me, Mook!
Let's go, Whan.
Mama's got work to do. Stop acting up!
Start already! What's wrong with you?
What should we do, Mook?
I don't think it's going to start.
Here's the plan.
You go to the print shop
and finalize the artwork.
Don't wait for me.
I'll call a mechanic.
Once my car's fixed, I'll be right over.
Got it. I've got it from here.
- I'm counting on you.
- Okay.
Go.
What the hell? It was still fine before.
What's up?
Hey!
Could be a problem
with the starter or the battery.
Call a mechanic.
You know, how about I drive you?
I'll have Mr. Pitak take care of your car.
Thank you,
but no, thank you.
TOR'S GARAGE
MR. PAT
I see you and Mommy fighting all the time.
Why do you have to fight?
Don't you love each other anymore?
I-- Hey!
Can you stand still just for a minute?
Let me recharge my energy.
…attach their map…
Stay focused.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya