( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I see you and Mommy fighting all the time.
Why do you have to fight?
Don't you love each other anymore?
I-- Hey!
Can you stand still just for a minute?
Let me recharge my energy.
…with their map attached--
Stay focused.
Where are we going?
Wait.
Aren't you going to tell me anything?
How much?
Excuse me?
How much for the ride?
I'm not a taxi driver, you know.
Just let me know when you want the fare.
Daddy's here!
I'll get to go play
in the water now, right, Mommy?
Where were you?
Did you know you upset my dad?
What about me, Prao?
Did you ever ask me if I was upset?
Why? What did I do wrong?
I'm trying to give you a stable career.
Are you planning to be the CEO of that
stupid travel agency until you die?
With everything going on,
are you planning to starve to death?
What you did wrong
is you never believed in me,
no matter what I'd do.
You're supposed to encourage me
and support me,
not dictate how my life should go.
- Well, it's because you--
- Let's talk later.
We're here to take him
on a trip, remember?
Then take him. I'm not in the mood for it.
You two were yelling at each other again.
It's nothing, Pun.
Let Mommy take a rest, okay?
Okay.
Let's go swim, shall we?
Yes, please!
Come on.Let's get changed.
Can I help you?
Or what do you want me to change?
Let me know, so I can finish it.
Is your car good now?
Not yet.
How'd you get here?
Taxi.
How are you going home?
What does any of that
have to do with work?
It doesn't, but I only asked
because I'm worried about you,
and I want to talk to you.
ANAPAT
Yes, Boss?
I think it's over.
What happened?
You don't sound okay.
Prao and I,
we barely said a few words
and we fought again.
And she's using this trip
with our son as an excuse
just to pull me into her cage again.
Where are you, though?
I'm still editing my work at The One.
Let's talk more when you're back.
Boss.
Good luck. I hope it goes well.
Are you having fun?
Yes, I am.
Careful, alright?
You seem to worry a lot about Mr. Pat.
Yes.
We're always worried about each other.
It smells so good, Grandma.
Today, I'm making
only the tasty dishes you love.
Let's prepare them and wait
for Mommy to come home and eat with us.
Sounds good!
She'll be home early today, right?
Of course she will!
Why don't you
go shower and wear some nice clothes
while waiting for Mommy?
Go on.
Okay. Okay. Here…
I've made the edits we discussed
and emailed the file to you.
That should be all.
You haven't eaten anything.
Wanna grab some food together?
We can't. I have to be with my daughter.
It's her birthday.
Why didn't you tell me
it's Kongkwan's birthday?
I would've let you leave early.
It's alright.
I wanted to finish it,
so the other teams can keep working on it.
- Let me help you.
- No, it's okay! I've got it.
I'll drive you.
Don't keep Kongkwan waiting.
- Let's go.
- Hey!
Hurry up, would you?
No one remembers my birthday.
She probably hasn't finished her work.
Just wait a little longer, okay?
You know what?
I can go get you
the banana in coconut milk
that you love right now.
I'll be right back, okay?
Those are for Kongkwan.
You really shouldn't have.
It's alright.
She's your daughter,
so she's important to me too.
We should hurry.
Daddy's coming home now, right?
Yes, Daddy's rushing back home in his car.
Just wait a little longer, okay?
Good girl.
Kongkwan, it's half past ten already.
It's late, honey.
Why aren't you in bed yet?
You should go to bed.
I want to blow the candles with Daddy.
It'll be a while until he gets off work.
You shouldn't wait, honey. Just go to bed.
Hey,
take her to bed
and turn off the lights,
so we can save money.
Are you hungry, Kongkwan?
Do you want the éclairs?
They're really good, though. Are you sure?
Kongkwan, your cake's here!
Go welcome him. Go on.
Daddy's home!
How are you, honey?
Come here. Let Daddy hug you.
Come on, come on.
Did you miss me?
Kuk, where's her birthday cake?
Is it in there?
Oh, right!
I completely forgot.
I was busy with work all day.
I'm sorry.
Let me buy you one tomorrow, okay?
Here!
I have chicken!
See?
Here.
Eat it instead of the cake for now.
Here it comes.
Don't you like it?
Yes, Mom,
I'm almost home.
What'd you say?!
How long has she been gone?
Kongkwan!
Mom, I found her!
I've got to go.
Kongkwan!
Mr. Thee!
Mr. Thee! Kongkwan!
Kongkwan, honey!
Are you hurt?
Mr. Thee! Mr. Thee?
Mr. Thee!
Help!
Somebody help us!
Mr. Thee!
Somebody help!
Somebody help us!
Mr. Thee…
You sure love your friend.
I wonder what Ploy would think
if she found out that you and I
- knew each other so well--
- I don't care.
She can hate me all she wants.
I just can't let you hurt her anymore.
Then you'll see
that the video I'm leaking this time
is not yours yet,
but actually your best friend's.
You can check if it's HD enough.
‪Ploy…
What do I do?
Mook, what happened to you?
Who hurt you?!
Mook.
What happened?
How'd Mr. Thee get hit by a car?
He got hit while trying to save Kongkwan.
What do I do? I'm scared.
He's in the doctor's care now. Calm down.
Doctor,
how's Mr. Thee doing?
He's stable now.
He had a concussion,
but there's no bleeding in the brain.
The speed of his recovery
depends on his condition.
If you'll excuse me.
Okay.
It's okay. He's okay now.
What did the doctor say?
How's Mr. Thee doing?
He's stable now,
but we'll have to see when he wakes up.
I'll go speak with the doctor.
Okay.
It's okay.
Ms. Mook, please go home
and get some rest.
I'll take care of him.
Please don't worry.
Come on. I'll drive you home.
Is this yours?
I found it in Mr. Thee's car.
Good evening.
How's Mr. Thee?
Is he okay?
He's stable now,
but the doctor said
we'd have to wait and see
because he had a concussion.
I'm sorry, Mommy.
I'm just glad you're safe, honey.
But can you promise me
you won't run off
on your own like that again?
If you go missing,
what would Mommy and Grandma do?
Here.
Mr. Thee bought it for you as a gift.
- There you go.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for today.
Why'd you call me earlier today, though?
It's nothing. Let's talk later.
Get some rest.
You look…
really wiped out.
You love Mr. Thee, don't you, Mook?
But it's impossible for us to be together.
I understand.
You aren't all by yourself.
You have a daughter,
and you've been married before,
but you can't dwell
in the past forever, Mook.
And stop letting society limit you.
Give yourself a chance,
and give him a chance too.
These days,
good guys are hard to find.
Thank you.
Think about it. I'm going home now.
- Drive safe.
- Okay.
Bye.
WIH INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL
Mr. Thee.
Can you hear me?
Why aren't you waking up yet?
I've got something to tell you.
Please wake up and listen to me.
What you asked me before…
I have an answer for you now.
Please wake up and hear me.
Mr. Thee.
Don't cry. I'm alright now.
Are you messing with-- Oh! You okay?
Well?
What did you want to tell me?
Thank you for saving Kongkwan,
and…
thank you for everything.
That's it?
Let me help you.
When I heard the news,
I hurried back here.
How are you doing?
I'm doing better now. Thank you.
Don't.
So you've decided about Mr. Thee?
I don't know either,
but I do know that
if I could turn back time,
I wouldn't have denied
my feelings like I did.
I think we both should accept the truth.
No matter if it's good or bad,
we should still face it.
Well, how'd your trip go, Boss?
It made me more sure about things.
With the problem between me and Prao,
I'll make sure to solve it carefully,
so when the time comes,
and I have to decide,
I won't regret it.
You can stay here
and take care of Mr. Thee today.
I'll handle your work
for you at the office.
Thank you, Boss.
Boss,
I believe a good man like you
will surely be met with good things.
Good luck!
See you later.
What's wrong, Usa?
Mr. Thee was in an accident.
"THEE" BUSINESSMAN INJURED IN ACCIDENT
AFTER TRYING TO SAVE "KONGKWAN"
That's Kongkwan and Mook!
Wait!
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Mook.
I want to see how Kongkwan's doing.
Hold on!
Calm down, Kuk.
It says that the mom
and the daughter are safe.
Visiting Mook isn't what
we have to do right now.
Kongkwan!
How'd you get here, honey?
I took her.
I was the one who told Khim
to give me a ride here.
I wanted to cook him something too,
but I saw that you're busy,
so I didn't tell you.
And Kongkwan was begging
to visit Mr. Thee.
Is that true?
Mommy, come take a look!
Thee drew me.
Really? Let me see.
Can Mommy see?
Aw, how cute!
How is it? I'm good at drawing, right?
Here, look.
As pretty as in real life, right?
- You have to hold your hand up.
- My hand?
- Okay.
- There.
I think you're prettier in real life.
That's my daughter, alright.
What should we draw next?
Let me draw you next.
Sure. Here's your pencil.
His head's so big!
Hey.
Mr. Thee.
Done!
That's… how I look?!
- And what's that?
- A hat.
- Really?
- I have eyelashes too?
Mook.
Daddy!
Careful, honey.
What's up?
What are you doing here, Kongkwan?
I'm here to visit Thee.
Thee?
He's a friend of mine.
What's this about, Mook?
How come she's here with Mr. Thee,
and why do they seem so close?
Are you using our daughter?
Have some respect, Kuk.
I would never do such a thing.
She just wanted
to thank him for saving her.
Like I'd believe that.
Anyone can tell
you're trying to play house with them.
I really don't understand.
What else do you want?
Why are you using
our daughter to woo a guy?
You already won the deal,
but you weren't satisfied,
so now you want Mr. Thee too?
If I'm going to start
a new life with someone,
I reassure you,
I won't make the wrong decision again.
Sure.
We'll see about that.
This path that you're choosing,
how good will it really be?
You should be taking care of Kongkwan,
yet you can't even do it right!
If something happens to her,
you're the one responsible.
I'm relieved to see
that you aren't badly hurt.
When I saw the news,
I was so worried about you, Mr. Thee.
Come to think of it,
ever since you met Mook,
I see you've had all kinds of trouble.
I think you might want
to stay away from her sometimes.
Ms. Usa,
I don't think I can stay away
from someone I love.
I really don't know
what good you see in Mook
that makes you love her so much.
She's a single mom who got divorced,
and she isn't rich either.
She doesn't deserve you at all.
I never dated anyone
for their social status.
Let me be clear with you,
so you don't have to keep insulting her.
I love Mook.
I love everything about her.
- I think--
- Usa, let's go home.
Get well soon, Mr. Thee.
If you'll excuse me.
I don't care if you want to date Mook,
but don't drag my daughter into this.
I don't like it.
Kongkwan's asleep already?
Yes, Mom.
Is something wrong, Mook?
You've been quiet
since we got back from the hospital.
Did you and Kuk fight again?
Mom,
is it so wrong
if I choose what feels good
over what's right?
I don't know how to answer that.
Some people
choose what's right, yet they're unhappy,
and they have to put up
with it until they die.
Some people choose
what feels good over what's right,
and still, there's no guarantee
they'll be happy until they die.
So,
what should we choose, Mom?
You choose to do what makes you happy
without causing trouble for others,
and you must be sure
that it won't make others unhappy.
Being an adult sure is hard, Mom.
You like Mr. Thee, don't you?
Is it that obvious?
It's not hard to tell at all.
Mom.
So… would you mind
if I gave dating Mr. Thee a shot?
You're all grown up now.
You can make your own decisions.
From what I've seen,
Mr. Thee is a good man,
but time will tell, and we must let it.
What'd you talk to Mook about?
I was just reminding her
to behave herself,
since she's a mother.
And that Mr. Thee too.
I don't know why he's so in love with her.
Warning him's no use.
Since they started dating,
all they had is trouble.
I've never met anyone
as shameless as Mook.
A single mom who's in the news
with a different guy every day.
I feel so bad for your daughter
for having a mom like her.
I'll wait and see just how long
Mook and Mr. Thee will last.
A guy like Mr. Thee,
he's just having fun at most.
Your ex-wife, though,
is probably aiming for more.
- Ploy didn't come into work?
- Yes.
She hasn't for a couple of days now.
I heard she's hospitalized too.
Hospitalized?
Do you know why?
No, she didn't specify.
Thank you.
ACCOUNTING
Khim, did you hear
about Ploy being in the hospital?
What?
You two are dealing
with such a horrible situation,
yet I never got to help
because I was so deep in my own mess.
It's all my fault.
At first, I was scared.
I couldn't admit the truth.
I thought things would die down,
but I never thought
Top could be such a monster.
Mook,
what should we do?
I feel bad for Ploy.
What about you? What will you do?
Just when your career's going well…
I don't care.
What I need to do right now
is drag Top to jail.
But If I expose him now,
Ploy will go down just as hard.
But we can't leave it like this.
We have to tell Ploy.
Ploy…
Ploy will definitely hate me
if she hears the truth.
We're friends, you know.
I'm sure she'll understand.
If you'd behaved yourself,
you wouldn't have had to get hurt.
I hope you learned
how you should behave from now on.
Hello?
I'm just heading out now.
See ya.
MOOK
Hello? What's up, Mook?
Ploy, we need to talk.
Where are you right now?
I'm in my room.
Is there something urgent?
Now's not really a good time.
I'll let you know later, okay?
I want to see you too.
Talk to you later, Mook.
Ploy! Ploy, Wait! Ploy!
I won't let you two face
something so horrible again.
We'll get through this together.
It's okay.
Ma, I'm filing for custody of Kongkwan.
Why? What happened?
What did Mook do to her?
Well, yesterday, I visited Mr. Thee,
and she took her to see him.
Kongkwan seemed so close to him, Ma.
That Mook is such a schemer.
She's planning to woo a rich guy
by using her daughter.
I feel bad for my daughter, Ma,
so I want to take care of her myself.
That's good.
She'll be devastated
to lose custody of her daughter to you.
No way!
You'll only fall right into her trap.
Without her daughter around,
she'll win Mr. Thee over more easily.
You're right. That's a good point, Usa.
Why should we take care of Kongkwan
and let Mook happily
roam free with her guy?
What should we do, then, Ma?
I can't stand seeing her happy
with another guy!
Do you still have feelings for her?
That's not it, Usa.
I just don't want her
to succeed in any way.
She already won the deal,
and now she's winning Mr. Thee over?
I won't let him take my place
and be Kongkwan's father.
Then don't let him!
WIH INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL
I'm here. I just had
to take care of something.
Please hurry. I miss you.
Okay.
Sorry.
Don't look at him that way.
If Mr. Pitak didn't tell me,
I wouldn't have known
you're in a hospital.
I wasn't hurt too badly,
so I didn't want you to worry.
You're hospitalized,
yet you're saying it's not that bad?
You've changed a lot.
What do you think you're doing?
What if you get seriously hurt?
What about your company?
So many people
would suffer because of you.
Not to mention our partners.
I'm well aware of what I'm doing.
You don't have to worry, Mom.
I won't let our partners and employees
suffer because of me.
If that's true, why'd you do it?
You should know
what you're supposed to do.
You can't get distracted like this.
And about Veluree too.
You--
Please take this before your meal.
Perhaps I've been too kind to you.
I'd better deal with everything
and whip it into shape.
I hope you haven't forgotten
the important job
you're supposed to be doing.
Take your pill.
MOOK
Meet me at the print shop, Whan.
Don't forget the laptop,
so I can edit it here.
Okay. See ya.
Mr. Thee, there's a problem with my work.
I just need to go edit it,
then I'll be right back.
Okay.
I've finalized the artwork, Boss.
We should be able
to produce everything on time.
Thank you for always
helping me solve the problems, Mook.
What are you working on, by the way?
Why are there documents
all over your desk?
I'm going over our financial summary.
Although we've signed
the contract with The One,
I still need to get
a better handle on our cash flow.
It's been a bit tight.
Can I help you in any way?
Please just don't.
This is for me and Mr. Suetrong to handle.
I'm already really grateful
that you're handling
almost everything for our company.
Wanna grab dinner?
If you'll excuse me,
it's just…
You have a date with a sick guy.
Boss, don't make fun of me!
I'm going to visit Mr. Thee.
See you later. Bye. You've got it, Boss.
Just let me know when you want the fare.
WIH INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL
Hey.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Did you eat yet?
No. I came straight here
after I finished work.
Then let's eat together.
I had Mr. Pitak buy us something simple
because I know you skip
your meals when you're busy.
Thank you.
Okay.
May I?
Go ahead.
Let me wipe your mouth.
It's okay. I've got it.
So, what's the issue with work?
The campaign's artwork
just needed an edit.
I already took care of it, though.
I can leave tomorrow. I'll come help you.
Really?
But I wanted to ask you a favor.
What is it?
I want to eat your mom's cooking again.
It's the best Thai food I've had
since I got back in Thailand.
Would it be possible?
Please? I want to see Kongkwan too.
I'll go ask my mom.
I don't know if she and Kongkwan
will say yes, though.
You should have some too.
Sure.
Everything tastes good
when I'm eating with you.
How is it?
How could you?!
I didn't start it.
And actually,
she slept with me
the night before we got married.
Khim.
- You want to say cheers that bad?
- Yes.
You bitch!
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya