( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
- What's going on?
- What does this mean?
- How'd you two meet?
- Mr. Thee.
Ms. Veluree and I are seeing each other.
Her company only won
because she slept with the CEO.
It's all over the news now
that Mr. Thee's dating her.
Can I see?
I want an answer…
that comes from your true feelings.
Preaw invited us
to her birthday party tonight.
She said there's going to be
a surprise too,
so she wanted you to come.
Come on. It'll be just us anyway.
We rarely ever get to meet up.
Come on, Khim. Join us.
- Yeah.
Join us, please.
Okay, fine.
Let's meet at Preaw's, then.
I'm going to a salon first.
- Sure.
- I'll go with you.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Pull me up.
- Here.
Let's meet tonight then, Khim.
Yeah. Go on ahead.
PLOY
Sorry, the number you've dialed
is currently unavailable--
Sorry, the number you've dialed--
Look, I made my own signature.
Why's it so long?
A.
Wow.
Kongkwan, Kongkwan.
Is your mom about to remarry?
Yeah, my mom told me
you're about to have a new dad.
That's not true.
She's not going to remarry.
Your mom lied to you.
I don't wanna talk to you two anymore.
Wait, Kongkwan!
Good afternoon, Grandma.
Why do you look so unhappy today?
Do you feel ill, honey?
Is Mom really going to remarry?
Why are you asking me that?
My friends told me Mom's going to remarry.
Am I really going to have a new dad?
Kongkwan, listen to me, honey.
Your mom's not getting remarried,
and she'll never stop loving you.
If you don't believe me,
ask her at home this evening, okay?
Really, Grandma?
Of course.
Have your mom and I ever lied to you?
No, you haven't.
Yes. So let's go home, shall we?
Okay? Don't be sad, honey. My good girl.
Okay?
Come on. Let's go eat something delicious.
I'm working on this year's marketing plan.
I'll send it to you,
in case you want to adjust it
or add something to make it suit
the hotel's target group better.
Excuse me? What are you doing?
I'm not done yet!
Eat first. You can continue later.
No. I want to finish it first.
Either eat it or I'll feed you.
Eat all of it.
I'm going to a meeting.
When I'm done, I'll come check
if you did what I told you.
- It really is a photo of those two!
- Yeah!
- How do you explain this?
Ms. Veluree and I are seeing each other.
THAI WOMAN WINS BUSINESSMAN'S HEART
AT YOU ARE THE ONE'S PRESS CONFERENCE
My friends told me Mom's going to remarry.
Am I really going to have a new dad?
Mook.
See? I ate it all, like you told me to.
It's pretty late. Come on.
I'll drive you home.
When will I get an answer?
On what?
On how you feel about me.
I…
Was it tasty?
Hey!
Here comes the real thing.
- Yeah.
- You're so wrong
Oh, Khim!
- Hi!
There you are.
Preaw's just about to reveal the surprise.
What's the surprise? Do you know?
She's about to reveal her boyfriend.
Yeah.
- Like that's so important.
- Eat something.
No, it's a carb.
Here we are!
- Isn't he hot?
- He's so hot!
- He's a total oppa.
- Oppa.
You've been sneaky!
Guys, this is Top, my boyfriend.
"Boyfriend," she says!
Damn, girl!
- Big reveal.
- Right?
- Took you long enough.
- No wonder.
Why'd you do this? What about Ploy?
Wait, you know Ploy?
Hey.
Top, this is Mook, my best friend.
- Hello, Top.
- Hello.
Too bad Khim left,
so we don't have a photo together.
Who's Khim?
She's another best friend of mine.
The three of us are really close.
This morning, Khim was here too.
Yes, but an important meeting came up,
so she had to leave.
It's fine, though.
I'll introduce you later.
Sure.
Don't tell me you're… Khim?
Ploy's friend?
Small world, huh?
Nice to meet you,
Ms. Khim.
What are you doing here? Where's Ploy?
Ploy?
She's home, of course.
You married my friend.
Why do you still have the nerve
to claim you're dating Preaw?
Why can't I?
Even we have slept together too.
How dare you, you asshole?
So this is your true nature.
I'm going to tell Ploy
what your true nature is like.
Please go ahead.
Then I'll also tell Ploy
about your true nature…
because I have proof
of just how well we know each other.
What do you mean?
I mean that I have video evidence
to show Ploy her best friend's wild side.
If you don't want to lose a friend,
then stay in your lane.
Don't be a snitch about my business.
Got it?
Top,
- there you are!
- What's up?
Let's go blow the candles.
Sure, let's go.
- Come with us.
- Sure.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Are you mad at me?
Everything I do,
I do it because I really like you, Mook.
Please don't be mad.
I'm more mad at myself.
I shouldn't have done that.
I don't think
it can ever work between us.
Mook.
Why do you think so?
Because I'm not ready
to start over with anyone.
I don't want to get hurt again.
More importantly, it's not just me.
I have a daughter.
I have to prioritize her feelings.
I'm sorry,
Mr. Thee.
Mom.
You're still up?
I was waiting for you.
Who drove you home?
That's not Mr. Pat's car.
Mr. Thee did.
I'm working with him for now.
Is this the man
who's in the news with you?
You know about that too?
It's not just me who knows.
Kongkwan does too.
What?
Kongkwan's friends
were talking about how
you're going to remarry.
It made her very sad, Mook.
She was waiting to ask you
and cried herself to sleep.
I'm sorry, honey.
I won't make you sad again.
I promise.
Can I help you, Mook?
I need to talk to you
about something important.
Ms. Mook called,
saying she won't work here anymore.
What should we do, Mr. Thee?
Because I'm not ready
to start over with anyone.
I don't want to get hurt again.
More importantly, it's not just me.
I have a daughter.
I have to prioritize her feelings.
The news that got out
hurt my daughter's feelings.
I don't want it to happen again.
I understand. I'll talk to Mr. Thee.
What if he doesn't understand?
What will you do?
Will it affect our contract?
We've gone through so many struggles.
What's one more going to hurt?
Come on in.
What's wrong, Whan?
Come see for yourselves.
Careful. Slowly. Slowly.
Right in the middle there.
- Right there. Stop.
- Mr. Pitak.
What's this about?
Mr. Thee's orders.
When he heard Ms. Mook
would no longer work at The One,
he said--
I'll just work here instead.
We need to talk.
It's so obvious.
What is, Kemtit?
They're obviously flirting.
What kind of joke is this?
This is not your place.
Well, you wouldn't work at my place.
So I had to come here instead.
But I already said it all last night.
I was being very clear too.
I was being clear too.
Look,
I'm a woman who's been through a marriage
and failed with my love life.
I have a daughter to take care of,
and I have to be both her mom and her dad.
But I love this woman.
But I…
I don't love you.
I never thought of you that way.
But I already told the reporters
we're seeing each other,
so I have to ask you
to please act the part.
But you're well aware that it's not true.
Why should I
have to play along and pretend?
You can call it pretending or whatever,
but for me, I just said what I thought,
and I'll do everything to make it reality.
- But I--
- Aren't you presenting the marketing plan?
- Gosh.
- Whoa.
W-What are you standing around here for?
- Let's go to the meeting.
- Meeting, yeah.
- You're right.
- Hey, hey.
- This way.
- Oh, that way?
Don't be silly.
If you're available this evening,
may I speak to you?
Did you see the news on Kongkwan's mom?
She really hit the jackpot.
Ms. Prao.
We need to talk.
Congratulations, Mook.
Your guy's in the top-tier this time.
He's one of the richest businessmen.
You've got great taste.
I'm sure you know it's not true.
But that's what he said to the reporters.
How can I not believe it?
Then I hope you're ready to go to court
because that reporter's already named you.
As for anyone else involved,
Mr. Thee won't let you get off easy.
You think I'm scared?
You know who my father is.
Of course I do.
Everybody knows your father.
But if a minister's daughter
ends up in court
for something this stupid,
that should be a big scandal, right?
I heard your father's aiming
for a Grade A ministry this year too.
You dare threaten me?
I wasn't. I just wanted to inform you.
You'd better be ready too.
After all, you took the picture.
Here.
Kongkwan,
are you still upset with me?
Gino said you're going to remarry.
It's a lie, right?
It is.
You see how I work every day.
So who would I marry?
That's what I thought too.
And do you still love Daddy?
Poonpun told me his mom and dad
don't love each other anymore.
They always fight
whenever they're together,
and they aren't together anymore,
just like you and Daddy.
And if that's the case for me,
would it make you sad?
No, it wouldn't.
I'll still have you and Grandma.
But you have to promise me
you won't love anyone other than me.
I promise I'll love you only.
Come here.
Wanna eat something else?
Some french fries?
French fries it is.
Here you go.
Want some sauce? You want the sauce too?
‪Come on.
Good job!
Whose daughter is this?
Who's your mommy?
How do you feel about Mook?
What about you? How do you feel about her?
Mook and I are good friends.
We talk about everything,
and we get each other,
probably because we have a lot in common.
Your families, for one thing.
You must already know all about me.
Mook and I may have nothing in common,
but I insist that
I do have feelings for her
like a man likes a woman.
How well do you think you know her?
I'm well aware
that she's still afraid of love
and too scared to start over.
So how can you be sure
you won't hurt her just like before?
So this is why you're still confused
about your relationship with Mook.
You're afraid of getting hurt again too.
But for me,
when I'm serious about something,
I won't be afraid,
and I'll make sure I win.
I'll show Mook that love isn't scary.
Don't worry,
I'm serious about Mook.
So if you also like her
and wish to compete with me,
then by all means.
But if not,
get out of my way.
As for Ms. Primprao
being involved with that reporter,
I'll let it slide.
But you must tell her
to apologize to Mook.
You want me to apologize to Mook?
No way!
You made both her and my company look bad.
You're lucky Mr. Thee's not suing you.
I already told you
I'd make her life miserable.
My plan just went a little wrong,
so that single mom
hit the jackpot instead.
You have to apologize to her,
no matter what.
You have no right to ruin anyone's life.
But she has the right
to destroy my family?
How many times have I told you
Mook has nothing to do
with our family falling apart?
We're the ones who ruined
our own relationship.
Don't you get it, Prao?
We're the ones to blame!
We don't love each other anymore.
I'm tired of putting up with this.
I can't move forward,
but I can't fall back.
I think it's time to stop.
We should stop fighting
and just end things already.
Let's get a divorce, Prao.
You're just a coward
who won't admit the truth!
You just like Mook better than me.
This wouldn't have happened
if it weren't for her!
It's happened for a while now, Prao.
Even before I met Mook!
Just accept the truth, Prao.
We can't go on any further.
I'll get these files to Mr. Thee.
Can you set up a meeting
with the department heads?
Of course.
Mrs. Anna?
MRS. ANNA
As for the reception,
we haven't really been affected.
We've still had quite a few customers
calling us or coming
to the front desk to inquire
about the special campaign
you plan to promote.
That's good.
I think, if we capitalize on this crisis,
it'll be good for our hotel.
Yes.
- Mr. Pitak,
- Yes?
please tell Ms. Mook to summarize
this year's marketing plan
for servicing tourists.
Sure, Mr. Thee.
I want to scale our brand.
Apart from the hotel,
I want us to offer package tours
as another option
for our customers.
Mr. Pitak,
are you alright?
You don't look too good.
Mom.
John?
John.
John!
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I would've picked you up at the airport.
I just wanted to check on you,
see if you're hiding any secrets from me.
I've seen the news.
You were just signing a contract
with a supplier.
What's with all the fuss?
It was only for damage control.
That day, one of the reporters
tried to sabotage the event.
You mean the news
that you're dating that woman
is false?
You know,
I don't want to see you
in this kind of news again.
Whatever you do,
please think about Bell.
‪One more thing.
When there's this kind of news,
many of our stockholders will get upset
because it looks unprofessional
if you get involved
with someone you've hired.
Should we just change our supplier
to get it over with?
I'm afraid we can't.
I judged them fairly in the contest.
I chose A Round Trip Travel
because I saw that they're suitable.
They're capable.
They'll work well as our partner.
Or do you not believe in my judgment?
But the news that got out
makes our stockholders
see us as unprofessional.
Then, I'll prove it to you.
I'll make sure we reach our target
in the first quarter.
Surely the numbers
can reassure our stockholders, right?
Fine.
Well, I'm curious to see if that company
is any good, like you said.
Ma'am, how long do you plan to stay here?
I'll arrange your accommodation.
No need. I'm flying back right away.
Have the driver take me to the airport.
I hope you won't disappoint me, Thee.
I want to know
everything about that woman.
What was her name again?
It's Ms. Mook, ma'am.
Keep me updated on every situation.
Do you understand, Pitak?
Yes, Mrs. Anna.
You know, my boss chewed me out
for not fact-checking first.
What if we caught him lying?
What if those two weren't really together,
but only told a lie
to handle the situation?
If that's the case, Mr. Thee
would be seen as a fraud
who lied to spread fake news
and deceive people.
Boss.
If the performance evaluation needs
exact numbers, can we really do it?
These days, people like to travel
on their own without a travel agency.
- Mook.
- Yes?
What's your comment on this?
We'll have to adjust our plan to survive.
If we let it go on like this,
we're doomed.
We could plan a tour in Thailand.
Find tourist spots
that are interesting and underrated
and make it a special add-on deal
for customers at The One hotel.
What do you think, Boss?
Sounds interesting.
After all,
special campaigns made for couples
who are soon to be wed
are a hot topic currently.
We can also add on honeymoon packages.
They get married, then go
on their honeymoon. It's all-in-one.
Fabulous!
Start finding a spot.
Can I see?
This is really bad, guys.
The page "High-Class Gossip" just posted.
"Following the news on the relationship
of Mr. Businessman and Ms. Cinderella,
turns out it may have been
just a cover-up story.
We'll have to wait and see
what's real and what's fake."
Mr. Thee.
You've probably seen the news.
Yes.
It must've been that reporter.
She sure is tenacious.
How about this?
Since Mook and Mr. Thee
are already trending,
and everyone's watching,
especially the press,
why don't we just show them
you're actually in love?
No way!
Sure.
Right now, what we need is damage control,
because if there's another scandal,
we'll really be in trouble this time.
Mr. Thee is right.
If another scandal gets out,
there'll be more consequences.
But if you feel uncomfortable,
we'll try to find another way.
I started this trouble,
so I'm responsible for it.
We just have to make it look like
you and Mr. Thee are a real couple.
Not only will we fool the reporters,
we'll make you the faces
of our new campaign for lovers.
We'll kill two birds with one stone.
You've seen the news about Mook?
What news?
FAKE COUPLE! REAL LOVE OR A SHAM
If this is true, I still have a shot.
I mean,
our company still has a shot.
How's this related to our company?
Well, if this news
ruins The One's reputation,
it will be hard for A Round Trip.
So A Round Trip's contract
might get terminated.
And we'll be the only nominee left.
And this might be our last chance.
We can't mess up anymore.
How do I open this? Okay.
Let me drink that.
Were you in a marathon?
You look more wiped out
every time we meet.
If you count the work I'm doing,
it's even worse than a marathon.
Sure sounds like a lot of work.
I don't mind a lot of work.
There's just too many problems.
So,
what's the story about you and Mr. Thee?
It's really nothing.
That day, Mr. Thee said it
just as a cover up,
but that reporter just wouldn't stop.
Guess I'll have to play along for now.
Sure, keep playing along,
but one day, you'll end up
handing out wedding invitations.
Don't be silly. Like I would get married.
Wait, what about Ploy?
Didn't you invite her?
I'm going to tell Ploy
what your true nature is like.
Please go ahead.
Then I'll also tell Ploy
about your true nature.
What do you mean?
I mean that I have video evidence
to show Ploy her best friend's wild side.
Sorry, the number you've dialed
is currently unavailable--
Sorry, the number you've dialed--
Does she know?
I can't get ahold of her.
Do you think… she's okay?
Look, it's normal for newlyweds.
When I got married and moved to Kuk's,
I had to do all kinds of chores.
Next thing I know, I'm already passed out.
Give her some time to settle in.
Right.
Hey,
or is there something
you two haven't told me?
Of course not!
I'm just worried about her.
Aren't you hungry?
Don't go finishing my drink.
Order something.
You almost drank it all.
What should I get?
Where'd you park your car?
I parked it at my office.
I took a motorcycle taxi.
Oh? Then I'll drive you to your office.
Okay.
Aren't you going to introduce me, honey?
What are you doing?
I'm Khim, Mook's best friend.
I've heard about you.
First time seeing you in person.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Thee.
You already told her about us?
Well, of course, everyone knows you now.
We're all over the headlines.
Let go already.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Khim.
Are you two leaving?
Yes,
- I was about to drive her to her office.
- Let's go.
No worries. I'll drive her myself.
Of course.
‪-No.
‪-I'll see you later then. See ya.
- Khim!
- Goodbye.
- Wait, Khim!
What are you doing?
Come on. Act the part.
The paparazzi are filming us.
Really?
Where?
Hey, don't be suspicious.
Let's go.
Hey, I'm not a prisoner.
Why are you watching me work?
I'm waiting to drive you home.
Drive me?
Why? You don't have to.
I can go home myself.
What if that paparazzi is still around?
Hey.
Aren't they invading our privacy
a little too much?
I promise I'll sit and wait quietly.
I won't bother you.
And once you're done with work,
I'll drive you home.
Okay? Sound good?
Darn it.
You're back?
Oh, Mom.
Work's so busy lately.
You don't have to wait for me.
I was just waiting with Kongkwan.
She only gave up and went to bed just now.
She kept saying she'd wait for you.
Right. Here, Mook.
The school's sent us a letter
inviting parents to see
the students showcasing their work.
Okay, Mom. I'll try to make it.
That's good.
Kongkwan will be so happy.
She kept telling me
not to forget to tell you.
Okay.
I'm going to bed now. Lock up
and turn off the lights for me, okay?
- Good night, Mom.
- Good night.
Get lots of rest, honey.
Walk pretty. Walk pretty and hold hands.
Mook!
Smile, please. Big smile.
Not a forced smile. A pretty smile.
Can we be done now?
Smile nicely. Look sweeter.
Do we really have to do all this?
Isn't this a bit much?
Hold on, hold on.
Hey.
"A bit much" is good.
We need the photos for promotion.
Smile nicely. Smile.
- Show your teeth.
- Yes.
There.
You look great already. Gosh, I like him.
Okay, this time,
I want some teasing. Make it look cute.
Wait, hey!
What are you doing?
Tell yourself it's for your job.
Wonderful!
Enough.
Let's go.
Smile, Mook.
- Mook, smile!
- Have I not smiled enough?
- Yeah!
- No. Be sweet and look at the camera.
- Quick!
- Yeah.
Too close.
You're really good, Whan. And smart too.
We get to take CSR photos too
while we're here.
It wasn't my idea.
Mr. Thee chose this place.
No wonder he's a successful businessman.
Just imagine, once their photos are posted
with them helping orphans,
showing they love kids,
they'll get so many likes and shares.
Businessmen really do
calculate every move, huh?
Mr. Thee is hot, rich, capable, and smart.
He's so good in every way.
Only thing is,
he never sees me.
- The hell are you doing?
- Looking at you, of course.
I'm looking at you deeply.
I've been for a while now.
You think I can replace him?
You done setting it up?
No.
Just a second.
But
where's Mook and Mr. Thee?
Oh. Oh!
Mr. Thee said he's taking Mook
to see someone he really respects.
They should be back soon.
He even took her to meet the elders?
I guess it's over for me.
Ice cream, please. I need lots of sugar.
PIAMSUK ORPHANAGE
This is Ms. Tassanee.
She's both the teacher, the mother,
and the owner of this place.
Hello.
Sai-- Thee, so this is the woman
you told me about.
Make yourself at home.
Thee comes here a lot.
From now on, Ms.…
My name's Mook.
You'll probably come
with him often, Ms. Mook.
You seem familiar with this place.
Do you do CSR activities here a lot?
He's fostered many of the children here.
We're very grateful to him
for helping our disadvantaged children.
We appreciate it.
You're welcome.
I hope you don't mind us
using the place today.
Not at all.
This place is like your home.
Go right ahead.
Okay.
We should be going, then.
The team is waiting.
- Okay.
- Go ahead, Ms. Mook.
Please.
- I'll follow you.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Here you go.
You seem close to Ms. Tassanee.
Yes.
If it weren't for her,
I wouldn't be where I am today.
I mean,
she's taught me many things,
so I think of her like my second mom.
No wonder you come here a lot.
On our pilot trip, I was wondering
why you chose this place for the program.
Now I understand.
- Yes.
- Mook.
Mook.
Can you feed him? Make it look sweet.
You can feed him now.
- Do it.
- Can we keep handing it out now?
- Go ahead.
Excuse me, miss.
I found this kid
standing there crying outside my house.
I didn't know what to do,
so I brought him here,
in case you can help him.
What happened, sweetie?
Take your time and tell me.
There was a fire at my house.
My little brother was stuck inside.
I couldn't get him out.
Don't blame yourself.
It was an accident.
It's good that you're safe.
- Don't be scared.
- You're okay.
What's your name?
My name is Saifah.
Where are your parents?
Mom said she was going to buy us food.
But… But
she never came back.
Tawan, my brother, he's dead.
It's alright, sweetie.
Mook!
You've got a nosebleed.
- Hold on.
- Wait, Mr. Thee!
My friends are making fun of me.
They say my mom's going to remarry.
I don't want her to remarry.
I don't want my mom to be sad.
Because I got to see
just how much love
Mook has for her daughter.
I want to protect their feelings.
But I hope you haven't forgotten
that you already have someone.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya