( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Hey!
Don't leave me.
I can't breathe! Mr. Thee!
Get off me!
Hey.
Boss? Boss-- Mr. Thee!
Boss!
How could you do this?
You're not a gentleman!
Mook? You'll regret this.
Come on, Mr. Thee.
Don't leave me like that.
WELCOMING CEREMONY
MR. THEECHUDA TEERASU
Mr. Thee,
about yesterday, there was
a little misunderstanding,
- so I wanted to--
- To your company.
What?!
Where'd you want to go?
You're heading
to your company, aren't you?
I'll tag along.
I'm checking it out to assess
your company's credibility,
so I can make my decision.
Of course.
What are you looking at?
Why the serious look?
Just a job search.
Job search?
Are you quitting?
Well, after Boss caused that scene,
it's definitely over for our company.
MR. THEE IS HEADING TO OUR OFFICE
Mr. Thee's here. Mr. Thee's here!
Where is he? Mr. Thee? Where?
Mr. Thee?
- Mr. Thee?
- Sis!
Mook texted me
that he's heading to our office.
Why didn't you just say that? Gosh.
I just did.
Where are you going?
Making some coffee to welcome him.
So Mr. Thee's gone?
But you told us we'd get to interview him.
I'm really sorry.
He had something urgent come up.
What a waste of time.
I should've done the other gig.
- Let's go.
- What a waste of time.
- Quick, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
- Big waste of time.
How could he do this, Mr. Pitak?
This is costing us.
I apologize for this.
But you should've known
that Mr. Thee doesn't like a big fuss.
Especially reporters.
And in that program you sent us,
you never mentioned
the press would be here.
I must apologize.
I figured it'd be good PR for Mr. Thee,
and The One would get
some media coverage too.
But if we've upset Mr. Thee,
we'll go apologize to him in person.
If you'll excuse me.
He really went with Mook?
She went too far,
stealing our client right in front of us.
I won't stand for this.
May all evil stay away.
May only fortune come to my family.
Bless us with wealth and riches.
Yeah.
Please grant Kuk success
at his work today.
Let the client be happy and pleased,
so he can beat Mook's company.
Please accept my offerings.
If he really wins this,
I'll give you even bigger offerings!
USA
The incense isn't even out yet,
and it's already working?
Hello, Usa.
Our company won, right?
What?
Damn you, Mook!
There, here he comes!
- Really?
- Yeah!
I'm going, then.
This way, please, Mr. Thee. Good morning.
He's so hot!
This way, Mr. Thee.
A Round Trip Travel.
We treat you like family.
Great tours, no cancellations.
Welcome!
Mr. Thee doesn't like formalities.
You can relax, guys.
Okay.
Mr. Thee,
this is Ms. May and Mr. Kemtit.
They're on our sales team.
Hi.
Come on.
Hello. Welcome.
And this is Whan, our creative director.
Hello.
And this is Mr. Suetrong, our accountant.
Our boss is in a meeting,
so he isn't here to welcome you.
He sent his apologies.
That's alright. I came on short notice.
Besides, I'm not ready to meet him yet.
Then, my team will give you
a tour of our office.
I'll handle the tour, Mr. Thee.
I hate formalities too.
I'm just like you.
Let me give you a tour. Easy--
This way, please.
Please, right this way.
Hey, tone it down already.
He just hates formalities.
It doesn't mean you have
to throw yourself at him.
That hurts.
Mook, does this mean he chose us?
Mook!
Mook, watch out!
I have to go talk to Mook.
What she did cost our company a lot.
Trying to win this way
is simply dirty work.
I don't think you need to go now.
Why, Usa?
If I don't go, the problem won't end.
Because I already sent someone
to talk to her.
What do you mean?
This is nothing compared
to your dirty little tricks!
What are you on about, Auntie?!
I can call the cops on you for that!
Call them, then. I'm not scared.
This girl deserves it.
You cheaters!
Want to win so bad that you stole
our client with no shame?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Shouldn't you be asking Kuk?
How'd he go so wrong
to make his client run off like that?
You haven't changed a bit.
You never admit you're wrong,
always blaming everyone!
This is exactly why
Kuk couldn't stand you!
He ended up like that
because he has a mother like you.
No, it's because you were a lousy wife!
You never supported your husband.
All you did was sabotage him!
You're nothing but bad luck.
From the day you stepped into our house
up to this day, you still are!
I'll teach you a lesson today!
- Hey!
- Hey, hey!
- No!
I was the one who called her.
She didn't do anything.
Who are you? Mind your own business!
So you're her other man?
You're juggling two at once?
How "around the world" of you!
Shameless skank!
Ma, what are you doing here?
Mr. Thee. Mook.
I never thought you'd use
this kind of dirty trick.
You wanted the deal so bad
you had to steal him from us?
How shameless can you be?
If anyone here is shameless,
it’s definitely not me.
Besides, I don't need dirty tricks
to beat someone like you.
- Damn you, Mook!
- Hey!
Mr. Thee, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Why don't you all leave?
What happened has nothing to do with Mook.
- It was my decision.
- But…
And I'm currently evaluating
both your companies.
Let's leave, Ma.
I'm not leaving.
We have to settle this today!
You shameless skank!
- Freaking bitch!
- Ma.
- Kuk!
- How dare you?!
Cheater! Shamelessly stealing
other people's clients!
- Don't just stand there.
- Cheater! Bitch!
Take her home already!
- No!
- Ma, let's go home.
- Ma!
- No!
I hope you'll make
a fair decision, Mr. Thee.
Alright, kids, please get into groups.
I want groups of five.
I have a game for you to play. Understood?
- Understood.
Start getting into groups.
I'll be right back.
Go ahead, form your groups.
This way.
Satang,
wanna be in a group?
My mom told me
that your mom's a bad person.
I don't want to be with you.
Why are you insulting my mom?
My mom said that too,
that your mom's a bad person.
She's dating many guys at once.
Stop insulting her.
She never did any of that.
But it's true!
If you don't believe us,
why don't you ask your mom?
Kongkwan, don't!
Did you just push me?
- Satang, calm down!
- Satang, Satang!
- Satang!
- Everyone, stop!
- Stop! Stop it!
What's going on here?
She pushed me first!
She insulted my mom.
She said my mom's a bad person.
But it's true!
Calm down. Let's speak one at a time.
WELCOME - RAGE ROOM
STRESSED? ANGRY? LET IT OUT
Why'd you bring me here?
You don't have to act tough all the time.
You can let it out sometimes.
I…
Hey!
Are you mad at that auntie?
Hey.
When you're angry,
you need to find a way to handle it.
If you can't handle that auntie,
you have to handle your emotions.
You're nothing but bad luck.
From the day you stepped into our house
up to this day, you still are!
Are we going on vacation?
Yes.
We're going to Grandma's house.
You like that house, right?
Yes! She's so kind. She always makes
something delicious for me.
Isn't Daddy coming with us?
Kongkwan, honey.
I'm taking care of you from now on.
Ms. Mook and Mr. Apichart
were married before.
They started
Family Tour and Travel together,
but…
What is it?
They're divorced now.
She now works with Mr. Anapat
at A round Trip Travel.
But they're both still business rivals.
They had a child.
She's in Ms. Mook's custody.
A child?
Yes.
A daughter.
She's still very young, too.
That's all the information I got.
Okay. Thank you.
Of course.
How was it? Feeling better?
I'm feeling a lot better.
I never knew there were places like this.
Here. Let me help.
From now on, if you're hurt, just say so.
You can't take it, just say so.
Stop forcing yourself, okay?
Hello.
Okay, got it. I'll be right over.
I should go. I have to rush
to my daughter's school.
Let me drive you.
But…
Aren't you in a rush?
You have to discipline Kongkwan.
She can't use force like that.
Does no one at home teach her?
Before you complain, why don't we
hear the whole story first?
Please continue, Teacher.
I asked the students
to form a group for an activity.
Then, Kongkwan had a fight
with her classmates.
She said Satang and Gino made fun of her.
Made fun of her? About what?
They said…
that you're a bad person
who dates many men.
Something like that.
Did you tell your kids that nonsense?
I'm sure kids
can't think that on their own.
I didn't say anything much.
I just told them what I saw.
That's all. They probably remembered it.
You're saying those things
when you don't even know the truth.
You two have no right to judge me.
Alright,
it's bad enough
that the kids are fighting.
We don't need to fight too.
I asked you all to come here today
because I don't want your issues
to cause trauma for the kids.
After all, they're at an age
where they're old enough
to understand things.
I must apologize, Teacher,
but none of it is true.
I'll explain it to my daughter.
I must ask you to be more careful.
Whatever kids shouldn't hear,
please don't say it when they're near.
Children may not be able
to differentiate things.
I'll let it slide this time
because what happened
was caused by adults,
so we shouldn't blame it on the kids.
I just hope adults like us
can set a good example for the kids,
and I hope this kind of thing
won't happen again.
- Okay.
Okay.
‪FOR SCHOOL DIRECTORS AND ADMINISTRATORS
Don't cry, Kongkwan.
I'll be right by your side.
I won't cry because I know
my mom's not like that.
Of course she is!
That's what my mom said.
Kongkwan, honey.
Kongkwan,
did you push your friend?
Yes. But Satang insulted you first.
And do you believe what she said?
Exactly.
What she said isn't true.
But you pushed her,
and you hurt her, so what should you do?
Apologize.
Go.
I'm sorry.
Gino and Satang,
you have to say sorry
for making fun of her, too.
- I'm sorry.
If there's nothing else,
we'll be going now.
Let's go, honey.
Let's go.
Come on, Poonpun. Let's go.
Come on. Say goodbye to your teacher.
Thank you, Teacher.
I'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
Okay.
Let's go.
Daddy.
How'd it go, Mook?
We worked it out. Everything's fine.
How are you?
- Are you hungry?
- Yes?
I'll be going now.
Let's talk about work later.
But…
Are you mad at me?
No. Not at all,
but if anyone says anything again,
come tell me first, okay?
What happened, Mook?
I'll tell you later.
Guys, do we want pizza today?
Yes! I want pizza!
What about you, Kongkwan?
- Okay, then let's go.
- Let's go.
- What should we get?
- I don't know.
Are you hungry, Kongkwan?
- Cheese pizza?
- Sure.
Same as always.
- Why not try a different topping?
- Let's go.
- No, thanks, I like the usual.
- No?
What were you doing at the school?
I went there with Mook.
And why exactly did you go there with her?
When you disappeared this morning,
things got so chaotic over there.
I called and asked Mook to pick me up.
And…
What is it, sir?
Forget it. It's a long story.
Mr. Pitak,
please arrange for both companies
to hear my decision.
I've made up my mind.
Sure, Mr. Thee.
Here.
Mook,
I heard there was a commotion
at our office?
Are you alright?
About Kuk's mother causing a scene, right?
I'm used to it now.
Your haters will hate you,
no matter how good you behave.
I think it depends on the person,
but if they only act on emotion
and not reason,
it's probably hard to fix.
Mook,
why'd Mr. Thee want to come
to our office today?
He called, asking me to pick him up
from Family Tour's trip.
He was probably unhappy,
so he wanted me to take him away.
Why did it have to be you?
I bet he's still angry
that I had a fight with him the other day,
yet still he asked you to pick him up?
Don't you think
he's acting a little strange?
Maybe it's because I called
to make an appointment with him earlier.
I wanted to clear the air
about that fight the other day.
It's probably just good timing.
Is it good, honey?
Is it good, Poonpun?
It's so good.
Want some french fries?
Sure. Here.
Here you go.
Go to sleep, my good girl.
You have to get up early to go to school.
Mommy.
What's up?
You won't have many boyfriends
like they said, right?
Is Daddy your boyfriend too?
Kongkwan,
even if Mommy and Daddy
aren't together anymore,
we'll still be your mommy and daddy.
Go to sleep, okay?
Mommy will sleep holding you tonight.
Can I?
Come on.
Why'd Mr. Thee want to come
to our office today?
I bet he's still angry
that I had a fight with him the other day.
Don't you think
he's acting a little strange?
You did your best.
It's okay if we don't win. Don't worry.
Oh my.
Yesterday you were all sweet
with that guy, and now it's this guy.
How many more do you have
left in stock, Mook?
Have a little respect, would you?
Act like you deserve it, then.
Don't go smooching in a place like this.
Should I sneak around and sleep with him
in a five-star hotel like you two did?
Is that what you call
dignified and honorable?
Mr. Thee, I can explain about yesterday.
That's alright.
To me, taking care of your clients
is more important than your tour programs.
If that's the case,
you don't have to worry.
We're confident our service is number one.
Shouldn't we let him decide that?
Mr. Thee has invited
both your companies here today
to announce the winner
of the You Are The One project.
The winner will get to sign
a contract with us.
First of all, I'd like to thank
both your companies
for doing your best in the contest.
Let me preface by saying
that I've never judged anyone
based on their background
because it's in the past.
What do you mean by that?
I mean that I will make my decision
based on what I got
and what I experienced firsthand only.
And the company
that will sign a contract with us is…
A Round Trip Travel.
- Mook.
- Boss!
What did Family Tour do wrong?
You failed completely.
Understanding the customer
is crucial in this line of work.
I want to work with a travel agency
that prioritizes
their clients' preferences, needs,
and identity
rather than organize
a big, fancy tour in hopes of winning.
You should've known
that Mr. Thee doesn't like a big fuss.
Especially reporters.
And in that program you sent us,
you never mentioned
the press would be here.
You'll regret underestimating us.
He had a lot of hope for this project.
I apologize on his behalf, Mr. Thee.
Congrats, but we'll definitely see
each other again, Mook.
Thank you for giving
A Round Trip Travel a chance.
I must apologize about that day.
That's alright. It was a misunderstanding.
You should thank your employee instead.
Your company only won today
because she has the qualifications I need.
Mr. Thee!
May I have a moment?
I wanted to thank you for yesterday.
Is everything alright?
Yes.
You must be tired,
being a single mom
and still having to work.
You know about me?
Yes, I know about you and Mr. Apichart.
I need to know the background
of all my partners.
It's only natural.
There's nothing wrong
with being a single mom.
And no matter what state I'm in,
I'd do anything for my daughter
so she'd grow up to be the happiest.
Of course.
At least you're a good mom.
Your daughter must be really proud of you,
unlike some mothers
who only care about themselves
and never wonder how their child is doing.
Mook. There you are.
I told everyone the result.
We're celebrating after work tonight.
If you don’t mind,
I’d like to invite you to join us.
Mr. Thee doesn't really like big crowds.
I see.
It seems I'll have to learn
about customer analysis from Mook.
Thank you, Mook.
We finally did it.
I told you we'd win, no matter what.
Did you book the tables yet?
I did.
MRS. OH
Hello, Mrs. Oh.
Did you enjoy your vacation?
I enjoyed it so much
that it's hard to express.
I have something to show you.
I'll send it to you.
My mom won't mind
If you wanna make a move
- Whoo! My mom won't mind.
- La la la
Ba ba ba
Heck yeah! Go, go!
She'll hand me over
My mom won't mind… Not you, though.
Future son-in-law
Let's drink to our victory!
Here's to the toughness and resilience
of our badass manager, Ms. Mook!
- Yeah.
- Right.
- Hear, hear.
- A Round Trip Travel, we slay!
- Yeah!
Bottoms up!
What?
What a shame. Mr. Thee should've come.
Mr. Thee's not here.
How about Mr. Tit for now?
- Oh my.
- Wow.
Look at him.
You're nothing alike.
You're like the sky and the abyss,
heaven and hell.
Looks like fun.
Can I join?
Prao.
Hello, Ms. Prao.
I can't get ahold of Pat.
Is he at the office?
He went to a meeting with a client.
He isn't back yet.
Please check his schedule for me.
I'm inviting him
to an association event tonight.
Tonight, he's having
a celebration party with us
because we won the pitch.
I just booked the restaurant.
That's okay. Just send me the location.
I'll send a gift to congratulate him.
Of course.
Why didn't you tell me you're coming?
Well, then it wouldn't be a surprise.
I wanted to congratulate you all today.
Have a blast, everyone. It's all on me.
Hey.
Good evening, Mook.
Good evening, Ms. Prao.
If only I could have you back
Just to buy a little more time
Even one minute would mean so much to me
- Shut it!
- I beg of you
Alone
Drink up! Why are you so quiet?
Sure.
Another glass.
A Round Trip Travel.
Come on.
Mr. Pitak, do you know where
A Round Trip Travel is celebrating?
I'd like to officially congratulate
all of you again.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I bet this was thanks
to Mook again, right?
We work as a team,
so I think it's thanks to everyone.
But I brought a special gift just for you.
Excuse me.
REWARD FOR BEST HUSBAND-STEALER
What are you doing, Prao?
Congratulating this girl
who's so good at everything, of course.
Especially at stealing husbands.
Prao, stop imagining things.
Mook and I aren't what you think we are!
Then what's this?
She's dating both of you at once,
so you had to fight over her.
So this picture was enough
for you to assume it all?
Did you ever think to ask me
what happened earlier?
Why should I?
She's using work as a cover.
I'm not stupid. I know her game!
Hey.
If you're not stupid,
pull yourself together.
Don't just believe
what you see or hear them say.
- Stop it!
- Prao!
You think I wouldn't touch you
because Pat's backing you up?
- Prao, stop it!
- Let go!
- Hey! Hey!
- Ms. Prao!
- Prao!
- You keep blaming other people
for destroying your family,
but you never see your own faults.
You never thought about changing
to save your family!
Take a look at yourself!
Have you done your best?
Ask yourself before blaming everyone!
Don't act all wise now.
I know you want to steal my husband!
- Calm down, Ms. Prao!
- Prao!
I… I…
I think you should take
Ms. Primprao home, Mr. Pat.
Prao, let's talk at home.
I'm not leaving.
I have to settle this with her today,
so she'd stop taking what's mine!
Let go of me!
Prao!
If you didn't exist,
my husband wouldn't be this way!
Remember that, Mook!
Let go!
Mook, are you okay?
Mook. Mook, Mook.
Mook. Mook!
Where are you going?
Should I come with you?
It's okay. I want to be alone.
Mr. Suetrong, please handle things here.
Got it.
Mook, I…
Thank you.
Why do you always see me
when I'm in this state?
I'm rather happy
to see you when you're in this state.
At least, I feel like
I can be your support.
Whatever's bugging you,
can you tell me about it?
Sometimes when you get to vent,
it might help you feel better.
It's just a little misunderstanding.
Ms. Prao, my boss' wife,
she misunderstood me.
We ran a background check on Mr. Anapat,
CEO of A Round Trip Travel.
There's nothing of concern.
He's got a clean track record.
Working with him should be no problem.
You said he's married?
Yes, he's married.
They have a son. His wife is Ms. Primprao.
She's the daughter of Mr. Pansak,
the famous politician.
Is it about what happened
at the school that day too?
My daughter,
she goes to the same school
as my boss' son.
Because we're so close,
Ms. Prao misunderstood us.
And your relationship with Mr. Pat,
what's it like?
He's both my boss
and someone I can talk to about anything.
We're just good friends.
It's really late. If you'll excuse me.
As for the robe,
I'll return it after it's washed.
Wait.
I can't let you go home in this state.
Follow me.
Sorry, do you have other ones that's--
I think this one looks great.
We'll buy this one.
I'll bag up your old clothes for you.
Sorry, how much is it?
Four thousand nine hundred.
I'll buy a different one, then.
Is there any that's cheaper?
It's fine.
Just buy me dinner someday.
Are you sure you won't send me
a bill later like last time?
Yes, Boss?
I'm alright.
I'm with Mr. Thee now.
I thought we were clear, Prao.
If you keep this up, I won't stand for it.
You won't? I'm the one
who's standing for it!
Even a three-year-old
can tell she likes you!
Fire her and I'll stop.
No! Mook's done nothing wrong.
She’s always given her all for my company.
You're always defending her.
How far have you two really gone?
Can you stop having those filthy thoughts?
Mook and I have never slept together.
And let me tell you this.
Leave her alone.
Don't ever accuse her again,
or you will regret it.
Try me, then.
I'll make sure she pays,
and your stupid travel agency
will suffer too!
Pat, stop! Pat!
Don't you walk away!
Pat!
- So what is it?
- What does it mean?
- How'd you two meet?
- Mr. Thee.
Ms. Veluree and I are seeing each other.
Her company only won
because she slept with him.
It's all over the news now.
Mr. Thee's dating her.
Can I see?
I want an answer…
that comes from your true feelings.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya