( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Mook!
You've got a nosebleed.
- Hold on.
- Wait, Mr. Thee!
My friends are making fun of me.
They say my mom's going to remarry.
I don't want her to remarry.
I don't want my mom to be sad.
Because I got to see
just how great the love
Mook has for her daughter is.
I want to protect their feelings.
Well, I hope you haven't forgotten
that you already have someone.
TOR'S GARAGE
MR. PAT
Boss, my car broke down at The One.
Okay. See you soon, Boss.
I'm leaving my car here.
Mr. Pat will take care of it.
We brought this for you.
Next time, you don't have
to bring anything.
We're already happy to see you two.
- Have a seat.
- Yes.
Thank you for taking good care
of our daughter, Top.
- My pleasure.
- How about you, Ploy?
How have you been?
Did you trouble him in any way?
Not at all.
She's a really good wife,
and she takes great care of me.
If I'd known being married to her
would be this great,
I would've had Pa talk to you sooner.
That's great. Keep your love strong.
Help each other out when in need.
And you too, Ploy.
Take good care of him, okay?
Remember to forgive each other,
and don't forget
to give me a grandchild soon.
Of course.
How are you?
Who did this to you, Preaw?
Can you tell me?
Even if I told you,
there's nothing you can do, Khim.
After all, you're one
of Top's victims too.
So… you knew?
Yeah.
I saw your video on his phone.
At first, he was a really good man.
He spoiled me in every way.
But before long, he changed…
from someone good to a complete monster.
He threatened me
that if I told anyone he beat me,
he'd leak the video he secretly took of me
to expose me online.
At first, I thought it was just a threat.
But it turned out
that scumbag would actually do it.
Did you know he was married?
At first, I didn't know,
but then I found out,
so I broke up with him.
He wouldn't let me.
And he even told me
it's not just me and his wife.
There are other girls too.
From then on, he started beating me,
threatening me, and abusing me.
It's exactly like what you've heard.
That's how that scumbag threatened me too.
You have to be careful, Khim.
He's a very scary guy.
He's got videos
of every girl he's slept with.
He'd do anything
to make everyone obey his orders.
PLOY
KHIM
Don't you dare tell anyone
about what's going on at home,
or you'll regret it.
Hello? Ploy!
Hello. What's up, Khim?
How have you been lately?
I haven't seen you in a while.
Are you okay?
I'm…
I'm doing alright.
How are you?
I'm doing alright too.
How come I can't get hold of you lately?
Busy with work?
Yeah, work's been busy.
I haven't had a chance to talk to anyone.
And also…
Also what?
It's normal.
I'm used to it now.
Year-end closing times are always busy.
Ploy.
It's been a while.
Can we meet sometime?
Of course.
So, tomorrow, at our usual place?
I miss you both.
Thank you for taking care of my car, Boss.
So you've thought it through?
Sorry?
Normally, if your car broke down,
you'd be able to handle it easily
on your own.
You never had to call me.
But this time, you wanted
to prove a point to Mr. Thee, right?
That's why you called me.
You sure know me well.
Well, it's probably the best way
to make him understand
that I've made my decision.
Yeah.
Let's go, honey. Mind your hand.
Mommy!
I'm back.
Good evening.
- Good evening.
- Good evening, Uncle.
Mook's car broke down,
so I offered to drive her.
I see. Thank you very much.
Why don't you have dinner with us?
That's alright.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Sure.
Thanks again, Boss.
Of course.
- Good night, ma'am.
- Good night.
Say goodbye to Uncle Pat. Let's go.
- Let's eat.
- Good night.
Wash your hands first, okay?
Walk slowly, Kongkwan!
Bye.
Wait for your mommy!
Yes, Mom.
What's up?
- Hey!
- Could be the starter or the battery.
You know, how about I drive you?
I'll have Mr. Pitak take care of your car.
Thank you,
but no thank you.
Why am I thinking of him?
Stop thinking, Mook. Stop, stop, stop.
If you're making me apologize to her,
you can just leave,
because I'd never do that.
But you started it all, Prao!
You almost destroyed my company.
You're lucky Mr. Thee didn't sue.
It's still just "almost".
It's not destroyed yet, the way I want it!
- Prao!
- What?!
Can you two stop fighting?
Pun.
I see you and Mommy fighting all the time.
Why do you have to fight?
Don't you love each other anymore?
He's the one who stopped loving me.
Seriously, Prao?
Can't you see our son's upset?
Mommy and Daddy
were having a little disagreement,
so we had to settle it.
It's like when I have a fight
with my friends, right?
My teacher told us to hold hands
and apologize to each other,
so that we wouldn't fight again.
I'll try my best.
Hey. How about this?
We will take you on a vacation.
- It's been a while, hasn't it?
- Really?
Are we really going on vacation?
- You're not lying to me, right, Mommy?
- No.
Is it true, Daddy?
THEE
Are you coming out,
or do you want me to go inside?
Why are you doing this? I--
Hey!
Can you stand still just for a minute?
Let me recharge my energy.
Did something happen?
I have a very important event coming up.
So I wanted your energy.
Thank you.
I'm okay now.
Are you sure
that you're okay?
Yes.
Go get some rest.
I've contacted the investor
who wanted to invest in our hotel.
He wanted to meet with you,
Mrs. Narin. Are you available?
We'd better decide soon.
With our situation,
we won't be able to cope for long.
Did he make any offers?
What type of investment is it going to be?
He wants as many of our shares
as we can sell him
because he's very eager
to invest in our hotel.
Who is he, Mr. Chadchai? Can you tell me?
I suggest you go speak to him yourself.
Okay.
I wanted to hear his comments anyway.
Hi.
There's something off about you.
You two kept making fun of me,
so I tried a trendy makeup look.
Does it look good?
What about Mook? Isn't she coming?
She's kind of busy lately,
so she couldn't come.
I never got to see you
since you got married.
How's it been? Everything okay?
I'm okay.
I'm doing so fine.
Top's been really good to me.
Married life is actually not so bad.
I must've won the lottery,
like you both said.
Did you hear?
Preaw submitted a resignation letter.
I just visited her.
She didn't say anything about quitting.
She submitted it just a few days
before being hospitalized.
No one knows why, though.
I think it must've had
something to do with that guy.
I feel bad for her.
Her career was going well.
Ploy, I've got something to tell you.
TOP
Hey, I just remembered
I have a date with Top.
Let's meet again soon. I'll call you.
Ploy! Ploy, Wait!
Opposite this house is like a slum.
Unacceptable.
Why buy a house so far from town
if it's going to be this sunny?
You sure came a long way. Are you tired?
For me, it's no hassle,
but it really was a long way.
So, what brought you all the way here?
I'll be frank with you.
I wanted to warn you about how
your daughter's been behaving.
You must've seen the news
about your naughty daughter,
how she attracted those guys.
You know, it really
isn't any of my business,
but I came to warn you
because she's still my son's ex-wife
and my granddaughter's mom.
You are a mother too.
I'm sure you understand.
Actually, it's Mook's personal life,
and she's already divorced your son.
Also,
when Kuk did a bad thing
and cheated on her,
I never got involved.
So, I don't think
you should worry about her.
Just take good care of your son.
I see where she got her stubbornness from.
I just wanted to warn her
not to be so obnoxious.
If you won't do it for Kuk,
at least do it for Kongkwan!
I just don't want her to be embarrassed
to have a mom like that.
Even the door's sticking. Fix it sometime.
Whan told me you wanted to see me.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just wanted to ask
if I could take a couple days off.
Is there anything urgent planned?
You're the CEO here.
Why are you asking for my approval?
There's nothing urgent coming up.
There's just our campaign with The One.
I can handle it. You don't have to worry.
Prao wanted me
to take Poonpun on a vacation.
Really? Does that mean
you've worked things out?
It's still the same as always.
We barely got a few words in
before we started fighting.
What should I do, Mook?
I can't even deal
with my own problems, Boss.
But to be honest, in my case,
there was no way
we could go back to normal.
But in your case,
you two might still
be able to stay together.
Don't you think?
To be honest, Mook,
I'm only doing this for my son.
But when two people must stay together
because of a responsibility,
not because of love,
it just seems so fragile,
like it'll easily fall apart.
But in the end,
no matter how it turns out,
at least you'll have tried
your best for your son.
Where were you?
I was at work, of course.
I called your work.
They said you asked to leave early.
Why'd you have to call my work to check?
Why do you never respect me?
Don't change the topic.
I asked you, where were you today?
Give me that.
Top! That's mine!
Here's your milk, Mom.
Thank you, honey.
Is something wrong?
You seem a little stressed.
Mrs. Tiansee was here today.
Why was she here?
Did she say something
to make you feel bad?
Is it about the news?
I need to go talk to her tomorrow.
All this back-and-forth
won't do you any good.
Let's just leave her alone.
If she wants to be spiteful,
then it's up to her.
We just have to do our best,
so she won't be able to insult us.
Okay, Mom.
I'm well aware what I should do or not do.
Get plenty of rest, honey.
- I'm going to bed.
- Okay.
I went to Mook's house today.
Mook's house? Why, Ma?
Well, I just couldn't stand it,
having an ex-daughter-in-law
who's involved in so many scandals.
That's good, Ma.
It's time someone said something.
There's news about her
and Mr. Thee every day.
I don't really care, but I just feel bad
for Kuk's daughter,
for having her as a mom.
MOOK
Ma, Mook called me.
I've got it.
Why are you calling your ex?
What do you want?
It's good that you answered.
I wanted to talk to Kuk,
but talking to you directly is better.
Just tell me what you want. I'm eating.
I beg of you, from now on,
if you're going to talk about me,
come say it to me.
Leave my mom alone.
I don't want her to be upset.
Then behave yourself!
Stop acting like a dirty toilet
in front of your house.
I never should've let my son marry you.
Hello? Hello?
Look at her, hanging up on me like that.
Here.
How rude! Just you wait.
I'll never stop making her life miserable.
Damn her for making my son sad.
I'll keep going after her.
Is something wrong?
I see now why Preaw quit.
Her leaked video's everywhere online.
And worst of all,
someone sent it to our airline.
Actually, Preaw got fired,
but our airline's hushing it up,
saying she quit on her own.
I'm sure this has to do with that Top guy.
Scumbag. All you can do is harass women.
Khim, where are you going?
Screw it. Whatever happens, happens.
Hello, ma'am.
Hello. Khim,
can you take me to the hospital?
- Is someone hurt?
- Ploy's hospitalized.
What?! What did you say?
Ploy's hospitalized.
Let's go.
Who did this to you? Tell me.
- There you are, Ma.
- Yes, Top.
- Good afternoon.
Just a small accident, Ma.
I didn't call you at first
because I didn't want to scare you.
It's okay.
You were clumsy, weren't you?
You're all bruised up.
I got lightheaded, Ma,
then I fainted and hit a table.
That's how I got this cut on my head.
Are you sure you fell, Ploy?
Why are you asking that?
This is Khim. She's my friend.
Is this
the friend that came to our wedding,
but left early, like you said?
Hello, Ms. Khim.
Nice to meet you.
But on our wedding day,
why didn't you stay until the end?
We missed our photo op.
What a shame.
Anyway, it's good that you're okay.
From now on, whatever you do,
please be more careful.
Please don't scold her, Ma.
And please don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
Okay. Thank you so much
for taking good care of her, Top.
What were you doing, though?
Can I help you?
I was just going to peel her some fruits.
Let me help you then.
Sure.
- You can peel the pear.
- Okay.
Are you sure you're okay, Ploy?
How are you getting home?
Let me drive you.
It's fine, honey. I can get home myself.
You just stay here with Ploy.
Okay.
I really am okay. Don't worry.
Please drive my mom home.
Okay. I'll drive her home.
I'll drive you home, Ma.
Okay, honey.
Don't take care of her so much
you forget to take care of yourself.
You should eat some more.
Look at you.
You got married not long ago,
and you're already so thin.
Thank you for worrying about me, Ma.
I'll take good care of myself,
and I'll give you a grandchild soon.
That's good, honey.
Here.
- Let's go.
- Let me help you.
- Okay.
Have some, Ploy. I'll be going now.
Okay, Ma.
- See you later, Ma.
- See you later.
Alright.
Please take care of her, Ms. Khim.
Don't be scared.
I just wanted to tell you
to get well soon.
We'll get to go home soon.
Smile a bit.
Please smile.
How cute.
This is Mrs. Narin, the chairman
of the board at Narin Beach Resort.
Good morning.
You look so familiar, Mr. Thee.
Have we met before?
No.
Let's not waste time
and get straight to business.
Right.
I've briefed Mrs. Narin
on your interest in an investment.
She's interested too,
so she wanted to meet you today.
I'm happy to hear
you're interested in my small hotel.
I learned that your numbers
have gone down by a lot,
and you've missed your targets for years.
Why'd you never bring in an investor?
Can I ask you this in return?
If you know all about our situation,
why do you still want
to invest in my hotel?
As an investor,
once I've assessed
that something is worth it,
I'm ready to invest in it.
My reason's that simple.
Then, we'll wait
for your proposal and contract, Mr. Thee.
But I have just one condition
that must be clearly specified
in the contract.
You may not fire anyone.
Everyone must remain working here.
You sure seem to care
about others, Mrs. Narin.
Mr. Pitak,
can you run the contract by me
when you're done?
Of course, Mr. Thee.
If you'll excuse me.
I hope we'll meet again soon.
He has an urgent meeting.
Oh, no! Careful!
Are you okay, ma'am?
Thank you.
I'm a little dizzy.
I just need to sit down.
Let's go sit outside, then.
Here, I'll help you.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Just a second.
- Thank you.
- Careful, okay?
Are you okay? Let's go.
- Here's some hot tea.
- Thank you.
How are you? Feeling any better?
I'm okay now that I got to sit down.
You sure you don't need
to go to a hospital?
It's fine. It's just how old people are.
Feeling lightheaded
and fainting is normal.
Kid, are you okay? Are you hurt?
Why'd you stop suddenly?
- Are you hurt? You're fine, honey.
- Are you okay?
Thank you.
I remember now.
We met at Narin Beach Resort, didn't we?
I remember you now.
You were with your friend.
I'm so sorry.
It really was him.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing. I just had a random thought.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
CHADCHAI
If you'll excuse me.
I hope we'll meet again,
- Ms.…
- I'm Mook.
Okay, Ms. Mook.
Thank you.
Feel free to visit anytime.
Here's mine.
Thank you.
- If you'll excuse me.
- Sure.
"Narin".
I've looked into
Narin Beach Resort, Mr. Thee.
The hotel's situation is very severe.
Are you sure about investing with them?
If their business is doing great,
why would they be looking
for an investor, Mr. Pitak?
I want to own the business.
What do you mean, Mr. Thee?
I'll invest with them
as an executive
with a share higher than 80%.
It's almost like
you're taking over the hotel.
Where are we on the contract?
Our legal team is drafting it
to cover all the details, like you asked.
Once I get it,
I'll send it over right away.
Come on in.
I brought the revised summary
and a rough budget for you to look over.
It's good that you're here. I'm hungry.
You're hungry now?
It's past lunchtime, you know.
Yes, but I had an urgent meeting today,
so I haven't eaten at all.
Then, call me when you're done eating.
I'll find a place to wait nearby.
I think
we should eat during our meeting.
I've got another meeting after this.
I'll take care of it.
Your food's ready.
Why is there so much food?
When will we be done eating?
Are you messing with me again?
I'm not. I'm just hungry.
The other night, you said
you had an important job that came up.
How did it go?
So deep down, you're worried about me too?
So, can I recharge my energy again?
Don't you dare!
If you get closer,
I'm tasing you this time.
Let's get started, shall we?
As for the work plan, I'm going to revise
for the "Lover: New Normal" campaign,
- I'm going to separate it into--
- Can I miss you still?
You can, but there's no point.
You'll only waste your time.
Can I continue?
Okay, as I said,
for the work plan,
I have a plan A and a plan B.
Okay.
Mr. Thee.
This is all of plan A.
But I might have to ask your hotel
for more information…
Just a little bit, okay?
And then, this is all of plan B.
I'm going to make gift vouchers.
And for the couples
who want to go on a honeymoon,
I'll send a letter
with their map attached--
Stay focused.
Pick whichever one you like.
- But for--
- What was plan A again?
For plan A, I will attach this
along with it for them.
Thank you for driving me, Khim.
Don't worry, Ma.
I'll help take care of Ploy.
Thank you.
You and Mook are the only ones
who've taken care of Ploy
since she was in school.
Ploy is too soft.
She can't keep up with anyone.
She's lucky to have
a great husband like Top.
Stay close like this, okay?
Don't ever leave each other.
Of course, Ma.
- I'll head inside now.
- Okay.
- See you later, Ma.
- See you later.
Come meet me.
What an unfamiliar place to meet.
Why not a hotel room like last time?
What did you do to Ploy?
Why is she at the hospital?
And what happened to Preaw
was your doing, right?
I already told you,
whoever doesn't obey me
or doesn't understand me
will need to get punished.
You're not a real man.
All you can do is hurt people.
You monster.
You want that treatment too?
Think you can do whatever to me
just because you have the video?
I only wanted to meet you today
to tell you that I'm not scared
that you'll do to me
what you did to Preaw.
I'll expose everything,
so everyone knows just how evil you are.
What's this about, Prao?
You said we're taking our son on a trip.
Well, since we're back home,
I invited my dad to have dinner with us.
Poonpun hasn't seen
his grandpa for over a year.
You haven't either.
Then what about the others?
Those are local politicians, aren't they?
- Hello, Dad.
- Hi, honey.
Hello, Dad.
It sure has been a while, son-in-law.
Poonpun! You're already this tall?
Has it really been that long
since I saw him?
Come to Grandpa, Poonpun. Come on.
Come on. Come here.
You've grown so much, handsome.
Study hard, okay?
So when you graduate,
you can come work with me.
Which ministry do you want?
Come on, tell me.
The Ministry of Magic,
like in Harry Potter.
Oh? Ministry of Magic?
Sure, I'll set it up for you.
Are you hungry? Let's go.
Let's go inside and eat together.
Let's go.
It's just dinner. Don't be so serious.
It's normal for politicians.
They have to meet once in a while.
You have to get to know them too,
for your own future.
We've gone over this so many times, Prao.
Go eat with your dad.
I'll pick you up when you're done.
Yes, Dad.
I'll go home by myself.
Don't send anyone to bother me.
Okay?
Are you okay?
- Do you have a car?
- Huh?
Hey!
Mr. Thee!
Mr. Thee! Kongkwan!
If you go missing,
what would Mommy and Grandma do?
You should know
what you're supposed to do.
You can't get distracted like this.
And about Veluree too.
You--
Let me help you.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya