( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
…that your mom's a bad person.
She's dating many guys at once.
Kongkwan, don't!
Did you just push me?
- Satang, calm down!
- Satang, Satang!
- Satang!
- Everyone, stop!
…and what I experienced firsthand only.
And the company
that will sign a contract with us
is…
Mook and I aren't what you think we are!
Then what's this?
Mook.
Thank you for taking care of her.
Come on, Mook. I'll drive you home.
I can drive her.
It's pretty late.
I don't want to bother you.
You both don't have to drive me.
I can go home myself.
- No.
You should go home, Boss.
I don't want Ms. Primprao
to misunderstand us.
Mook, I'm sorry about what happened.
I never thought she'd go that far.
It's alright, Boss.
I'm just tired today.
I don't want to get into any more fights.
Here you go.
Don't worry. I'll drive her home safely
because I care about her
no less than you do.
Thank you for driving me.
Wait.
Besides being your customer,
can I also be your friend?
Can we really be friends?
Of course.
And right now,
you really need someone
to listen to your problems
and ease your pain.
And…
I want to be that person.
Uh…
Well… I'd better go.
Good night, Mook.
Good night.
MOOK
CALLING…
Are you sleeping?
Are you leaving?
Yes, Mr. Pop.
It's Top.
Can we meet again?
I'm afraid not. I don't do repeats.
You're still up?
Why didn't you answer my call?
Well, I was a bit busy.
Hey,
what's wrong? You don't sound okay.
It's a long story. I'll tell you later.
Why'd you call me?
I wanted to remind you.
Tomorrow is Ploy's wedding.
You remember, right?
Of course I do.
Are you okay? Need me to pick you up?
No. Let's just meet at the wedding.
I'm hanging up now.
Elevator's almost here.
What?
Don't tell me you're at a hotel again.
You know me too well.
Are you my biggest fan?
Would you stop being that single girl
who's seeking fun
and sleeping around already?
Find a real partner already.
A real partner like Kuk?
No, thanks. That's nothing but hell.
I'm enjoying this more.
A love with no strings attached.
Okay. Suit yourself, bestie.
I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
Bye.
NEW MESSAGE FROM THEE
Stop missing me and go to bed already.
Who called you, Mook?
Why the big smile?
It's just Khim, Mom.
She was just gossiping like always.
Did you need something?
No. I'm just worried about you,
since you're always coming home late.
Mom,
I'm sorry.
Work's been so busy lately.
Right! Mom,
at my company,
we just landed a new client.
Really? Congratulations, honey.
But don't work so hard
you don't have time for your daughter.
Kongkwan's growing up fast.
She needs love and care.
She's growing up without a dad,
so I'm especially worried.
Of course, Mom.
I'll do my best to take care of her,
so she won't feel like
something's missing.
- Thank you, Mom.
- Of course.
Is your boss' wife really that evil?
She's like a pageant queen
when she's on TV,
helping the society and stuff.
How come she's like the devil
in real life?
Are you okay, Mook?
Not really.
I really don't know
how to make her understand
that my boss and I
aren't what she thinks we are.
How could she?
Sometimes, even I don't get it.
You and your boss are so close
and lovey-dovey to each other.
Anyone who sees would find it fishy.
Honestly, though,
you never caught feelings at all?
Hey, of course not!
We really are just friends.
Sure, I haven't worked with him that long,
yet I find him to be
very understanding and caring.
Still, we're just friends. Do you feel me?
If you insist
that you're really just friends,
then find a boyfriend,
so his wife won't have to be so paranoid.
Ploy, I'm not a 17-year-old girl
who's still so young and pretty
that all the boys would want me.
That's it. Enough about me.
Today's your good day.
Let's only talk about good things.
Congratulations, Ploy.
You look so pretty today.
Thank you.
Really?
You almost can't tell
who's the bride here.
There you go again.
You acted this way at my wedding too.
Ploy and I sure can't wait to see
how your wedding will turn out.
Fine. But where's the groom?
I haven't seen him since we came.
Top's here.
Mook, there's Top, my husband-to-be.
He's handsome.
Are you leaving?
Yes, Mr. Pop.
It's Top.
I'm so excited for you.
Ploy, your groom's here.
- Khim?
- Where's Khim?
Quick.
Go ahead, Ploy.
Join the ceremony. It's time.
- Okay.
- Go ahead, Pa, Ma.
Ploy.
Hi, Pa. Hi, Ma.
- Hi.
Hello.
Go inside, honey.
We'll start the tea ceremony.
- Okay?
- Okay.
‪Let's go.
Let's go.
What should I do? What should I do?
SOMETHING CAME UP AT WORK. GOTTA GO
TELL PLOY FOR ME
Here.
Where's Khim?
I don't know. I'll go find her.
Where is she?
Something came up at work. Gotta go.
Tell Ploy for me.
Please come take a group photo.
- Please.
- In the center, please.
Last night, you all must've been shocked.
I apologize on my wife's behalf.
We're fine, Boss.
Mook, however…
She must've been so shocked.
Can I be frank with you, Boss?
This time, Ms. Prao
really went too far.
Don't.
I apologized to Mook.
I'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
Mr. Pat.
I've roughly summarized
this year's expenses.
After we signed the contract with The One,
our performance figures
have picked up by a lot.
Thank you all a lot for this success.
Where's Mook, though?
She's at her friend's wedding
this morning.
After that, she'll go to a meeting
with Mr. Thee at The One.
Then, I'd better go prepare
for this afternoon's meeting.
After the meeting ends,
Mook and I will update you
on The One's project plan.
- Okay, Boss.
- Okay.
Then, if you'll excuse us.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Excuse me.
Try me, then. I'll make sure she pays,
and your stupid travel agency
will pay too!
Ms. Mook's not here yet?
No.
The meeting's at two, isn't it?
It's not time yet, Mr. Thee.
I thought she'd be here earlier,
since it's an important meeting.
Would you like something special
for lunch today?
No, thank you. I'm not very hungry.
Okay.
I'm hungry. Are you almost here?
I'm at The One now.
Mook.
It's not time yet.
Should we have lunch first?
I'm so hungry.
No!
Where are you right now?
I'm down in the lobby,
but do you mind if I have lunch first?
Who was that, Mook?
It's Mr. Thee.
But it's not time yet.
Please enjoy.
Mr. Thee, you haven't had lunch either?
I wanted to have it with you.
It's good that you came too.
Yes.
Besides talking about
the upcoming press conference,
where we'll officially sign a contract,
I also wanted to discuss
something with you today.
What is it, Mr. Thee?
Excuse me? Mr. Thee wants Mook
to go work at The One?
Why does she have to go, Boss?
Is Mr. Thee taking over our company?
Guys, calm down.
I'm not moving to The One.
I'll just be there twice a week
to collaborate with them.
But I don't get it.
We can just do emails, Zoom,
or online meetings.
Yeah.
Judging by the situation,
we'd better just do what Mr. Thee wants.
But I don't see the need--
It's fine. It's probably just temporary.
Once everything's all set,
I'll transfer her back here.
She's okay with this arrangement too.
- May, for the signing ceremony,
- Yes?
can you invite reporters
who work on business and tourism?
That way, we can promote our company.
Sure. They'll definitely want in,
since Mr. Thee never shows up on TV
or gives any interviews.
It'll be easy.
As for Whan and Kemtit,
please arrange for package tours
with discounts
only for The One's customers.
I want there to be
something special for them
because right now, we're about
to be the main vendor for the hotel.
So we'll have work
for the rest of the year, right?
Awesome! Now I'll be able to pay
my mortgage every month.
I love my company!
This is just the beginning.
The best is yet to come.
Let's do this together!
Boss.
Oh. Right.
- A Round Trip Travel,
- we never cancel our tours!
What was that? Can you repeat that?
What?
A Round Trip Travel,
we never cancel our parties!
- Hey! Not parties!
- No!
"We never cancel our tours," Boss.
I've set up Ms. Mook's office
as you instructed.
It's close to your office, too.
I've also finished drafting the contract.
Would you like me to mention in it
that Ms. Mook
is required to work here too?
That's alright. It's a special agreement.
It's off the record.
Yes, sir. Understood.
It's late, Mook. Aren't you going home?
I'm adjusting this year's marketing data
to cater to The One's contract.
I also want to expand our customer base.
Thank you, Mook,
for doing this for all of us.
My pleasure, Boss.
Honestly, Mook,
I don't feel too good about this.
About what?
About Mr. Thee.
You see, I'm glad
that we won The One as a client.
But I suspect Mr. Thee
also wants something else besides work.
You know that, right?
That Mr. Thee doesn't
just see you as his coworker.
Don't worry.
For me, love's not on my mind.
I only want to focus on work for now.
What about you and Ms. Prao?
How are you two doing?
Have you worked it out?
It's still awkward.
I think we really are at a dead end.
Either way, I'll always support you.
Good luck.
Here you go.
Just you tonight, Khim?
PLOY
What should I do? Why am I so unlucky?
You're going to see her, aren't you?
I'm not letting you go!
Why are you so damn annoying?!
- Don't go!
- Let go!
- Mom!
- No!
Go away!
Get out!
- No!
- Don't move!
Mind your own business!
- I'm scared!
- You're scared?
Mook, there's Top, my husband-to-be.
He's handsome.
Thank you.
Mr. Pitak, this morning,
I want a continental breakfast.
I don't want it to be too heavy.
And for lunch, can I have…
Pardon?
Mook, do you want anything in particular?
What's all this about?
I thought we're having a meeting
about the signing ceremony.
What's this room?
It's your office, of course.
We already discussed this.
You have to move here to work,
so I prepared this room for you.
- But I think it's--
- Let's talk later. I'm hungry. Let's go.
- Hey, Mr. Thee!
- But…
What about your lunch?
Hey.
Hey, I'm not a kid.
You don't have to hold my hand.
It's your first day here.
You can't know
the directions better than I do.
- This way.
- Good morning, Mr. Thee.
Good morning, Ms. Usa.
What are you doing here so early?
I wanted to see you.
We have a special deal
we wanted to propose to The One.
Thank you,
but if it's a tour, I'll have to pass
because we're officially signing
a contract with A Round Trip Travel.
We can't work with other companies.
Okay.
If there's ever a chance, we hope
Family Tour can be of service to you.
Sure. If you'll excuse us.
- Let's go.
- Mook,
can I talk to you?
You can go on ahead. I'll meet you there.
Didn't think I'd see you here so early.
Did you just get here,
or did you stay here last night?
I have a meeting
with Mr. Thee this morning,
and this is my new workplace.
So, I can be here whenever I want.
And I'm not one
to show up at a hotel uninvited
to see some guy, like you are.
You're pretty good.
No wonder Mr. Anapat's
so possessive of you.
After all,
you really throw yourself
into your work, so much so,
you'd sleep your way to the top.
Mr. Thee isn't like Kuk.
He's smart enough to know
what's good and useful for him.
You can keep
your special deals to yourself.
Here's my advice.
You'd better work hard
and find a new client.
I never thought
she'd use that kind of dirty trick.
I never thought she'd go that far either.
It just makes my blood boil.
If they competed fairly,
maybe we wouldn't have lost.
But Mr.Thee already decided.
He even sent me a confirmation email.
I'm so pissed!
Kuk, we may have lost to her this time,
but I think we still have a shot.
What is it?
She may have won the deal,
but that doesn't mean she won't fail.
If there's nothing else,
I'm going to summarize.
Whan will collaborate
with all the reporters
and prepare the documents
to give out to them.
As for the location,
we'll use one of the rooms at The One
so that we can promote the hotel too.
Whan, once you have
a list of the reporters,
run it by Mr. Thee,
in case he wants to add
or change anything.
Okay. Mook, as for the tour program,
we're working on it.
Once it's done,
I'll run it by you before
presenting it in the meeting.
- Great work.
- Thanks.
- Mr. Pitak.
- Yes?
May I have the information
of the customers at The One?
That way, I can plan
a program that suits them.
Of course, Ms. Mook.
I really appreciate it.
Let's call it a day for now.
Whan, let's go talk at my office.
I have a few more tasks for you.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
If you'll excuse me.
Let's go.
Mook!
He gave you a giant office.
Did he hire you to move here already?
Don't be silly.
I told you, I'm working here temporarily.
Why'd he have to do all this, then?
He's hitting on you!
Am I right?
Am I? Am I?
- I knew it. See?
- What are you talking about?
Well, it's weird, Mook.
Normally, you'd yell at me already.
If you don't stop talking, I'll do it.
Here. Let me see your work.
What's this? I told you to change this.
Why's it still the same?
Okay, okay. I'll change it for you.
Roger.
Change it. Hurry.
Go ahead, take a seat.
I know!
Very natural.
You look good.
- Wrong side.
- What?
Are you going to edit it,
or do you want a new job?
I am, I am! Wow, look at you.
Isn't the screen too tilted? Oh, okay.
Didn't want you to hurt your neck.
It was tilted too far.
Oh, boy.
Mook's office is so fancy!
It's huge too.
It's as if she's an executive.
Really?
Could it be Mr. Thee's
already falling for her?
Man…
Why does this kind of thing
never happen to me?
I'm ready to fall for you too, you know.
You interested?
Think I'm your friend?
I never wanted to be a friend.
Maybe he has a crush on Mook?
That's right.
Maybe we beat Family Tour because of this.
Sis, how could you think that?
We beat them thanks to Mook's skills!
Calm down. I was just joking.
Here you go.
What do you want for lunch?
That's alright.
I can order something to eat in my office.
Are you okay?
Ever since you talked to Ms. Usa,
you haven't seemed okay.
Nothing happened. I'm okay.
False. I don't believe you.
You're keeping something from me.
I just don't want anyone to badmouth us.
I want to be here to work.
To be the best at my job.
I don't want any
non-work-related problems.
But for me,
what's happening is not a problem.
It's the answer.
What do you mean?
For me, it's the answer.
It tells me how I feel for you.
Now I know why I was so worried about you,
why I cared about you,
why I wanted to be your friend
and help you with everything.
Now, it's only up to you
to find your answer
on how you feel about me.
But…
You don't have to answer me today.
I want an answer…
that comes from your true feelings.
- Good morning!
- Good morning.
- Right here, please.
- Yes,
- right here, please.
- Thank you.
- May.
- Yes?
- We'll get to interview Mr. Thee today?
You will for sure.
After the ceremony, that is.
This is the first time
we get to interview him.
Let's go claim our spots.
- Thank you.
- I'll meet you inside.
Good morning.
- Good morning, Boss.
How are we doing?
Everything's in order.
So many reporters today.
Where's Mook, though?
Mook's setting up inside with Whan.
Mr. Anapat, may I take a picture?
- Sure.
- Please, go ahead.
Just him first, please.
I'll get yours next.
P-Please, go ahead.
- Okay.
- This way too, please.
- Smile, please.
- This way too.
- This way, please.
- Perfect!
- One more, please.
- This way too.
- Okay, perfect.
- Thank you.
- Looking great.
- This camera too, please.
- This one too, please.
- This one too.
Smile, please.
Thank you.
Is it true that A Round Trip Travel
won this deal
because of a private relationship
between Mr. Thee and Ms. Veluree?
- What's the story?
- Please give us an answer.
- Is it true?
- What's the story behind this?
- Please tell us.
- Is it true?
- Please answer.
- Is it true, Mr. Thee? What's the story?
- What happened?
What are you talking about?
We won this deal fair and square.
But we have solid proof
that Mr. Thee and Ms. Veluree
were together at a hotel.
- Really?
- A hotel?
If you don't stop accusing Ms. Veluree,
I'll sue you for defamation.
Here's the proof.
Let me get a shot of that.
- This way, please.
- Can I see?
She really does have proof!
- It's a clear photo!
- What's this about?
- Hey.
- Can we get a shot too?
That's when Mook was checking out
the hotel with Mr. Thee!
How come the reporter has that photo?
So what's this about?
What do we do now?
They're being so close in the photo, too.
This camera, please.
- This camera too.
- Here too.
They're close to each other.
- This camera, please.
- This way too.
- This camera.
- They were hugging.
- This camera too.
- This is big.
- What's going on?
- What does this mean?
- How'd you two meet?
- Mr. Thee.
Ms. Veluree and I are seeing each other.
What?
So, I don't think it strange
if we go out together.
As for the criteria deciding the winner
of my project, You Are The One,
I've prepared the scoresheets
used in the contest.
We will send the files
to all of you here today.
If you have any doubts about the criteria,
please inquire with me directly.
When did you two start dating?
Yes, since when?
- So?
- Since when?
I think this is a personal matter
that has nothing to do with today's event.
So let me just tell you officially
that we're seeing each other.
As for you and your agency,
I'll have to press charges,
since you harassed us
and violated both our rights to privacy.
Regarding our project,
does anyone have any more questions?
Aren't you worried people will think
you were being biased toward her?
- That's right. Someone will think that.
- Please answer us.
Let's just say,
once you've seen my criteria,
you surely won't have
any doubts about that.
Thank you.
- Wait! Please don't go yet!
- Hold on!
Can we please have more time?
- Mr. Thee!
- Please!
- Please talk to us more!
- Everyone!
- Please stop.
- Mr. Thee!
What was that, Mr. Thee?
How could you answer them like that?
He was just doing
some quick damage control.
No. I was telling the truth.
I already told you.
Tell me what?
That I like you.
Let's deal with the reporters first.
They probably won't leave so easily.
Then, you two should stay in this room.
Don't give any more interviews.
Is that fine by you?
I'll come with you.
Sure.
Never had anyone confess
in front of many people, huh?
It wasn't funny.
Do you have any idea what you've done?
I am aware, and I know myself well.
I won't deny my own feelings.
I really do like you, Mook.
How'd it go? I bet Mook's done for, right?
I'm the one who's done for.
What?
Why? What happened?
Well, Mr. Thee announced on the spot
that he and Mook are seeing each other.
And he even threatened me
that he'd sue me for harassment
and violation of privacy.
Isn't that Mr. Theechuda,
the CEO of The One hotel?
All the reporters
are keeping an eye on him daily.
Mook? Dating Mr. Thee?
YOUNG RISING CEO
INTRODUCES THAI GIRLFRIEND
FAMOUS CEO, EXECUTIVE OF TJ GROUP
ADMITS TO FALLING FOR "VELUREE"
CEO OF TJ GROUP FALLS FOR THAI GIRL!!!
EXECUTIVE OF TJ GROUP FALLS IN LOVE
WITH THAI GIRL "VELUREE"
"VELUREE" 2023'S CINDERELLA - WHO IS SHE?
"VELUREE" TALENTED WOMAN
FROM THE TRAVEL INDUSTRY
YOUNG RISING CEO
INTRODUCES THAI GIRLFRIEND
EXECUTIVE OF TJ GROUP FALLS IN LOVE
WITH THAI GIRL "VELUREE"
"VELUREE" 2023'S CINDERELLA - WHO IS SHE?
I fried these spring rolls myself
this morning. Eat up.
- Are you full?
- Thank you, Ma.
You've got to eat the fish too.
Eat it so you'd get smarter
and get more ideas at work.
I bought this grouper myself.
Kuk! Kuk! Did you see this?
I knew I was right.
Look.
She only beat us because of this.
FAMOUS BUSINESSMAN, EXECUTIVE OF CJ GROUP
CONFESSES TO FALLING IN LOVE
WITH THAI GIRL "VELUREE"
TALENTED WOMAN FROM THE TRAVEL INDUSTRY
What's wrong, Usa?
It's Mook, Ma.
Her company only won
because she slept with the CEO.
It's all over the news now.
Mr. Thee's dating her.
Can I see?
"Famous young businessman,
executive of TJ Group admits
to falling in love
with Thai girlfriend, Veluree,
talented woman from the travel industry."
Bullshit.
You're just using work as an excuse.
That's what they wrote?
Kuk, you have to do something.
We can't just watch Mook get everything!
I won't stand for this.
I'd better do something.
"Insiders are reporting
that Mr. Thee is planning
a shotgun wedding
with Ms. Veluree. The dowry
is said to be enormous."
Hey.
What's with those sunken eyes?
I was scrolling my phone all night.
I went on Facebook,
Instagram, Twitter, and every single page
posted news about Mook and Mr. Thee.
The more I read, the more I got…
Stressed, right? Me too.
…jealous.
Did you see that part?
Which part?
"The two of us
are seeing each other."
Boss, we're in big trouble.
What should we do, Mr. Thee?
The news that got out
really hurt our stock.
I'm afraid that…
But in just one day,
searches for our hotel
have increased by 20%.
I find this to be
a perfect opportunity for The One.
Mr. Pitak, please ask our sales team
to promote our campaigns
and discounted packages online right away.
You're turning the crisis
into an opportunity, aren't you?
Sure. I'll handle it right away, Mr. Thee.
Okay.
Did you see the news on TJ Group's stock?
We wanted to apologize to you
for causing you trouble.
Is there any way we can help?
I'm glad you're here.
I'm going to launch a special campaign
to promote our hotel.
I would appreciate it
if your team can come brainstorm
with our marketing team.
I think we should capitalize
on the current trend as much as we can.
Of course.
I'll send my team over to help you.
Okay.
- Mr. Pitak.
- Yes?
Please look into that reporter for me.
I want to know how she got the story.
We will sue everyone involved
for violating our privacy
and for the damage they've caused.
Of course, Mr. Thee.
Prao must've had something to do with it.
I never thought
the woman I used to love
could change this much.
Maybe in her eyes,
you've changed too.
That's why it's come to this.
Boss, please don't worry.
I'll talk to Mr. Thee about this.
Once there's different news,
they'll all forget anyway.
But this had nothing to do with you.
I should just go and make things clear.
What do you mean?
What are you going to do?
Problems are meant to be solved,
not for me to run away.
That's what you told me.
I think it's time I faced it for real.
And what do you think about Mr. Thee?
I…
It's alright, Mook.
You don't have to answer
if you're not ready.
When two people love each other,
everything suddenly looks beautiful.
But when the love runs out,
it all gets so scary.
Don't you think so?
- Good morning.
- Say hello. Good morning.
Kongkwan, Mommy has a meeting today.
Grandma will come pick you up, okay?
Okay.
See you later, Mommy.
See you later. Give me a kiss. Here too.
Okay, pay attention in class.
Bye-bye.
Ms. Prao. Ms. Prao.
Let's gossip about Kongkwan's mom
bagging that rich guy.
It came as no surprise.
She's always sleeping around anyway.
But on the news, Mr. Thee said
he'd take it all the way to court.
He said he'd sue everyone who spread
the fake news and even the reporter
from that day.
Do you happen to know
how the reporter got that picture?
I sent it to her myself,
and I'm not scared either.
We're telling the truth.
Why should we be scared?
Am I right?
- Yes.
If you'll excuse me,
I have a meeting at the association.
- Okay.
Will we get in trouble too, Oh?
Will Mr. Thee sue us too?
Are you alright? You don't look too good.
Mom.
You just like Mook better than me.
This wouldn't have happened
if it weren't for her!
It's happened for a while now, Prao!
Even before I met Mook.
Here comes the real thing.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya