( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
'Love in the Making' - Ian Yan
♫ The flowers on the windowsill bloom ♫
♫ Longing rushes in and won’t fade ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand ♫
♫ Walk through crowded streets ♫
♫ Let the wind gently sway your skirt ♫
♫ In my heart ♫
♫ You are irreplaceable ♫
♫ Every time I see you,
my heart grows lighter ♫
♫ Do you know this love
has been hidden so long? ♫
♫ I've always existed for you ♫
♫ Running from the stars to the sea ♫
♫ I no longer want to hide this love ♫
♫ My gaze has already betrayed me ♫
♫ So, let us truly fall in love ♫
[You Are My Fateful Love]
[Episode 1: A Secret in the Diary]
[Su City, 2024]
Team name
Dear Ms. Ruan, I'm calling to inform you
that by 5:00 p.m. on August 3, 2024,
you hadn't submitted
a new novel outline to your editor.
Since the completion
of your last novel, it's been...
a full year already!
Got it, got it, Editor Shen.
Ms. Ruan is sorting out
her belongings at home.
She remembered she promised
the outline by the end of this month.
Then, may I ask if she has
decided on the theme?
Not yet.
It's been a year, Ruan Yu!
You're a rising full-time web novelist.
Do you want to become a has-been?
But there's no inspiration, what can I do?
Because you're cooped up all day!
Inspiration isn't handed to you,
it's built through hands-on experience, got it?
May 11, Sunny.
I encountered Xu Huai Song three times today.
The first time was on my way to the office
with Chinese test papers.
I saw him and some classmates
being punished in the hallway.
The Dean looked angry.
I've got it.
What? The theme?
Yes.
Setting in a campus, theme, and secret crush.
What do you think?
[Jan. 1, 2014 | SOS! Today Xu Huai Song...]
[2014 New Year's Eve]
[Su City No.1 High School]
At midnight that day, for New Year's Eve fireworks,
the playground was packed.
All of high school, she had never been so close
to her secret crush.
Eleven, ten, nine, eight, seven, six...
-- As if unconsciously, she snuck to his left.
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Unexpectedly, the moment the fireworks exploded,
he suddenly took her hand.
Sorry. I took the wrong hand.
She turned around in shock,
only to see in the flickering light...
his apologetic look.
He released her hand
and said awkwardly,
"Sorry."
"I took the wrong hand."
[I Really Want to Whisper In Your Ear - Draft]
I took the wrong hand?
I took the wrong hand.
So whose hand is right?
Did Xu Huai Song like someone else?
You're not writing
an unrequited love based on him, are you?
Come on!
Life is hard enough.
Who goes online for a tragedy?
Yes. The author has a hard life.
The heroine should have a happier one.
[I Really Want to Whisper In Your Ear - Draft]
With this said, his heart pounded,
louder than the fireworks overhead.
No one knew that
"I took the wrong hand" was just a cover-up.
[Hang City]
For your review, Great Editor Shen.
Your novel is going to be a hit.
Personal experience is so touching, right?
But, don't you worry that
he might see this novel?
Of course I considered the risk.
You know, it was my unrequited love.
Back then, he didn't even know my name.
Even if he sees it, he won't know it's me.
Besides, would unattainable flowers
like Xu Huai Song read romance novels?
You can rest easy.
Indeed.
Hello, Mom. What's up?
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Another blind date?
Hey, your new ringtone...
sounds like Xu Huai Song's tune
at the school anniversary, "After the Rain."
Stop guessing.
I only changed it to recall memories.
Well, be careful. It might recall something else.
I want an explanation!
Do you understand?
Listen, Ma'am. I'm sorry.
- But this verdict isn't going to change.
- What's going on?
- Her house was leased to American students.
- It's my house!
- But they neither paid nor moved out.
- Why should I give them money?
So she went and cut off the water and power,
and contacted Jay to file a lawsuit
to claim the rent.
But she was charged with trespassing,
and required to pay a heavy fine instead.
- Now she's arguing with Jay.
- It was nice chatting with you but I have to go.
- You can't go! Hey, you can't go!
- Ma'am.
- It's not settled yet! You can't go!
- Let go of me! Let go! Ma'am.
- You can't go!
- This is America. You have to obey the laws of the USA.
It doesn't matter what country's laws
we are talking about.
If you lose, you lose.
Finally, a fellow countryman!
Tell me, aren't they bullying me?
Emotionally or rationally, I shouldn't pay them!
The court doesn't recognize
emotion or reason, only law.
So I have to compensate them?
That's right.
But I have two questions.
I want your honest reply.
First, what's the expiration date on the lease?
And for which months are you claiming rent?
The lease expired in February.
They didn't renew the lease.
We only made a verbal agreement.
But they haven't paid since February.
After the lease expired,
did you know they were still living in your house?
Yes, I did.
Are you sure you knew?
In that case...
I didn't know?
If you didn't know, it's not only the unpaid rent,
but also they were trespassing.
After all, they occupied your property
without your knowledge.
I don't need to say more, right?
Thank you so much!
I never knew such a solution existed!
The law is rigid, but people are flexible.
Song, are you sure that you want
to be meddling in my affairs?
This is my case.
I guess we have different definitions
of the word "meddle".
And in my view, I'm cleaning up your mess.
Listen, just because you have
some type of big win rate
doesn't mean you can be an arrogant prick.
I'll take that as a compliment.
And just do your job.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Let's go to my office
where we can talk more privately and I can help you.
Boss, you didn't notice, Jay was green with rage.
He deserved it.
I don't care about his rage.
I care about the case.
Otherwise, it's the firm's reputation at stake.
Drink less cola. It's bad for you.
By the way, this is the criminal case
I mentioned last time.
The client insists on having you handle it.
Take another look.
I said before, I won't take criminal cases.
It's been years.
Something can't be changed by time.
Okay.
Hello, Ms. Wen Xiang.
Your new novel "Whisper in Your Ear"
topped major lists as soon as it was serialized.
I hear that film companies are contacting you for the copyright.
Could you give us a sneak peek?
First of all, thank you for supporting this novel.
It's about mutual unrequited love in high school.
I really hope you'll all like it.
As for the copyright,
I'll share with you once it's confirmed.
Look. She's suspected of plagiarism.
It seems true.
Look at this comparison chart.
Check it out. She plagiarized.
- Yes, I agree.
- This...
- Thank you.
- Ms. Wen Xiang, have you noticed
the controversy online
regarding your work's originality?
In "New Year's Eve Fireworks", the plot, the dialogue,
[Wen Xiang's novel is accused of plagiarism]
and even the male lead's monologue
largely overlap those by Poet.
What caused such high similarity?
Are the copyright buyers aware of this?
Does this explain your previous high productivity?
What do you think of
the current controversy online?
Everyone. Like you, I just got the news.
I hope you can give me some time.
I will definitely give everyone
and my work an explanation soon.
Thank you.
Ms. Wen Xiang! So you deny the plagiarism?
- Yes, Ms. Wen Xiang, say something.
- Ms. Wen Xiang!
- Wait! Ms. Wen Xiang!
- Please wait!
- Ms. Wen Xiang! We want a direct answer.
- Please reply. Ms. Wen Xiang!
- Ms. Wen Xiang!
- Please wait, Ms. Wen Xiang!
- For your six years of original creation...
- Ms. Wen Xiang!
Ming Ying, what's going on?
Your novel resembles "Her Smiling Eyes"
in so many tropes.
- Ms. Wen Xiang!
- Are you leaving because you feel guilty?
It's been six years. Why now?
- Ms. Wen Xiang!
- Please answer us.
- We want a direct reply.
Please, Ms. Wen Xiang.
Ms. Wen Xiang, say something!
Ms. Wen Xiang! Ms. Wen Xiang!
Ms. Wen Xiang!
Check the comparison chart.
It was published weeks before
"Whisper in Your Ear."
The biggest difference is that yours centers on the heroine,
his centers on the hero.
Sorry. I took the wrong hand.
No one knew that "I took the wrong hand"
was just a cover-up.
"I Really Want to Whisper in Your Ear".
Just kidding. I didn't take the wrong hand.
"Her Smiling Eyes."
Even the male lead's inner monologue is the same.
I found it. The author's Weibo account.
"Going back to school again."
[A Poet]
A student?
I'll message her to ask about it.
Ask her why they are so similar.
"Whisper in Your Ear" is my original work.
I can prove it.
Yet I'm surprised and confused by the similarities.
I'm writing to inquire about this.
I look forward to your reply.
Ten years ago, you endured unrequited love
because of him.
Ten years later, you based a fiction on this,
only to be accused of plagiarism.
It's not a fiction.
Alright.
If I have to admit it, then I guess it is.
A'Yu, the young man I mentioned yesterday
is available tomorrow.
I'll show you his photos, okay? If you agree...
Mom, I'm busy right now.
Busy, busy, busy, all year round.
When are you not busy?
Dating and work don't conflict.
Mrs. Li said he's very capable.
Most notably, he's a lawyer.
I'll send you his photos first.
If he looks okay, go see him tomorrow.
I think he's quite nice.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm Liu Mao from Zhikun Law Firm.
Here's my business card.
Hello. I'm Ruan Yu.
Hello, hello.
Mr. Liu, you seem much older than me.
[Liu Mao]
You're a law firm partner at such a young age.
A true "young talent".
No, no. You flatter me.
Our firm has four partners.
I'm the doer, not very high-ranking.
A senior counsel who lives abroad long-term
is more powerful.
Living abroad means he's not a doer?
No. That's not what I mean.
I mean, he practices law abroad.
You know, financial support is part of the work.
[Huai Song]
This guy has sharp ears.
Excuse me, Ms. Ruan.
I don't talk about work in my personal life.
It's okay to talk about work.
No, really. I separate work from life.
I mean, we can talk about work.
Mr. Liu, sorry for bringing up work at lunch.
It's okay.
I'm used to drawing experience from life
and applying it to my work.
As they say, work is a part of life,
and life is a part of work.
So, Mr. Liu, do you have any solutions?
Based on your description,
she published online earlier than you did.
In theory, she didn't plagiarize you.
And as you said, so far,
she has neither shown up nor taken a stance.
So she can't be considered a defendant.
We can't sue everyone commenting online, right?
Of course, it is feasible.
But I wouldn't recommend it.
Because it's thankless and unpromising.
I see.
Mr. Liu, could you give me some advice?
Let the bullets fly for a while
and see what she wants.
Excuse me.
Uh, Mr. Liu, I have to go now.
Thank you so much for your advice today.
Let's meet some other day.
I've settled the bill.
Consider it the consultation fee.
I'll transfer more if it's not enough.
So kind of you. When will we meet again?
When we find the defendant.
He told me to wait and see until A Poet shows up.
Is he reliable?
I don't know.
But I agree with him that
A Poet's stance matters to us.
What if she clarifies that I didn't plagiarize.
Theoretically,
you're lucky if she doesn't sue you.
You really expect her to clarify?
At least I'll try to convince her
it's my original work.
- I'll wait...
- Wait!
A Poet posted on Weibo.
She's too much. A writer?
So spineless!
Which writer?
I didn't plagiarize or mix tropes.
As for the similarities
between "Whisper in Your Ear" and "Her Smiling Eyes",
I've contacted the author to inquire
and I'm waiting for a reply.
Once clear, I'll provide further explanation.
God knows, this unrequited love
was my personal experience in high school.
Personal experience?
She's a better actress than the pros.
See whose personal experience it is.
So heavy.
[Two months ago, Su City]
My brother's old phone?
The fireworks are beautiful tonight.
And...
Just kidding. I didn't take the wrong hand.
Happy New Year.
Oh my god.
So much stuff.
So you found your brother's crush on a girl
from his old phone
when you helped your grandma move?
Keep it down!
His crush.
- So, this is your brother's experience?
- Yes.
And that is Wen Xiang's experience.
They're both in the story.
Is it possible that...
What?
You mean...
Wen Xiang was my brother's schoolmate,
he had a crush on her,
and she had a crush on him too?
No way! That's impossible.
Impossible.
I'm viewing her Weibo.
Look, she posted photos of Su cuisine.
She's likely from here.
It seems so.
It can't be that coincidental, can it?
Impressive, Zhao Yi!
You aren't good at studying,
but still have a sharp mind.
Thanks.
Zhao Yi,
your hairstyle is so cool today.
And your skin is looking amazing.
And your outfit, though the same as usual,
is extremely handsome today.
Look, a chiseled jawline, and an amazing profile.
Incredible!
Even a school hunk looks small by your side...
That's enough.
Flattery out of the blue
means you're up to no good.
We're great buddies, aren't we?
That depends on what you're going to say next.
Considering your wide network,
go look into Wen Xiang for me.
I just knew you're my buddy!
What do you know?
It means three months of math homework.
One month will do.
Deal!
A cup of milk tea.
[Prince Cafe]
Okay, okay.
Thanks. I'll treat you to crayfish next time.
What? What did he say?
[Ruan Yu]
Ruan Yu?
She's the one you're looking for.
[Wen Xiang]
Zhao, go the whole way
and follow me to the school art gallery.
What for?
To confirm something.
It should be here.
The piano.
Zhao, come here!
Help me move this.
Do you think the wall has been repainted?
I don't think so. They're stingy.
Let me do it.
In Wen Xiang's novel,
the heroine wrote some initials
on the wall of the piano room
where the hero practices.
What are you looking for?
Let me help you.
[RYXHXHS]
I found it!
RYXHXHS...
Loves Xu Huai Song?
Who's RY? Tell me.
Is it Ren Yi from Class 1, or Ran Yu from Class 5?
Nanny Rong from Grade 10?
Xu Huai Shi, you're dating a junior at this age!
Ruan Yu loves Xu Huai Song.
My god!
Zhao Yi, this is so touching!
Hey, what are you two doing?
Which class are you in?
Get out here!
Your IQ is touching, too.
You stayed up all night?
Strange.
That's more than similar.
Remember? In my novel,
potted plants were popular at school.
When others grow clover and mimosa,
I refit mine with other seeds. Remember?
Yeah.
- You grew sunflowers and lavender at the same time.
- Yes.
An early pastoral heroine.
Come and see.
See what A Poet wrote here.
- Hurry, come here.
- What? What did you find?
Look at this.
"That weekend, she left school
with her Little Florist,
where sunflower and lavender bloomed."
- This is way too similar! Goodness!
- Yeah.
Who on earth is it?
If no progress is made by 9:00 p.m.,
your novel will be removed. Look at the time!
Hello. Sorry for the trouble.
"Her Smiling Eyes" isn't my original,
but adapted from an outline my friend bought.
Sorry for violating your rights.
I'm willing to publicly explain this
and apologize to you,
delete my article, and close my account.
I drafted a statement, attached for your review.
An outline leak?
Who else did you show the outline to?
No one.
My USB flash disk!
I brought it to the cafe
where we discussed the outline.
Was it left there?
What's going on?
Your novel... is going to be a hit.
Yeah, she said the outline was purchased.
Wait. Where are you going?
The cafe, Ming Ying. You should go home.
- Okay, and...
- I know. I'll ask her about the source.
Yes.
Okay. Don't rush us. We're sure.
Buddy, here you are.
Thanks.
She asked me about the source.
What should I say?
I told you it was a bad idea.
Then tell her the truth.
That's even worse.
If she knows, so will my brother.
If he knows I wrote a novel based on his draft,
I'm dead!
He's a lawyer.
He won't break the law.
He'll cut off my allowance, which will kill me.
That makes sense.
Listen, tell her that
you signed a non-disclosure agreement
with the seller.
Anyway, she doesn't know you.
But that would be unfair to Ruan Yu.
Hey, is it possible
that my brother still loves Ruan Yu,
and he'll reward me for what I did?
Please! It has been ten years. Still?
Do you think he'd love one person his whole life?
- You don't understand men.
- Because I'm not, and I don't need to.
Please post the statement first.
[Apology Statement]
No one in the cafe saw it.
We checked the security footage.
But it's too small to be noticed.
Anyway, her statement put it to an end.
After grocery shopping, I'll come over
and boil away your bad luck in hot pot.
[Forwarded Apology Statement]
It's a common tactic
to plagiarize the ideas of unknown writers
and pay in exchange for their silence.
The fake statement... Wen Xiang is fooling us.
The web novel community is corrupted
by people like her.
Qianhe Net, do something!
Only when Wen Xiang is banned
can emerging talents survive.
Wen Xiang, quit the internet!
A Poet is a new account with few readers
and little exposure.
Yet the news went viral, as if planned.
It must be Su Cheng. She's cunning and vicious.
Remember? When she signed with Qianhe Net,
she blamed her poor work on an editor,
and made the young girl lose her job.
Watch out.
Or you'll be another slaughtered lamb.
If you don't act,
you'll be cooked like this.
Who told you I'll wait to be slaughtered?
If we play dirty, we may not be her match.
But if we play by rules, she may not be our match.
You have a plan?
Look, the slanderers on the trending topics
of Qianhe Net's Weibo and other platforms
must be her trolls.
I can accuse her of defamation
considering the large-scale
planned slander, right?
Your blind date really inspired you.
We have an appointment at his firm tomorrow.
I hope it'll go well.
[Zhikun Law Firm]
Hello. I have an appointment
with Lawyer Liu, Liu Mao.
Okay, I'll check for you.
[Monday, September 9, 2024]
September 9, 2013, sunny.
After today,
I'll remember Xu Huai Song for many years.
We think effort shouldn't be denied by a doomed failure.
Success and failure
are deeply rooted in our subconscious.
Facing an insurmountable barrier
or inevitable abyss,
perhaps they are the ones struggling,
just like you.
So we think only when we give up
can we quit the painful cycle
and find hope elsewhere.
Instead of repeating
the painful cycle of failure and expectation,
it's better to turn around and take another route
where new hope and life lie ahead.
[Debate Final, Su City No.1 High School, 2013]
Opposition, congratulations on your win.
The Best Debater award goes to Xu Huai Song.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Principal.
Huai Song, without a preset side,
which opinion would you support?
We'd like to hear from you.
A line from a movie can represent my choice,
"I'll keep searching,
even if the endless stars blur my hope,
even if alone."
Ruan Yu?
Lawyer Liu.
Excuse me for coming late.
It's fine. I was early.
- Let's go to the meeting room.
- Okay.
This way.
By the way, Ruan Yu, our legal counsel,
the one I mentioned last time,
might join us today.
He returned recently.
He's interested in your case
and wants to get involved.
Would you mind?
I don't mind. More lawyers, more hope.
Technically, he hasn't passed the bar exam here,
so he can't be called a lawyer in China.
If you mind, I can tell him.
It's really okay.
Despite a lack of qualification,
he still wants to get involved.
Is the big shot here to supervise you?
Well, you might be right.
Life is tough.
This way, Ms. Ruan.
- Please come in.
- Thank you.
Let me introduce you.
Xu Huai Song?
How can it be Xu Huai Song?
team name
I'm looking forward to tonight.
I heard there's a performance tonight.
Here!
So many people have come.
So lively.
Here, here, hurry!
Coming!
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two, one!
'Yesterday' - Vision Wei
♫ Rewinding scenes from the past ♫
♫ A full stop written in haste ♫
♫ Tracing through endless days and nights ♫
♫ An unspoken goodbye ♫
♫ At the edge of a blurred gaze ♫
♫ The wind scatters what remains ♫
♫ Thoughts cloud my vision ♫
♫ Turning into drifting smoke ♫
♫ Silently fading away ♫
♫ Every chapter of the past ♫
♫ Yesterday’s faded pages ♫
♫ As I turn through each one,
I find you behind every story ♫
♫ Relentlessly returning ♫
♫ The smile upon your face ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye,
with no time to hold on ♫
♫ Every chapter of the past ♫
♫ Yesterday’s faded pages ♫
♫ As I turn through each one,
I find you behind every story ♫
♫ Relentlessly returning ♫
♫ The smile upon your face ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye,
with no time to hold on ♫
♫ Fading into yesterday ♫