( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[EP6: Who Sees Whom as an Imaginary Rival?]
I think we have to talk about the performance.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
Let's talk about performance.
So what kind of idea do you have there?
Honey...
Are you home?
Ruan Yu?
Yeah. I'm almost home.
Okay.
What? You'll meet me at the corner?
[Urgent call]
Okay.
I'll be there in five.
Someone's following you?
Yes.
Don't panic.
Go where it's crowded and bright.
Tell him I'm on my way.
I'm coming to you now.
I'm almost there.
Then...
It's okay, Lawyer Xu. I'm home now.
Maybe I was overthinking.
Good.
Get some rest.
About the stuff online,
I'm handling it already.
Honey.
Are you home?
I...
Sorry.
That call was meant for a friend.
I dialed you by mistake.
What's wrong?
Lawyer Xu.
I...
downstairs at my place,
there's a black van parked outside.
When I was downstairs earlier, it wasn't there.
Can you see the plate?
Not clearly.
But it looks like
the kind used for kidnappings.
Usually, this isn't the kind of criminal
you're imagining.
Even if it is, they won't just break in.
You need to do two things.
First, send me your location
and the number for property management
or the security office.
Second, take your phone
and check the peephole.
Okay.
[Tian Heng Residence]
I sent it.
Don't make a sound yet.
If you see someone suspicious
but they haven't moved yet,
don't lock the door yet.
Step back from the door.
Put me on speaker.
Say my name out loud.
Say you're doing laundry
and want me to get the door.
Got it?
Got it.
If I'm done calling
and they still don't leave,
lock the door fast
and call the police.
What's wrong?
Hello?
Hello.
The number you dialed is powered off.
Ruan Yu,
are you home?
It's me, Li Shi Can.
Shi Can? What are you doing here?
Didn't we say
to see at the usual place?
Didn't you call me because of the livestream?
You knew I was livestreaming?
Ming Ying and I were free at home that day,
so we watched your livestream.
You actually quite care about me.
Can I come in first?
I'm a little...
Sure. Come in.
Shi Can.
I don't have men's slippers.
Just keep your shoes on.
Still no boyfriend?
Before showbiz, you weren't this gossipy.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Then I'll...
Sure, go ahead.
Other people's gossip, I really don't care.
But you're different.
You're my...
closest senior.
So you do know I'm your senior.
Yet you didn't call me that just now.
My bad.
This is my apology.
I saw it on the way,
so I grabbed one for you.
Isn't this from that tea shop
by the college town?
- That place is still open?
- Yes.
Here.
Thanks.
Red and mung bean milk tea.
Full sugar, no tea base.
Swap the milk for soy milk.
Red beans only, no mung beans.
Back when I ran errands
for you seniors, I kept notes.
The names are gone now, though.
Good thing I remembered right.
Or I'd be even more guilty.
That's thoughtful of you.
But I don't have much to offer.
May I get you a cup of warm water?
Sure. Warm water's fine.
I'm resting my voice lately, so less drink.
Okay, hang on.
Here.
Thanks.
By the way, Shi Can,
is that car downstairs yours?
Yeah, it's mine.
It's kind of messy.
It rained on the way from Su City.
Got dirty from the road.
You came all the way from Su City?
You could've just told me
you were here for work.
Of course, not just for work.
I already wanted to see you.
The stream just gave me a reason to call.
There's something
I had to apologize for
in person.
Shi Can, give me a second.
I need to deal with something.
Okay.
[xhs invites you to a video call]
Lawyer Xu, I'm really sorry.
My phone died just now,
so I couldn't let you know I was safe.
Sorry.
A friend came over.
While you were staring at Li Shi Can,
you were reminiscing about Xu someone, right?
Lawyer Xu?
Yes.
Hello.
Sorry.
Don't report to me.
Tell the police instead.
[Call duration: 3:20]
The police?
He's your lawyer?
Yeah.
I need to take this.
Hello?
Can, the police got me downstairs.
Come help me!
Give me a moment, both of you.
Thanks.
Let's wait over there.
Yes.
I'm really sorry, Shi Can.
I overthought it.
I'm so sorry that
I dragged you and your innocent friend
into this incident.
I should be the one apologizing.
I didn't handle things well with Cen Si Si.
Cen Si Si told me
you two are childhood friends.
I'm from Su City.
She's from Hang City.
How would we be childhood friends?
Back then,
her dad came to Su City for business.
She transferred there with him.
We were classmates for two years.
Then we went to the same college.
Maybe to her, that counts as
half a childhood friend?
And all these years, she's had feelings
for me.
I have an alt Weibo account.
I followed your account, Wen Xiang.
She tracked you down from that.
So she probably got the wrong idea.
Then how did you know I was Wen Xiang?
Back in college,
you asked me to fix your computer.
Remember?
One of your files had that pen name on it.
I remembered it
and followed you quietly.
You've really stayed hidden all these years.
I figured you creators
like to keep online
and real life separate.
Otherwise, it's like running naked online.
What's the difference?
But don't worry.
I don't snoop on you.
Otherwise I wouldn't have only found out
after coming back home.
If I'd known sooner,
I'd have dealt with it already.
Someone was deleting comments for me on Weibo,
and someone also leaked Cen Si Si's identity.
Was that your PR team?
I only told them to moderate comments.
As for the information leak...
it wasn't me.
Maybe netizens did it
on their own?
Is that so?
Either way, I dragged you into this.
I'll clean it up.
Things have died down now.
You just focus on the case.
Leave the rest to me.
No need.
None of this was your fault.
And you're busy enough already.
Don't worry about this.
I have lawyers helping me.
Right. I saw the signature
on your legal statement
was Zhikun Law Firm.
Lawyer Xu
works at Zhikun Law Firm?
Yes.
I-Is he any good?
Don't worry. He's very professional
and very experienced.
[Xu Huai Song from Su City No.1 High School]
Found you at last.
Xu someone.
But looks like you found her, too.
[2016 Midsummer Night's Dream Art Performance]
So, did you find
your Hua Ze Lei?
Lawyer Xu.
I'm really sorry about today.
I made you worry for nothing.
Lawyer Xu.
Did you read the file?
Not even one reply.
Then again...
Got played like this
and reported to the police...
anyone could be annoyed.
Besides,
he's busy to begin with.
Or maybe he never saw it at all?
Lawyer Xu.
Have you been busy these past two days?
When can we go further into the case?
In ten minutes.
Then I'll turn on my laptop.
No need. In ten minutes,
downstairs at your place.
You don't have to rush over.
Sorry, Lawyer Xu. Kept you waiting.
Because of that stupid mix-up,
that high-up Mr. Xu ignored me
for two whole days.
Not even a comma.
How could I make someone like you
wait even one more second?
Get in.
We're going to the firm.
Lawyer Xu.
What are you doing near my place?
I am passing by on the way
from the airport to the firm.
The airport to the firm passing by here?
Thanks for picking me up.
Hello?
Ms. Zhang.
Okay, got it.
Lawyer Xu.
Ms. Zhang is handling a case at the site
and something came up.
I may need to go over.
Then when you're done,
take my luggage to the apartment.
Okay.
Why not get a cab?
Want to talk at my place?
If it's not a good time, next time.
I'll head back to the office first.
No, it's fine. This way.
Watch your step.
He's only mad at you for two days.
Look how hard you're sucking up.
Oh no.
What is it?
Nothing, Lawyer Xu.
Please wait a moment.
Lawyer Xu, come in.
Sorry.
I don't have men's slippers.
Just keep your shoes on.
That was where I sat for video calls before.
My friend came over.
Yes.
Lawyer Xu.
Want something to drink?
Coffee is fine.
Instant okay?
Yes.
Sure. Have a seat.
I was only thinking not to make
the big shot come for nothing...
and forgot the time difference.
I should've let him back to sleep.
Xu...
Sorry.
I dozed off.
Hello?
I just fell asleep.
Haven't eaten yet.
Bye.
Lawyer Xu, you haven't eaten?
Want to grab a bite first?
It's too hot outside.
Then let's order takeout.
Oh, you don't eat takeout.
How about...
I cook you something?
I have food at home.
See if anything works.
If it's not too much trouble.
Not at all.
Come check the kitchen. See what you want.
With what's here,
I can make sandwiches or pasta.
Pick what you want.
This one.
Looks like your stomach
isn't fully westernized yet.
How do you want it cooked?
Fried.
Then go sit in the living room.
Milled rice cake isn't great fried.
He probably wants
Su City's lard rice cake.
Lawyer Xu.
I switched it to Su City lard rice cake.
You've been abroad,
so you probably don't get this much.
Thanks.
How did you know
I'm from Su City?
I looked you up.
There are articles about you online.
Why look into me?
Just...
basic background on my counsel.
I also know Lawyer Liu is from Hang City.
Lawyer Xu.
Eat it while it's hot.
Okay.
You're eating so politely.
So is it good or not?
You want some?
I don't.
Lawyer Xu, go ahead.
I'll wash the dishes.
Your appetite isn't very polite though.
Guess I fried it well today.
Lawyer Xu. You done eating?
I still haven't checked.
Busy these past few days?
Yes.
Didn't even check WeChat.
So you weren't ignoring me on purpose.
I knew it. You're not that petty.
Hello? What is it?
I put the cat food
in the lower kitchen cabinet.
Yeah.
Handle it.
First, he has a cat.
Second, he doesn't know how to bathe it.
So, who usually bathes the cat?
You mean
someone else lives with him?
His girlfriend?
Maybe he usually takes it to a pet shop.
But possibly you're right.
Ruan Yu.
I need some sleep.
Lawyer Xu.
You're sleeping here?
Or maybe I should...
Xu...
Out that fast.
Being a lawyer
really drains you.
[Yet reality was always cruel.
He Shi Qian seemed not to notice...]
[I'm leaving]
Counselor Xu.
You've been showing up pretty rarely lately.
Feels like the last time
was half a month ago.
Yes.
Want a tea egg? My treat.
No.
I ate too much last night.
Still digesting it.
What did you eat that you're still full?
Fried lard rice cake.
That's a pretty nice life.
Well, it's a Su City specialty.
Fried rice cake for yourself?
Not bad.
Wasn't me, actually.
Oh, there's a story.
Ruan Yu made it for me.
Who?
Ruan Yu.
Why did she fry rice cake for you?
What's going on with you two?
A client making rice cake
for her lawyer is weird?
Isn't it? Forget client and lawyer.
What kind of client makes food for a lawyer?
Depends on the client,
and the lawyer too.
What kind?
At least not some lovestruck lawyer.
Being likable is a gift.
Take your bag.
Time for work.
Did you just roast me?
But I can't prove it.
When's the update coming?
My comfort read!
Come back already!
Every writer gets stuck.
This time's different.
The hero is right there.
How could I keep writing like nothing happened?
I believe the author is innocent now.
Now I'm just wondering
if it's her real story.
Same here.
This blew up so much,
does the real-life hero know yet?
[Let's meet by
Counter-Plagiarism Comparison Chart]
Anyone still working this late
is this city's elite.
Lawyer Xu.
I got your email.
You're still working on my case this late.
Thanks.
Jet lag, that's all.
If you're still up,
let's talk about the case.
Okay. Video?
Voice call.
Lawyer Xu.
Sorry, one moment.
I'm going downstairs for a file.
Okay.
Lawyer Xu.
Yes. I'm here.
Is it raining there?
It is.
Then I guess
we're under the same cloud.
Lawyer Xu, I'm back.
Okay.
Then...
let's start with paragraph 3.
In this part,
the heroine is scared of thunder
and stuck in the gallery by rain.
She hears him playing piano
and feels comforted.
In the other novel, that's not there.
So should we point it out?
In the two novels,
the piano room descriptions are pretty similar.
Piano rooms probably all look alike.
Did you forget?
Forget what?
Did you forget to switch to Wi-Fi?
Your signal sounds bad.
I can't hear you clearly.
I switched it already.
Better now.
I can hear you now.
Okay, let's continue.
In the next part,
the heroine once turned down
a clingy male classmate in public.
She told him not to mess with her studies.
And that's exactly why after seeing that,
the hero didn't want
to affect her studies, so he never confessed.
Right.
From what I saw, in the Poet's posts,
it still doesn't explain
why he never confessed.
This part shouldn't overlap, right?
But this setup
feels a little weak.
A little weak?
But for high schoolers,
studying is the biggest thing.
Besides that,
what other reason would he have not to confess?
Not every high schooler
is that lucky.
I was being too absolute.
Then this setup
won't hurt the case, right?
It's okay. I'm just reminding you.
The novel still has to be updated, right?
So sort it out early
and start posting again.
That way public opinion can turn your way.
Yeah.
The rain stopped.
It rained so hard.
If I'd known,
I wouldn't have come feed the cat.
Is it him?
Xu Huai Song.
That bright, clean boyish glow in you
lit up all
all my rainy seasons,
in my girlhood.
Hello, Dad.
Okay, I'm heading out now.
The rain stopped here, too.
Then let's keep going.
Okay.
Ruan Yu.
What is it?
Lawyer Xu, sorry.
I accidentally fell asleep last night.
Why didn't you hang up?
I think I was asleep too.
Then...
I'll hang up first.
What was that?
An ambulance.
Why is there an ambulance?
I'm at the hospital.