( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[EP8: No Cheap Shots From Drunks]
Look over there. The flowers look great.
Coming.
- Hello.
Are you Ms. Ruan Yu?
- Yes.
- Hello. I'm the
property manager here.
Here's the thing. Early this morning,
a drunk was loitering downstairs.
He didn't bother you, right?
A drunk?
Bother me?
No.
Good.
Please lock your doors and windows at night.
- Stay safe.
- Okay.
We'll also step up patrols.
If anything happens,
call us right away.
I'll leave you to it.
Wait a moment.
About that drunk,
did you find him?
He was taken away last night.
That's a relief.
Still, it's creepy.
He was right under your place,
pacing by that tree,
talking, singing, dancing.
What kind of weirdo does that?
Li Shi Can...
I could do that too.
Is Li Shi Can that famous now?
Some crazy male fan?
Chasing a star at midnight?
Could it have been then...
a Li Shi Can fan?
Why stalk him under my place?
Thanks.
I'll get going.
Thanks, bye.
A drunk...
Kinda scary.
Late night bar, drinking with someone...
Nothing special.
Just one character.
Vertical, turn.
Horizontal, vertical.
Left, dot, horizontal.
That's "Trapped".
Lawyer Liu is funny.
Dear two lawyers,
May I ask you a question?
Do you know how to deal with criminals?
If at midnight a drunk shows up,
what should I do?
What's got you so happy, Mao?
Don't ask me.
Ask the person involved. Song.
Is our firm this idle?
No legal consults at all?
If that's the case, Liu Mao,
we don't need interns.
Yes, we do. I've got over ten cases today.
I-I'll get back to work.
- Ma'am Zhang.
- I'm free.
Then tell me about it.
How are you free?
You've got all those domestic abuse cases,
and construction site disputes, too.
Mine's nothing.
I won't waste your time.
I'm heading back.
How small could it be?
Now that you say that,
I'm even more curious.
Ma'am Zhang,
curious, huh?
Let me show you.
Look at the guy in this video.
Doesn't he look like Lawyer Xu
at least seventy percent?
Come on.
You got this.
Xu Huai Song,
you can do it.
We need to stay rational.
Rational.
Right.
Image matters.
We can't go in unprepared.
So think it through.
Those key traits...
elegant,
aloof.
Right. Aloof.
Aloof.
And besides that, one more thing.
Singing and dancing.
Li Shi Can sings and dances.
How hard can it be?
Seriously, how hard?
If Li Shi Can can do it, I can too.
Li Shi Can,
so can I.
Hello? Property management?
I just got up to use the bathroom,
and there's a drunk downstairs.
He's losing it.
Get over here now.
Hurry up.
Elegant.
Aloof.
Sing and dance.
I can do it.
Ruan Yu.
I'm here.
Where are we going?
Don't ask.
Just drag him away.
Wait, what? What do you mean?
- No, I...
- Move.
How...
It's not 70% alike.
At least 50%, right?
Two at most.
Three. At least three.
I'd say a full ten.
Nice moves.
Shame you're not debuting.
What a pity. Even Ma'am Zhang says so.
Ruan Yu, Ruan Yu.
I already asked a police I know.
About last night, the guy in your complex
was just sad, pitiful and heartbroken.
Drank too much
and lost his mind.
The police gave him a warning.
So don't worry.
He should've...
turned over a new leaf.
Relax. No more trouble.
You've got bad luck.
Right as you hit it,
property got there first.
What a pity.
Not pity,
lucky.
Why?
With Lawyer Xu,
love is like court.
All reckless moves must be forbidden.
Till it's settled, don't rush it.
But,
love isn't court.
The court needs evidence.
Love's a tug-of-war.
Every relationship is a push and pull.
Love is war.
Let's go. Time to stake out the site.
- Got it.
- Lawyer Xu.
One more thing, I really think
you can't treat love like a case.
If you wait for a perfect shot,
someone else will take her.
Right?
Aren't you leaving?
I... okay, my bad.
I'll get back to work.
Bye.
He's getting cuter.
One shot, one kill.
He should've...
turned over a new leaf.
Relax, no more trouble.
There's nothing you can't get over,
just that you can never go back.
So cheesy.
When did I like that?
Finalize the color palette.
Prep work for the case is basically done.
Good thing he didn't nitpick my Chapter 23.
Adults
know how to save face.
Lawyer Liu, Lawyer Xu,
you've worked hard on my case.
If you're free,
dinner's on me.
Looks like Ruan Yu is fine.
Didn't see your "great" video.
Sure.
Let's get Cantonese.
This place okay?
Lawyer Xu just recovered,
this place is light.
If Ruan Yu knew
"just recovered" Lawyer Xu
went wild last night...
Ruan Yu, sorry.
I've got a blind date.
I can't make it.
You two enjoy dinner.
He and I?
How's that?
Pretty loyal, right?
Real date or fake?
Of course, it's real.
Let's both try hard
and meet at the top.
Hope so.
One tip.
Dinner with Ruan Yu,
don't drink.
Some people get messy drunk.
Without Lawyer Liu,
feels a bit weird.
Black bean pork intestines.
Not very aloof, is it?
Crispy roast duck.
He just got out of the hospital.
Probably can't eat greasy food.
But that duck looks so good.
Pork congee with century egg?
No century egg.
It's bad for the stomach.
Hand-held ribs?
No hand-held.
Not very elegant.
No beef either.
Hard to digest.
No garlic.
Smell's too strong.
Seafood's out too.
What if his stomach's inflamed?
No cartilage bites.
Too noisy to eat.
Done ordering?
Yeah.
All that for two bowls of congee?
Men...
looks can't beat stingy.
You can't eat good looks.
Lawyer Xu, don't save money for me.
We can order more.
This is enough.
Any trolls bothering you lately?
Not anymore, since the lawyer's letter,
it's been quiet.
Lately,
still reading comments?
Sometimes.
I'm handling it better now.
Don't worry, Lawyer Xu.
Good.
People would normally think
a like online or a reply is nothing.
But in a case,
those actions can reflect your stance.
I did like one by accident.
I undid it right away.
Will that affect the case?
What did you like?
Trial's coming.
No extra trouble.
But it's not related to the case.
Just some sad, poetic posts.
Then why
undo it?
That line about "can't go back"...
felt too cheesy.
I currently write romance,
but not that style.
Good then.
What did you say, Lawyer Xu?
I said...
that's good.
Just eat your congee.
Weren't you chatting first?
Sorry, Lawyer Xu.
Ruan Yu, look.
That drunk from the other day.
So ridiculous.
This drunk kinda looks like...
The drunk...
like me?
No.
Just the build, a bit.
You're so disciplined,
you wouldn't drink that much.
Even if you did,
you wouldn't be like that.
The video is blurry.
A suit doesn't mean
you can ID him.
One more tip.
Tell your property team to tighten security.
This guy
is probably Li Shi Can's fan.
The moves look like
Li Shi Can's dance.
Still pretty funny.
Let's eat.
It'll get cold.
Yes.
Li Shi Can dances well.
He's a pro.
After all, that's his job.
Lawyer Xu, you know him too?
Shouldn't I ask you?
Everyone knows stars.
But to be with one
under the same roof
same couch...
that's quite close, isn't it?
You mean last time?
I knew him before fame.
We're college alumni.
Not just that, huh?
You're from the same place too.
As how I remember it, he's from Su City, right?
Yes.
Met in high school?
Not really.
He was at No.2 High.
I was...
Which school were you at then?
I...
- Sorry, Lawyer Xu.
- It's fine.
- I've got it.
- Sorry.
It's okay.
Thanks.
Lawyer Xu, let's eat first.
It'll get cold.
Then thank that glass for its sacrifice.
You're laughing?
How is Xu Huai Song living abroad...
How could he know that
Li Shi Can's from Su City?
Is he that famous now?
Not his fault.
After all, you brought him up.
Still, I always got this feeling...
that Xu Huai Song
has an issue with him.
I got it.
It's that misunderstanding.
He even called the police.
True.
Talking to Xu Huai Song, it's all traps.
One after another.
From now on,
I'll avoid seeing him alone.
Or I'll slip up.
If you ask me,
you, instead of being on edge,
just be bold and tell the truth.
If you don't care about him,
then let the past drift by
and keep your spirit light.
Okay?
That's not about whether I care.
I just don't want to rip off my past
and lay it bare in the open.
It's too embarrassing.
Mom, Dad, I'm home.
Our girl's back.
Hold on, turning this off.
What's for dinner, Mom?
Tomorrow's Winter Solstice, right?
I'm making your dumplings.
Nice.
Then I want it with
osmanthus wine.
Sure, I got you.
I'll help in a second, Mom.
Stop it, you'll just get in the way.
You'll slow me down.
Right?
You're killing my vibe.
Mom, where's Dad?
Your dad was just here.
- Ruan Yu's back.
- Dad.
We're in for a treat.
Thanks, Mom.
Come on. Let's get some sun.
Mom, I'll be outside.
You two just left me?
No one cares?
This weather's great.
Still talking to Xiao Liu?
Not again.
I told you,
we're not a match.
I'm just saying,
being a lawyer is good.
If you get in trouble,
he can help.
Dad,
you want me to get in trouble?
Kid,
can't you tell?
Exactly.
Here.
By the way,
we're going back to Su City.
No way.
It's been windy and rainy.
Today's the only sunny day.
All that travel around
will trigger your rheumatism.
We haven't lived there for years,
but for the Solstice,
- we should clean it.
- Right.
Your mom's been missing it.
She wants to go back.
Okay then.
I'll go with her.
You stay home and rest.
Then
I can have some alone time with Mom.
You, honestly.
You're all grown up,
not with your boyfriend,
but "alone time" with Mom?
Exactly.
Fine.
Then I can only
go along with it.
I'd be happy to.
Then I'll just...
let it all be.
Alright.
Go enjoy yourselves.
The weather's great.
Maybe call Xiao Liu.
Young people
need to meet more
to make it work.
Remember us back then?
Your daughter
if she had half your skills,
I wouldn't worry.
Who's she like?
Me, of course.
Aunt Qu just texted me.
Guess she still thinks of me.
Even good stuff, she thinks of me.
Unlike some people.
Once they prep for a case,
it's been a long time since seeing Ruan Yu.
True.
Hard to run into her.
Not like me though.
See? She asked me out.
Lately,
my neck's really stiff.
Probably overworked.
Must be tiring you out.
Yeah, right there.
A bit more pressure.
Here, take it.
Not bad.
Xiao Liu, last time you said
you go to Su City a lot.
Got any plans soon?
Maybe drop me and Ruan Yu at the old house?
No pressure if it's a hassle.
Come eat at my place sometime.
How about this,
you handle it all.
Reply however you want.
Just tell her
I'm busy.
Or tell her
I don't get along with her daughter.
We clash.
For your happiness, man,
I can take the hit.
It's fine.
One more thing.
That place next door, the matchmaking agency,
lease ends next month.
I'm thinking
we take it over.
Expand the office.
Make the firm bigger.
More space, brighter.
My pleasure.
I've got a case tomorrow.
- Just leave it to me!
- Not tomorrow night. I've got a date.
Set up by that agency?
Yes.
You sure a place that can't even pay rent
can secure your happiness
for the rest of your life?
Rent needs money.
Love doesn't.
Daytime won't take long.
Surely it won't ruin your date at night.
No wonder no train ticket.
Should've known it's this kind of ride.
Sorry, Lawyer Liu.
Thanks for the trouble.
No trouble.
It's on the way.
You really going to Su City for work?
Yeah, doing visits.
One client's...
old classmate
happens to be there.
Even old classmates get visits.
That's a lot of work.
Tell me about it. Some clients
are really tough.
By the way, Ruan Yu,
I saw the location you sent.
It's close to Xu Huai Song's grandma's.
Xu Huai Song?
My mom taught him for half a year.
What if she remembers?
Then we're busted.
Really? What a coincidence.
Mom, when we get there,
want to grab that--
That name sounds familiar.
Just can't recall.
It's okay, Auntie.
If you can't recall, just let it go.
Not important anyway.
Just remember me.
Of course I do.
You know,
when you get older, things change.
Back in those alleys, all those kids,
I remembered them all.
Same with my students.
But now,
I forget so many.
It's okay, Mom.
My memory's not great either.
See?
Use the computer less.
You two keep chatting.
Listen,
I've dropped those two off safe.
Don't worry.
By the way,
got some intel for you.
Aunt Qu said in the car
she's meeting old coworkers today.
Not sure if Ruan Yu'll visit school.
Up to you.
Liu the wingman, mission accomplished.
Mom, it's raining.
Use an umbrella.
See? Right?
So young,
sitting all day.
Move a bit, everything aches.
What, you're old like me?
I accept your criticism.
I'll work out more.
Look,
One less look each time.
This yard, this old house...
I really can't let go.
Back then,
your dad and I got married here.
You used to play all around here.
Remember?
I liked going there.
Two dogs chased you. Remember?
Speaking of that, back then,
your grandparents were still around.
Mom,
all our family memories
are still here.
Come to think of it,
we'll come back less and less.
Not really.
Travel's so easy now.
I'll get a license in Hang City.
Whenever you and Dad want back,
I can drive you anytime.
That'd be tiring for you.
If you ask me,
if my son-in-law drives, that'd be perfect.
Mom,
you always bring this up.
Couldn't say it in the car.
Lawyer Liu
already has a new match.
So from now on, don't trouble him.
Really?
He seemed pretty into it. I thought...
You'd asked him.
Lawyer Liu is kind-hearted.
Hard to say no.
That's awkward.
It's fine. So...
if Liu's not right, there are others.
I'll find someone.
Okay, okay.
Take your time.
I'll grab some water.
Go ahead.
Let me look a bit more.
Okay, Mom.
Boss.
What do you need?
Soy sauce.
Over there.
Boss,
Which one's better for cooking?
At Ms. Ruan's place,
your parents use this one.
This one works too.
What about dipping?
Which tastes better?
For dipping, let me see.
This one's good.
Only for dipping?
Can it do cold dishes?
Sure.
Both can.
Then...
Then which is better value?
Which won't stick when cooking?
I'll pick more for you then.
Okay.
Finally noticed me.
But that look...
like I'm an idiot.
Ten years.
Everything's changed.
All set?
Yes.
Boss, I'll take this.
Coming, Mom.
Yeah.
Why's it sunny now?
Southern weather.
Rain on and off.
It's noon, let's eat.
- Sure.
- What do you want?
Up to you. I'm all good.
Now that you mention it,
I kinda miss the cafeteria dishes.
At noon? Cafeteria?
Might run into Xu Huai Shi.
Mom,
let's go to Old Zhou Steak House.
I'm craving it.
Didn't you say anything's fine?
Didn't think of it, now I really want
the cafeteria meatballs.
They're so good.
And we can
see Ms. Guo and Mr. Li, catch up.
The more I think, the better.
It's settled, let's go.
You foodie.
Eat your jelly.
Let's hit the cafeteria.
Bring the umbrella.
Might rain again.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Let's go.
Youth is great.
Used to hate uniforms.
Now I can't even wear them.
Then what about you, Mom?
We're both young.
Still young.
How about this,
I borrow two uniforms, and we put them on,
maybe someone'll ask,
"Excuse me, where's the art hall?"
What did I teach you?
Smooth talker.
Shameless too.
Well said.
Auntie, three drumsticks.
- Okay.
- I'm starving.
- Auntie.
- Yes?
Is Chef Cai still here?
Which Cai?
The one who updated the menu.
Not a clue.
Aunt Zhu,
it's Ms. Qu.
- Oh, hi!
- Two veggie dishes too.
Sure.
Since we're here,
all those drumsticks I missed
I'll make up today.
- So good.
- Tastes great?
Huai Shi, I'm off.
Song,
over here.
What's up?
Mom, just eat more.
You look better with some weight.
You just said you'd eat three drumsticks.
You were hungry.
Now you've lost your appetite.
How can I finish three alone?
Why is Xu Huai Song here?
I barely dodged his questions last time.
If he sees me eating here,
with his old Chinese teacher,
he'll know I'm from this school.
Then he'll ask
my class and year.
I might recall stuff I shouldn't.
Speaking of, when I was young,
your dad said
I looked like Baochai.
I'll send the edits later.
Okay,
bye.
Song, why're you back?
Felt like it.
Tonight, let's go for
the first solstice hotpot.
Today?
I'm busy.
I don't buy it.
You're free, watching me eat.
Who said I'm here for you?
Got another sister here?
Stop looking around.
Focus on eating.
It's good.
I'm leaving.
Song, leaving already?
Go back and rest after.
Wait for me.
Ruan Yu,
I'll go see Ms. Li.
You look around.
It's good.
I'll have one anyway.
See?
Just eat it.
Knew you couldn't resist.
Go baseline.
Pass it, pass!
- Here!
- Defense!
- Left, hurry!
- Okay.
Dec 21, Winter Solstice.
Sunny.
Back at Su City No.1 High.
Watch out!
You okay?
I'm fine.
Didn't interrupt you writing?
No, just journaling.
Not at all.
You still handwrite now?
Just jotting life down.
So artsy.
You a writer?
I...
Kind of.
What do you write?
Romance.
Then you must be good at love.
At your age,
not focusing on school,
thinking about dating?
Adults don't allow it
because they worry about grades.
My grades
can't drop any lower.
That's actually...
Pretty insightful.
Either mindset or grades, you need one.
If you've got neither,
that's rough.
So, the one you like, do they like you back?
Like me?
If she doesn't hit me,
I'm grateful.
Then I guess
your kind of situation is a bit like
a crush?
Didn't expect that.
You seem so carefree.
Even carefree people
in front of someone they like get cautious.
Everyone shows it differently, that's it.
True.
Then tell me,
what should I do?
I can tell you
how to study Chinese.
I was pretty good at it.
So?
You adults...
boring.
What's your name?
Zhao Yi.
Like "runaway cart-Yi." Not "iron."
When you graduate,
confess to her.
You have to.
Lawyer Liu,
Ruan Yu,
sorry, something came up.
This afternoon, I met two key clients.
I have to drive them to Hang City.
So I might...
It's fine.
We'll take the train back.
No, don't book yet.
I still have a seat.
Enough for your mom too.
Ride with me, it's easier.
On your way back,
stay safe, okay?
Okay. Thanks, Lawyer Liu.
No problem, that's it then.
- Bye.
Sorry for that.
Lawyer Liu, we shouldn't trouble you.
We can go ourselves.
No, it's fine.
And my boss has already told me,
you two must ride with me.
Well...
Alright.
[Books half off. Favorites? Even more off.]
Boss, what's the "More off"?
Finally!
If you were later,
I couldn't hold the good stuff.
You've been waiting on me.
Don't tell me
no one else is buying.
Of course not.
You know this shop's been around.
Not long ago,
that guy came by.
Which one?
That one
you know...
Yes. The kid who fought you for the Foundation.
Remember?
Who?
Don't recall.
Fine, keep browsing.
Okay, talk later.
Sure. I'll leave you to it.
Alright.
See what you like.
[June, 2013]
June, 2013.
My pre-senior year.
I'll take this too.
Okay.
Here you go.
Zhao Yi,
not coming?
You go ahead.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
What's your name?
We're not in the same class.
Had me worried all break.
Si Yu chose arts too.
But not with us.
She's in Class 5.
So we're apart.
No idea why.
Everyone's got strengths.
I won't follow the crowd.
Not into science.
I'll choose...
history, politics, geo.
At least we sit close.
We can still visit her.
What about dinner?
Hello, class.
Take your seats.
Class rep,
Yes, teacher.
Let's do roll call.
Get to know each other.
Good morning, teacher.
Chen Yan.
Here.
Wang Hao Lin.
Zhao "Tie" (Iron).
Hey there,
you're the rep and can't read?
That's "Tie"?
It's "Yi."
Like "runaway cart Yi."
What?
Rep can't be nearsighted?
What's up, Zhao "Tie"?
Lost in space?
Zhao Yi.
Zhao...
because of you,
my name's been wrong a year.
Too late now.
Where are you going?
Going to study, okay?
Listen to yourself.
I don't buy it.
Boss, I'm off.
Okay.
Yu,
Mom's with Liu in his car now.
Stay safe.
Keep me posted.
Who is this?
I don't add strangers.
New cafeteria contractor.
If you want dishes, tell me.
I'm Cai.
That's why you wanted QQs.
Thorough work.
Make more drumsticks.
They're always gone.
Got it.