( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[EP5: Lawyer Xu's Quiet Longing]
- Come down!
- Come catch me!
I'm sorry, miss.
Sorry,
I didn't keep an eye on him.
It's okay.
I noticed that a lot of Cen Si Si's photos
on social media
are imitating yours.
What were you thinking?
Lawyer Xu,
thanks to your quick wit.
Otherwise, I would've been exposed.
Nice performance.
Adequate for a prime-time drama?
Adequate to fool a layperson.
So he's a pro?
He'd think my acting...
Chen Hui,
drive Ms. Ruan
and deliver a recording copy to Lawyer Liu.
I will.
Lawyer Xu, you're not returning to the firm?
No, I'm heading to the airport.
To the US immediately?
Yes.
So you're...
here about my case?
In Ms. Ruan's eyes,
I'm such a loiterer?
Thank you anyway, Lawyer Xu,
for helping me collect evidence today.
You're so busy with work.
Take care of yourself.
Safe ride.
Senior,
I lost my temper.
I didn't mean it.
Actually, I didn't do them.
Are you still around?
Realizing she had been recorded,
she's trying to fix it.
It's not convenient. See you in court.
[Three days later]
Coming!
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Xu.
It's for you.
Flowers for me?
It's the flowers that you bought.
And don't worry.
The payment has already been made.
Can I help you move in?
Sorry, no.
What's the problem?
I just really don't need them.
And do me a favor and throw them out.
No need?
Thank you.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
♫ Boss, phone call ♫
Hello?
I told you my address,
not so that you could send this stuff.
What stuff?
A pot of ugly flowers.
Ugly?
Ruan Yu bought it to thank you.
Isn't it nice to liven up your house?
Besides...
Sir! Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Can you bring the flowers back to me?
Why?
Thank you.
Okay, no why.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Didn't you thank Xu Huai Song for such a favor?
Of course, I did.
Look,
I sent him flowers, and he received.
I knew it.
Romance novelists really know
how to be romantic.
What did you send?
Cappuccino roses or Blue Enchantress?
Carola roses are nice, too.
Kalanchoe.
It clears heat and detoxifies,
calms and refreshes the mind,
and helps with sleep.
He takes international flights frequently.
It's perfect for him with jet lag.
A practical gift?
Good idea.
So, did you only give one to him?
Careful. Easy, easy.
It's fine. It's not heavy.
- Where, Mao?
- There.
- In the corner.
- That corner?
What about the former one?
Thank you.
You're welcome, Lawyer Xu.
I'm organizing the rest documents.
I might bother you again.
No need to be so polite.
Yes.
Evil Polar Fleece wants me to go to the office.
What a freak.
Thank you, Ms. Ruan, for the money tree.
What did you mean by "Besides"?
I meant, besides you,
the whole firm received her gifts.
Terminate the contract?
You mean we'll terminate the contract
for Wen Xiang's new book?
Do you know how many netizens
attack us on our official Weibo?
They say we're publishing
plagiarized work shamelessly.
We've clarified the plagiarism dispute,
haven't we?
Poet clarified it herself.
The rest is manipulated by Su Cheng.
She's slandering Wen Xiang.
Facing a public outcry,
does the truth matter?
It certainly does!
If not, then why do we have laws?
The public outcry is incited by Su Cheng,
whom Wen Xiang is suing.
The netizens will know the truth soon.
Anyway, if the plagiarism dispute
doesn't settle in three days,
we'll definitely terminate
all her publishing deals.
Terminating her contract now
means we support Su Cheng, which--
That's enough!
I know
you favor your classmate.
But remember
your salary is paid by Liwen
rather than Wen Xiang.
Speaking of salary,
when I joined Liwen,
it gave me no resources.
Any promising author I scouted
would be poached by other editors.
It was Wen Xiang
who gave me her promising novels
and trusted me 100%.
She is my friend,
my classmate,
and more importantly,
my best partner in my career.
Were it not for her,
I wouldn't have survived in this industry.
If I remember correctly,
you also owe this position to her.
If we can't tell right from wrong,
and kick down the ladder,
none will dare to work with us.
Shen Ming Ying.
You'd better watch your words.
Don't make yourself a target.
If the target can shield Wen Xiang,
I'll be it
for sure.
In court, the recording can only
serve as supplementary evidence.
But the counter-plagiarism comparison chart
can prove your novel's originality.
Finish this up.
Okay.
Lawyer Xu.
I have no more questions for Chapter 13.
I'll organize it tonight.
Yes.
Excuse me, I need to take this.
Hello?
I'm home.
Might be the defendant's retaliation.
The higher-ups at SG are clear that
the defendant is capable
of remote bomb control.
Yes.
That's a matter for the police.
Okay, you guys handle it.
Sorry.
Lawyer Xu,
isn't it getting late over there?
I drank coffee for nothing again?
What did you just say?
I said, "Isn't it getting late over there?"
Is it convenient to talk?
Sure.
Let's move to...
Chapter 14.
Chapter 14,
paragraph 3.
He originally disliked furry animals,
until the day he passed by the art museum
and saw her feed a stray cat in the grass.
Sunshine,
a breeze,
the green grass,
the cat,
and her.
All of them
formed an extremely tender landscape
in his heart.
From then on,
he loved what she loved,
followed her lead,
greeted every cat in their school,
but never...
greeted
her.
Xu Huai Song liked cats
from the very beginning.
Why did I adapt it for romance?
The two sentences are exactly the same,
word for word.
Lawyer Xu,
what do you think?
I notice some nuances.
Your hero loved what she loved,
while the other party's hero didn't.
I see.
The Poet's hero knew
the heroine would pass by the art museum,
and he orchestrated it.
So it's not that he loved what she loved.
I was being biased.
I forgot she adapted
the hero into a calculating man.
Calculating...
is a derogatory term, right?
No.
Lawyer Xu,
don't get me wrong, I'm not against him,
but analyzing rationally and calmly.
Calculating...
can be a neutral term.
From the positive side, it means he's smart.
Is the coffee hot?
Wipe it off, Lawyer Xu!
It's not hot.
Come here.
Lawyer Xu,
how old is it?
Is it fully vaccinated?
Is it okay to bathe it?
It's had all its shots.
It's about six months old.
Okay. Then bathe it.
The coffee residue
might be harmful for the kitten.
We can discuss the case later.
Okay.
How to bathe it?
You don't know?
Isn't it your cat?
Whose cat is it?
How to bathe it?
You need cat shampoo,
an absorbent towel,
and ideally a dryer.
Then put the kitten in a tub or a sink.
Use warm water between 38 and 40℃.
- Be careful...
- Wait.
What should I do now?
Adjust the water temperature first.
Don't shower it directly later.
Fill the tub with water first.
Keep the water level low.
It might be scared.
So be very gentle.
What should I do now?
Hold the scruff of its neck
with your left hand.
Try to be gentle.
And then?
Then wet it slowly from the neck down
with your right hand,
and apply the shampoo.
Be careful not to let it choke on water.
Finished.
Okay.
Lawyer Xu,
wipe it down with the absorbent towel
before putting it into the dryer.
Wipe it gently.
And mute the dryer.
So he likes cats, too.
Nice.
Lawyer Xu. I'm still here.
I forgot.
I need to take a shower.
Then, Lawyer Xu.
Then move me...
No, you move the laptop.
Can't you just end the video call?
Oh yes.
Yes.
I...
Oh my god, a naked man!
You scared the life out of me!
Xu Huai Song?
What?
What are you doing? What's going on?
- I...
- Confess everything. Now!
Confess what?
His cat splashed coffee all over him.
He didn't know how to bathe it,
so he got splashed with water too.
That's what you saw.
No.
Something's fishy.
What is it?
First,
he has a cat.
Second, he doesn't know how to bathe it.
So, who usually bathes the cat?
You mean,
someone else lives with him?
His girlfriend?
Maybe he usually takes it to a pet shop.
But possibly you're right.
True.
He clearly has a dryer at home.
There must be someone who bathes the cat.
Besides, he's not young anymore.
And he's so outstanding.
It'd be weird if he doesn't have one.
Yes, back to business.
Good news.
Your website's official account
posted a statement,
confirming it wasn't the Poet's original work,
Su Cheng's claim was groundless,
and you were the innocent, original writer.
I sent you the statement. Check it.
I didn't notice it just now.
Counsels, this is the investigative report
by Qianhe Net.
Can it serve as supplementary evidence
in court?
You should have seen our chief editor's face.
Yesterday, she was ranting like a machine gun.
But today?
Seeing the report,
she did a complete 180 so fast!
I guess only the adaptive
can get that position.
You quarreled with her again?
No.
I just stood my ground.
And she lashed out in impotent rage.
Thanks for taking the bullet for me.
It's fine. Just treat me to a meal.
I'll treat you to many meals.
Deal.
With this investigative report,
the odds are in our favor.
But shamed publicly by the website,
she'll probably pay trolls
to spin the story again.
No big deal.
Since we can't shut them up,
we'll just close our eyes.
Out of sight, out of mind.
[she'll probably pay trolls
to spin the story again.]
True.
As soon as we close the curtain,
- Lawyer Liu revealed it.
- A replacement?
- They gave up Poet
- Look.
and shamed Su Cheng to protect Wen Xiang.
What a trade-off!
The cash cow is always favored!
But I think Wen Xiang owes it to luck.
Su Cheng is clearly a better writer.
Society needs a voice for justice.
I side with Su Cheng unconditionally.
Are you that free?
Not really.
Then rewrite this.
Your statement isn't strong enough.
Don't I have any pride?
You only get one chance for a statement.
If it's not to the point,
it's a total failure.
Is the client's interest more important,
or is your pride?
Put up or shut up!
Lawyer Liu, I'm not joking.
Your work really isn't up to par.
I did write it in a hurry.
I was swamped with all these cases.
I didn't think twice
before sending the screenshots.
The recording evidence is secured.
We can now face the defendant head-on.
The website's report is only the first step.
A backlash in public opinion is normal.
Don't worry about it.
A lawyer's statement will follow.
By the end of today,
the tide of public opinion will turn.
Lawyer Liu really isn't that great.
He's so careless.
When it comes to being reliable,
it has to be Lawyer Xu.
But he seems to be already taken.
The tone of his messages
to you is way too formal.
Well...
Then I'll be formal, too.
Okay, Lawyer Xu.
Thank both of you for your hard work.
Received.
Remember? Someone made snide remarks
about your serials,
claiming that Su Cheng was
a much better storyteller than you.
You didn't care,
saying everyone has their own taste
and readers are free to choose and comment.
But now?
It turns out it wasn't a real reader.
It might be Cen Si Si's alt account.
Probably.
How did you offend her back in college?
She's been hounding
and troubling you for years.
I wish I knew.
You robbed her of scholarship?
Or her recommendation spot?
Or...
her man?
No.
You've been single since birth.
Ming Ying.
Do you think it has something
to do with Li Shi Can?
The way she mentioned him at the mall that day,
sounded like an admirer.
Yes.
She targets and imitates you,
because she regards you as a rival in love?
But I don't feel that way about Li Shi Can.
In her case,
it's more like an imaginary enemy.
Precisely.
That day, Cen Si Si did bring up
the three of us being in the Arts Department,
in a snide tone.
But it has been years.
She's still hung up on it?
Exactly.
We haven't seen him in ages.
He's now a top-tier idol.
Hello, everyone. I'm Li Shi Can.
Thank you for joining my livestream today.
The livestream just started,
and we've already had
more than a million views.
Today's giveaway seems very appealing to you.
Yes, we have giveaways for Can's fans today.
Play Truth or Dare with Shi Can.
- Shi Can...
- As a superstar, he's still accessible.
He even plays Truth or Dare with his fans.
Since you all want to see it,
let's play it together.
Good. Do you dare to accept the challenge?
Sure.
The lawyer's statement is closely followed
by marketing accounts' apologetic statements.
The trolls Cen Si Si hired all turn silent now.
Xu Huai Song is quite impressive.
Our chief editor even said today
that considering your good image now,
it's high time you updated your serial
and capitalized on the trend.
She's playing both sides.
Just eat.
The rules are as follows:
Comment what you'd like Shi Can to do.
If it's accepted,
Shi Can will not only do it,
but also give you a signed photo.
All right, let's take a look.
A fan named "Poetic and Picturesque" says,
"7 is your lucky number.
Call the 7th number in your contacts
and say, see you at the usual place
the day after tomorrow morning."
That's a tough request.
But since a fan's request,
Shi Can won't refuse, right?
Of course.
Today's motto is to grant every request.
Give me the phone.
[Call Song and say it's your classmate.]
Okay, let's hear
[Contacts]
who is the lucky one.
This game is exciting.
If it were me, I'd call my mom.
That way, nothing could go wrong.
Yeah, clever girl.
Me?
I don't think so.
It's not his name.
Besides, Ruan definitely
won't rank 7th in the contacts.
Yeah.
Accept it, and you'll know.
Hello?
Hello.
Long time no see.
It's Shi Can.
How have you been lately?
Not bad.
So, are you still living there?
I just came back from abroad
and wanted to catch up with you.
So, the day after tomorrow morning,
see you at the usual place.
Okay.
See you there. Bye.
What a coincidence!
When you need it, it comes.
Meet him, and ask him about Cen Si Si.
The comments blow up.
Whose sweet voice?
Can, you can't see her at the usual place!
Who came up with that dare?
Come out so that we can
"take good care" of you.
My troublemakers.
Remember to remind me
to apologize to her after the livestream.
Otherwise, it'd be bad if I stood her up.
As honey-tongued as before.
He cleared it up indirectly in no time,
and pacified his fans.
Cool.
So he meant it was just a game,
not an invitation?
Fine.
When he calls you, ask him about Cen Si Si.
I don't think that's a good idea.
We haven't been in touch for so long.
It's awkward to ask about
that right off the bat.
And he doesn't know my pen name.
He must be unaware of the situation.
Well, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Shi Can has prepared milk tea
for everyone in the lounge.
Thank you for your hard work today. Thank you.
- Xiao Fei, lead the way.
- Okay.
This way, please. I'll take you to the drinks.
- Good job.
- Bye.
Shi Can.
Take a quick 15-minute break.
Then get changed for the next commercial event.
Okay.
It's over.
Don't even ask. I'm exhausted.
Miss, this is for you.
For me?
[2016 Midsummer Night's Dream Art Performance]
Shi Can, it's perfect.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Jing Jing was there.
Why did the director ask me
to send the bouquet in her place?
Because he's gossipy.
When you were absent,
he said you,
a golden scriptwriter backstage,
and Li Shi Can,
a male lead onstage,
can be a perfect match in our department.
You stared blankly at him just now.
So our director wanted to set you two up.
No.
- I was just...
- Alright.
No need to explain to your best friend.
As if I wouldn't know.
The same scenery,
but a different person.
While you were staring at Li Shi Can,
you were reminiscing about Xu someone, right?
[Wen Xiang's Weibo]
[It's my personal experience...]
Xu someone...
is your hero, right?
It's said that Su Cheng, Wen Xiang's junior,
targets her due to a real-life dispute.
Waiting for the truth. @Wen Xiang.
No wonder after Poet's clarification
and apology,
Su Cheng, a third party,
still smeared Wen Xiang.
So it's a real-life dispute.
Fridge horror.
Which school is Su Cheng from? Dig deeper.
Why are they doxxing her?
Don't become a pawn.
Can't you see this move
is from a professional PR team?
Wen Xiang has someone backing her.
Online matters should stay online.
I would never do such a thing.
The tide is turning so fast.
Doesn't anyone think it's fishy?
Lawyer Xu, have you browsed Weibo?
Lawyer Liu, have you browsed Weibo?
I have.
Did your firm do this?
No.
Then who could it be?
No idea.
To fight fire with fire isn't our solution.
However,
the defendant might think we were behind this.
Senior, now I know you.
In that case,
don't blame me for not being nice.
Let's see who can play dirtier.
Have you ever been nice to me?
The exposure wasn't done by me or my lawyer.
[The message has been sent,
but rejected by the receiver.]
Might be the defendant's retaliation.
The higher-ups at SG are clear that
the defendant is capable
of remote bomb control.
Public security is so good here.
Even if Cen Si Si wants revenge,
she can't do much.
That's an incredible legend.
Due to a groundless infringement accusation,
SG was sued by its competitors.
The scandal resulted in
a plummeting stock price
and a serious economic crisis.
Xu Yin, a reputable lawyer
at the California bar,
accepted the case.
But two days before the trial,
he suffered a sudden stroke.
After being resuscitated,
he was diagnosed with vascular dementia.
[San Francisco, 2022]
Xu is currently unconscious!
What should we do about our case?
This is the most critical time.
And someone needs to take responsibility.
You understand?
If no one is responsible,
I will sue your firm!
Just bear with me.
I don't want to bear with you!
Mr. Lawrence.
Now I'm on it.
In the end, Xu Yin's son,
Xu Huai Song, stepped forward.
He claimed that he had learned from his father
and followed the case throughout,
thus could take charge.
If the case dragged on any longer,
the stock situation would only worsen.
At the last minute,
the board chose Xu Huai Song.
They didn't have much hope.
After all,
changing counsel last minute is a huge risk.
But the result...
SG won the lawsuit.
Xu Huai Song single-handedly
brought SG
back to life.
Almost.
Be good.
Stay with me a little longer.
I promise I'll feed you for a month, okay?
Stay with me for a while.
Look, a token of my sincerity.
Stay with me a little longer.
She's coming, she's coming.
I'll give you a bit more. Here.
Be good.
I don't like cats.
I like you.