( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[EP4: The Longest Plan Called You]
Lawyer Xu!
Why are you back in the country?
You said "See you at the firm."
What's this?
Cen Si Si's another move.
[After consideration,
I still suggest you sue Wen Xiang...]
That's so two-faced.
Sorry, got a little worked up.
Two-faced?
Look in the mirror and you'll see.
But I have a question.
How did you get in touch with the Poet?
I reached out to her before.
She was always so secretive.
The most she'd do was issue a statement.
Now she's actually willing
to work undercover for you.
We're professional lawyers.
Of course, we know a few tricks of the trade.
Otherwise, we'd be taking your legal fees
for nothing.
So for someone like Cen Si Si,
who shows up just to stir trouble,
all sweet to my face but nasty behind my back,
what's our next move?
You're the pros.
If she asks what's next, later on,
just say she should block her to vent.
Why?
Show some professionalism, okay?
Now's the time
to preserve the online evidence again.
I know. Just answer as I told you.
If you really hate this Cen Si Si,
you can just block her.
Are you five?
The evidence has been handed to you.
Of course, we should help the client
do another evidence preservation.
What's going on between these two?
Exactly.
Right.
Lawyer Liu, there's something
I probably shouldn't say,
but as a partner at our firm,
you really should improve
your case-handling skills
and professional competence.
Based on your performance on this case so far,
I suggest
I take over as the main point of contact.
Things are already so tense!
Fine.
Lawyer Liu,
don't take it to heart.
Xu Huai Song! You sly fox.
Thank you, both of you.
Do you have her number?
Cen Si Si's?
- Right.
- I do.
Do you know how to record evidence?
You mean Cen Si Si doesn't know yet
that the Poet sold her out?
I can pretend to be in the dark
to get her to talk.
Yes.
I'm not sure.
Lawyer Xu, could you show me how?
How do we effectively
record a phone call for evidence?
We need to get the other party
to confirm her identity right away.
Go straight to the point.
I see.
So I can't beat around the bush for too long.
I need to get her to the point quickly.
Exactly.
So, do you have the confidence?
I think I've got a handle on her.
I'll give it a try.
I'll call her tomorrow at noon sharp.
Right after lunch
with less blood to the brain,
she'll react slower.
Maybe she won't get suspicious then.
Ruan Yu,
so after lunch tomorrow,
will your brain
slow down too?
Don't worry, Lawyer Liu.
I'll just eat earlier.
Alright.
Speaking of eating,
shouldn't we also get our dinner for today?
It's already this late.
I'm so sorry. I've kept you both so late.
How about I treat you
and Lawyer Xu to dinner?
Sure!
Dean Zhu,
please give me back my phone.
I promise I won't use it ever again.
I really won't!
Dean Zhu, don't give it back.
She'll definitely use it again.
She really will!
What are you two doing?
Doing a comedy routine?
Call your parents now!
Dean Zhu, my parents are abroad.
So what if they're abroad?
Don't they have phones over there?
Is there no signal?
Let me tell you,
if this call doesn't go through today,
neither of you is leaving.
You'll see.
Look at you.
They're abroad, right?
Hello.
I'm Feng Zhu,
Huai Shi Xu's teacher.
Today, the...
Oh, you speak Chinese?
That's great, that's great.
Here's the thing. I'm the Dean of Students
at No. 1 High School,
Zhu Feng.
Today, Xu Huai Shi violated school regulations
by bringing a phone onto campus.
Although this is the first time
I've caught her,
the nature of this offense...
I'm sorry.
I'm not in a position
to handle her matter right now.
You can contact her guardians directly.
The number is 133...
Wait a second!
Song!
This is a betrayal!
You're settling a personal score!
You're just getting back at me
for reading your texts!
By the way,
this isn't the first time
she's brought a phone to school.
After you reach her guardians,
please also explain to them
her dishonest behavior.
Okay, okay.
Thanks. Thanks for your cooperation.
Alright then.
I won't take up more of your time. Goodbye.
A 1,000-word self-reflection.
Before class tomorrow,
put it on my desk.
What are you "ah-ing" about?
What's so funny?
Yours is 1,500 words.
So you're not really that close
with your sister, huh?
She gets into trouble,
yet you won't even cover for her.
She has caused
enough trouble already.
I can't keep covering for her.
Thank you so much for everything,
Lawyer Xu and Lawyer Liu,
during this time.
Ruan Yu, you're being too polite.
We're just doing our jobs.
I'm driving, so I'll pass.
Then Lawyer Xu, have something else.
Let me get you a Coke.
Not healthy.
Excuse me. A glass of lemon water, please.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Ruan Yu, let's drink.
True, work is stressful.
It's better to drink something healthy.
Right.
Here, try this.
You know him?
Ms. Ruan, let me remind you.
Taking photos of others
without their permission
carries certain legal risks.
I'm not just taking photos.
I'm going to throw a punch too.
- Need a hand?
- No, it's personal.
The perfume you're wearing
smells quite nice.
I picked this especially for you.
Don't you think it suits
your elegant style perfectly?
Is that so?
I saw your girlfriend buy this perfume.
I don't think
it suits this lady's style at all.
Ruan Yu.
What a coincidence!
Indeed.
It's a small world.
If it weren't for this coincidence,
I wouldn't have seen this.
Who do you think that guy is?
Didn't you hear her? She said it's personal.
Must be an ex-boyfriend.
If he's already an ex,
why get so worked up?
No love, no hate.
She clearly hasn't let go.
Let me introduce you.
This is Ms. Lin,
who's here for a business partnership with me.
- And this is my--
- I'm Zhang Chuan's girlfriend's best friend.
I don't think Ms. Lin knows
Zhang Chuan has a girlfriend.
But then again,
it's just business, not like you're dating.
No need to share personal details.
Right, Zhang Chuan?
Right.
Plenty of people want to do business with me.
Who do you think you are?
Why should I do business with you?
Ms. Lin...
Ruan Yu, that's not what you think.
- Then what is it?
- I was really...
What's going on?
Who is this?
My girlfriend's best friend.
You're overstepping.
We had a good partnership going,
but you ruined it.
You call that a business talk?
What kind of business
requires holding her hand?
What's wrong with holding her hand?
Let me hold your hand then.
- So what?
- What are you doing?
- I'm doing it.
- Hey!
- You...
- I'm...
And who the hell are you?
I am her lawyer.
Sir, let me remind you.
Under Article 1010 of the Civil Code,
if someone sexually harasses another
through physical conduct
against their will,
the victim has the right
to request that the perpetrator
assume civil liability.
Bringing a lawyer to dinner.
What a big shot.
Come on. Let's go.
What about our deal?
Are you okay?
Back to dinner.
I'm so sorry.
Some personal stuff just now
interrupted our dinner.
You're being too polite again.
It's fine. We had a great meal.
Right, Huai Song?
But it seems you might be running late.
For your next client meeting.
Right.
See? Glad you reminded me.
I totally forgot. Ruan Yu,
I have somewhere to be.
I won't be able to give you a ride.
Let him drive you.
No need to bother. I'll just take a taxi.
No.
Don't take a taxi. It's not safe.
What if you run into
those two guys again? You...
Get in.
Go.
Then, thank you, Lawyer Xu.
[Send to Contacts]
Should I tell her?
If you need any legal assistance,
you can tell me.
Okay!
But for now, it hasn't come to that yet.
Lawyer Xu!
Tell me.
If you see your boyfriend
touching another woman's hand,
does that mean he's cheating?
Are you sure he's still a boyfriend?
Of course I am.
Emotionally, yes.
But legally, the evidence is insufficient.
He held her hand.
Is that not enough to call it cheating?
It doesn't count as solid evidence.
But,
you have the right to break up with him.
Me, break up with him?
Yes.
Lawyer Xu, you've got it wrong.
That guy is my best friend's boyfriend.
Sorry, my mistake.
It's okay.
I'm just torn about
whether to send her the photo or not.
What if I send it to her
and it turns out I was wrong?
Wouldn't that just be causing drama?
But if he really is a jerk, cheating--
If they are truly in love,
they won't split just because you sent a photo.
If they already have trust issues,
even if you don't send this photo,
their relationship
will come to an end sooner or later.
That makes sense.
Lawyer Xu,
you seem to have quite a lot of insight
and experience in relationships.
Lawyer Xu,
that's not what I meant.
While abroad, I handled some divorce cases.
When you see enough of them,
you naturally gain more experience.
I see.
What I said might not be right.
Think it over yourself
before making a decision.
Thank you, Lawyer Xu.
[Volume Down]
I'm so sorry, Lawyer Xu.
I accidentally fell asleep.
When did we arrive?
Just now.
I was just about to wake you.
Thank you for driving me back.
You're welcome.
I'll get going now.
Drive safely, Lawyer Xu.
Yes.
- Goodbye.
- Okay.
Ming Ying, what's up?
Hey, Ruan Yu. Do you have a minute?
I have something to tell you.
I actually have something to tell you, too.
You go first.
I noticed that a lot of Cen Si Si's
photos on social media are imitating yours.
You wanted to tell me about Cen Si Si?
Yeah, what's wrong?
Nothing else to say?
You mean the thing with Zhang Chuan?
He told me as soon as he got home.
He said that,
today he dined with a female client,
and you happened to see them.
It was just a misunderstanding.
It's fine. That deal's dead. Whatever.
He can just find another one.
So he just told you
he was dining with a female client?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
What else did you see?
Look at this.
He told me about this, too.
The product they were testing today
was a hand cream.
They were just testing the product.
But you saw them,
and thought he was holding her hand.
He was just applying hand cream.
Oh, maybe I was wrong.
Don't worry.
If he ever actually dares to cheat,
you won't have to tell me.
I'll dump him immediately.
- Alright.
- Just keep an eye out. I'm hanging up.
Bye!
From now on, let someone else
handle the offline coordination.
I'll only be responsible
for remote product testing
and livestream promotions.
I just thought that face of yours
would work on those female clients.
You're wasting your edge by acting like this.
It's just playing along.
It's not like you're cheating.
How will you make money being so rigid?
Don't regret it
when your girlfriend dumps you broke.
That's just your opinion!
My girlfriend and I are doing great!
You don't need to worry about us!
Are you done soaking, babe?
The water's gone cold.
I told you,
soaking for too long isn't good for you.
Why has this thing been auto-shutting lately?
I wasn't paying attention.
I got you some new saffron soak packets.
Coming tomorrow.
Really? That's great.
I'm already tired of using these mugwort ones.
Here.
Go pour it out.
Babe, have you seen my phone? I just...
Why can't you break
that forgetful habit of yours?
Well, I have you, don't I?
Yeah.
The fried chicken is almost here.
Ruan Yu is almost here, too.
Get ready, okay?
It's only eleven. Isn't she arriving at noon?
She's afraid of missing the best time
to make the phone call.
That's why she left an hour early.
Why aren't you picking up?
- Hello!
Excuse me. Is Zhikun Law Firm right here?
Yes, it is.
This is for someone called
Xu Huai...
It's a food delivery.
Excuse me.
Is this a delivery for Xu Huai Song?
I think so.
Give it to me. I'll take it up for you.
Thanks for the help.
Pick up the phone!
Lawyer Xu,
your delivery's here.
Delivery? I didn't order anything.
Your name is on it.
Then it must be a mistake.
I never eat takeout.
Besides, I don't have any
local food delivery apps.
There you are.
Ruan Yu, you're here.
Where's your fried chicken?
I got you a Coke. It's already downstairs.
Coke and fried chicken. A perfect match, buddy.
Where's the fried chicken?
Right here.
You brought it up?
Perfect. Let's eat together then.
Song, listen!
Ruan Yu might not
even like you anymore.
Even if she still feels something,
the person in her heart
isn't the real you at all.
She doesn't even know
that you love fried chicken.
If you come clean,
will she accept the real you?
Lawyer Liu recently joined a weight loss
group with his colleagues.
If anyone gets caught ordering takeout,
they have to send a red packet
in the company group chat.
But it's okay, Lawyer Liu.
If you want to order it again,
you can still use my name.
I'll cover for you.
But just so you know,
fried chicken is really unhealthy.
You should eat less of it.
Got it. Alright,
I understand.
Well, Lawyer Xu,
you stay disciplined.
- Of course.
- Alright then.
Here, Ruan Yu. Let me pour you some Coke.
Coke and fried chicken.
Perfect!
Thank you!
Lawyer Xu, no Coke for you either.
Coke is just as unhealthy.
This is delicious.
Smells amazing!
Ming Ying, you want a drumstick, right?
You take it.
Didn't you just say
you were so hungry you could eat two?
I want stir-fried cucumber and eggs.
I'll just eat this.
Give me a drumstick.
A drumstick is what I desire,
and Xu Huai Song is also what I desire.
But I cannot have both.
So I'll give up the drumstick for Xu Huai Song.
You're really not eating?
I don't like it.
Then it's mine.
I actually ate before I left,
so I'm not hungry.
Lawyer Liu, you go ahead and eat.
You're not eating either?
Then, Ruan Yu,
have this drink.
It's good.
Lawyer Xu.
Have a drink.
I think you'll like this one.
It's healthier too.
Thanks.
A cup of pure black coffee for you.
Wishing you an energetic day!
Last time, Lawyer Xu
drank coffee like it were Coke.
Isn't it bitter?
My habit.
Lawyer Xu, are you drinking...
black coffee?
It's the first time I've seen
someone gulp black coffee.
Yes.
My habit.
Well, for some things,
only you know
if they're bitter or not.
Right, Lawyer Xu?
This is delicious.
I'm making the call now.
[Cen Si Si]
Hello, this is Ruan Yu.
Is this Cen Si Si?
Yes, it's me.
I've saved your number.
Identity confirmed.
Is it a good time to talk?
Yes, go ahead.
Here's the thing.
I was planning to have my lawyer
handle the settlement talks.
But I changed my mind.
I think it's better if we talk first.
Actually, a film company
reached out to me a while back
about an adaptation.
Here's the deal.
They want me to
properly handle this scandal.
Otherwise,
the film adaptation will fall through.
Senior, the signal's bad here.
Why don't we talk in person?
How about we meet
at Nanhu Restaurant at 1:00 PM?
It's pretty close to your place.
Okay, see you then.
She seems to be on guard.
From here to Nanhu Restaurant,
it takes about 20 minutes.
I'll head over now
to make sure nothing goes wrong.
Can you handle it alone?
Should be fine.
We only have one shot at this.
I'll go with you.
The voice recorder.
Push up to record.
Push down to save.
Thank you, Lawyer Xu.
I thought getting her to talk over the phone
wouldn't be that hard.
But now that we're actually meeting,
my heart is racing.
Do some eye exercises.
You wrote about it in your novel.
It seemed to work.
Sorry,
I held the wrong hand.
Wrong hand?
Then...
Who is the right person?
Jerk!
Just a novel.
It's all fake.
So was the eye exercise thing fake?
Or was liking me fake?
What's the use of eye exercises?
That day, I just called him a jerk
a hundred times
till I calmed down and fell asleep.
Senior,
thanks for giving me this chance
to explain to you in person.
Si Si,
I've thought it over.
Settlement is fine.
But my lawyer
doesn't just represent me.
He also has to consider the film company.
In order not to affect
the adaptation of the novel,
they require that in your apologetic statement,
you admit that you both posted
that defamatory Weibo,
and sent trolls after me.
I...
I didn't do that!
I know that issuing such a statement
would be really hard on you.
But the film company's position is that
if we can't settle, we go to court.
Senior,
I...
I really didn't mean it.
When I posted that thread,
I genuinely believed it.
I didn't know back then
that you were Wen Xiang.
And that thread going viral later.
That wasn't me.
That was just the netizens' own doing.
Si Si.
The Internet is not a lawless place.
Everything leaves a trace.
Even if you deny it now,
once the investigation begins,
it will come out.
After all, we went to the same school.
You're my junior.
Of course, I don't want things
to get too ugly.
Then...
Then, Senior...
can you drop the case first?
You can still
have your lawyer look into everything after.
We settle out of court.
Nice and peaceful.
Wouldn't that be great?
That's not a bad idea.
But what if I drop the case,
and someone with bad intentions
twists it into me being guilty,
then gets the Poet to sue me?
What would I do then?
Senior, aren't you overthinking it?
If the conversation hits a dead end,
break away from your original logic.
Try changing the subject, stir her emotions
to make her let her guard down.
Si Si,
to be honest,
I've been having a hard time lately.
I know
that in this situation,
forget selling the film rights.
If this keeps up, the platform
could drop me at any moment.
How could that be, Senior?
You're the platform's cash cow.
New authors pop up all the time.
Once I'm kicked out of Qianhe Net,
no other platform will want to sign me.
You're worrying too much.
Even if that day comes,
at least Shi Can won't just sit back and watch.
After all, back in school,
you looked out for him.
Right?
He's so busy now.
He won't have time for such trifles.
I was thinking,
if it really was you behind the trolls,
at least with Shi Can as the connection,
I could still beg you to stop.
In that case,
why not just beg me, Senior?
It really was you!
You knew all along that I was Wen Xiang!
Even if I said I didn't know,
you never believed me anyway.
Didn't you tell me that in college,
you decided to become a writer
because you saw my work
in a magazine?
You're thinking way too highly of yourself.
You've been plagiarizing since then, right?
Why should a plagiarized story
get such good stats?
I just wanted everyone to see the truth.
I just didn't expect you
to be so fragile, Ruan Yu.
I only hired a few trolls,
and you're already...
falling apart.
- Come down!
- Come catch me!
I'm sorry, miss!
Having fun with the phone?
Yeah.
You never played with it before?
Let me try it for a bit.
Caught red-handed.
No use denying it. Hand it over.
Dean Zhu!
Xu Huai Shi!
You've gone too far!
You're such a real "loyal" friend.
You gave my phone to the teacher!
So this phone is yours?
Yes. I don't hide from who I am.
It's mine.
So this is what you're into?
A male celebrity winking at you?
No laughing!
That's my freedom.
Freedom, huh?
There are words here, too.
"Shi Can, Shi Can,
my love will never change."
That your freedom, too?
I...
wrote this too.
Okay!
You wrote this, too.
Then I'm curious.
Why is your phone's wallpaper
a picture of her with a male celebrity?
What does this mean?
I...
I ship them as partners!
So you'll just play along with anything, huh?
No laughing!
Both of you, come to my office.
No going home after school.
Call your parents.
Please log in to your Huawei account.
What account?
Thanks.
For what?
Didn't really help you though.
That's not what I meant.
Then what is it?
I can't believe you said
Li Shi Can and I are partners.