( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
'Love in the Making' - Ian Yan
♫ The flowers on the windowsill bloom ♫
♫ Longing rushes in and won’t fade ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand ♫
♫ Walk through crowded streets ♫
♫ Let the wind gently sway your skirt ♫
♫ In my heart ♫
♫ You are irreplaceable ♫
♫ Every time I see you,
my heart grows lighter ♫
♫ Do you know this love
has been hidden so long? ♫
♫ I've always existed for you ♫
♫ Running from the stars to the sea ♫
♫ I no longer want to hide this love ♫
♫ My gaze has already betrayed me ♫
♫ So, let us truly fall in love ♫
[You Are My Fateful Love]
[Episode 2: A Reunion Years in the Making]
This way, Ms. Ruan.
- Please, come in.
- Thank you.
team name
Lawyer Liu. I've got it.
No worries, it's no trouble at all.
I'll get it. Thanks.
Do you two know each other?
No, we don't.
We don't.
Then let me introduce you.
This is our firm's legal counsel, Xu Huai Song.
Hello.
And this is our client in this case,
Ruan Yu.
Ms. Ruan.
A novelist who specializes in romance.
How did you know that, Lawyer Xu?
I looked into your background.
How much do you know exactly?
Are you asking about the case, or about you personally?
Or maybe your novel?
What Lawyer Xu means is,
before a consultation, we always look into the client's basic background.
It's one of our fundamental obligations as lawyers. Right?
We've covered what we needed to. But you haven't read the novel yet, right?
Oh, right. Ms. Ruan, did you bring the novel?
Yes, I did.
Great. Just hand it to Lawyer Xu later.
That'll do.
Come on, have a seat.
Here.
This novel is packed with fantasies
about Xu Huai Song, from his body to his soul.
And now I'm supposed to hand it to Xu Huai Song himself.
And I'll have to discuss these fantasies with him,
on an in-depth, legal level.
Counselors. As the saying goes, "Forgive and forget.
Just a bit more.
This'll pass. Take a step back and breathe."
"Save a life, and you're a hero."
Ms. Ruan, you mean...
I mean
I've suddenly decided not to sue.
- Not to sue?
- Yes.
Are you sure about this?
♫ Boss, phone call ♫
Excuse me for a moment.
I need to take a call. Sorry.
♫ Pick up the phone ♫
Hello?
What delivery? I need to sign for it in person?
Okay, I'm coming.
She suddenly doesn't want to sue.
Was my performance not good enough?
Lawyer Liu is usually pretty busy, huh?
Last time we met, we were just chatting when a call came in.
Last time?
Please.
He hasn't changed much at all.
Time has been really kind to him.
Ms. Ruan, do you have any issues with me?
No, none at all. I wouldn't dare.
I was just feeling sorry for myself.
What's wrong, Lawyer Xu?
My apologies. I have a delivery to sign for downstairs.
So, Ms. Ruan, have you made up your mind?
Lawyer Liu, I've decided.
Alright. I'll respect your decision.
I've dealt with quite a few clients who got cold feet at the last minute.
But after hesitation, they still end up choosing to sue.
No worries. Take your time and think it over.
Lawyer Liu, you mean divorce clients, right?
Are they not on good terms?
Thank you, Lawyer Liu.
I'll give it some thought.
Alright, let me walk you out.
No need. Please, get back to your work.
If you go back and forth now, you'll miss your lunch break.
I'm not busy. Actually, I'd like to treat you to lunch.
- Then let it be my treat. I've troubled you enough.
- Fine.
Western food?
There's a Western restaurant near her place.
Okay.
You... You two already have lunch plans?
Yes.
I totally forgot.
How about next time?
But he's already gone downstairs.
It's fine. I'll go talk to him.
Let's go.
Go back upstairs and wait for me. Once I've dropped Ruan Yu off,
I'll come back for lunch, okay?
There's a bed upstairs.
Are you trying to catch up on sleep
and get over your jet lag now?
Let's go.
Lawyer Liu. I've left the key in the car.
- Then I'll head back upstairs now.
- Sure, thanks.
Let's drive Ms. Ruan home first.
Thanks...
Thank you, Lawyer Liu.
It's okay, Ruan Yu. The back is the same. The back is even more comfortable.
Close the door yourself.
Lawyer Liu, I'm not going home yet.
Could you drop me off at a friend's?
Of course.
It's not a detour. It's closer that way.
Sure, no problem. Just send me the address.
Okay.
Ms. Ruan.
If you don't mind me asking, what kind of friend are you visiting?
That's a bit too direct, don't you think?
Then you ask her.
I'm going to my editor's place.
Got it.
To your editor's, I see.
What's up?
The case didn't work out.
Ming Ying, do you know who I ran into today?
Liu Mao...
Did he confess to you?
It was Xu Huai Song.
Ming Ying,
I ran into the real-world version of
Xu Huai Song.
Something's not right.
It's normal for me to care about my blind date.
That makes sense.
But may I ask, why are you so concerned?
I'm just keeping track
of my client's whereabouts.
Is there a problem?
She's already going on blind dates
to find a boyfriend.
Where else could she go?
She's definitely just
visiting a regular friend.
Now you're acting like
a Monday morning quarterback.
What if she's going on blind dates
just to appease her family?
Do you think you know
my blind date better than I do?
That call at the office this morning. You arranged for someone
to call me, didn't you?
You sent me away on purpose.
You've got a slow reaction time.
How did you even become a lawyer?
Is she an ex-girlfriend?
How should I put it?
It's a bit complicated.
What's more complicated than being exes?
How about a debtor and a creditor? Isn't that complicated?
Does she owe you money?
- No.
- Then what's the relationship? Just make it clear.
Chinese or Western food?
Fine, don't tell me then.
Anything works for me. I'm not hungry. It's up to you.
When are you leaving this time?
Tomorrow.
Didn't you just get back? Why so soon to leave?
My client's trial starts in less than 48 hours. Of course, I'm in a hurry.
Then why come back now of all times?
What could possibly be more important than the trial?
Excuse me.
Hello?
Song. I think I did something wrong.
I think I've caused trouble for Ruan Yu.
Who did you just say?
Ruan Yu. Have you forgotten her?
Take it easy. Walk me through it.
I don't know what to do.
Let me send you a photo first.
Song. Here is a document for you.
[RYXHXHS]
That night,
I found this in the piano room of the school's art gallery.
A ten-hour flight back here, a one-day stay,
and another ten-hour flight back.
I think you've lost your mind.
Who wouldn't lose his mind?
I really am losing it.
I'm seriously about to lose it.
Who was so sure that she wouldn't get caught?
This is so surreal.
Never thought it would actually reach him.
Even a novel wouldn't dare go this far.
What should I do?
My Weibo post saying the novel was based on my personal experience...
I posted it along with a video
clarifying the outline and the creation date.
I can't take it down or edit it.
W-What if he sees it?
Don't worry about that for now.
Isn't he an elite lawyer from the US?
He shouldn't have time to check your Weibo.
Besides, you said he didn't even recognize you.
But what if he sees the content of Chapter 23?
You were the one
who insisted on adding that erotic dream.
No. I... R-Right now,
I'm going to lock that chapter.
I'll lock it up now.
But seriously, are you really dropping the lawsuit over this?
I'm suing. I'm definitely going to sue.
No way there isn't a more reliable law firm
in all of Hang City.
[Whisper in Your Ear]
[Contents]
[Weibo]
[Wen Xiang]
Do you two know each other?
No, we don't.
We don't.
Luckily, he doesn't remember me.
Friends recommended these law firms. I've made appointments for you.
Just head over tomorrow.
When it really counts,
Editor Shen is always the one I can count on.
Regarding copyright disputes, we're experts.
We guarantee you'll win. So what level are you at now?
How much can you earn from one book?
Ms. Ruan. What Lawyer Chen means is,
it's better to settle this case out of court.
What Lawyer Chen means is,
it costs a lot to fight a PR war.
What Lawyer Chen...
Follow me right now.
Then we'll have some public interactions.
Let's build up the hype first.
Tell Lawyer Zhang to get the hell out here!
He's always hyping things up.
Is he a lawyer or a social media clown?
I'm going to sue him!
There's a saying that's so true.
The world is just a giant, makeshift stage.
Lawyer Fan is definitely not one of those performers on a makeshift stage.
If Zhikun Law Firm is the rising star of Hang City's legal scene,
Lawyer Fan and Dingzheng Law Firm
are definitely the gold standard of the old guard.
Aside from being expensive, they have no flaws.
This case, to put it simply, is about proving that your outline was stolen.
Can we compare the text of the two works
to prove that my content and the other author's are actually not similar?
That would show I'm original and not infringing on any rights.
That path doesn't look easy right now.
There are plenty of similarities in the plots.
It might work against you.
Proving the outline was stolen is the most direct and simple way.
I understand what you're saying.
But in fact, these two works just look similar.
As the original creator, I hope to get legal recognition.
Ms. Ruan, I'm sorry. I'm a lawyer, not your PR team.
I can't support your literary ideals.
Got it.
Ms. Ruan. Just a friendly reminder.
I don't think any lawyer will take your advice.
How did it go with Lawyer Fan?
Lawyer Fan heard my request and almost showed me the door.
But doing it my way might indeed be a thankless task.
Hello, Lawyer Liu.
Ruan Yu.
I'm calling to ask if you've made up your mind.
Are you really not going to sue?
Lawyer Liu, how do you see my case being handled?
Proving the outline was stolen is the easiest way.
What's wrong?Did you run into some trouble?
You can talk to me. Even if I'm not your lawyer,
aren't we still friends?
I was wondering if I could prove
the originality of my work in this case.
Well, actually...
It's okay, Lawyer Liu. I understand.
You could.
I could?
Lawyer Liu, if you're doing this
as a favor to a friend, don't force yourself.
- I know it's--
- Of course not.
I'm not forcing myself.
Not at all.
Are you on speakerphone over there, Lawyer Liu?
Yes.
Sorry about that, Ruan Yu. Excuse me for a moment.
I have to sign two documents.
Okay!
What are your instructions?
"Proving your originality isn't essential,
but as supporting evidence,
it could have a positive impact on the outcome of the case.
This request is feasible."
Aren't you worried, though, that the comparison might not go well?
Hold on.
I need to sign two more documents.
Okay!
In China, for cases like this, the simplest way
is to start with the theft of the outline.
That's different from how things work abroad.
In any country, you have to start with the outline theft.
Haven't we been saying...
What if the outline wasn't stolen at all?
What do you mean?
Lawyer Liu, are you still there?
If you're busy,
we can talk later.
Hurry up.
I don't have that many documents to sign.
"Regardless of how the comparison turns out,
I believe a truly original work is worth taking a shot like this."
Really?
Thank you so much, Lawyer Liu.
You're welcome. Goodbye.
You can't handle the case like this.
Aren't you just forcing a sale on her?
So many firms in Hang City. Why make her choose Zhikun Law Firm?
Because for this case, only I know how to win it.
"Only I know how to win it."
Don't tell me it's because of me.
Why go through all this trouble?
You could have just told me directly.
But come to think of it, Ruan Yu
is definitely the best
among all the blind dates I've had over the years.
She's pretty, well-educated, and a writer.
I'm a lawyer.
A writer and a lawyer.
It'd be a lovely story if word got out.
Alright.
Then I'll just wait and see
in which episode you two get together.
You've watched too many dramas.
- Grab dinner together tonight?
- I'll pass.
Where are you going then?
Su City.
Fine, I'll eat with someone else.
A work meeting turns into a date.
Ms. Ruan, see you tonight.
A lawyer and a writer. It'd be a lovely story.
It does have a nice ring to it.
Song, you're back!
When did you get back?
Did you come back because of that thing?
Fine, don't answer me then.
Song, come home for dinner tonight!
I'm eating out.
Come on!
Mom really missed you.
I'll pick you up after school.We'll go to that place you sent me.
Okay, okay! It's a deal.
See you after school. Love you!
What a coincidence.
Who are you calling? You seem so happy.
The man who loves me the most in this world.
[...]
Give it back!
Put his photo down!
Xu Huai Shi!
I've noticed that you're
getting more and more violent.
I only looked at Li Shi Can's photo.
It's not like looking at him
will ruin his career.
Say that again!
I think you just have too much pocket money.
Well, as for me, I've always had good luck with money.
Just as I ran out of pocket money,
someone offered to treat me to dinner.
- Who?
- My Bro Song.
A handsome guy who's second only to Shi Can. Handsome and loaded.
Most importantly, he spends money on me.
Bro Song!
What was I thinking? I have to go back again.
What's Shi up to?
So you're Bro Song. Who said you could call her Shi?
Don't throw your age around and take advantage of her.
Are you her classmate?
We're ride-or-die.
Not just classmates.
Not just classmates? Then what else are you?
None of your business.
You want to know more about her, so you're trying to pump me for info?
No way.
Didn't Shi tell you who I am?
You?
Aren't you just that
handsome and loaded guy
who's willing to spend money on her?
Is that really how Shi talks about me?
It's just money. Who doesn't have that?
Let me tell you,
if you have any more bad intentions toward Xu Huai Shi,
- I won't let you off easy!
- Song.
You're still here?
This is the classmate I mentioned, Zhao Yi.
You've already met, right?
So you're Zhao Yi.
Not only have we met, I also know that you two
are more than just classmates.
Zhao Yi!
What nonsense did you say to Bro Song?
Shouldn't Bro Song's surname be Song?
Then what about Sis Shi?
Xu Huai Song is my own brother. Got a problem with that?
No problem, Bro Xu.
Bro Xu.
I have work to do tonight, so I can't have dinner with you.
Mr. Liu, your friend has arrived. I'll show you the way.
Sure, thanks.
Didn't you go to Su City?
You're back so soon.
Shouldn't Bro Song's surname be Song?
Is our Lawyer Liu serious this time?
This suit is very expensive. I've never seen him wear it since he bought it.
Who is it? Who is it? Do I know this lady?
It's the one suing for defamation, Ms. Ruan.
Lawyer Liu drafted the contract.
He must seal it tonight.
Seal the deal on the contract, or seal the deal with the lady?
If I go with Zhikun Law Firm
would you be my lawyer, Lawyer Liu?
Yes, me.
So we will proceed according to the plan we discussed on the phone, right?
Of course.
We will provide legal advice
at the appropriate time,
but will never go against the client's wishes.
That's great! I trust your professionalism, Lawyer Liu.
Then let's get the contract signed right away.
So soon?
No rush.
It's fine if the contract
is delayed a few days.
As for the online backlash, a few days won't make a big difference.
Right, Lawyer Liu?
How is that not a big difference?
No! This can't be delayed.
Every extra day the backlash grows,
the more risk we take on.
Ruan Yu. Read the contract carefully.
If you have any questions, ask me now. Don't hold back.
I've already signed both copies.
Okay!
I don't have any questions.
Great!
Lawyer Liu, for the lawsuit,
what materials do I need to prepare?
The top priority is to get the key records of defamation against you
from the online platforms to the notary office
for preservation of evidence.
I'll help you with that.
Also, don't disclose your intention
to sue for now, to avoid tipping them off.
- As for the rest--
- Hold on.
I thought you were my lawyer, Lawyer Liu?
Lawyer Xu.
Are you going to be involved too?
Lawyer Liu will appear in court.
I will assist in preparing the case.
But I can't afford to pay the retainer fees
for two lawyers at once.
Don't worry about that. He's doing it for practice.
No need to pay him. And between you and me?
I can give you a 20% discount.
Thank you, Lawyer Liu.
Actually, I've got contacts in the industry with copyright disputes.
Maybe Lawyer Xu could
gain some experience there.
I'm fine with it.
What about Lawyer Liu?
After all,
those aren't Zhikun Law Firm's cases.
So if Lawyer Xu gets involved, it might not look good within the firm.
Right?
Lawyer Xu.
My understanding of you
assisting in preparing the case
is that you'll help Lawyer Liu with the strategy, not take over the whole--
The first step of preparation is to fully understand the case.
So you have to read all the materials, including the entire novel.
Ms. Ruan, is there anything in your novel that is inconvenient to disclose?
No, not at all.
No.
Okay, the contract is signed.
I'll start a work group chat to facilitate our communication going forward.
Okay?
Okay.
In one kilometer, you will enter the airport expressway.
[...]
[Ruan Yu]
[Send]
[Notice: The user's privacy settings
don't allow adding via group chat.]
In our case, the part about organizing the plot will be handled by Lawyer Xu.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask him anytime.
Lawyer Liu, for the plot organization part, can I just work directly with you on it?
For counter-plagiarism comparison, Lawyer Xu is more experienced.
I just feel that Lawyer Xu is abroad, different time zone.
It's too inconvenient. Plus, he's probably pretty busy.
Don't worry about it. He's a night owl.
And no matter how busy he is,
he'll have to do me a favor and squeeze in time for this case.
Once the materials are ready, just share them in the group.
[Clues Related to Su Cheng. pdf]
[@xhs]
Hello?
Buddy.
This type of case is your specialty, right?
You asked me to say in the group that you'd be handling this case.
I did as you asked. But when Ruan Yu spoke up,
you just played dead. What's that about?
If you keep this up,
it makes things very awkward for me.
If you really feel uncomfortable being stuck in the middle,
why don't you move over here?
Fine.
You can tell her to add me on WeChat directly.
I've figured it out.
So you suddenly came back just for Ruan Yu.
Shi got into some trouble.
What a lame excuse. For real?
Instead of gossiping here, why not just have the client
contact me directly.
Hold on.
Why are you making her reach out to you?
Don't tell me you tried to add her, but she didn't accept.
Nonsense.
So I guessed right.
Looks like when it comes to being rejected, Lawyer Liu is more experienced than me.
Are you done? If so, I'm hanging up.
I haven't hung up yet!
I'm more experienced than you at everything.
[Add to Contacts]
[...]
[How to Add Me]
[Via Group Chat]
This is my preliminary record
of the defamation.
I went to the notary office this morning
for the preservation of evidence.
Please take a look, lawyers.
Let me know if anything else is needed.
Why don't you add him on WeChat?
He's in too many work groups. He might miss your messages there.
Adding Xu Huai Song on WeChat?
[636014308]
4308.
[Search]
[xhs]
[QQ: 636014308]
Back then, I pored over his profile for three whole years.
But I never found a reason to add him.
Ten years later, the reason is here.
Is fate playing a joke on me?
What should I say?
"Hello, Lawyer Xu."
"I'm Ruan Yu."
No, that's too formal.
[Sorry to bother you, Lawyer Xu.
Please accept my request.]
No!
That's too stiff.
What should I do?
No, I can't add him.
Discussing my novel with him alone is way too awkward.
What if I let something slip?
[San Francisco]
She's just a layperson, yet she'd rather figure out the
preservation of evidence on her own than ask for your help.
It seems she really doesn't want
to deal with you.
[Ruan Yu]
[I've accepted your friend request.
We can start chatting now.]
Wait, how did I add him?
What...
What did I write in the verification message?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Meant2Be Team @Viki.com
[Debate Final, Su City No.1 High School, 2013]
Please, take a seat.
One more thing.
A student found a phone in the auditorium just now.
Is anyone here to claim it?
No one?
Whose phone is it?
"If I don't study, I'll have to marry the teacher."
Come up to the stage quickly
and claim your phone.
Whose phone is it?
Teacher! Teacher!
I'm so sorry, teacher. It's my phone.
Don't bring your phone to school anymore.
Focus on your studies.
Thank you, teacher. I'm sorry.
'Yesterday' - Vision Wei
♫ Rewinding scenes from the past ♫
♫ A full stop written in haste ♫
♫ Tracing through endless days and nights ♫
♫ An unspoken goodbye ♫
♫ At the edge of a blurred gaze ♫
♫ The wind scatters what remains ♫
♫ Thoughts cloud my vision ♫
♫ Turning into drifting smoke ♫
♫ Silently fading away ♫
♫ Every chapter of the past ♫
♫ Yesterday’s faded pages ♫
♫ As I turn through each one,
I find you behind every story ♫
♫ Relentlessly returning ♫
♫ The smile upon your face ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye,
with no time to hold on ♫
♫ Every chapter of the past ♫
♫ Yesterday’s faded pages ♫
♫ As I turn through each one,
I find you behind every story ♫
♫ Relentlessly returning ♫
♫ The smile upon your face ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye,
with no time to hold on ♫
♫ Fading into yesterday ♫