( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[EP7: The Mysterious Chapter 23]
What was that?
An ambulance.
Why is there an ambulance?
I'm at the hospital.
Lawyer Xu, what happened?
My stomach's just acting up.
Nothing serious.
Well, get some rest.
Hope you feel better soon.
[Emergency Center]
What are you two doing here?
You're looking a lot better now.
Does it still hurt?
Not anymore.
It doesn't? Then have something to drink.
Okay.
I'm not that hungry.
You need to eat something,
even if you're not hungry.
Ambulance siren samples?
Lawyer Xu, what are you listening to that for?
No reason. Just changing up
my musical taste recently.
That's a new one.
First time I've ever heard of someone
"changing their music taste"
to ambulance sirens.
All right.
Life getting a little too dull for you?
Looking for some excitement?
Mr. Xu, a Miss Ruan is here to see you.
Let her in. Thanks.
How did Ruan Yu find out?
Xu Huai Song. You old fox.
I thought you were listening to sirens
to get your thrills.
Turns out you're trying to find a girlfriend.
Take these.
Go ahead and eat.
I'm taking them, then.
Okay.
How was I supposed
to know you didn't eat lunch?
You never told me.
What do you mean, I never told you?
I sent you a message on WeChat.
You must have sent it to the wrong person.
I never got it.
[Bring me some porridge for lunch.
New District Hospital, Room 106.]
Bring me some porridge for lunch.
New District Hospital, Room 106.
So the message wasn't for me.
Should I go in now or not?
I want that porridge right now.
Fine! I'll go buy it for you now.
Miss Ruan?
Lawyer Liu,
you're buying porridge?
How'd you know?
Come in, come in.
Miss Ruan,
what are you doing here?
Lawyer Xu,
your porridge.
I sent that to Liu Mao.
How did it end up with you?
- Sorry to have bothered you.
- It's no problem.
Lawyer Xu, I didn't know you were sick.
If I had,
I really wouldn't have kept you up
so late talking about the case yesterday.
Don't worry about it.
When you were talking about the case,
he wasn't checked in yet.
On the way to the hospital,
he was staring at his phone's signal,
so scared the call would drop,
but he didn't dare turn on his mic,
afraid he'd wake you up.
Love really does make a fool of us all.
Lawyer Xu,
are you feeling any better today?
No.
Lawyer Xu, you really need to start
taking better care of your stomach.
You know,
the stomach is an emotional organ.
When you're in a good mood,
your stomach feels good.
Miss Ruan,
you're a writer,
so you must have a way with words.
When you have a moment,
you should chat more with Lawyer Xu.
It'll put him in a good mood,
which will be a great help
in his recovery.
It's just the same old problem.
Don't put her on the spot.
How is this putting her on the spot?
It's not a problem at all.
I'm here anyway,
and I don't have anything else to do today.
See what she said?
So considerate.
Thank you.
What kind of way is that to eat?
It's a Su City specialty.
It's how we locals eat.
How would you know that?
I'm also from Su City.
I did my research.
It's in your WeChat profile.
Miss Ruan,
you're here to see Lawyer Xu too?
Lawyer Xu, didn't you just say you weren't--
He's hungry now.
We're done talking.
We should get going.
There's still work at the firm.
Bye.
By the way, Lawyer Xu, that email
you sent me at three in the morning...
I just saw it.
I'll send you the file right away.
Three in the morning?
Didn't Xu Huai Song say he fell asleep too,
so he didn't hang up the call?
Are you saying I was sleepwalking
at three in the morning?
He means...
you must have been dreaming.
I sent it to you, right?
- I sent it to him.
- Really?
I sent it to him.
Let's go.
- We're leaving.
- Are you serious?
Sit.
No, wait, Bro Mao, it was definitely Lawyer Xu
who sent that email.
You've been with me for so many years.
How can you be so clueless?
Think about it again.
Come to think of it,
Lawyer Xu acts strangely
whenever Miss Ruan is around.
Like the day he got back,
he made me put on a whole act,
saying Ms. Zhang was in trouble.
Later, when I called
to ask when to pick him up,
he randomly told me he hadn't eaten.
That sly old fox.
Lawyer Xu, are you finished eating?
Yes, all done.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- It was nothing.
Well, get some rest.
I'll be heading back now.
That counter-plagiarism file, I organized it
and brought it over for you.
You can take a look
when you have a free moment.
Okay. Could you please hand it to me?
Yes.
- Here.
- Okay, thanks.
Ruan Yu's fried rice cakes
even come with after-sales service.
She seems pretty into you.
Why not test the waters?
You might have a shot.
Lawyer Xu, I'll be going now.
Okay.
You rest up.
Wait.
Your manuscript...
it seems to be missing a chapter.
Chapter 23.
Xu Huai Song.
Ruan Yu.
Do you want me...
Do you want me
to read it?
No!
Why not?
Chapter 23 is a transitional chapter.
It should be pretty important, right?
It's...
It's not that important.
Whether it's important or not
is for me to decide after I've read it.
Now?
Now.
Please, have a seat.
Lawyer Xu,
I don't have the original manuscript with me.
It should be on the website's back end, right?
He's a lawyer.
How does he know his way around
the back end of a women's fiction site?
Lawyer Xu,
the signal in this room isn't very good.
I'll send it to you after I get back.
The hospital has Wi-Fi.
The password is four sixes, four eights.
I've already sent it to you.
Well, I'll be going now.
Lawyer Xu, what's wrong?
Is your stomach bothering you again?
I'll go get a doctor.
It's okay, it's okay.
I've been straining my eyes too much lately.
My eyes hurt.
I thought he was here for a stomach ache.
Since my eyes are bothering me,
you can read it to me. Thank you.
What did you say?
I still roughly remember the plot
involving the Poet.
You just need to read it to me once.
Once we confirm there are no issues,
we can close the book on this.
You'll have no issues,
but I'll have a huge one.
Lawyer Xu, that's not necessary.
I've already confirmed there are
no problems with that chapter.
The most dangerous place
is the safest place.
And the reverse is also true.
The more certain you are there's no problem,
the more likely it is that there is one.
It's fine, it's fine.
It's just a dream the main character has.
What's it got to do with me?
It's just reading a dream sequence
that goes a little something like this...
Life is short.
It'll be over before you know it.
Chapter 23.
He Shi Qian.
- He...
- Forget it.
I'll just read it myself later.
Okay.
I'm leaving, Lawyer Xu.
Goodbye.
Song,
what room are you in?
Mom and I will come see you in a bit.
We're here, Mom.
Stop eating so much candy.
You're too old for that.
And you have to use floss.
You made me come with you to the dentist.
Where are we?
Mom, since you're already here,
just go in and see my brother.
He's sick.
This is when he needs family support the most.
I told you a long time ago,
I don't have a son.
He is not my family.
Look at you.
Don't be angry. Don't say that.
If you want to go, go by yourself.
Liar.
Mom.
Song.
Let me see you.
What happened?
Let me see.
Why are you so pale?
You look like you're on death's door.
If you're going to be so dramatic,
you can just not talk.
Why are you alone?
Mom is actually really worried about you,
but she's been so busy with work
these past two days
she didn't have time to come.
So she sent me as her special envoy
to check on you.
Lawyer Xu,
I forgot something.
Come in.
Who's this pretty girl?
Not worried about your brother's life,
but you're interested in the pretty girls?
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
I'll be going now.
Sis.
Hello.
I'm the sister of this very difficult,
handsome man.
My name is Xu Huai Shi.
Hello. I'm Lawyer Xu's...
client.
Client?
Let me guess.
You wouldn't happen to be
Ruan Yu, would you?
How did you know?
I heard my brother mention you.
He said he's currently handling a case
for a writer named Ruan Yu.
And you just have this aura of a well-read,
articulate, cultured person.
I just guessed and got it right.
I can't believe Lawyer Xu has
a sister as charming as you.
Song, you should reflect on
why she said "I can't believe."
I didn't mean it like that.
Well.
It's okay, Ruan Yu.
My brother's social skills well, you get it.
If Lawyer Xu were half as charming as you,
he could probably double his caseload.
A lawyer's caseload depends
on their ability to handle cases,
not on being a smooth talker.
Whether he's charming or not,
or if he could take on more cases,
I really don't know.
But at least he wouldn't still be single.
Doesn't he have a girlfriend?
I'm telling you,
even if pigs learned to fly,
he probably still wouldn't find a girlfriend.
He's been single for 28 years.
Xu Huai Shi, let me remind you,
spreading someone's private information
may constitute an infringement of a citizen's
personal information and a crime of defamation.
How is this "spreading"?
If I told a lot of people,
that would be spreading.
I only told Ruan Yu.
And she won't tell anyone else, right?
Of course not.
I will definitely keep
Lawyer Xu's secret.
Yes.
Shouldn't you hurry up
and wash some fruit for her
as hush money?
Okay.
No need,
I'm just grabbing my things and leaving.
- You're leaving already?
- It's no trouble, no trouble at all.
I was going to eat some anyway.
How about this, I'll go wash it.
I need to wash this container anyway.
You're too kind.
- It's nothing.
- I'll go with you.
No.
Close the door.
What?
When we go back out there,
don't say anything stupid.
Song, I'm totally trying
to be your wingman here.
Think about it. In just a few sentences,
I established your "single guy" persona.
What if Ruan Yu mistakenly
thought you had a girlfriend?
Even if she was interested,
she wouldn't dare make a move.
Kids should stay out of adults' business.
If I don't get involved, how long
are you going to drag this out?
Mr. Great Lawyer,
why are you and Ruan Yu still stuck in
a client-lawyer relationship?
Have you ever thought about that?
Of course, I know.
It's because...
she doesn't know I recognized her.
Wrong.
It's because you and Ruan Yu
haven't seen each other in so many years.
You're not sure if she still likes you.
Or rather,
if she could like the real you.
You're not confident,
so you don't dare make a reckless move,
worried you'll scare her away.
Let me put it this way:
You may understand how to win a lawsuit,
but that doesn't mean you understand love.
You may understand love,
but that doesn't mean you understand women.
You may understand women,
but that doesn't mean you understand
that sin^2(x) + cos^2(x) = 1.
Now you're just being ridiculous.
You're a high school student
who hasn't even graduated,
and you're here teaching me,
a man almost 30, how to date.
You think that makes sense?
You can underestimate your opponent,
but you should never underestimate
a member of Gen Z.
I'm done talking to you.
I'm going to go bond with Ruan Yu.
Don't say anything stupid.
Ruan Yu, I'll help you.
No need, I've got it.
Don't be polite.
I'll prep this, then.
Ruan Yu,
my brother specifically told me
to come out here, work more, and talk less,
so I wouldn't bother you with my chattering.
He's pretty thoughtful, isn't he?
Your brother is more than thoughtful.
Actually,
I quite enjoy talking with you.
So, do you prefer talking to me,
or to my brother?
It's different.
Talking to you is fun.
Talking to your brother is reassuring.
When he talks to me about the case,
he's very professional.
And besides professional?
Do you have any other opinions of him?
An opinion?
Well, when you writers are working,
you like to create a persona
for a character, right?
Like, what kind of person is he?
If he were in a novel,
he would probably be
the aloof, untouchable "cool city guy" type.
Good news.
My brother's "cool guy" persona is intact.
Ruan Yu,
you're so pretty, a lot of guys must like you.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Not yet.
So what type of guy
do you like?
I like guys who are as charming as you.
Oh no.
The persona is too strong.
But even without the persona,
my brother's mouth
is more venomous than charming.
Does that mean he's out of the running?
Huai Shi, what part of the city
did you come from today?
Su City.
You go to high school in Su City?
Yes, my brother and I both went
to Su City No. 1 High School.
That case you hired my brother for,
how's it progressing?
We're almost there.
The court date is soon.
Did you run into any difficulties?
We're missing a piece of evidence
we had planned on.
But it won't affect anything.
It was probably the evidence
I was supposed to provide
about the sale of the outline.
That whole thing was fake to begin with,
and I couldn't fabricate
any transaction records.
Besides, perjury is illegal.
Ruan Yu,
don't worry.
If you have any trouble, just ask my brother.
He's really good.
I'm back.
Song, have an apple.
I don't want one.
Just give one to Ruan Yu.
Here, you have it.
Thank you.
Can I get your WeChat?
Xu Huai Shi.
Sure.
Let me scan you.
Let's keep in touch.
Okay.
Lawyer Xu, I won't disturb you any longer.
You get some rest.
Thanks for the hush money.
And thank you for the porridge.
Okay, I'm leaving.
- Bye.
Take care.
Xu Huai Shi.
What did you say when you were out there?
You don't like apples, do you?
Not big ones,
not small ones.
Not red ones or green ones.
You don't like any of them.
Because what you like isn't apples at all.
Speak English.
You wouldn't understand.
Song,
you still have a lot to learn.
It's okay, let's not rush.
Let's take it slow.
Well, I'm heading out. Bye.
What red apple, green apple?
Bye...
What's wrong with red apples?
[Doesn't have a girlfriend]
[There's nothing you can't get over,
just that you can never go back.]
Wrong.
It's because you and Ruan Yu
haven't seen each other in so many years.
You're not sure if she still likes you.
Or rather,
if she could like the real you.
You're not confident,
so you don't dare make a reckless move,
worried you'll scare her away.
Song?
- It's me.
- You're out of the hospital?
I am.
I have a question for you.
Earlier today at the hospital,
you were talking about red apples,
green apples, and all that.
What did you mean?
Your reaction time is impressively slow.
But, better late than never.
Spare me the idioms.
Just get to the point.
I asked Ruan Yu today
what type of guy she likes.
And what did she say?
She said...
I'm a little tired.
She said she likes charming guys.
She said she likes charming guys?
But here's a friendly little tip.
I don't think
you can overdo the cool guy act.
What Ruan Yu might like is...
Is...
Is what?
I'm thirsty.
Okay.
Please.
Someone who's aloof but charming.
Aloof but charming.
Can a person be aloof
and charming at the same time?
That's a pretty tough standard to meet.
But...
I have an excellent role model
you can learn from.
What role model?
Welcome to Xu's Love Class.
Satisfaction guaranteed, affordable price.
One-on-one tutoring for only 666 yuan.
[Tap to receive]
Sent. What role model? Tell me.
Do you remember I asked you
for some allowance money a while back
to go to a concert?
I remember. And?
My Can's stage presence is just so versatile.
When he's playing a ballad,
he's both elegant and aloof.
- A ballad.
- Right, a ballad.
- Elegant. Aloof.
- Elegant, aloof.
Like this.
Like this?
You're so bad at this.
What's it supposed to look like?
- Like this.
- This?
- This aloof?
- Right.
When he's rapping,
when he's dancing,
he's both fierce and cool.
Fierce and cool.
Fierce, cool.
- Fierce, cool.
No.
No?
- Fierce.
- Cool.
This?
Right.
- This?
- Just like that.
Just like that.
Song, you're a natural!
- You think so?
- And also, when he meets his fans,
he's incredibly friendly,
and his words are so sweet.
Handsome, you're so handsome.
What should I say to sound handsome?
Sweet talk.
Sweet talk?
Sweet talk, sweet talk...
Your hair looks great today.
You're so handsome.
Just like that.
And then,
I think you can search for his videos online
and really study his style.
So, who is this person
you've been talking about?
Oh, I forgot to introduce you.
His name is Li Shi Can.
Li Shi Can.
So you're saying
you gave all the allowance
I gave you straight to this guy?
And now you want me to imitate him
to win over Ruan Yu?
Exactly.
And while you're imitating him, you have
to remember the six principles of heart.
You need to use your attentiveness,
patience, and loyalty
to show her your sincerity and dedication,
and thus, reveal your true heart.
I think you're the one who's heartless.
Check your phone.
Why did you take back the tuition fee?
I didn't just take back the tuition fee.
Your allowance for next month,
and the month after that,
I've taken it all back.
You can't...
So unreasonable.
Everyone, stop gossiping.
The author wrote this story,
which means she and the real-life hero
are no longer connected.
Otherwise, why would she
name the hero He Shi Qian?
Doesn't that just mean celebrating that
time has passed and things have changed?
There's nothing you can't get over,
just that you can never go back.
Hello?
Want to go for a drink?
You're drinking this much?
Do you have a death wish?
Weren't you just in the hospital yesterday
for your stomach?
There's nothing you can't get over,
just that you can never go back.
Hello?
Did the alcohol make you go mute?
Ever since I sat down,
you've just been chugging in silence.
Look at the time.
Have you considered that a health nut like me
with a normal sleep schedule
might be getting tired?
If you don't start talking, I'm leaving.
Stop drinking.
If you don't talk, I'm really leaving.
What is there to talk about?
About your blind date?
My dear friend,
is that what this is about?
I've told you so many times,
my blind date with Ruan Yu
was over before it began.
It didn't even last five minutes.
She's my client now.
You two are all sweet and lovey-dovey,
making fried rice cakes and video-calling
across the ocean.
How come you've never said a word to me?
What's the use of talking about it?
Well, if you don't say anything,
how can I help you analyze
if there's any potential here?
What's the barrier between you two?
Just say it.
You're killing me here.
If I told you,
it would blow your mind.
Go on, I'm listening.
What kind of
earth-shattering story
could possibly blow the mind
of a thirty-year-old man?
So you're saying you fell for her
before you even saw
what she looked like?
Well...
Then why didn't you just confess back then?
You know what my family situation
was like back then.
Get out of my house!
You're a family of blood-sucking
vampires!
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about you!
Accomplice to a murderer!
So what are you thinking now?
I don't know.
Honestly, I'm not afraid
that she wasn't interested.
I'm afraid she was.
I get it.
A one-sided crush isn't the scary part.
What's scary is
when many years later, someone tells you
that you two could have actually been together.
You know what? The male lead
in her novel
is named He Shi Qian.
"He" means
to celebrate.
"Shi Qian,"
time has passed and things have changed.
So it means
celebrating that time has passed
and things have changed.
Man, this is real life
not a movie.
It's not as simple as
a black screen with white text that says,
Ten years later,
and just brushes
everything away.
And I don't believe that Ruan Yu has
absolutely no feelings for you now.
But have you ever heard the term
"pseudo-liking"?
What's pseudo-liking?
Let me tell you a story.
I had this buddy in college.
Not long after school started,
he and this girl had a mutual crush.
But neither of them ever said anything.
It wasn't until they were about to graduate
that he heard from someone else
that the girl liked him too.
- And then?
- Later, my friend
went all out pursuing this girl,
and they got together.
But after they got together,
he realized something was wrong.
Because neither of them
knew anything about the other.
When they first developed that mutual crush,
they were both just completely lost
in their own fantasy
of who the other person was.
That's pseudo-liking.
Later, my friend
told me
that when he was chasing the girl so intensely,
he was completely caught up
in a vortex of regret
and obsession.
He was swept up in the moment.
He was thinking, if I don't go after her now,
it'll be too much of a shame to miss out again.
After he calmed down and they broke up,
he regretted his irrationality back then.
Because originally, they both had this
perfect image of each other in their minds.
And in one moment of irrationality,
he shattered
all of that beauty.
So, my friend, I want to remind you,
sometimes,
having regrets isn't necessarily a bad thing.
Even if you seize the opportunity,
you might end up regretting it.
Right?
Think things through carefully
before you act.
Act.
Out of everything I said, you heard one word:
"Act."
- Hello?
- Where are you?
In the car.
Back to your apartment?
To her place.
To Ruan Yu's place?
What are you doing?
I just told you to calm down,
don't be impulsive.
What are you doing? Are you going to confess?
He hung up on me.
So you're saying you fell for her
before you even saw
what she looked like?
Sir, is the third issue
of Galactic Empire in yet?
You're too late, kid.
There was only one copy.
It was just checked out.
That handsome guy over there got it.
Judging by his uniform,
he seems to go to your school, too.
Maybe you can talk to him?
But it looks like he's sleeping.
Never mind.
I'll just read it after he's done.
That's fine.
A weekend afternoon with such nice weather...
Falling asleep while reading
your favorite manga...
It's so peaceful.
Life...
should be lived over and over
in these beautiful moments.
Yes.
I'm facing
pressure from all sides.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
I can't figure it out.
We had a perfectly good life as a family,
and you refused to live it.
Why did you have to take this case?
It's my job.
I'm a lawyer!
Are you the only lawyer in all of Su City?
A case no one else would take, but you had to.
- Can you please try to understand me?
- How have I not understood?
For all these years,
when have I not understood you?
Have you ever thought about our child?
Have you ever thought about us?
You're being completely unreasonable!
What if all these beautiful moments
are drowned out by pain?
I will keep searching.
Even if these endless stars
make my search seem hopeless.
Even if I must go it alone.
This quote from Galactic Empire is for you,
my fellow manga-reading stranger.
Life...
has its bright, free, and happy moments,
but also times when you're stuck in the mud,
lost and helpless.
If you get swallowed up,
just keep searching for
and creating beautiful moments.
[Galactic Empire, Issue 3
Checked out by: Ruan Yu]
You can do it.
Xu Huai Song.
Don't move. It's sharp.
It's okay. I'll clean it up in a bit.
Lawyer Xu, leave it. I'll get it.
A rag, tape.
Okay.
Lawyer Xu,
this kind of material
shouldn't leave tiny shards, right?
You never know.
That should be about it.
Lawyer Xu, let's wash up and eat.
Okay.
Lawyer Xu, give it to me.
No, there are shards on it.
Over there.