( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
OST
♫ ♫
You Are My Fateful Love
[EP3: Camouflage of Prince Charming]
Wait, how did I add him?
What...
What did I write in the verification message?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Meant2Be Team @Viki.com
Hello, Lawyer Xu.
I'm Ruan Yu.
Okay.
Lawyer Xu, if it's convenient,
I'd like to ask you a question.
Well,
what verification message did I send?
[Prprpr...]
[I accept your request. Now we can talk.]
Sorry, Lawyer Xu.
I sent it by mistake.
Lawyer Xu, are you in the US right now?
Yes.
Excuse me. I didn't know.
Sorry for disturbing your rest.
We can talk when it's convenient for you.
I drank that coffee for nothing?
[At 5:00 p.m. (UTC-7)]
At 5:00 p.m. (UTC-7).
5:00 p.m. (UTC-7)?
[5:00 p.m. (UTC-7)=? (UTC+8)]
[5:00 p.m. (UTC-7)=8:00 a.m. (UTC+8)]
8:00 a.m. (UTC+8)?
I need to discuss the case with him as soon as I wake up?
It's fine.
Anyway, we're over 10,000 km apart.
We don't have to talk face-to-face.
It's still early.
It's this late already?
As a lawyer in California,
Xu Huai Song wouldn't be so free as to
wait for me till now,
would he?
Lawyer Xu, I'm so sorry. I woke up late.
Are you free now?
Yes.
Shall we start right away?
Let's talk face to face.
Isn't he in San Francisco?
Video call.
Video call?
If I may ask, does this case require a video call?
Yes.
Yes?
I'm sorry. It's not a proper time.
How long?
One mustn't lose face
when with an ex-boyfriend.
"Ex-crush" and "ex-boyfriend"
are only one word apart.
I can't look so sloppy!
Ten minutes.
♫ ♫
This is too informal.
No.
♫ ♫
It's okay.
Lawyer Xu, I'm ready.
Hello, Lawyer Xu.
Ms. Ruan, I'm skimming through your long manuscript.
If it's too long, you don't have to read it.
It's good and readable.
Thank you.
Xu Huai Song's home
looks sterile and lifeless.
Lawyer Xu, are you drinking...
black coffee?
It's the first time I've seen someone gulp black coffee.
Yes.
My habit.
Any ideas for
a counter-plagiarism comparison chart‌?
Ruan Yu, Ruan Yu, what are you doing?
Lawyer Xu, excuse me. I'll go get the documents.
Well. Lawyer Xu...
I'll go get the documents.
Lawyer Xu.
Well, a friend in the sector
has made a counter-plagiarism comparison chart‌ for me.
I think some examples therein can serve as our angle for counterattack.
Go on.
First, the plot.
For example, in Chapter 10, I wrote a scene
involving the hero
and some supporting characters,
where they ate fried chicken.
I'm in.
Put a ladder at the postern after school.
after school.
- Ladder? What for?
- You know it!
You know it!
Climbing over the wall to buy fried chicken.
Would someone as nonchalant and graceful as Xu Huai Song
and graceful as Xu Huai Song
join them and break school rules for fried chicken?
for fried chicken?
Have you finished your homework? I'm not interested.
I'm not interested.
- Study?
- Forget the homework!
You're not going? If so, I'll give the phone to Mr. Ruan.
If so, I'll give the phone to Mr. Ruan.
Oh no! If it's given to my short-tempered dad, Xu Huai Song is finished.
Xu Huai Song is finished.
No, I must find a solution.
Are you going or not?
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll return it as soon as he finishes.
No rush. Mr. Ruan can take his time.
- Just return it when convenient.
- I can handle it.
Thank you, ma'am.
Xu Huai Song,
now they won't make things difficult for you.
Though it's true,
after so many years,
he can't remember a thing, can he?
What about this plot?
Poet also wrote such a plot.
But specifically
we have different narrative intentions.
Mine is based on the heroine.
I wrote this plot to
show her mood in unrequited love.
By contrast, Poet's plot is based on the hero,
followed by his inner monologue
that he loves fried chicken,
but considering the heroine is around,
and wall climbing looks awkward,
he is otherworldly on purpose.
I think Poet's plot
is to show his duplicity.
Are you okay, Lawyer Xu?
So,
after the ladder was returned,
did you get punished?
He's asking about me,
rather than the heroine.
Has he browsed my Weibo
and realized it's my personal experience?
Lawyer Xu,
have you browsed my Weibo?
No.
Anything I should pay attention to
on your Weibo?
If so, I can browse it now.
No, no.
Nothing worth your attention.
- Let's continue.
- Yes.
Where were we?
When I returned the ladder...
No.
You've got me all confused.
Lawyer Xu, let me clarify.
It's not about me,
but the heroine in my novel.
Besides, your question
seems irrelevant to our case.
Ms. Ruan,
for a mutually satisfactory result,
as your attorney, I hope you can trust me 100%,
instead of questioning my expertise.
Well.
So,
what does the heroine's punishment
to do with this case?
Poet wrote that
the following day,
the hero saw the heroine
standing there, punished.
If your heroine
was also punished...
Luckily, pitying the heroine,
I didn't include that part.
Lawyer Xu, you have a keen eye.
Sorry for misunderstanding you.
Let's move on to the second point.
Okay.
Second, characterization.
Despite so many similar tropes
in the two novels,
the heroes have quite different characters.
In my novel, the hero is...
quiet and elegant,
mature and steady.
Though he seems aloof,
he's gentle on the inside.
He's also a cultured,
top student.
Song.
I read Ruan Yu's novel all over again.
In her novel,
how come you're so unattainable?
Song.
Did you put on an act whenever she was around?
She seems
to prefer
such characters.
Song, be careful.
Don't lose your persona.
You have so little homework?
But Poet's hero,
I feel...
If my hero
is like
Hua Ze Lei
in "Meteor Garden",
then Poet's hero
is like...
Dao Ming Si in "Meteor Garden".
Don't touch!
This is for Ruan Yu.
Ruan Yu!
- For Ruan Yu again?
- This is for her too?
Chasing her every day.
You bet.
Excuse me!
Lady,
your favorite grilled corn from the canteen.
Take it.
No need.
You again?
Dao Ming Si of Class 10?
You think you're a domineering boss?
Childish.
- Childish.
What are you looking at?
Don't you know Ruan Yu is my aim?
I'm showing you mercy
by not reporting you to Mr. Ruan.
If you keep pestering me
and disturbing my studies,
see you in the Dean's office.
Ruan Yu! Ruan Yu!
Ruan Yu!
Also,
so what if you're like Dao Ming Si?
I like Hua Ze Lei instead!
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
I might be overcomplicating it.
To put it simply,
I think Poet's hero
is too playful and childish.
Aren't boys at that age
all pretty much like that?
Not at all!
How could they be the same?
Poet's hero and mine are way too different!
Look, he goes through so much trouble
for fried chicken and coke.
Isn't that playful?
And to gain the heroine's favor,
he puts on an act every day.
Isn't that childish?
It's completely different from mine.
Other plots can also prove this.
Wait, I'll show you.
No need.
Let's call it a day.
We'll continue some other day.
He ended just like that?
He seems a bit angry?
I didn't mean him.
[How to look nonchalant?]
What are you dreaming about, buddy?
If you ask such a question,
you're definitely not nonchalant this life.
To look nonchalant,
you need grace and confidence.
How can I become nonchalant?
Something's wrong.
Something's very wrong.
Lawyer Xu, are you asleep?
It's nothing urgent.
I just wonder
if I said something wrong
at today's meeting,
and why you suddenly
ended the video call.
You didn't.
Other work came up at that time.
But I do feel that,
given your strong emotions
to criticize that hero harshly,
in a biased, irrational state,
it's not a proper time to discuss.
So that was why.
He's way too strict.
Lawyer Xu, you misunderstood me!
It was because
I was eager to persuade you
that they're different.
I admit it.
She doesn't like me at all.
How can I have a showdown now?
Elite lawyers are really something.
They must remain objective
and rational at all times.
Did he schedule another meeting with you?
No.
I hope he's tied up with some big case
and has no time for video conferences.
Or I'll feel proctored like a student.
It's not impossible.
I checked his profile.
The SG infringement case he handled in the US
was a sensation in foreign media back then.
They said the young, outstanding Lawyer Xu
single-handedly brought SG back to life.
Word has it that the fees SG pays him
as a legal counselor
can cover a well-off life.
He's that impressive?
Then my long unrequited love wasn't in vain.
It proves my good taste.
Good taste isn't enough.
He's so smart.
Are you sure you didn't slip up?
Missy, thank you. We'll try it ourselves.
Okay.
Not yet.
Listen, in order not to slip up,
I'm in a constant,
exhausting battle of wits with him.
A video call is like an 800-meter race.
But after so many years,
he hasn't changed much.
I notice a lingering affection in your tone.
No, there isn't.
There isn't?
Every time you mention Xu Huai Song,
your emotional fluctuations
are like those at 18.
Everyone has emotional fluctuations
in such an unusual case.
Besides,
unlike at 18,
hormone isn't enough
for love at 28.
It requires physical attraction,
personal charisma,
shared values,
and resonance,
all of which are essential.
My current emotional fluctuations
are far from rekindling old flames.
At most, it's just
reminiscing about my youth,
and missing the person
I used to be back then.
A writer's tone.
All of which are essential,
reminiscing and missing.
You've made a very clean break.
But you loved him so much.
Don't you feel a sense of closeness
when meeting again?
Worrying about slipping up every day,
I daren't feel that!
Besides,
it's been ten years.
Now I only regard him
as a good, responsible lawyer.
I'd rather he weren't so responsible
and handed my case over to Lawyer Liu instead.
What about Lawyer Liu then?
After all these days,
do you have any
spark of love?
I'm not in that mood.
Even if I want,
he is not my type.
You never know unless you try.
I disliked Zhang Chuan at first.
But now?
So sweet!
It does smell good.
Hey, one bottle of this, please.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
What's wrong?
I feel like we're being watched.
It's creepy.
In broad daylight,
you switch from a romance to a horror?
Pick one.
- Which one?
- I'm done.
- This one.
- Senior Ruan?
It really is you!
You are...
I'm Cen Si Si, Senior.
Don't you remember me?
Oh my god, Senior.
It's been so long since I last saw you.
I peeked over,
worried I'd get you wrong.
So you stayed in Hang City after graduation?
Yes.
This is Cen Si Si, our junior,
a Chinese major like me.
This is my best friend, Shen Ming Ying.
- Hello.
- Hello, Senior Shen.
I remember now.
You, Ruan Yu and Shi Can
were in the Arts Department, right?
Shi Can and I are childhood friends.
When I went to him,
I saw you many times.
You three were always there.
Those were the days.
By the way,
he has a show here these days.
Haven't you planned to meet up?
We aren't in touch much now.
We didn't know his schedule.
Indeed, since he returned to China last year,
he's been quite busy.
Even his family seldom see him.
Yet however busy he gets,
he shouldn't forget old friends, right?
Tell you what,
I check his schedule
and arrange for our reunion,
okay?
Senior,
what do you do now?
I'm a freelancer, I guess.
You aren't a writer, are you?
Not really.
Just a scribbler.
And you? What have you done since graduation?
Me?
I work for my family's company.
But our college is a cradle of talent,
nurturing superstars like Shi Can
and famous writers like you.
Actually, I know a few web novelists.
It seems a tough profession.
They all have it pretty hard.
I'm doing okay.
I'm pretty laid-back,
happy with what I write.
Indeed, cyberspace is harsh now.
It's good you don't let it get to you.
[Xu Huai Song]
Sorry, I have to take this call.
Don't worry. Go ahead.
Lawyer Xu.
Notice from the court,
your case has progressed to adding defendants.
That fast?
Lawyer Xu, it must be late where you are.
Are you still at work?
Insomnia, as usual.
I'm calling to ask you something.
I don't know if it's a coincidence,
but you might know the defendant.
I know?
Yes.
She was in the same department as you,
two years below you.
From Heng University?
That's right.
Her name is Cen Si Si.
Does that ring a bell?
I'm having dessert with her right now.
From the online slander
to today's encounter,
none were coincidences.
It's a common tactic
to plagiarize the ideas of unknown writers
and pay in exchange for their silence.
The fake statement...
Wen Xiang is fooling us.
Is her unproductive year
due to writer's block
or a lack of plagiarism source?
Were the previous works written by herself?
Senior, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Feeling unwell?
You look pale.
Senior?
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
Junior,
is your Qianhe ID Su Cheng?
You...
Senior, are you psychic?
I'm not psychic.
I'm Wen Xiang.
A showdown?
How about I have a judge here
to hold a trial for you two?
Senior,
are you joking?
[Wen Xiang]
It's a small world.
Well, on Weibo, I...
Oh my god.
Oh my god, oh my god.
I need to calm down.
Senior, no, look.
It's a huge misunderstanding.
Had I known you were Wen Xiang,
I wouldn't have posted that.
- Really?
- Yes.
Why?
Because you definitely wouldn't plagiarize!
Senior,
did you sue me?
Look,
this misunderstanding is huge.
Had I known you were Su Cheng,
I...
would have sued you sooner.
It was my fault anyway, Senior.
I didn't want to make a big deal of it.
If you think it's a misunderstanding,
we can settle.
Really, Senior?
That'd be great!
If my dad knew, he'd scold me to death.
If Shi Can knew,
he'd feel so awkward.
Senior,
if you could forgive me,
I'll definitely apologize publicly,
try to eliminate all the negative impact,
never do such stupid things again,
and do anything for you.
So you do know you've been a terrible person.
It's not a big deal.
But I don't know much about settlement.
Settlement certainly requires a lawyer.
But we don't know the procedure.
If anything goes wrong, it'll cause trouble.
Indeed, we can't decide a lawsuit on our own.
Are you free tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I...
I might be in meetings all day tomorrow,
and I cannot leave.
Senior, how about the day after tomorrow?
That works.
And...
the court?
I'll inform them of the delay.
No worries.
Add on WeChat to keep in touch.
Okay.
[Conversation with Su Cheng]
A transcript of my conversation with Su Cheng
for your review.
Judging from it,
Cen Si Si may really not know you're Wen Xiang.
Not necessarily.
It's a bit complicated.
Let's talk in person tomorrow.
What time works for you two?
Is 1:00 p.m. tomorrow okay?
That works for me.
Lawyer Xu?
Let's push it back four hours.
It'd be midnight for you then.
Any time is fine with me.
Let's go with Lawyer Xu's schedule.
Okay, Ruan Yu.
See you at the firm at 5:00 p.m. tomorrow.
Thank you.
Okay, this way.
Lawyer Xu.
Thank you so much.
Without you,
a foreign lawsuit
might be unfair to us.
Law is here
to justly protect
and save the innocent.
That's what we lawyers should do.
That may be so.
But we're penniless employees.
Only you took our case pro bono,
and did so much preparatory work.
In a word, thanks!
Thank you.
When you're abroad,
you can trust your fellow countrymen.
Alright.
I won't keep you from your work.
I'll head out now.
- Hello?
- Hey, Song!
I'm so mad!
Su Cheng instigated me
to sue Ruan Yu.
I'll send you the screenshot.
After consideration,
I still suggest you sue Wen Xiang.
After all, she violated your copyright.
Missy, as a newbie in the web novel market,
you have no idea
how much her plagiarism will harm you.
See?
What should I do?
Ask her to prove that
she is Su Cheng.
Lawyer Xu must be asleep.
It's wee hours there.
True. Let's not wait for him then.
No worries. Lawyer Xu is absent.
We still have Lawyer Liu,
right?
From where we left off?
Okay.
Cen Si Si seemed to try too hard.
When I told her that I was Wen Xiang,
her chin slammed into the glass,
and she hurt so much that she shedded tears.
She rubbed her eyes and asked,
"Are you joking?"
And after she was exposed,
she flushed
and fanned herself frantically.
Those acts
made her look shocked then.
But,
the more I think about it,
the more I feel something was off.
You mean she was acting?
Yes.
She probably didn't expect my showdown.
So those exaggerated acts,
I think, were to divert my attention
and buy herself some time to react.
Yes.
So,
I think she has another move planned.
Another move?
Yes.
No way.
How could she have another move?
Are you writers just too imaginative?
But her acts made me...
Xu...
Lawyer Xu!
Why are you back in the country?
You said "See you at the firm."
What is this?
Cen Si Si's another move.
Let's eat fried chicken this afternoon.
Sure.
Fried chicken? Xu,
is it proper for a smart, well-behaved
student like you to take the lead?
In or not?
I'm in!
Put a ladder at the postern
after school.
Ladder? What for?
Find a ladder
and put it at the postern.
What are you talking about?
You know it!
Climbing over the wall to buy fried chicken.
Have you finished your homework?
I'm not interested.
- Study?
- Forget the homework!
Go for fried chicken.
What's the deal? Are you eating or not?
Let's go! They'll close soon.
You're in charge of the ladder!
How can you be like this?
It's a deal then.
Hey, you guys.
A lower tone won't hurt.
But that's the way we talk.
We've always been this loud.
You never complained before.
Don't you talk like this too?
Are we going or not?
- Go.
- Go?
Go!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Meant2Be Team @Viki.com
OST
♫ ♫