[Disclaimer: This series is entirely fictional
and solely for entertainment purposes
with no association or reference
to any individuals, places, or events;
there may be inappropriate behaviors
and vulgarity based on the character's persona;
viewer discretion is advised]
I have something to tell you.
I don't know where to start.
When it's time,
you'll know how to tell it to me.
This song
It's for all of you.
Where we put ourselves
determines who we'll become.
Mom!
How is your mother?
Mom.
Wake up.
Hey!
Wake up!
Wake up, now!
Get up!
You're such an impersonator.
I shouldn't have trusted you.
Get the hell out of my house, now!
And don't you dare
show your face here again.
What were you talking about
so loudly in the morning?
Yeah.
So loud that I could hear it
from downstairs.
Grandpa, Grandma,
this asshole has been deceiving us.
He is one of the swindlers.
That explains!
I've been wondering about that.
I'm so disappointed.
I gave you my heart, Ritt.
You fake fortune teller.
How could you falsely claim
you're someone else?
This guy is taken.
You had the guts to claim him?
You impersonator.
Get out of this house!
Still acting confused?!
Get out.
Get out!
Don't you hear that?! Get out!
- Get out!
- Sorry.
- Shameless!
- Don't touch me.
- Get out!
- Leave!
Get out! Get out!
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering if your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line
where they should be♫
It's time to wake up, Young Master Ritt.
Wake up.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I'm so sorry.
Please don't push me away.
- I'm sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
What happened?
Who pushed you away?
Did you just have a bad dream?
You're grown up already.
It's nothing.
You were just dreaming.
Can you promise me?
No matter what happens,
please don't push me away from your life.
Can you promise me?
I love you.
Oh! Pitcha.
Why are you sleeping here?
Oh,
so, who is this person?
He is Pure.
I thought it was too late last night,
so I told him to stay over here.
Why didn't you let him
sleep upstairs properly?
No problem, Mom.
I can sleep anywhere. No worries.
The sofa in this house
is so soft.
Okay.
If you're already awake,
you can go take a shower upstairs,
so we can have breakfast.
Just washing my face is fine.
Taking a shower is fine.
It'll make you feel refreshed.
You can do it in Pitcha's room
and borrow his clothes first.
Follow me.
I exclusively get into
a famous idol's room.
It's such an honor for me.
Didn't you just tell my mom that
you slept well, huh?
In front of your mom,
I should say that, shouldn't I?
Actually,
I wanted to tell her so bad
that her son is mean.
He didn't want me
to sleep in his room.
Look,
his bed can fit two people,
but he let me sleep on the sofa
while having back pain for the whole night.
Just once.
The bathroom is on that side.
I'm going to bring you a new toothbrush.
And for the clothes,
you just
wear this for now, and your shirt...
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm just going to take a shower.
Have you done it?
Do you want to do it again with me?
That's fine.
Go right ahead.
Here.
Go ahead.
I thought you weren't going to eat.
We're almost full now.
- Go get them some more dim sum.
- Yes, sir.
What?
- Grandma.
- Hmm?
Are there any tricks
to ward off bad dreams?
What happened to you?
Do you have bad neck pain?
You must have got it
from sleeping the wrong way.
Here.
I have this green oil
for muscle relief.
It helps a lot. It's so nice.
No, it's not what you think, Grandpa.
Huh?
I mean, how to ward off a bad dream.
You're hard of hearing.
Bad dream? Who had a bad dream? Is it you?
It's Ritt.
His dream might be so real
that he woke up early with tears.
What did you dream about?
They said you have to tell the elders
in the house about it.
After I listen to it, I'll say,
"May the bad dream turn into a blessing."
Then you'll have good luck. It's just that.
Tell them.
Uh...
That's fine. That's fine.
If you don't want to share it,
that's fine. Let's do this.
They say that
you should go to the bathroom.
Tell your bad dream,
then flush the toilet and let it go.
Tell it to the toilet.
Or
pour the water into a water dipper,
then tell everything to it.
After that, just throw the water out.
That's all.
But don't tell anyone yet.
Yeah, just try it.
You've been coughing for many days.
I told you to see the doctor,
but you wouldn't listen.
I think you should go see the doctor, Grandpa.
I'm fine. It's just
because the weather is always changing.
Hot, cold, dusty, and a lot more.
Everyone gets this. I'll be fine.
So stubborn.
No matter what I say, he never listens.
I'll get well soon.
Last night, I dreamed about...
You're such an impersonator.
I shouldn't have trusted you.
There was also Pitcha,
his real sweetheart.
This guy is taken.
You had the guts to claim him?
Those three feng shui masters...
Get out of this house!
You tricked him into loving you,
but you didn't take it seriously.
You said you cared about him,
but you took him for granted.
You're just a bad omen for this house.
Get out!
May it flow away without returning.
Sadhu.
Smells so good. What are you cooking?
Wait a minute. It's almost done.
Do you need some help?
It's okay.
Just help me eat it, okay?
Hey, you!
I just proved what the good smell is.
I thought it was the smell of food,
but actually,
it was the smell of your cheeks.
You're taking advantage of me.
If I told my mom what you did,
you'd definitely be in trouble.
Is it done already? It smells so good.
Almost done, Mom.
You can come down to wait now.
Are these done?
I'll carry them there.
Take care of your health, Mom,
so that you'll be healthy soon.
I'll visit you next time.
Thank you.
Is Pure your friend from high school?
Pure...
is the owner of the bar
where you met me that night.
I see.
A new friend.
- Well, Pure...
- Get back to focusing on what you should do.
Yes.
Now, I'm helping a group
of younger ones practice dancing.
So, I got back to doing my practice, too.
But about singing that you caught me doing...
Consider it yourself
if the things you did
are really good for you.
You're now grown up.
Yes, Mom.
Don't let temporary pleasure
make you forget everything
you've worked for your whole life.
I told you I'm fine.
I could even walk here myself.
And...
I have a bit of a sore throat and a cold
because I'm allergic to the weather.
Let me check more meticulously.
Go ahead, doctor. To make it clear.
Let me talk to you a bit
about your grandpa's symptoms.
[SCHOOL OF ARCHITECTURE,
ART, AND DESIGN]
[Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master]
[There is only one truth,
just as there is one true identity]
A Chinese idiom says that...
"Even though the sky is calm,
there are still waves beneath the sea."
Oh, why is our dining table's vibe...
this quiet today?
Are there any waves under the sea here?
Let's just talk about what's on your mind.
We're in the same house.
Try to talk with each other.
Don't stay quiet
and let your feelings carry you away.
- Grandpa.
- Hmm?
This chicken is yummy.
You ate half the plate before telling me
it was yummy?
- There you go. Eat up.
- That's enough.
You keep serving him
until his plate is full.
Can Ritt eat all of that?
Let him gradually eat it.
Why?
What did the doctor say at the hospital?
Did he tell you that I'm going to die?
You're talking nonsense.
What you said makes no sense.
You're still strong.
You'll surely be with us for a long time.
I'm strong,
but I need to be there again next week?
Isn't that strange?
We need to follow up
to see how much you've improved.
Mmm...
If so, you don't have to worry.
Next week, we'll know.
Let's have some conversations.
You guys are too quiet.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Still quiet, huh?
Are you and Grandma
keeping some secrets from Grandpa?
At the dining table,
everyone seemed strange.
It was nothing.
That was so suspicious.
Are you still saying it was nothing?
It's about Grandpa's health.
It's nothing.
Okay.
I know I'm an outsider,
not your family members.
It's not like that.
- Well...
- It's fine.
I know that
it's none of my business.
It's gone too far.
So, what's wrong with Grandpa?
Cancer.
So...
what did the doctor say?
What stage is it?
It has spread everywhere.
And what did the doctor suggest?
Next week...
He made an appointment with us to
talk about the treatment.
Nowadays,
the doctors are talented.
But no matter what,
moral support is also important.
Thank you so much.
[Magic Move]
Magic Move isn't only
good at drinks and music,
but there are also
two accurate fortune tellers here.
And tonight is even more special
because the fortune tellers
are going to cast a spell
in the special show for everyone tonight.
Let's enjoy the show.
What is this?
Well,
you thought you looked like the singer,
so you danced to her song.
Can I have some special tips
for my fortune teller-themed dance team?
This is how you squeeze my money, right?
It's called encouraging
the nation's youth, you know?
Here, share it with everyone, okay?
The mission of today is complete.
Hey, everyone. Let's go back.
And let's practice
at the same time tomorrow.
But we need to take pictures first.
Join us, Pitcha.
Over there, the customers are coming.
Take care of them.
Try to present... Oh.
What?
♫Happy birthday to you♫
♫Happy birthday, happy birthday♫
♫Happy birthday to Pure♫
Confused, huh?
You're working so hard
that you forget your own birthday.
Thank you, naughty sister.
Thank you, everyone.
And... Thank you so much.
Wishing you all the happiness
so that you can share some of it with me.
It's Pure's birthday.
We already had a show for you.
Can you sing a song for him, Pitcha?
Sure.
What song do you want?
What song do you want to listen to?
Whatever you want to give it to me,
just bring it on.
Okay.
Let's consider it your birthday gift
because I just knew it was your birthday
when I entered the bar.
I don't have anything to give you.
Just you coming to my bar
is already a gift to me.
Something going on between you two?
Hold it.
Thank you.
You must make yin and yang shake.
I'm just coughing a little.
You've been together for more than 30 years.
The star line hasn't been changed.
You must change it.
No star is changing,
but the weather is.
There is a lot of dust.
That's why I cough.
Strengthen love fate
to support your health and good fortune.
Really? Okay, fine.
Just tell us what we should do.
You must get married!
Get married?!
Aiya...who will I marry?
I'm this old,
so how can I find a new wife?
You aren't stashing
a mistress anywhere else, are you?
- What? These guys told me to.
- Hey, just marry the same person.
- Marrying the same person is fine.
- Aiya.
Another wedding?
We just held a wedding last time.
But this time,
it's a wedding to strengthen his luck,
so his health horoscope
will be good.
No pain, no fever.
That sounds reasonable.
Bow to Heaven and Earth.
Bow to the elders.
Bow to each other.
Sorry.
And... cheek to cheek.
Right.
Cheek to cheek, please.
Yeah.
May Grandpa and Grandma
love each other for a long time.
Stay strong.
The time of happiness usually
comes and goes, Grandpa, Grandma.
But you've experienced happiness
in marriage twice already.
It's considered a bonus, you know?
Thank you so much to both of you.
Getting married again makes me feel
fitter and stronger
in the blink of an eye.
I love you, you know?
My love for you is still
the same as always.
How can it be the same?
Hasn't it grown at all?
It's fully grown.
So full you can't even breathe, huh?
Well,
you two should also remember that
during happy times,
you should enjoy every moment
so that when trouble comes,
you'll remember
how happy you were together, okay?
Good job, everyone.
You did much better
with the new move we added yesterday.
Of course, Pitcha.
If we're training this hard
and still don't improve,
we shouldn't dance anymore.
Good job.
"Practice makes perfect."
You're tired, right?
Let's take a break, shall we?
Hey, guys!
Ploy, look.
The contest we sent a video to last week
sent us a message that...
we passed!
- Let me see it!
- Here.
We need your help, Pitcha.
We need you to help us create a new show.
You must not say no.
Without you, we won't know what to do.
Of course.
I'll do my best to help you,
but you need to do your best, too.
Okay?
We promise.
Great. So, today,
go home to get enough rest,
and let me know your ideas tomorrow.
Then we're going to start with that, okay?
Yes, Pitcha.
What are you doing?
As Grandpa said,
"When we are happy together,
we should enjoy every moment of it."
I want to hold you like this forever.
What if one day,
I did something bad?
If I let you down or hurt your feelings,
would you still hold me like this?
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
You?
What could you possibly do to let me down?
I can't imagine...
you could do something like that.
Just imagine.
Just in case.
I'm not gonna tell you yet.
When it's time, you'll know...
how I deal with it.
Why are you making that face?
Now, everything is fine.
Why think about the future?
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫(But we're gonna try, try, try)♫
Please come in.
Have you reserved a table yet?
Does Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master,
come today?
Oh, Ritt won't come here today.
That's too bad.
If you would like to have your fortune read,
Ployplern, the Pictura Master,
is glad to assist you.
I'll give it a try.
Maybe there will be some answers
that can put my mind at rest.
Take a deep breath.
Stay focused.
Think of things you want to know,
then pick three cards.
The first card:
a secret hidden in the dark.
The second card:
a restraint
that prevents you from speaking up.
The third card:
a major change.
The things you're going to do
will reveal something important
that leads to a change in you.
Of course,
there must be some changes.
It's time for the truth
to come to light.
Contemporary house design,
which is a combination
of energy stones and runes,
offers not only physical comfort
but also builds new meanings,
a sense of safety,
and balanced energy for the residents
in a contemporary context.
Hello, well... My house design
is like this.
There is a chimney on top.
Okay, my piece is about the bedroom.
It's at the back because...
Well done, Ritt.
For today...
you did a great job, everyone.
See you next time.
Go home.
That's it.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Hey! Ritt.
Are you free next week?
Yes, professor.
Here is the thing: I would like you
to go to a restaurant,
which is my student's,
your senior.
Their space planning
is based on the concept of land breeze
and sea breeze.
The coming in
and the pulling back of waves.
I think there are
some similarities in your work.
That's great, professor.
I'm going to call them
to find out what day they'll be there,
so they can explain
the concept of its design.
Does that sound good?
Yes, professor.
See you later.
Goodbye.
[Unknown number:
See you at the usual place]
I thought you were not going to come.
Have...we known each other before?
Does it matter
whether you know me
or not,
since you
can just impersonate others, can't you?
What do you want?
I want nothing.
I just want to help you...
maintain that fake happiness
for a long time.
What did you know?
I know everything.
I know whose sweetheart
you are pretending to be.
On top of that, you deprived
the lovers of each other.
You're smart, aren't you?
You shouldn't study architecture.
You should study...
how to make up stories
or fiction writing.
Tons of people might
look forward to reading it.
Tell me what you want.
Five hundred thousand baht.
What?!
Five hundred thousand?!
I don't have that much money.
Also,
I intend to tell the whole truth.
Wow,
the time of happiness is about
to be over, isn't it?
That's so unfortunate.
I haven't taken part yet.
What you are doing right now
is clearly extortion.
And what will you call
the thing you're doing?
Huh?
What do you think
will happen if more people find out?
From one...
to two...
to three...
What do you think will happen?
"Master Ritt Abuses His Position
Using Sacred Means
for Personal Gain."
And what if Itthi or Pitcha finds out?
I don't even want to think about it.
What are your thoughts...
on Itthi's feeling
for having been as stupid
as a donkey for so long?
Can he have you arrested?
And what will you be charged with?
What if Pitcha finds out?
You actually stole
a celebrity's boyfriend.
What if people
at the university find out...
It might reflect badly on
your professional ethics as a future architect.
And who's going to hire
a swindler like you as an architect, huh?
But I don't have
that much money.
Ask Itthi for it!
He is so into you, isn't he?
For a multibillionaire like him,
this little amount of money
shouldn't cause him any trouble.
I'll be back.
Why are you making that face?
The Korean agency
sent me a message.
They told me to go back
to auditioning for a new project.
Well, that's nice, right?
This is a good opportunity for you,
so you can return to doing what you love.
You think so?
Why?
Don't you want to go back?
I don't know either.
Now, I feel like
the dream I had
is starting to change.
Is that because of me?
I thought you were going to tell me...
to stay here
and not go back to the audition.
Actually...
I wanted to say that,
but it would probably be too selfish of me.
You have a dream waiting for you there.
This place might be too small
to make your big dream come true.
And I'm just...
a small bar owner,
who can only be...
your fan at best
You're a bit too far from me.
I don't even dare to reach out
and make you stay.
Don't you want to try?
I'm not like you.
You've been trying for so long.
And...
it's going to pay off soon.
But for me...
it's wrong just to think about it.
What do you think?
Thank you so much.
If I go back to live there,
I will definitely miss this place a lot.
After you make your debut,
you probably can't come
to a place like this.
Or if you can, you might...
have many guards around you.
Perhaps
next time you come back,
you probably won't remember me anymore.
What?
I gave you my promise.
No matter what,
I'm going to come back.
Are you hurt, Grandma?
Ugh. No, I'm not.
Coming home so late, huh, Ritt?
Itthi is waiting for you.
He said he had something to talk to you.
I told him to call you, but he didn't.
He said he wanted
to talk to you in person.
What's the matter?
Oh, I don't know either.
Just go upstairs to talk to him yourself.
Yes, Grandma.
Are you sleeping?
Who should I tell the truth to first?
How about I start with the people
who came to you for fortune readings,
then your professors,
and post it on social media
and tag Pitcha
and Itthiphumi Pongpanyalert?
I'll give you time to think...
for three days.
And after that, I don't know who will be
the first to find out the truth.
Last time, you were famous for being
Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master.
This time, let me name you in advance.
Ritt...
the Fraud Master.
I have no idea what you are asking me,
but if it's time to say it,
I'm going to tell you the truth.
But just do me one favor.
Please don't hate me.
I never intended to deceive you
with anything that I did.
But I did it because
I love you so much.
I wanted to be the apple of your eye,
close to you,
and the person you loved.
I'm so sorry.
You saw the photo I sent you, right?
They finally met each other.
Well, this issue...
Did you know from the beginning
that I wasn't your childhood sweetheart?
Liars like us,
who love to make up stories,
aren't supposed to be together.
The more I look at you...
the more I want to know you.
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering if your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫(But we're gonna try, try, try)♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line
where they should be♫
♫(And we're gonna try, try, try)♫