[suspenseful music playing]
[Jerrod] Kitana...
I have something for you.
It will protect you.
It's beautiful, Father.
This was a gift
from Lord Raiden.
The God of Thunder.
If anything
were to happen to me,
he's always listening.
[guard] Shao Kahn
is arriving, Your Majesty.
What happens if you lose?
[Jerrod] Don't worry
about that.
But what if he's too strong?
Strength is not a closed fist.
Strength is here,
and here.
Be strong, Kitana.
[Jerrod sighs]
[citizens chanting]
Jerrod, our king!
[chanting continues]
[Kitana] Shao Kahn,
Emperor of Outworld,
sought to unite the various
realms under one rule.
His.
But the Elder Gods had put
certain precautions in place.
Our fates would not be settled
by the size of our armies.
They would be decided
by combat.
The rules were simple.
If one realm could win
10 tournaments in a row,
it would be given
dominion over the other.
Outworld would be allowed
to pillage Edenia's resources.
Enslave our people.
This was the final tournament.
Our last chance.
All of our greatest warriors
had already fallen.
Only one fighter remained.
My father,
King Jerrod of Edenia.
But he faced Outworld's
greatest warrior.
Shao Kahn himself.
[gasps softly]
[footsteps thudding]
[growls]
They will never bow to you.
[Shao Kahn] We shall see.
[gong tolls]
[tense music playing]
[growls]
[weapons clanging]
-[Jerrod straining]
-[grunting]
-[Jerrod yells]
-[thuds]
[growls]
-[citizens exclaim]
[Jerrod yells]
[gasps]
[groaning]
Never!
[weapon clatters]
[blade slicing]
[young Kitana gasps]
-[grunts loudly]
-[Shao Kahn screams]
-[blade slices]
-[Shao Kahn groans]
[Jerrod strains, screams]
[citizens gasping]
[screams]
[ominous music playing]
[Jerrod grunting]
[screaming]
[gasps] Kitana,
close your eyes.
Close your eyes right now.
[pained groans]
[breathing heavily]
[yells in pain]
-[screams]
-No!
No!
[struggling]
No! [sobbing]
[screaming]
[somber music playing]
[thuds]
[breath trembling]
[crying]
[women crying]
[growls]
[Shao Kahn] Edenia
now belongs to me.
[sinister music playing]
[dagger clanks]
-[grunting]
-[blade clanging]
[Sindel growls]
[Sindel grunts]
[Shao Kahn] Kneel.
Or you'll die.
[mournful music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
Your father shouldn't have
brought you here.
Kitana,
you're my daughter now.
[dramatic choral music playing]
[woman] Kitana!
[thrilling music playing]
[both grunting]
[panting]
[weapons clacking]
[Kitana grunts]
[thrilling music stops]
Yield.
[ribbon snaps]
You cannot be serious.
You're the one who taught me,
everything's a weapon.
[thrilling music resumes]
[woman grunts]
You yield.
What do you have there?
It's nothing.
Jade.
It was 20 years ago today
the Emperor named me
as your bodyguard.
I know what Shao Kahn
took from you.
And if you had been vicious
or cruel to me,
no one would have blamed you,
but you treated me
like family.
Like a sister.
You are my sister.
In every way that matters.
Um, I got you something.
For the tournament.
I was told
that a proper princess
is supposed to sit around
on pillows fanning herself.
Then I thought
you are not exactly
the pillow type.
[clanking]
These are amazing.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hello, Mother.
[Shao Kahn] I was beginning
to think you were avoiding me.
I've been busy.
Training for the tournament.
[Shao Kahn] Good.
Because I have petitioned
the Elder Gods
for the tournament to begin.
Let Raiden scrounge
for his little champions.
They will simply
be the first to die
and Earthrealm will be mine.
-[gasps]
-[door opens]
[Kitana] Why is he here?
[Shao Kahn] I have a task
for Shang Tsung.
I hope you bring
good news, Sorcerer.
My spies have located
the relic.
It was last seen
in Raiden's temple
where it was stolen
by the mercenary, Kano.
[Shao Kahn]
We seek the Amulet of Shinnok.
[Sindel] It is said the Amulet
can heal any wound.
Transform a man into a god.
To charge the amulet
would require
an impossible amount of power.
We would need to capture
a star from the heavens.
-A star...
-[dramatic music playing]
...or a god.
[Raiden] Outworld has issued
their challenge
and the Elder Gods
have spoken.
When the sand is gone,
the first round will begin.
Mortal Kombat is upon us
and yet we are still short
one champion.
[static]
-[tires screeching]
-[suspenseful music playing]
["Rock You Like A Hurricane"
by Scorpions playing]
[singer]
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ Rock you like a hurricane ♪
It's showtime.
[man screams]
["Rock You Like A Hurricane"
continues playing]
♪ Are you ready, baby? ♪
♪ Here I am ♪
[grunts]
♪ Rock you like a hurricane ♪
[steel rod thudding]
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ Rock you like a hurricane ♪
[growls]
[singer vocalizing]
[Johnny] You should have
brought more guys.
♪ The sun comes out ♪
♪ Last night was shaking
And pretty loud ♪
[Johnny grunts]
♪ It scratches my skin ♪
♪ So what is wrong
With another sin? ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ Rock you like a hurricane ♪
♪ Come on, come on
Come on, come on ♪
[explosion]
♪ Rock you like a hurricane ♪
[man 1] Man, Johnny Cage
got old as fuck.
-[snoring]
-[girls shrieking]
[announcer over speakers]
Attention, fans,
don't miss your chance to meet
your favorite influencers
and YouTube stars
in Autograph Alley.
[woman] All right,
everyone, get in close.
Black Orchid!
[girls cheering]
[upbeat dance music
playing over speakers]
[Johnny] It's showtime.
Johnny Cage.
Hey, guys. I'm off the clock.
Mr. Cage, you have been chosen
for Mortal Kombat.
Mortal Kombat, huh?
What's that?
Some kind of fan film?
It's a fighting tournament.
[sighs] Yeah, not really
my thing anymore.
Unless it's a paying gig?
More like a "fate
of the entire human race" gig.
Tell me you're
not some crazy fans.
Definitely not fans.
All right. All right.
You don't
have to say "definitely."
You have been chosen
as one of the champions
of Earthrealm.
The gods have selected you,
Mr. Cage.
All right, I think it's time
for you guys to fuck off.
But, hey, love the cosplay.
What's that?
Big Trouble in Little China?
Fantastic film.
Listen, I know
what it sounds like,
but he's telling the truth.
Very soon the champions
will be summoned to fight
and you will be among them.
The fate of your world
rests on the outcome
of this tournament.
Fantastic.
I will see you there.
Thanks for coming, drive safe,
and, uh, say hi to Dumbledore
for me.
You're gonna have to show him.
[crackling]
Holy shit.
How are you doing that?
[Raiden] Come with us,
Mr. Cage,
and discover the man
you were meant to be.
Now are you coming or what?
[mysterious music playing]
Where the hell am I?
[Sonya] It's okay.
You're still on Earth.
Welcome
to Raiden's Sky Temple.
[intriguing music playing]
[all grunting]
[Jax] Watch this. [grunts]
Robot arms.
That dude's got robot arms.
[Sonya] We served
in the Army together.
That's Jax Briggs.
Special Forces.
That's Cole Young.
His suit absorbs attacks
and makes him stronger.
He's a descendant of Scorpion.
One of Earthrealm's
greatest warriors.
Oh.
That's Liu Kang.
He's the best fighter we got.
-He shoots fire?
-[Sonya] Mm-hmm.
[scoffs]
I feel like that's cheating,
but okay.
It kind of feels like bullshit
that y'all have
these crazy powers
and I'm just, you know,
incredibly handsome.
It could take
months of training
to unlock your powers.
We don't have
that kind of time.
Yeah,
well, whose fault is that?
I mean,
if you knew this was coming,
why'd you wait till the
last second to find me?
We used to have
another champion. Kung Lao.
Oh, great,
so I'm just the fucking sub.
He was murdered.
By Shang Tsung.
Wait. Murdered?
Come on.
You can't be serious. Right?
I mean, that's, like,
gotta be against the rules.
You can't just go around
killing people.
It's called Mortal Kombat
for a reason.
Yo, Gandalf, send me back.
I wanna go back.
-Johnny, wait.
-No. No.
You said tournament
which implies rules,
and a referee, and I don't
know, maybe a medic.
Not some fucking Squid Game
murder party.
Dude wants to quit,
just let him go.
We don't need him.
Look, you wanna step
in the octagon
with a bunch
of happy assholes
that don't know how to lose,
go right ahead.
But I don't have
Transformer arms,
or shoot lightning bolts
or fireballs,
or do whatever the fuck it is
Flame Fingers does,
so forgive me if I don't
sign up to get mulched.
You are not wrong, Mr. Cage.
Nine times,
we have been challenged.
And nine times, we have lost.
And now, 20 years later,
Shao Kahn seeks to add
Earthrealm to his dominion.
This is a war
for the fate of your world.
[Jax] Look, Cage, I get it.
We all do.
Some stupid, fucking,
cosmic lottery
decided that we're the ones
that get to save the world.
Shit is terrifying.
[Cole] You wanna know
the last thing I did
before coming here?
I said goodbye to my wife
and my little girl.
The two most important things
in my life.
And there's a damn good chance
I'm never
gonna see them again.
And I'm okay with that.
Because I know if I die
out there, I'm dying for them.
We lose one more time,
the Earth is gone.
[Liu Kang] And our only chance
is to face this together.
You, Johnny Cage,
are a part of this now.
[heroic music builds, stops]
Fuck that.
[Sonya] Johnny,
even if you walk away,
the Elder Gods
can still summon you to fight.
Not if they can't find me.
So what are you gonna do, huh?
You just going to go hide?
No, first I'm gonna drink
every beer on the planet,
then I'm going to hide.
Because this shit's
got nothing to do with me.
I'm not some great warrior.
I'm not some champion.
Okay? I'm an actor.
[Sonya] Hmm.
And before that,
you were the guy
with five black belts
and a world title.
Yeah, I saw
some of those old fights.
Man, you could have been
one of the best.
But I wasn't.
And that was a long time ago.
That guy you want
is dead and buried.
Or maybe he's still in there
trying to get out.
Hey, listen...
I'm like 90% sure
I had an aneurysm
and this is some kind of
fucked up coma dream,
but on the off chance
this shit is real,
best of luck with the whole
saving the world thing.
[thunderclap]
[thunder rumbling]
[voices whispering]
[Quan Chi] You should know
that when you died,
it was not your so-called
friends who brought you back.
It was not Lord Raiden,
the Great Pretender.
It was Shao Kahn.
Rise now,
as a champion of Outworld.
[ominous music builds]
[Acolyte 1] Sire,
we retrieved the package.
Quan Chi!
I am told you sent your
followers to Earthrealm.
What were they doing there?
Simply retrieving
some lost property, my lady.
By order of your father.
What is that?
I believe it's called...
a "Kano."
[man] One Sling Dog, please.
[gasps]
You're Johnny Cage.
That's what the tab says.
[man] Holy shit.
I freaking loved Citizen Cage
when I was a kid.
Thanks, man. I appreciate it.
Dude, you know
what they should do?
They should
do another Citizen Cage.
Like a reboot.
Come on, man.
Give me a break.
-Nobody wants that.
-What?
You think the world
is crying out
for a Johnny Cage comeback?
Huh?
No. They want gritty,
they want grounded,
they want Keanu Reeves
murdering a thousand
fucking dudes with a pencil.
That's what people wanna see.
Not some dinosaur
doing a bunch of karate poses.
That shit went out
in the '90's.
I thought it was pretty cool.
[sighs]
[Quan Chi
chanting indistinctly]
[unsettling music playing]
[continues chanting]
[Kano screams]
Where's my fucking eye?
-[squelching]
-[Kano grunts]
Blondie.
[Raiden] The tournament
has begun.
Today you fight
for Earthrealm.
For the lives of everyone
you have ever known.
If you fail,
the Earth fails with you.
Two of our champions will
be chosen to compete today.
The winners will advance
to the next stage
of the tournament.
The losers will be eliminated.
To the death.
That is up to the winner.
Maybe don't lose.
[energy whooshing]
[pulsing]
Well, looks like
it's my lucky day.
Blade, you got this.
I thought you said
two of us were fighting.
[rock music
playing over stereo]
[announcer] It's Johnny Cage
with a brutal hit. He's down.
-[whistle blows]
-[announcer] It's official.
Johnny Cage just became
the youngest minor
to ever win this tournament.
This young man
is destined for greatness.
[bartender] You seem
a little down, Johnny.
You're normally
a little more animated.
Uno mas, thanks, Ed.
[zaps]
[grunts]
Oh, shit.
[suspenseful music playing]
I don't know
what you're on about.
The amulet of what now?
Shinnok. Pay attention!
Don't look at me
with that tone of voice,
you big bleached dildo.
I've just been dead.
And my fucking eye's AWOL.
Stop your incessant whinging.
We can build you another.
Why is he not a Revenant
like the rest of them?
[Quan Chi] He was not worth
the time or the effort.
This one barely has a soul
left to corrupt.
Ha! You hear that?
A fucking loophole.
[laughs] Go, you good thing.
Where is the amulet you took
from Raiden's temple?
I don't know,
probably in my pocket
where I keep
all the shit I steal.
Oh, right-oh.
-Here we go. How about...
-[metal clinking]
Nah, different temple.
Well, hold on.
This could be...
[chuckles] Yeah.
Should call her.
Ah! Here we are. Yahtzee.
Oi!
We could have left him dead.
Hey! First off, fuck off.
And you,
where are you going with that?
I will take it to my father.
Unfortunately, Princess,
it appears
you are needed elsewhere.
Oi, you creepy fucking mime.
I stole that fair and square.
Good luck.
[footsteps thudding]
[thrilling music playing]
[Kitana] Each flame
represents a fighter.
The tournament ends
when one side
has no champions left.
Hey. How's it going, babe?
[blades clanking]
Listen, I'm warning you,
I got a Saturn Award for
best fight in a feature film,
so don't mess with me.
[gong tolls]
Whoa! Whoa. Easy, all right.
Let's just take a timeout here
and talk about it.
Okay? I really don't feel
comfortable hitting a girl.
Don't worry, you won't.
[blades slashing]
[both grunting]
Whoa! Come on. Easy.
Let's just talk about this.
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
Why are you so fucking mean?
[Kitana scoffs]
[panting]
[Johnny grunting]
[both grunting]
[Kitana grunts]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[thrilling music continues]
[blades slashing]
[grunts]
-[blades slash]
-[groans]
[Johnny grunts]
[groans]
Finish him!
Hmm.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Sindel] It appears your side
is already down a man.
Tragic.
And who are you?
Sindel. High Queen of Edenia.
Consort to the great
Shao Kahn.
They send their queen
to fight?
No. We send our best to fight.
Oh.
No offense, babe, but you look
really fucking dead.
I was freed
from my mortal bonds.
Shao Kahn showed me
the pleasures
of a life eternal.
-[gong tolls]
-[metal clanks]
Perhaps I'll do the same
for you.
[metal clanking]
[Sonya yells]
What a pretty trick.
Would you like to see mine?
No, actually I'm good.
-[grunts]
-[screaming]
[yelling]
[grunts]
[metal slashing]
[screaming]
[Sonya] Fuck you!
You stupid bitch!
[grunts]
[groans]
[both straining]
[Sindel growling]
[screaming]
[thuds]
[Sonya grunting]
[both straining]
[screaming]
[Sonya grunts]
[squelches]
[panting]
It appears
our sides are now even.
What'd I miss? [sighs]
Fuck yeah! Look who's back.
Well? How bad was it?
Zombie queen.
Pit of spikes. Yeah.
-So pretty goddamn bad.
-Ow.
-[groans]
-[Sonya grunts]
-You okay?
-Yeah.
What happened?
You were eliminated
from the tournament.
You lost.
You are lucky, she was
charitable and let you live.
[Kano] Oi! Pennywise.
I've been looking all over
this shithole for you.
You promised me a new eye.
And it better be one
that shoots lasers.
-I have other priorities.
-[Kano] Like fucking what?
If it's putting on
more eyeliner,
trust me, you're good.
All right? Come on, mate.
I am bumping into shit
left, right, and center.
I mean, my peripheral vision
is fucked.
Proper fucked, mate.
So come on.
Chop-chop. Let's get to it.
[pulsing]
Well, you don't have
to do it right now.
I mean, you need to,
you know, take a measurement.
Check the color or wash
your grubby little hands.
All right, let's have a look.
Don't fucking roll it on
the fucking ground, you grub!
Oi, the amulet.
I want that back.
And don't fucking roll it.
[Quan Chi] You got your eye.
Now leave me alone.
The amulet
does not belong to you.
Its powers are well beyond
-your meager understanding.
-[blows air]
Idiot.
All right. Let's take
this baby for a test drive.
All right.
[inhales deeply]
One, two, three.
Oh! Fuck! Snug.
[zapping]
Wow. [chuckles]
Holy shit, is that HD?
That's pretty good.
How many eyes you made?
Can you do me other one?
You seem troubled, Mr. Cage.
Yeah. Well, 'cause of me
Earth's odds
just got 20% worse.
I had a chance to actually
do something worth a damn
and I screwed it all up.
So, yeah, I'd say "troubled"
just about sums it up.
[rustling]
What are those? Pills?
Huh?
Are they magic fighting pills?
Is that how
you get your powers?
[clattering]
Bird seed.
Oh. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bird seed. Yeah.
Well, I thought you were gonna
give me some kind of lecture,
but, yeah, chores are good.
You don't need a lecture.
You need perspective.
[scoffs] Perspective, huh?
There are eight billion people
on this planet
and yet the gods chose you.
Perhaps they saw
your true potential
-as a champion of Earthrealm.
-[sighs]
Maybe they made a mistake.
Maybe.
If I see the Elder Gods,
I'll be sure to tell them.
Well, I'm glad
you find this all so amusing.
Hey, great pep talk,
by the way. Just nailed it.
[pensive music playing]
[rumbling]
[crackling]
[thunder crashing]
Ouch.
You have done this before?
I've seen it done.
[Sonya] All right.
It's okay. The Princess Kitana
has been my eyes and ears
inside the palace
for many years now.
We know the risk you took
coming here.
Thank you, Kitana.
Wait, are you telling me
I got my ass kicked
by one of the good guys?
I had to make it look real.
He was watching.
They found
the Amulet of Shinnok.
It was in the possession
of a dead sellsword
named Kano.
Son of a bitch.
If the Emperor finds a way
to charge the amulet,
he would be unstoppable.
It would be
like fighting a god.
Yeah, well, let's not do that.
My friend
is in the tournament.
Jade was raised
under Shao Kahn's army.
Do what you must,
but do not make her suffer.
[crackling]
You went to another realm?
You followed me?
I am trying to keep you alive.
By spying on your friend.
By keeping my friend
from making a mistake.
You are conspiring
with Lord Raiden. The enemy.
I swore an oath, Kitana.
To serve as Shao Kahn's sword.
[Raiden] The second round
of the tournament
will consist of three matches.
Jax, Cole, Liu Kang.
[metal slashes]
[gasps]
Kung Lao.
I have been given new life.
My son?
[chiming]
[energy pulsing]
Look at that.
Still part of this tournament.
But that's not why I'm here.
[ominous choral music playing]
No!
[groaning]
Attack now!
[Sonya grunting]
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[choking]
[grunting]
[zaps]
Imagine what one
could do with such power.
[Shao Kahn] Careful, Sorcerer,
that doesn't belong to you.
The amulet must be bound
to a mortal soul.
Once it has imprinted
on to you,
Raiden's power will be yours.
The amulet
will give you immortality.
[amulet pulsing]
[dramatic music playing]
[Shao Kahn grunting]
[Shao Kahn growls]
[inhales, growls]
[bubbling]
[gate rattling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[growls]
[portal whooshing]
Well, this is fucking ominous.
I'm guessing you're Jade.
Let's get this over with.
[clangs]
[suit pulsing]
I am told you carry
the blood of Scorpion.
I look forward to spilling it.
[Jax yells]
You know you're fighting
on the wrong side, right?
[grunts]
[staff clangs, pulsing]
What the fuck
do you have under there?
Shit. [yells]
[panting]
[yells]
Well, hello there.
[yelling]
[Shao Kahn] I hope
your ancestors are watching.
[thrilling music playing]
[Cole yells]
[metal clangs]
-[yells]
-[Shao Kahn grunts]
[growls]
[yells]
[Jade yells]
For what it is worth,
I take no joy in this.
Then you're really going
to hate this shit.
-[yells]
-[groans]
[coughs]
This is for my family.
For my friends.
For every moment
that brought me here.
This is for Earth,
you son of a bitch.
[dramatic choral music playing]
[Cole grunts]
[Shao Kahn grunts]
[armor clanging]
-[blade slicing]
-[blood splattering]
[strains]
[groans]
[suit pulsing, powering up]
[Shao Kahn screams]
[Shao Kahn groans in pain]
[squelching]
[Cole] What?
[laughs]
[gasps]
[Shao Kahn yells]
-[gasps]
-[squelching]
[exhales]
[liquid sizzles]
Give my regards to the dead.
[weapon splashing]
[groans]
[grunts, pants]
Go on, do it.
Why?
Your friend spared
one of our guys.
Now we're even.
By the way, hell of a fight.
[energy warbling]
[portal whooshing]
[blade whirring, vibrating]
Kung Lao,
what have they done to you?
Opened my eyes to the truth.
What truth?
Look around. The gods have
abandoned their creation.
Only Shao Kahn
can save us now.
One of those gods raised you.
Loved you.
And you slit his throat.
[grunts]
[thuds]
[tense music playing]
[scraping]
-[growls]
-[Liu Kang grunts]
Stop. Kung Lao,
remember who you are!
You were my brother.
And when you're dead,
when your realm falls,
we will be brothers again.
[straining]
[grunts]
[sinister choral music playing]
Don't make me do this.
[thrilling music playing]
[straining]
[grunts]
[dramatic choral music playing]
[clangs]
[thuds]
[whirring]
I'll find a way to save you.
[grunts]
[grinding]
I'm going to bring you back.
[blow thuds]
[squelching]
[gurgling]
[grinding stops]
[groans, shudders]
But not today, brother.
[somber music playing]
-[crackling]
-Raiden!
-Is he?
-He's alive. Barely.
He's been asking for you.
[weakly] Liu Kang.
My son.
[exhales]
What happened?
I killed him.
I didn't have a choice.
I'm sorry.
Where's Cole?
He didn't come back?
Oh, shit.
[sighs]
[Shao Kahn] Necromancer,
give me your greatest warrior.
The one they call Sub-Zero.
[echoing] Bi-Han.
[Quan Chi] Rise now.
[sinister music playing]
I am reborn.
[crackling]
[Kitana] Raiden's portal
is already weakening.
It will not last
when he is gone.
Why would they
take his powers?
Shao Kahn has bonded
with the amulet.
Stolen the powers of a god.
The only way
to reverse the process
is to destroy the amulet.
Well, we'd better do it
before the next round starts.
[Jax] Mm-hmm.
[Johnny] So,
let's use the portal.
Jump in, we grab the amulet of
magic bullshit, destroy it,
and then get the fuck
out of there
before he even knows
we're there.
The palace has
defensive wards in place.
Open a portal
and they'll sense you at once.
So where does that leave us?
There is a tunnel
beneath the castle.
It is the only entrance
that is not under
constant watch.
Because?
Because it is
the service entrance
for the Tarkatans.
[chuckles]
What's a Tarkatan?
What?
[portal rumbling]
[whispering indistinctly]
[growls]
[gate opens]
Wait, what did you do?
I did not do this, Kitana.
You did.
[ominous music playing]
Wait, Jade. Jade.
[Tarkatans whispering]
Are you the leader
of this clan?
-I am Baraka.
-[Tarkatans cheering, snarling]
I am Liu Kang.
I know how your people
have suffered
at the hands of Shao Kahn.
He uses you like slaves.
He treats you like wild dogs.
[Tarkatans clamoring]
We are wild dogs.
We have come
to end Shao Kahn's reign.
Will you help us?
Shao Kahn has an army.
-Do you have an army?
-No.
Then you're wasting my time.
[Tarkatans snarling]
[Liu Kang]
Then I challenge you,
Baraka of Clan Tarkata
to single combat.
I decline your challenge.
Now leave.
You know,
everyone keeps talking
Tarkatan this, Tarkatan that.
Big teeth, stabby arms,
ooh, scary.
No one mentioned the fact that
you're all a bunch
of giant fucking pussies.
[Baraka growls]
All right, maybe don't insult
the monsters.
I mean, do you have any idea
who you're talking to?
I'm Johnny fucking Cage.
And this guy is Liu Kang.
Earth's greatest champion.
I mean, look, man, I get it.
I'd be scared of him too.
But someday,
when Shao Kahn's dead
and Outworld's
been defeated,
you're going to have to tell
all your little
Spirit Halloween
monster grandbabies
that you had the chance
to fight the great Liu Kang,
but you were
too much of a coward.
[Tarkatans growling]
I accept your challenge.
Okay.
[Liu Kang]
Thanks for making him angry.
Hollywood Negotiating 101.
But not him.
My fight is with you.
Oh, boy.
Me?
-Well, what did I do?
-I find you annoying,
and I wish to kill you
and eat you.
That would bring me
immense satisfaction.
Is this guy serious?
Uh-huh.
Guys, I'm just
a fucking actor, okay?
Johnny Cage is just
a character I play. All right?
I have stuntmen
that do this shit for me.
-You're gonna have to do it.
-Oh, no, no, no.
Johnny will definitely die.
Oh, agreed.
You're going to die.
Yeah, agreed. Hard agree!
-[Baraka growls]
-One minute, bub.
Guys, you saw me
in the tournament.
I... I can't do this.
[Jax and Sonya] No shit.
[Baraka] Enough!
We fight.
-[growls]
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's set some
ground rules okay?
Not the face.
[Baraka snarls]
[Johnny grunting]
-[Baraka snarls]
-[grunts]
[pants]
Weapon! I need a weapon!
Oh, shit.
[grunts]
[panting]
Ugh.
Shh.
[Johnny] Oh, come on.
[yells]
[both grunting]
-Oh.
-[snarls]
[crashes]
[Johnny grunts]
[Johnny] Now stay down!
[growling]
Oh, shit.
[yelling]
-[screaming]
-[thuds]
[roars]
[Johhny yelps, groans]
Well, this is
a stupid ass way to lose.
[Sonya] All right, get up.
Get up.
[heroic music playing]
You're an actor, so act.
All right, you big ugly fuck.
[sunglasses clicks]
["Mortal Kombat" theme playing]
It's showtime.
[roars]
[grunts]
Come on,
[mouthing] come on, come on.
-[Baraka groans]
-[Johnny grunts]
[growls]
[groans]
-Ooh!
-Goddamn!
[groans, panting]
[Baraka snarls]
That...
was the greatest fighting
-I've ever seen!
-[Tarkatans cheering]
Witness,
my brothers and sisters.
The cunning,
the speed, the ferocity
of the one they call
Johnny Fucking Cage.
[triumphant music playing]
You must share with me
your knowledge.
Mold me in your ways.
And I will.
I'll get right on that.
But first,
we need a little favor.
-[Baraka growling]
-[blades slashing]
[Baraka snarls]
[yells]
[body thuds]
[Baraka] I've brought you
as far as I dare.
Tarkatans are not allowed
in the castle.
Right.
You have done well, my pupil.
And someday I shall return,
as promised,
and we will
complete your training.
May the screams
of your enemies
echo in your dreams.
And may their sweet fat
melt upon your tongue.
Ah, yes. Mm.
And, uh, the same with you
and... your enemies,
and your tongue
and the sweet fat
[hesitates]
be on your tongue too.
As well. And... rock on.
We're not gonna
make it in time.
We have to try.
[Jax] Let's go, baby.
[Shao Kahn] So what punishment
befits a wayward princess?
As you can see,
I ordered Quan Chi
to resurrect her.
But perhaps your mother should
have another accident.
Stop.
[Shao Kahn] It may be hard
to perform a resurrection
when her skull is dripping
through my fingers.
Please!
Last chance, child.
-Where did you go?
-Earthrealm!
I went to Earthrealm.
Did you now?
I went looking
for Lord Raiden.
But he was gone.
So were his champions.
I do not know
what happened to them.
I only know that I am alone.
Chain her up
in the town square.
Let the princess's treason
serve as a warning to all.
[suspenseful music playing]
Jade.
I know she's like
a sister to you.
That was no small thing
you just did.
I still remember
the little girl
we pulled
from the fighting pits.
More animal than child.
But I see now
I made the right choice.
[Liu Kang] We'll cover
more ground if we split up.
Find the amulet.
And don't get caught.
[Sonya] Come on,
you're with me.
[door opens]
And what do we have here?
Raiden sends one of his
sad little followers.
[scoffs] A gift
from a dying god.
-[grunting]
-[punching]
-[Shao Kahn yells]
-[weapon clangs]
[dragons roar, chitter]
I am Liu Kang.
The last son of the dragon.
-And I shall watch you burn.
-[dragons roaring]
[grunting]
[groans]
[sighs]
[gasps]
[clangs]
[screams]
[thuds]
-[grunts]
-[clangs]
[groans]
[faintly] The amulet.
[Shao Kahn yells]
[Liu Kang groans]
[grunts]
[straining]
[yelling]
-[Liu Kang grunts]
-[screams]
[Liu Kang yelps]
[straining]
Shit.
Go!
[grunting]
[Sonya yells]
[grunts]
[screams, thuds]
[groans]
That's my goddamn partner!
[Shao Kahn] Bi-Han!
Protect the amulet!
[Bi-Han] I'll keep it safe.
[weapon clanging]
[Jax screaming]
[groaning]
[sighs]
[gasping] Fuck you.
-[groans]
-[pants]
[Shao Kahn grunting]
Jax!
[Sonya] Jax!
You fucking animal!
You're next.
[panting]
Fucking hell.
Oh, I know you.
I've seen some of your movies.
They're all shit.
Look at that.
Old Rock 'Em Sock 'Em's dead.
[smacks lips]
I'll cry later.
All right, boys. Over here.
You in the middle,
a little that way.
And you there,
just a step forward.
There.
-[laser buzzing]
-[bodies thud]
[laughs]
Now, let's you and me
talk terms.
Terms for what?
Now what do you
fucking reckon?
Old Kano's about to ride in
on a big white horse
and save all your
dumb fucking asses.
[Kano scoffs]
-[chains rattling]
-[Kitana struggling]
I told you to stop.
You forced his hand.
It was always gonna
end this way.
It is not too late.
Beg his forgiveness.
You cannot stand against him.
None of us can.
He is too strong.
-[chains rattling]
-[screams]
[Kitana panting]
[softly] You are
better than them.
[portal whooshing]
Well, here he is.
Fucking hell,
you've seen better days.
[weakly]
What do you want, Kano?
Well, right now I'm thinking
I want you lot
to win this thing.
Bullshit.
[Kano] Mate,
have you seen Outworld?
Or Edenia?
I mean it's nothing
but rocks, and sand,
and fucking sad people.
I don't want that.
I like air conditioning,
and beer,
and bottomless breadsticks...
and tan lines,
and one-night stands,
and threesomes,
and foursomes,
Jack and Coke.
Just Jack. Just coke.
And why should we trust you?
Because I know where
Bi-Han's taken the amulet.
Netherrealm.
What's Netherrealm?
[weakly]
The realm of the dead.
A place of fire
and punishment.
Sounds fun.
I can't wait to get there.
And by the looks of things,
you got enough juice left
in the tank
to get us down there.
So, here's what I'm thinking.
We smash the amulet,
we get your powers back.
Shao Kahn's mortal again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We kill that fucker.
Save the world.
Pretty Boy here
gives me a wristy.
Everybody wins.
[laughs] You dickheads in
or what?
Let's fucking go.
[resolute music playing]
I may not have enough
power to bring you back.
And you will be stuck there.
And no one will ever know
what you have done.
Still worth it.
You have changed, Mr. Cage.
It's called perspective.
[Kano] Yeah, blah, blah,
fuckity blah.
I thought you were
right behind me. Chop-chop.
You will not survive
in Netherrealm
without a guide.
[scraping]
You do not belong here.
[Kano] Holy shit.
I mean, if this is Hell,
you can sign me the fuck up.
[solemn music playing]
[Johnny] What is this place?
Reality is thin
in the Netherrealm.
It is a place where nightmares
walk and hunt.
But dreams
can be harnessed too.
If one's will
is strong enough.
Fucking hell, you have got
to try this peach, mate.
You know they try to scare you
with all the talk of
devils and pitchforks
and all that bullshit.
[chuckles]
But I knew Hell would be
a pretty fucking sweet place.
Go on.
Suit yourself.
[Johnny] We were sent
by Lord Raiden.
We need a guide.
Then you have come
to the wrong place.
I am sorry.
Bi-Han's alive.
Or is it Bi-Han.
No, I think it's Bi-Han.
That Sub-Zero fucker.
You know, he killed your
whole family or some shit.
I mean,
they tried to explain to me,
but to be honest,
I wasn't really listening.
[ice crackling]
[breath shudders]
[sinister music playing]
[spits]
[coughing]
[rumbling]
I am Hanzo Hasashi
of the Shirai Ryu
and Hell bends to my command.
[gate rattling]
Keeping the seat warm?
Raiden has sent his
last warriors to Netherrealm.
They are going
after the amulet.
That means there's no one
left to guard Lord Raiden.
If we lose that amulet,
we lose everything.
Shao Kahn will be
stripped of power.
And our empire would fall.
Send me down there.
I will protect the amulet
while you take care of Raiden.
I would think your loyalties
would be with your princess.
Kitana made her choice.
I'm making mine.
[staff thuds]
[screaming]
[shatters]
[energy chiming]
[staff thuds]
[screeching in distance]
[Johnny] How the hell
are we gonna find
the amulet in this place?
Bi-Han is here.
Hanzo Hasashi,
this is not your fight,
old man.
I'm not here for their war.
I'm here for your life.
You might be surprised.
I'm not the same man
you killed.
I belong to the shadows now.
And they belong to me.
[Sonya] Looks like
we're the main event.
Let's kill this fucker.
[thrilling music playing]
[Shao Kahn]
Just two more deaths
and then Earthrealm
belongs to me.
[gong tolls]
[growls]
Kano!
[Kano] Oi, where are you going?
This one's got the amulet.
[blades slashing]
[grunts]
[Kano screams]
[blades slashing]
[Scorpion]
Vengeance will be mine.
[yells]
Kano!
Now would be a good time
to use those powers, mate.
What powers?
Are you shitting me?
You don't have any powers?
Just incredibly handsome.
Oh, we're fucked.
[straining] Grab it!
[Johnny] I got it.
How do we destroy it?
Well fucked if I know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
Mate, I found it for you.
Do I have to do everything?
But this is your plan.
Don't talk to me like that.
Why don't you check
the instructions on the back?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Oh, here we go. Look.
One ring to rule them all.
-One ring to go fuck yourself!
-[laughs sarcastically]
Why don't you
leave the jokes to me?
You can stick to being a cunt.
Well, run!
[grunts]
[screams]
[Kano groans]
[screaming]
[weapon clangs]
-[weapon clangs]
-[Sonya groans]
-[screams]
[grunts]
[Liu Kang]
I am the one you want.
[blades slashing]
[tense music playing]
[straining]
[yelps]
Ah, fuck!
[blades clanging]
[Scorpion grunts]
[Bi-Han grunts]
[Shao Kahn grunts]
[punches]
[Liu Kang straining]
[yells]
[gasps]
[Liu Kang]
I finally understand.
[Shao Kahn growls]
Raiden told me
I am not the chosen one.
Your death belongs to another.
[yells]
My journey is to
bring back Kung Lao.
This is not the end.
It is only the beginning.
[chains shatter]
Fight.
[laughing]
Congratulations, daughter.
We just won.
Earthrealm is ours.
No.
One fighter still remains.
I renounce Outworld.
I renounce your legacy
of pain and cruelty.
I renounce you!
Today I fight for Earthrealm!
[people murmuring]
[heroic music playing]
[people cheering]
-So be it.
-[gong tolls]
[screams]
[blades slicing]
[Shao Kahn yells]
[Kano grunting]
[thrilling music playing]
[pants]
[Bi-Han] The amulet.
Never!
[grunts]
-[blades slashing]
-[Scorpion grunting]
Get over here!
[Kitana grunts]
[panting]
[Kitana screams]
-[grunts]
-[Kitana groans]
[sinister music playing]
[screaming]
Hello, sunshine.
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
With fire, be cleansed.
[roars]
[Raiden] Johnny Cage.
[grunting weakly]
[wincing]
[Raiden] There are eight
billion people on this planet
and yet the gods chose you.
[breathes heavily]
You want to know my power?
[Shao Kahn] It doesn't
have to end like this.
You do not have to die.
One of us does.
[heroic music playing]
For the first time
in my life,
I am Johnny fucking Cage.
[Kitana screams]
[crackling]
[Kitana yells]
No.
You should be dead.
And you should be running.
[Raiden grunts]
[breath trembling]
[Shao Kahn] No.
[Kitana screams]
[both grunting]
[screams]
[choking]
Weak. Just like your father.
[sentimental music playing]
[Jerrod] Be strong, Kitana.
[gasps]
[Kitana grunts]
[dramatic choral music playing]
It's time for them to see you
for what you really are.
[Kitana yells]
Mortal.
[screaming]
[whirring]
[indistinct chatter]
Stop. No.
Please stand. Stand. Please.
We are proud Edenians.
We do not kneel.
[woman chanting]
Kitana, our queen!
[citizens chanting]
[continues chanting]
[triumphant music playing]
[Johnny] You want to know
what makes a hero?
[sweeping music playing]
It's not destiny.
It's not something
you're born with.
It's discovering that
sometimes
even one small light
is enough to hold back
the darkness.
It's facing
unimaginable loss...
and finding peace
on the other side.
It's lifting up
the ones you love knowing...
that they'll be there
to catch you when you fall.
It's searching
for greatness,
then realizing you've had it
in you this entire time.
I say all of this to Raiden
and he looks at me
and he says...
[imitating Raiden] "You have
taught us so much, Mr. Cage.
Thank you. Thank you
for sharing your wisdom."
And you know what I tell him?
What did you say?
I said,
"That ain't no wisdom, bub.
That's perspective."
[children laugh]
[Raiden] Strange.
That is not how I remember it.
Oh. Yo.
I was just telling these guys
how we saved
all the realms, together.
Oh.
[Johnny] All right. Look...
I may have taken one or two
creative liberties.
Behold!
The human female you rescued
from the pit of spikes.
Seriously?
Two or three
creative liberties.
You know,
I've got to give it to you,
I thought you'd go
running back to Hollywood
first chance you got.
I made a promise
to these guys.
Hollywood can wait.
[portal whooshing]
[Johnny] Oh, shit.
Tell me there's not
another tournament.
No. Outworld
has been defeated.
Earthrealm has been saved.
So, uh, what the fuck
are you doing here?
We have lost far too many
of our champions.
It's time to bring them home.
[lightning crackles]
Someone order a Necromancer?
He might look like
Voldemort's nut sack,
but trust me, we're gonna
need this fucker.
Hey, g'day, Blondie.
Long time no see.
You ready
for your next lesson?
For the glory
of Johnny Fucking Cage.
[Baraka grunts]
Let's go get our friends.
Then we kill Kano.
Yeah. Good.
[heroic music playing]
[crackles]
["Techno Syndrome"
by The Immortals playing]
[announcer]
♪ Mortal Kombat! ♪
♪ Fight! ♪
♪ Test your might ♪
♪ Mortal Kombat! ♪
♪ Excellent! ♪
[Scorpion]
♪ Get over here! ♪
[announcer]
♪ Mortal Kombat! ♪
♪ Finish him! ♪
♪ Johnny Cage ♪
♪ Kitana ♪
♪ Sonya ♪
♪ Kano ♪
♪ Shao Kahn ♪
♪ Excellent! ♪
♪ Liu Kang ♪
♪ Jax ♪
♪ Fight! ♪
♪ Jade ♪
♪ Cole Young ♪
♪ Kung Lao ♪
♪ Quan Chi ♪
♪ Shang Tsung ♪
♪ Raiden ♪
♪ Bi-Han ♪
♪ Fight! ♪
♪ Scorpion ♪
♪ Flawless Victory! ♪
♪ Mortal Kombat! ♪
[song ends]
[dramatic music playing]