( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
What? You're seeing a guy?
Grandpa.
When he held your hand,
did your heart race?
It didn't... race exactly.
It was more like a jolt.
I just can't write like this.
"Saeng Karun Foundation."
Get those out.
A tomato does its job in your mouth.
Not in your shirt pocket.
Bat those eyes all you want,
I'm not budging.
Eat them.
Eat.
I told you many times
to drink water slowly.
Okay.
Hey, Deu's running away.
Hey.
Get him.
Stop. Stop running.
I used to run track, you know?
Get back and finish your breakfast.
You don't have to live up to
your name, Deu (stubborn).
Now. Back to your tomato.
No. I'm not eating it.
Fine. Until you do...
we're staying right here.
I really hate tomatoes, okay?
They smell and look gross.
Like little monsters.
How could anyone eat these?
You never know until you try.
You might like it.
I won't.
Just thinking about it... yuck.
Hmm?
Aw, don't make that face at food.
It's rude.
Alright, no tomato, no soccer today.
Oh, no, Grandpa.
Then eat them.
I won't.
Then, no soccer.
I'll save them for you.
Whenever you eat them,
you can do soccer. Okay?
So mean.
Grandpa, Auntie Mart,
and Auntie Oui
should have things
you don't want to do.
How would you feel
if you were forced to?
Grandpa, Auntie Mart,
and Auntie Oui
should have things
you don't want to do.
How would you feel
if you were forced to?
Thick...
lips...
pressed...
down...
on...
thin lips...
so...
gently...
Phuri, I've done my market research.
Writing a BL novel
shouldn't be too hard.
Are you actually going to do it?
Mm.
I think you're on the right track.
I hope to read your work soon.
But I could use some advice.
What direction should I write in?
Honestly, any direction works.
Mafia, period drama,
even reincarnation.
But the real key is this.
What's that?
At my publisher,
stories with NC scenes
sell exceptionally well.
What does NC mean?
NC stands for No Children.
Content not suitable for kids.
Put plainly, it's 18+ material, sir.
18+
Whew.
"Principal and interest:
12.5 million and change."
Fine.
If writing NC scenes
is what it takes...
then I'll die doing it.
Let's go.
Ugh.
Save, quick question.
Do you know how...
two guys actually... do it?
Grandpa.
Great-grandma could hear.
Nah.
Maybe reciting prayers in her head.
Just answer.
I need to go write this.
One second.
Huh.
Great-grandma...
listen to the music, okay?
I don't know. I've never done it.
Should I go try it?
No, no. I just can't
get this scene out.
Been stuck on it
since last night.
Then come here.
Here.
I've downloaded onto your phone
the 18+ scenes from BL series.
Have a look.
Here...
Headphones.
So it's not awkward.
Hmm. Much appreciated.
- Want me to watch with you?
- No need.
Holler if you need anything.
- Phi Guy.
Phi Guy.
Hi, good morning.
Going live with more
ship content today?
I'm not here to sell the ship.
I'm here to sell sweets.
Well... you can sell sweets
or the ship at the same time
because you two are...
Are what?
A couple.
You wanted to hear that, right?
Happy now?
Get out of here.
Mm-hmm.
Sanae Chan sweets,
grab them now, ladies.
Order now before they're gone.
Miss the sweets, miss the moment.
"Are you two a couple?"
Um... the sweets...
can be kept outside for 2 days.
In the fridge, up to 5 days.
If you can't finish them,
pop them in the fridge.
Phi Guy, why are you smiling?
Why are you smiling?
Nothing. My mouth is just tired.
Just stretching it out.
Buy five, get one free.
Grab some before they're gone.
Great for souvenirs or gifts.
Hmm.
Mom.
Oh, why didn't you call me over?
No, no. Get back to your stream.
You need to be careful.
"Wow, my son is such a good boy."
"What a sweet boy, helping his mom."
"Phi Guy is so lucky."
"His hand reached down
to undo the pants,"
"pulled the fly down,"
"and slowly slid the pants off."
Hey.
Khun Phuri, quick question.
Are NC scenes absolutely necessary?
Why? Can't write them?
No, no. Not even a challenge.
Just want to know
whether the readers like them.
Not everyone, really.
Some read these novels for the plot.
But a massive crowd out there
is into NC.
You'll need them to sell the novel.
Short and simple.
And does it need to be a lot?
Every chapter would be ideal.
Every chapter?
Isn't that too much?
Every chapter isn't even enough.
Every scene needs
to be steaming hot.
Hrr.
Hurry up.
- Come on.
- Go.
Stop.
Eaten your tomato yet?
- Get in there.
- Hey.
Pipe.
Pipe, can I join you?
Sure, Phi Save.
And my friend too? He's an athlete.
An athlete, really?
Then I'll have to take you on.
Gladly.
Alright. Let's kick it.
Hey, Deu.
Eat your tomato, then you can play.
Stubborn, huh?
Hey, come on.
Hey, hey. Pass it.
Phi Guy...
Everyone ready?
- Ready.
3, 4.
Guy, go, go.
Guy, you've got this.
Ow.
- Ow.
- Hey.
Ow.
Jedi.
Jedi, you okay?
Oh, wow.
Come here.
Go.
- Go.
- I'll help.
Ow, Phi Save, it stings.
Stinging means
it's killing the germs.
See? Like a laser.
- Pew pew pew.
- Ow, it stings.
Stop playing. I know it stings.
I've had that before.
Well, it's just one second.
I'll be gentle.
Okay?
- Oh, see.
- Ow.
A little jumpy, huh? Relax.
Thought you were
the territorial type.
Why would I be? It's just a bed.
Here, water.
Am I the first one to
sleep in your bed?
No.
Huh... I am the first one.
It's my bed.
Save, can I borrow your laptop?
I need to send something to Jang.
Sure, it's on the desk.
"BL Bedroom Scenes."
"Top Spicy NC Scenes."...
You tired?
Why? Are you...
asking me to do something?
Are you tired or not?
Not really.
Got some juice left.
Wanna stream again?
Yeah, sure.
Let me send Jang this stuff first.
Go ahead. Hurry.
Their bodies...
pressed...
close... together...
intertwined...
as if...
they were...
one.
Ugh.
Come in.
How's it going, Grandpa?
I think my brain is going... dead.
Don't go dead yet.
You haven't finished it.
Well, anything else you need?
A technique or a secret
that helps with writing NC scenes?
Here you go.
See? "Write NC that Hits the Spot."
"Write That Insatiable NC Scenes."
And this is
"Complete NC Vocab Cheat Sheet."
They thought of everything.
That's right.
- Here, I'll save them for you.
- Mm-hmm.
So you can jump to them easily.
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
There.
Alright then.
This should...
get the words flowing again.
Hmph.
How go is it, Dad?
Save said you've been
having trouble writing.
Who, me? I've been writing a lot.
- Is that right?
- Mm-hmm.
Good, good.
Heading out, Dad?
What are you doing here?
Oh, Sun came to visit.
Hmph.
You never showed up
without a reason.
This is my home too.
Why couldn't I come?
Hey...
Hey, Sun's got a point.
Dad.
Well, try to relax.
He saw us sell sweets
on live streams.
He's suggesting we consign them
at his friend's cafe.
- This place, Dad.
- Mm-hmm.
It's not far from here.
I've already talked to them.
Just need to work out the details.
That's a good idea.
Another income for the household.
Yes, Father.
Thank you so much, Sun.
Phi Mart, these here...
are other cafes near us
that take consignments.
I'll pull together
about ten of them.
I'll send them to you.
Pick the ones you like.
Okay, great.
I really appreciate this.
I know you're very busy,
and thanks for your help.
It's nothing, Phi Mart.
Ahem.
Ouch, Dad.
He is trying to help.
Phi Sorn, go contact the cafe today.
Wait, why me?
Well, someone has to
make the products.
Since Save and Guy helped us,
I can barely keep up.
Can we go together
after you're done for the day?
If you don't move fast and
someone else gets them first,
don't blame me.
- Well...
- Yeah, Phi Sorn. Go.
It's simple. Just dropping off goods
for consignment.
Either that or you make the goods.
Can you do it?
Well.
Stop hemming and hawing.
Start making yourself useful.
Hi there.
This is our vacuum cleaner.
Whisper quiet, guaranteed.
Switch it on and it won't
make a sound.
Here, let me show you.
- Not interested.
- Ah... just one sec.
Hey, wait. What are you doing?
Right here.
- Easy, easy.
- Let me show you.
- Plug it in, turn it on.
- No.
For your dog, it picks up pet hair
like a dream.
This is just level one.
- Oh, sorry. Let me turn it off.
- Get out, out.
It's off.
Get out of here now.
I'm not buying.
I'm so sorry.
Our water purifier runs
an RO filtration system.
High-grade membrane filtration.
Go, go. Not interested.
Uh. The water from our purifier
does wonders for your health.
For someone your age,
the more you drink, the better.
You'll live to see
your grandkids grow up.
You like that now, don't you, sir?
Which model are you interested in?
We've got plenty of options.
Alright, stand here.
I said I'm not buying anything.
This is the third time this week.
Get out.
Don't show your face here again.
Not going?
Ow, ow. Okay, I'm going.
Hello, Dad.
Well.
What happened to you?
You're soaking wet.
It was... hot out, Dad.
I splashed some water on my face.
How did you do today? Good sales?
Zero.
Dad, I don't think
this line of work is for me.
Already? Salesman is the easiest job
there is.
If you can't even manage this,
how will you make a living?
Easy, he said.
"Quick tips for writing NC
as a beginner."
"The most important thing
is vivid description."
"Expressions, body language,
touch, sensation."
"So readers can picture it
all in their heads."
A face lost in a dream,
lips crushed and bruised,
flushed red,
skin...
slick with sweat
grinding together
until warmth builds
deep in the core.
Hmm. Let me dial it up a notch.
A face contorted
in unbearable agony.
Lips crushed until they split
with the force
of raw rage.
The taste of blood
seeping
on the tip of the tongue
sends desire surging,
flooding every inch.
Uhm-mm. Is this too intense?
See. I can't take it anymore.
Easy. Tell me what happened.
I'm listening.
He and his mom are so sweet.
How about that?
So sweet that he's always
on my mind.
I can't wait to be his.
I don't want to. Understand?
Totally. Who wants to wait?
Right? And I found that
he's been watching NC clips.
Save might be looking to...
take things further, right?
Honestly, based on
what you've said,
he sounds like a real catch.
He probably has people lining up.
Better make a move
before someone else does.
Come on, dude.
You said nothing was going on.
What's not going on?
Well, check this out.
We watched your livestream.
Blushing and giggling,
what was that about?
Heh.
- Say something. We're your friends.
- Yeah.
Read my lips.
I'm doing it for the money.
Guy and I, there's nothing real.
People are just shipping us.
Are you blushing?
Your cheeks are red too.
I'm not blushing.
Know any ships that
actually make it?
Hey.
Save.
Hey, I think while we're at school,
we should keep our distance.
Why?
Pheem, Jang, and Ron keep
teasing me, and it's getting old.
What are they saying?
That you're my boyfriend.
"You can ramp up
the mood with dialogue."
"Some readers love sound cues,
like..."
"Umm... Ahh."
"Owh..."
Easy.
I'll pop those in.
Ooh.
Awh.
Does this actually work?
Ugh.
Flat.
Huh. This is hopeless.
Ugh.
People keep eavesdropping.
Hurry. We're here.
Yeah, come on.
Wait till we're inside.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hey, really.
The lead in that series is awesome.
- Total green flag.
- Which one?
- What series?
- Tell us.
Can't remember the title,
but I saved it. One sec.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
- Come on.
- Hey.
Major green flag alert.
- What is it?
- What?
Don't tell me it's gone.
- Uh oh.
- Hey.
Is your phone at school?
You forgot your phone?
Oh, no.
Maybe it's still in the car?
You left it in the car.
Thanks, Deu.
Here it is.
- Hey, I've seen this one.
- Hey, me too.
- But I haven't read it yet.
- Neither have I.
You have to read it.
- Let's go.
- Really?
During our duty shift?
Nobody will see us.
- Let's go. Quickly.
- We'll read it together.
Redder than a tomato.
Haha.
You okay, Deu? Hot?
No, I'm fine.
Ready to eat? Come on.
Hmph.
I'm back.
How'd it go? Did they take them?
It's okay.
Tomorrow, you go to other shops.
One will say yes eventually.
Okay.
Huh.
Grandpa.
Ever heard of paperless?
Why not write on the computer?
Not for me.
Hey.
Grandpa, use the whole page.
Why is this so hard?
You can do it. Just imagine them
as a man and woman.
The gender isn't the problem.
It's that NC stuff.
Whatever I write feels forced.
I'm trying for something subtle,
less graphic.
I'm not there yet.
You know
what the market wants, right?
Your readers might not
find it forced at all.
It's got no artistry.
Then give it some.
You can do it.
Honestly, I think you're just
not open to it yet.
Once you open your mind,
the words will come.
Give it a shot.
The money's right there
in front of you.
You've got this.
Why the look?
Grandpa...
How did you get here?
You wanted to see me, didn't you?
I wanted to apologize for...
not being able to take care
of Saeng Karun well enough.
Don't blame yourself.
Everything has its causes.
So how's the BL novel coming along?
Not that good, I'm afraid.
Giving up already?
Not at all.
Sak...
sometimes we must push through
and do things we don't enjoy.
If we see the benefit in it,
we just carry on
and do what we must.
I know that, sir.
But...
Take a look at this, Grandpa.
If you were the one writing this,
could you live with it?
Of course. It's perfectly normal.
Grandpa.
This sort of thing
has been around forever.
Look at it as
love between two people.
Sak.
Sometimes we must push through
and do things we don't enjoy.
But if we see the benefit in it,
we just carry on
and do what we must.
Hmph.
Alright.
Fine.
Thick skin. No shame.
For all of us at Saeng Karun.
Hmph.
Hello, what can I get for you?
Um...
Hmm...
Americano, please.
Of course.
Hmph.
"Incoming: 1."
"Mart: I'm waiting for good news."
Here you go.
Um...
Hi, can I get you anything else?
Um, another Americano, please.
Not a single shop will take it?
No, Dad.
Why not?
Her sweets are genuinely good.
Did you show them our online channel
to show how well we sell?
I did, but...
they weren't interested.
Okay. It's fine.
We'll try other shops tomorrow.
Okay.
Hey.
Tell your wife to take a break.
She's working hard.
Um... can I help?
I can do it.
While the kids are at school,
Auntie Oui helps a lot.
Take some rest.
No. These must get done.
Ow.
- Hey, hey.
- Ouch.
- I knew it.
- Mart.
- Look.
- Ow.
Take her to the doctor.
This is the second time today.
Whew.
Sorn, take her to the doctor.
Yes, yes.
Hold down the fort, Auntie Oui.
Got it. Got it.
Easy now.
Ow.
Ouch.
Ugh.
Does it hurt here?
Yes, Doctor.
Please lie on your back.
Any numbness or
trouble with bladder control?
No.
You have inflammation
of the back muscles.
The bones and nerves are fine.
Can I still make sweets?
I'd recommend resting for now.
If you keep lifting heavy things
or straining those muscles,
the inflammation will get worse.
- But...
- Listen to the doctor.
How am I supposed to stop?
People have already paid
for their orders.
We have to hold up our end.
The doctor says to stop.
So you stop.
So, what's the treatment?
I'll prescribe medication
and a topical cream
to reduce the inflammation,
combined with complete rest
of that muscle group.
Slowly. Slowly.
Easy. Easy.
Come here. This way.
- Here.
- Ow.
Step down.
Slowly.
Oh... ugh.
Okay, shift left a little.
Shift left.
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
Come here.
I'm going to carry you.
Oh, no, no. What are you doing?
I don't need that. I can still walk.
- Oh really?
- Yes.
Then your arm.
That back of yours
would give out too.
Give me your hand.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Hmm.
Ow.
Hold this. Hold.
Take your time. No rush.
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
Huh.
- Mart.
- Hmm?
You've been running yourself
into the ground.
Just rest, okay?
What's with you,
going all sentimental?
Listen. Don't worry about a thing.
I'll handle the consignment.
Mom.
Aw, aw. Easy.
Hmm.
I told you not to lift heavy things.
Please don't scold a sick person.
- Mom.
- Hmm?
Does it hurt anywhere?
I'll give you a massage.
Save.
Thanks so much
for picking up the kids.
Mm-hmm.
Are you holding up?
Don't go coming down
with something too.
Hmm. I'm fine.
Look after Mom, will you?
I'll be right in.
Huh.
Let's go.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Um, well, here's the thing.
It's just that...
I'd like to consign
some sweets here.
Who should I talk to, please?
Hang in there.
Just hang in there.
Phi Save.
My friend wants to know...
if you're single.
Um.
Your friend... or you?
Puean (friend).
My name is Puean.
I'm single.
Hmm?
Ahem.
Here you go. Enjoy.
Thanks.
- Must be smooth like this. See?
- Hey.
The doctor told you to rest.
- Heh.
- Hmm?
Phi Sorn, how did it go?
Any shops take it?
Huh.
Again?
It's okay.
We'll keep streaming for now.
Three shops agreed to
carry our sweets.
- What?
- Are you serious?
- Of course.
Hey.
Sorn, don't mess around.
I'm not messing around.
They really took us in.
- Yay.
- Alright.
- Oh, aww.
- Hey, easy. Sit down.
Ow... hehe. I got carried away.
I'll help handle the orders
going to those shops.
- Dad.
- Hmm?
I made it.
It's nothing.
Heh.
- Okay.
- Come here.
My turn now.
Here.
It's good. You want some?
What's up? You swallowed a lemon?
Did that guy flirt with you?
Probably.
What do you think?
Think about what?
Do you like him?
Don't tell me you're jealous.
What if I am?
Why would you be jealous?
Don't I have the right to be?
Come on. It was just for fun.
Come on. Let's go home.
If I asked to make it official now,
what are the odds he'd say yes?
99.9 percent.
Save.
Will you be my boyfriend?
Sorry?
Hey...
thanks a lot for...
asking me that.
But I'm not ready.
Yeah, I kind of figured.
I braced myself for it.
But you still asked anyway.
Better than not asking, right?
You're not upset with me, right?
Why would I be?
See, you're so hard to read.
I just wanted to try my luck.
And?
Shot down.
When the time is right,
I'll let you know.
Okay, then I'll just keep asking.
Won't you get tired of it?
By all means. If you can take it.
Save.
See? You can eat them.
Won't kill you.
It's actually good, Deu. Refreshing.
Stop lying. Not buying it.
Fine. No tomato, no soccer.
We need backup, Deu.
If we lose to Phi Guy,
Saeng Karun's pride goes with it.
Fine, don't eat it then.
Stay off the field
for the rest of your life, Deu.
Fine, I won't play then.
I won't forget
you ditched your friends, Deu.
You're not my friend.
Pipe.
Can we play with you today?
What? For real?
Yeah, yesterday the teacher told us
about female soccers.
Made me want to try it.
I'll do soccer now, sir.
Snow, let's go.
- Pipe, let me play.
- Snow, you've got this.
You ate your tomato?
Yeah, I did.
Cool.
Snow, you've got this.
Deu, over here.
Snow, you can do it.
Go, Snow.
Snow, go, go.
- Yay.
- Hooray.
So how was the tomato?
Disgusting, Grandpa.
But...
But what?
Not as bad as I thought.
I'll live with it.
Snow, let's do it.
Three shops agreed to
carry our sweets.
- What?
- Are you serious?
- Of course.
I made it.
Disgusting, Grandpa. But...
But what?
But not as bad as I thought.
I'll live with it.
Stories with NC scenes
sell exceptionally well.
Once you open your mind,
the words will come.
The money's right there
in front of you.
Principal and interest
come to 12,508,649.75 baht.
Sometimes we must push through
and do things we don't enjoy.
Hmph.
Accounts over 180 days past due
will be subject to legal action.
I'm not afraid.
Every scene needs
to be steaming hot.
I am that dang good.
Hm... hm.
Muahaha.
I ain't writing anymore.
Hngh. Hngh.
At his age, he doesn't need to work.
Just sit around and that's it.
Right. He can barely even walk now.
You promised Khun Tiad, right?
Don't you feel guilty?
I said I'm done. I quit.
You can go now.
We've come as far as we can.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?