( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
FIVE HOURS BEFORE THE FLIGHT
You like Luwak coffee, Ms. Mo?
Yes, I do.
I enjoy it as a drip brew sometimes.
What about you?
I used to,
until a business trip
to Bali three years ago.
I went for a raw materials survey
and caught the first flight back.
Why?
It just rubbed me the wrong way.
That expensive coffee
is made from cat poop, after all.
I couldn't drink it
once I saw it for myself.
The same applies here.
I could have dated you in ignorance,
but the truth won't allow it now, you see.
It sounds like you're upset.
Marriage is a lifelong business.
Shouldn't trust be paramount?
You should pay for the coffee.
Let's call it a damages settlement.
-Hold on.
-Right.
Just a heads up.
You should go somewhere else for lunch.
I have a blind date
on the second floor in ten minutes.
I'm all about efficiency,
so I figured I'd kill two birds
with one stone.
Don't be too offended.
Se-gye!
That blind date
is with me.
Give me a chance to apologize properly.
What's going on here?
I fail to see why you must insist
on this union.
Mochang's value-driven approach
and Chail's formidable tech assets
would make a perfectly synergistic pair.
When the need is this great,
even broken trust might be
worth rebuilding.
You've never lost, have you?
No. I don't recall
any losses in particular.
You've never known defeat or loss.
Life isn't particularly easy,
but it's not too hard either.
Even so, you're only satisfied
when you get what you need.
Is that a bad thing?
Not necessarily.
I can't stand people who don't know jack,
meddle in everything,
and insist on wallowing
in their entitlement.
Since it appears you're a woman
who shares my values,
I guess we can skip
the needless mind games and runaround.
You're toxic, like poison.
Cha Se-gye!
Have you gone mad?
Cha Se-gye! Open your eyes!
I can't stand people who don't know jack,
meddle in everything…
and insist on wallowing
in their entitlement.
-Cha Se-gye, no!
-One, two, three!
Oh no…
Since it appears you're a woman
who shares my values,
I guess we can skip
the needless mind games and runaround.
Passengers,
we will soon be arriving
at Jeju International Airport.
Please fasten your seatbelts…
No feelings, my foot.
EPISODE 6
ONE MAGICAL NIGHT
All white walls
and nothing but white everywhere…
Could this be…
Have I finally…
crossed over to the afterlife?
I see no hellfire.
No King of Hell either.
Paradise?
My goodness!
No, I am in hell.
Oh no…
Hey. Are you awake?
I see I am still alive.
Man, you really scared me.
Who gets electrocuted on a plane?
Talk about a hardcore first day.
We are still alive, so cease your fussing.
What of Cha Se-gye?
What has become of Cha Se-gye?
Your pre-flight medication
didn't contain the substance,
but your blood test indicates
digitoxin poisoning,
resulting in acute cardiac arrest.
Is that a poison?
It is a digitalis-extracted compound
primarily used as a cardiac stimulant.
It's used to treat heart failure,
arrhythmia, and epilepsy.
We've administered the antidote,
so just rest up for a day,
and you should be able to resume
daily activities without any issue.
What about…
What about her?
-Is she okay?
-Who exactly?
A woman should've been brought in with me.
Shin Seo-ri.
I'll look into it and let you know.
Hold on.
Oh my gosh.
What?
They're doing a CT, an MRI,
and even drawing blood?
Blood?
You cannot have my blood!
Who knows what you will use it for?
We'll use it for your health checkup.
She is something else.
We just had the first-class passengers
sign notarized NDAs,
and their compensation
has been paid out.
Good thing weekday flights are quiet.
We're bleeding money.
Sir, you should request
a proper police investigation.
It's not just rumors anymore.
They bribed a nurse to drug you this time.
You were in real danger.
For someone in my position,
this kind of threat is all too common.
I can't be terrified every time.
The moment I show my fear,
it's game over for me.
Even so, some people need to know.
Hiding this even from your doctor friend--
Isn't that a given?
He could've been bought off.
Lead with suspicion.
By that logic,
isn't Ms. Shin Seo-ri the most suspicious?
Shin Seo-ri?
-What about her?
-Just think about it.
You two met over a fender bender,
then came an assault, investor problems,
a police summons,
and now corporate shakedown rumors.
It looks like she straight-up brought
calamity into your life.
I'll give you the fender bender,
but the rest has
absolutely nothing to do with her.
Mr. Son.
Yes, sir.
You are an executive aide.
Your job is to deliver the facts.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
I guess I'm just the big old jerk
in this scenario.
Unbelievable.
What a stand-up guy he is.
They said there's
nothing seriously wrong with her.
She's good to go after an IV drip.
Must have been quite the shock
on your first day.
It's Gwang-nam, right?
I heard you two are close, like siblings.
Please take good care of her.
I'll head down
after my meetings in Seoul.
I think there's been
a huge misunderstanding,
so let me clear it up right now.
We are not like siblings at all.
It's strictly business between us.
And I'm not staying long.
It's just a temp job
until I get a real one.
You should start looking
for a replacement right away.
Damn it.
Leave it to her
to hire someone exactly like her.
Why? What did her manager say?
He said he's just a temp
and told me to replace him.
He's really drawing
a bold line in the sand.
Birds of a feather flock together.
Can you blame him?
Look at who he works for.
I wondered why the pushover
suddenly grew a spine.
Turns out there was a good reason.
What reason?
It looked like
that loser hooked a rich boyfriend.
Although I'm not sure if he's
a boyfriend or a sugar daddy.
Okay.
You're good to proceed
with the ad campaign now.
I'm off.
What blind idiot would go for her?
My ideal type?
A man like Hugh Grant in Notting Hill.
He's practically every woman's dream.
Yoon Ji-hyo's manager is so lucky.
He gets paid to go
to a free fan meeting every day.
If I were her manager,
I'd totally work for free.
They'll all recognize you in Jeju.
Maybe I could look into flights
to Taiwan or Japan
that leave today instead?
Everyone will recognize you in Jeju.
Taiwan is where that jerk Gong Tae-woo
and I celebrated our first anniversary.
Japan is where we had
that Christmas birthday event.
Don't worry.
I rented out
an entire private resort anyway.
I won't be running into anyone there.
HALLA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Listen here.
Where is the one named Cha Se-gye?
How can I help you?
I have come to see him.
Lead the way.
What's with her tone…
Miss, may I have your name first?
Why do you need my name?
I don't think you should be
wandering alone just yet.
Don't go anywhere.
Just stay put for now.
How dare you!
You have yet to answer my question.
Is this the psych ward?
-Listen here, I have a question.
-Yes?
Do you know where the one named
Cha Se-gye is convalescing?
Pardon me? "Convalescing"?
Miss, do you happen to remember
which room you're in?
Is giving nonsensical answers
the physicians' specialty at this clinic?
Everybody refuses to answer my questions.
Just stay right here.
Why do you all keep telling me
to stay still like a sack of grain!
Shin Seo-ri.
The media response to the groundbreaking
of Songjin Resort has been positive.
Let's wrap up
the foundation work this year.
Once it's completed in 2029,
I trust Chail Food will handle
the F&amp;B operations well.
Thanks to that, we're finally seeing
some green after a long time.
The shareholders are very pleased.
Thanks to Mun-do,
you can finally hold your head up
in front of your shareholders.
Ever since the accounting fraud
sent their stock tanking,
they've been absolutely miserable.
Without even lifting a finger.
It's a total win-win.
CHA SE-GYE FAINTS ON FLIGHT TO JEJU
RECOVERING IN JEJU HOSPITAL
Are you truly all right?
Stop fussing. You're giving me a headache.
You must truly be okay after all
if you're still able to be this cranky.
I'm not okay at all, you clueless woman.
Why not just stay out of the way?
I very nearly died thanks to you.
People do not die that easily.
I speak from extensive experience
with near-death events.
The thread of life is
surprisingly tough, like steel.
Unless your time has come,
it does not snap easily.
Spare me the cheap philosophy.
Why are you here?
I am not here for you.
I was just passing through.
The VIP ward is nowhere
near the first-floor ER.
There's no way
you were just passing through.
Looks like you were
pretty worried about me.
Worried?
Of course I was worried.
If the money man goes down,
my prospects naturally go down with him.
I had no choice but to worry.
That's enough.
Spare me your capitalist concerns.
There you are, Mr. Cha.
We've forwarded the detailed results
to your primary physician,
so you may be discharged immediately
as requested.
Thank you.
And regarding that patient
you asked about earlier…
Hold on. You go in here for a second.
Why?
Don't argue. Just go.
-Please continue.
-According to the results,
Ms. Shin Seo-ri has
no major health issues.
Nothing to worry about.
-I see.
-Yes. Take care.
Goodness me.
That flying palanquin was split
into beggar and commoner sections.
It seems this clinic is no different.
My goodness. It is so big.
FOR A FLIRTY MOOD
There.
Cha Se-gye.
I thought your complexion
had gone from deathly to radiant.
-Now I see why.
-What is it now?
This room is an absolute palace.
We're both patients,
yet they have me cooped up in a shoebox.
This room has everything.
Did you think we were on the same level?
Just look at the size of that TV.
And the sound quality is superb!
Hey, that's too loud. Turn it down.
Let me enjoy this palace too!
-Not a chance.
-Hand it over, now!
Try to take it.
-What's wrong with you?
-Come on!
Don't use force. Hey, wait a minute.
We're going to fall. Hold on…
Hey.
-Let me watch some TV too!
-Hey!
Stop that.
Hey!
WARMTH OF THE CANOLA FLOWER FIELD
Oh my.
I think I have the wrong room…
No, I just have terrible timing.
No.
It's not what it looks like.
I definitely knocked,
but not hard enough.
Since you hate loud noises so much,
I just knocked lightly like I always do.
If I had known a lady…
I mean, Ms. Shin Seo-ri was here,
I should've knocked harder. Darn it.
What are you talking about?
This was… just an accident.
It was like… a car accident.
Yes… Right.
As the old proverb goes,
"Do not take your shoes off
in a cucumber patch, and do not adjust
your hat string under a pear tree."
It looks suspicious
to any onlooker, but this is…
just a coincidence.
Save the rambling explanation.
You're just making it weirder.
Was I?
I was trying my best.
I'll come back later.
-Don't go!
-Freeze!
Damn it.
That nearly scared me to death.
That wicked creature.
Is it all done?
I made sure to keep
the passengers quiet.
And your discharge is all sorted.
Good work.
I'll get changed and head out,
so be on standby.
Sir, don't you think
you should stay a day
and see how you feel?
My test results are fine.
Even if they weren't,
discharge is unavoidable.
If we throw
health scare rumors into the mix,
investors will demand
their money back before the launch.
That's true.
What about the other thing?
After the shareholders' meeting,
President Choi is carrying out
his schedule as planned.
He must've been briefed
on my condition by now.
Perfectly healthy.
So,
you really think
President Choi is behind this?
Who else has the guts
to pull off something like this?
The deepfake,
the attack, the rumors…
And most importantly,
the Kaiserman private equity fund.
All evidence points to him.
He doesn't even seem to be hiding it.
I'm not sure if he's just confident…
or if he has a massive ego.
Good work, everyone.
Mr. Cha had the airline
and all the passengers
sign notarized NDAs.
Should we offer to pay the penalty
if they talk to us?
Just make contact for now.
We don't want needless chatter
tanking the group's stock.
Block any related articles.
-For now.
-Just for now?
Cha Se-gye must know by now.
How far I'm willing to go for Chail
and what I'm aiming for.
It's a mental game from here on out.
Whoever backs down first loses.
-You really haven't seen her?
-I haven't.
Where did she go?
I'm about to lose it.
Hey, where did you go without telling me?
Must I report my every move to you?
When a master leaves the premises,
it is the servant's duty
to wait quietly for her return.
You still need to tell me,
so I don't worry.
You were worried
about your money, not me.
Cease your fretting and prepare to leave.
You know our destination, yes?
Discharging already?
I have secured an iron palanquin for us,
so come along.
Iron palanquin?
Mr. Son, what exactly is going on here?
Well, the ad agency must have
booked the whole place.
Turns out they're staying
at the same resort.
They asked for a ride.
This isn't an airport shuttle.
You can't just let anyone ride with us.
Must you be so unyielding?
We can keep you company
on this lonely journey
and fill these empty seats.
Kill two birds with one stone.
I never asked for company.
We should've just rented a car
to avoid this being so awkward.
I do not trust
your palanquin-driving skills,
so hold your tongue.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but can we stop at a rest area?
Already? It hasn't even been five minutes.
Well, I drank a latte on the plane,
and it's making my stomach
rumble like crazy.
You're lactose intolerant.
Why would you drink a latte?
Oh man.
-Lactose intolerance?
-Wait, could this be…
If we throw
health scare rumors into the mix,
investors will demand
their money back before the launch.
"Health scare"?
One collapses backward,
and the other's stomach is rumbling.
Chest pain, fainting,
and now dysentery too.
These sound like the symptoms…
Could it be a plague?
Halt this iron palanquin.
Stop the car right now!
What's wrong now?
-Seo-ri.
-Are you carsick?
I am going to get out now.
Stop the car at once!
-No! Please…
-We can't just stop
in the middle of the road. Just wait.
The plague is far worse
than any tiger or smallpox!
This is tantamount to suicide!
Manager Baek! Open the door!
-Okay.
-Open the door!
-Don't open it.
-Someone help!
Help! It is the plague! The plague!
Someone help me!
It is the plague!
Did you really just throw a fit
in the middle of the road
to save yourself?
I had no other choice.
If not poison, the symptoms matched
the plague perfectly.
What else was I supposed to do?
You hitched a ride, offering "company,"
but I guess a plague changes everything.
You do not know
the true terror of a plague.
Once infected, it spares no one,
be it a king or a commoner.
I see now. So is that why
you maintain such a great distance?
"Hope for the best,
prepare for the worst."
It is always best
to be prepared for anything.
From now on,
I shall do nothing but breathe.
Think of me as a sack of barley,
and pay me no mind.
A plague fighter to a sack of barley.
One hell of a switch in attitude.
Sir, we should get going.
The sun is setting.
For dysentery of unknown cause,
cranesbill is a surefire remedy.
Cranesbill petals have three stripes,
while geraniums have five.
Do not confuse them.
Look at our Joseon-era doctor over here.
Your meddling stretches
as far as the Great Wall.
Why are you nitpicking
every little thing today?
Just because I rejected your affections,
you hound me all damn day?
Oh my goodness.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you trying to broadcast
your rejection of me to the whole world?
Jeez.
You'd better stop.
Let's go.
Get in, hurry.
It might look like nothing special,
but this tree is a handful to maintain.
-You see…
-Father?
Hey.
Hello.
I'm Mo Tae-hee.
She went on a blind date with Se-gye.
The third daughter of the Mochang Group.
-Is that so?
-You must be the second aunt.
Thanks to you, Mochang Woolen
is forever stuck in second place.
Well, latecomers don't have
much of a choice.
Father, did you hear about Se-gye?
Yes.
I was so shocked on my way here.
So, I was thinking we should
ask outsiders to leave
and talk among ourselves.
I heard the news too.
A small incident on the plane.
-An incident?
-Yes.
Fortunately, they handled it quickly
and resumed their schedule.
Se-gye said that?
I was surprised too,
but she came by to reassure me
that it was nothing to worry about.
You must have been
very worried about Se-gye.
Seeing how you rushed right over.
I thought he'd be lonely
growing up without a mother,
but he's lucky to have an aunt like you.
Yes.
I have cleaned up a lot of his messes.
What's this?
I thought you went home.
Hello. You must be the eldest aunt.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Mo Tae-hee.
Okay. Nice to meet you.
May I visit again?
You both seem so lovely.
I'd love to see you more often.
Visiting Jeju Island for work.
Even the sky welcomes me.
Should I report this or not?
The road is quite bumpy. Hold on tight.
She's actually shut up.
Finally, some peace and quiet.
Threatened by an assassin
in broad daylight.
Why are you sprawled out like this?
And he just collapsed,
despite being in perfect health.
Mr. Son.
Try to drive more carefully.
Gosh.
Come on now.
Ms. Shin.
You should be friends with Cha Se-gye.
Is that man wearing the king's face
the poisonous influence in your life,
not mine?
Your luck with people rivals mine.
Jesus, you startled me.
What are you staring at?
Are you absolutely certain
you didn't swallow poison?
Who's being poisoned in the 21st century?
If it isn't a plague or poison,
how does a healthy man--
It's just chronic fatigue. So what?
What good is a man so frail?
Who are you calling frail? I'm…
You have no idea
how much I can squat.
You are all talk.
Look. The ocean.
Well, Mr. Cha's office
won't stop calling me.
I can't keep pretending I'm not home.
When can I stop hiding?
There are no cameras in the lab.
They can't do anything
with just suspicions.
They have no proof.
And there's no way
they can trace the accounts.
Go overseas for a while.
I'll have a place ready for you
when things quiet down.
Thank you.
What should we do?
She looks very anxious.
Wait for the right time
to take care of her quietly.
The world truly has changed.
This island of Tamna was infamous
as a desolate place of exile,
reserved only for the worst traitors
who plotted treason against the throne.
How does this look like an exile site?
It's a paradise resort.
Jeju is too crowded now
to even be a resort.
Maybe some deserted Pacific island
might come close to a retreat.
Yeah.
You might actually get
some rest somewhere like that.
It gives off Mont Saint-Michel vibes.
What? "Monsoon Seashell"?
It's a rocky island
off the coast of Normandy, France.
Is that Mont-whatever
a deserted island too?
No, it only becomes
an island at high tide.
It's pretty nice.
If my new launch is a huge hit,
I'm thinking of buying an island.
A private island retreat
sounds nice, doesn't it?
Forget about your Monsoon Seashells.
I think Tamna is pretty nice already.
Actually, I like it very much.
First time in Jeju?
-Bring it down a notch.
-It is my first time.
It is my first time seeing the ocean.
You live in a country surrounded
by water on three sides,
and this is your first time?
Cha Se-gye.
You should try taking in
a deep breath too.
If I had died without witnessing
this wonderful sight…
it would have been my greatest regret.
SEOGEON ISLAND
JEJU'S ISLAND OF MYSTERY
Korea's very own Miracle of Moses.
The Seogeon Island Sea Parting.
When you need to take a break.
Are you on vacation too?
It's like we read each other's minds.
Korea is full of amazing places.
The sea parts at low tide.
Maybe the Miracle of Moses
was just low tide.
Gosh.
Wait.
There are brine stones here.
-"Brine stone"?
-Brine stone.
As in "pebble."
Wasn't that your nickname?
Gravel? Pebble?
Or something like that.
What an absurd nickname.
Instead of a measly pebble,
I shall be a chunk of rock.
If anyone messes with me,
this chunk of rock
will come crashing down.
Yeah. "Chunk of rock"
suits you better than "pebble."
So salty!
Did you think seawater would be sweet?
Why would you taste that?
I see.
Seawater is quite salty.
I am truly glad to be alive.
The sea dyed by the sunset
is ridiculously beautiful.
You've been going on like some old lady.
What, are you back from the dead?
It is because I am happy.
I am so happy to be alive.
It's Yoon Ji-hyo.
It's a private villa, right?
I heard the security was airtight.
She's pretty, right?
I apologize.
Would you like a tour of the resort?
Or to head straight to your room?
To the room.
Sure. Just give me a moment.
Excuse me, but you can't film here.
-Okay.
-Sorry about that.
Shin Seo-ri?
Cha and his aide?
What a scandal.
Wow.
What do you want for dinner?
I can look for a place.
Since we are by the sea,
let us eat ostrea.
According to the Dongui Bogam,
consuming it refines the skin
and improves one's complexion.
The finest tonic the sea has to offer.
"Ostrea"? Is that a type of meat?
You do not know what ostrea is?
Its white, milky flesh tends
to be quite plump--
Octopus?
No, not that.
It is sweet when grilled,
and as a soup,
the broth is so refreshing.
-Hairtail?
-No!
You can eat the meat
and grind the leftover shells into powder
that can be used to calm a racing heart
and aid a man's nocturnal emissions.
Both food and remedy,
not a single part wasted--
Right. So what is it exactly?
Could it be oysters?
Oysters?
My grandpa used to run an apothecary.
Apothecaries call oysters "ostrea."
Yes, that's it! Oysters. Ostrea.
Just say it normally.
Did we really need to play 20 Questions?
Do you really expect me
to solve all your riddles?
Even if I speak like a fool,
my servant should understand
like a genius.
I can't eat oysters. Bad stomach.
Nobody asked for the servant's opinion.
Who's that?
Shin Seo-ri, that loser, has a boyfriend?
Is that guy Mr. Supercar?
-How about black pork?
-Sounds good.
We are by the sea, so we must eat ostrea.
But he looks way too shabby to own one.
Jeez. Who knew a trip to Tamna
would be so damn exhausting?
Wow, it's so spacious.
The TV is huge too.
-You're late.
-Goodness me.
What took you so long?
Why are you so surprised?
Guilty conscience?
Oh, you must be Seo-ri's manager.
Gwang-nam, right?
Right?
Nice to meet you.
Let's do some good work together.
Oh right. The ad agency said
Mr. Cha's team is staying here as well.
Tell them I'll treat them to dinner.
Yes, ma'am.
Calling to invite them is bad manners.
You must go and tell them in person.
Making me run around like a dog.
Seo-ri, where in the world
did you find a kid like him?
Why are you here unannounced, Ms. Hong?
Where the needle goes, the thread follows.
Why wouldn't I be here for your shoot?
I thought that minx
was your needle, not me.
Ji-hyo is completely drained right now.
She went far away to recharge.
Far away?
Where?
Damn it. There are couples everywhere.
Maybe I should've gone camping?
-Wait.
-He says he just wants to rest.
Okay, I'll pass that on.
Hold on. You have some dust.
-You're good now.
-Thank you.
You have some on your back too.
-Maybe he really is Mr. Supercar?
-Thanks.
Wait, he's coming here.
He's coming right towards me.
What the…
Hello, my name is Baek Gwang-nam.
Excuse me?
Well, it looked like you were on vacation,
so I didn't want to bother you,
but I gathered up the courage
and decided to say hi.
Oh, I see.
I'm a huge fan.
I saw on Insta that you were on vacation,
but I never expected
to run into you like this.
You're a fan of mine?
Yes, a huge fan.
You're really heavenly in person.
An angel on screen too.
Right.
I can't believe this.
Well, do you want to take a selfie?
I'm too nervous for that.
I don't think I could.
Okay.
At least he has a good eye.
Hello, my name is Baek Gwang-nam.
But…
what's with the getup?
Looking so raggedy.
Or maybe it's vintage?
They make a pretty good kimchi broth.
We should've grilled some black pork.
Why are we eating kimchi noodles?
Let me know if you need anything else.
I'll be right on it.
That's enough.
Just toast and be gone. I'm tired.
-Okay. Cheers.
-Cheers.
From now on,
I intend to give this job
everything I have.
Just leave it all to me.
That's nice.
We got this, Jeju Shoot Team!
Have a good night!
What's gotten into him?
He just suddenly decided to stop sulking?
The human mind will forever elude us.
I could not care less.
Anyway, to finish what I was saying.
The concept for this shoot is
"Jeju Goddess."
No.
Is she possessed by the spirit of nudity?
I mean, is she dressed or naked?
That is profoundly vulgar.
That's exactly the point.
Look. Barely there.
Almost see-through. You know?
Look at Greek mythology.
They're all butt-naked
and staring right at you.
Gods have no shame.
That's just how they are.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Our bodies will just rot away
when we die anyway.
We must use our beauty at its peak
to make it worthwhile.
Exactly.
All right. If I am doing this,
I might as well
go all out and show it all off.
That's the spirit.
Cheers.
You look a bit pale, sir.
Yeah. I just didn't sleep well last night.
You should be resting at the hotel.
Why are you out here?
Never mind that. Where's the model?
There…
she is. Ms. Shin Seo-ri.
Hello.
-Hello.
-Hello there.
They weren't kidding.
The clothes really do make the person.
What do you think, Mr. Cha?
Don't you think
that outfit is a bit too much?
You must be kidding, Mr. Cha.
She looks absolutely gorgeous.
Seo-ri, maybe we can try
moving around a bit. Yeah.
Change her outfit. Right now.
-Please go change.
-Let's go change.
The design is too haute couture. Next.
We'll be right back.
And this one is too prêt-à-porter.
Swap.
I mean,
what's up with all these clothes?
I don't even know where to look.
Am I some mutt you are trying to train?
-Your eyes are the issue.
-Come on.
Are your eyes possessed or something?
-Stop it.
-Let go of me! Why, that little…
Hold on.
-Manager Baek!
-No, let's not do that.
Come on, Mr. Cha.
The marketing team signed off
on the final concept,
and you personally approved these outfits.
You can't just change them suddenly.
The photos didn't show the fabric quality.
This is an ad campaign,
not a personal photo shoot.
The model stands out
way too much right now.
She doesn't stand out that much.
Her very being stands out too much.
The outfit suits the location well.
Screw the location.
She's the only thing I can see right now!
It looks fine. What's wrong with him?
Why can't he just approve it?
Replace all the outfits
and get my approval again.
I'm the advertiser,
so you should meet my needs.
Yes, sir.
Why are my legs so numb?
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable…
Ms. An Seong-hui, are you home?
Ms. An Seong-hui?
I'm from Biojei.
Ms. An Seong-hui, are you home?
Ms. An Seong-hui?
We handled the nurse as instructed.
How did Cha Se-gye react?
Without proof, it seems he decided
to stick to his schedule.
Word from the set is a bit strange.
He began interfering heavily
before shooting even began,
causing some friction.
He kept changing the model's outfits,
upsetting the crew.
Changing outfits?
How amusing.
It seems
the time has come.
Excuse me,
can I ask you for a little help?
My grandson got lost.
Your grandson?
I am not so meddlesome that I would go
searching for some stranger's kid.
I'll make it worth your while.
Here. This is licorice taffy.
Boiled with honey for three days.
I'll give you this too.
NODO MANAGER BAEK GWANG-NAM
WE DISCOVERED THE QUEEN OF DYNAESTIE
GREAT JOB, EVERYONE!
Is Seo-ri still not answering?
I called over ten times
and checked her room.
I can't find her.
Then you should send people out
to find her. What are you doing?
Don't worry.
Maybe she went to get a snack--
Where's she going this late
when she doesn't even know her way around?
You should stay here, sir.
It'll only make her look bad
if you leave now.
The crew is already upset over the delays
caused by all the wardrobe changes.
It'll only start weird rumors.
What do I…
All right. Thanks.
Sir, can we step outside?
Ms. Kim found her and is taking her
to a nearby hospital.
And the nurse's current state?
They say she's stable,
but she hasn't woken up yet,
so we have to wait.
Sir, where are you…
Our policy prohibits sharing this footage
with the guests.
But since you said it's an emergency…
-Stop there.
-What?
-Bottom right, third one.
-Here?
I mean, this is like
finding a needle in a haystack.
We should let your family know
or get more men to help out.
If it is just us,
we will end up going in circles all night.
Gosh, I am sorry.
We shouldn't have rushed here.
You're going through
all this trouble because of me.
My goodness.
Wait.
-Jeez. What happened?
-Oh no.
Don't worry.
I'll make you a fresh batch.
Never mind that. Think carefully.
Whereabouts did he let go of your hand?
I'm sure
it was around here
that he disappeared.
Goodness.
How old is your grandson?
He's 6 years old.
My Hyeon-ho is 6.
You look to be at least 80,
but your grandson is only 6?
How old are you, old man?
Old man? What do you mean?
I just got married early.
I'm only 55 years old.
Fifty-five?
Grandpa!
What are you doing?
Mom and Dad
went to the police to find you.
Where have you been?
Who are you?
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
My grandfather came to see me…
SONG HYEON-HO
…and must have gotten lost.
Your party was looking for you.
Grandpa! Where are you going now?
Could it be dotage?
DOTAGE: DEMENTIA
SEORI'S NOODLE SHOP
My goodness.
Her after school class
should've ended by now.
What's taking her so long?
She must be hungry.
Hello, sir.
I'm a bit busy right now.
Did your guest make it back okay?
You saw her? Where?
We would've been in serious trouble
without her help.
My grandfather got lost--
Where is she right now?
I saw her earlier
in the woods near the beach,
but I'm not sure…
Damn it.
Why she brought in someone like you…
Is anyone out there?
Please help me!
Are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
Why are you suddenly trying to be a hero?
You don't know the area.
How could you have found anyone?
I was not trying to be a hero.
The old man kept clinging to me.
You're not the type to just accept
anyone who latches on. Why help?
Why are you suddenly such a busybody?
Why do you care if I am being
a busybody or not?
Of course I care.
We're on a business trip.
You can't just go off on your own.
Do not be angry.
What did I do so wrong--
You were wrong
to blindly follow a stranger at night.
What if something happened to you?
Are you this angry
because you were worried about me?
Because I could have been hurt?
Don't twist my words.
Keep work and private life separate.
You were late for work
because of your personal actions.
A nuisance to your colleagues.
Am I wrong?
A nuisance?
Yes. Poking around everywhere
and meddling all day.
Professionally, it's an obstruction.
Privately, it's a waste of time.
So please! God damn it.
Just stay out of trouble, please.
Very well, I understand.
I shall take care not to be a nuisance.
So do not come looking for me
like this next time.
I too shall treat you
as a complete stranger from now on.
Great work, everyone.
-May I have your attention, please?
-Yes.
Please let me apologize.
My grandfather lost his way,
but Ms. Shin Seo-ri helped me find him.
That was what made her late.
Is that true?
Well, I did not exactly help find him.
Do you break out in hives
when you do good deeds?
His grandson confirmed it.
Why keep denying it?
Please allow me to offer
a bottle of Premier Cru Burgundy
for each table.
-Wow.
-Shin Seo-ri!
-Thank you for the wine!
Thank you for the wine!
Now, have you ever heard of it?
This has gone unrecorded for 500 years.
It is the Chaos Wine of Joseon.
Makgeolli mixed with wine.
The perfect harmony of East and West.
And I am the only one who can brew it.
Drink up!
-Drink up!
I'm not drinking tonight.
Come on.
Drink, Mr. Son! Drink!
-Drink!
-Down the hatch! Chug!
-Chug!
-How long will you make us dance?
Mr. Son.
-Look at my dislocated shoulders!
Mr. Son!
-Wow!
Wait!
Michelin class? No?
I'll have one more. This is so good.
-Mr. Son.
-Yes, Michelin.
Isn't this after-party
an extension of work?
Pace yourself.
No fun!
What are you even doing?
Not drinking at a drinking party,
just sitting around chattering
like a petty little miser.
You should have a glass too, Lord CEO.
-Drink!
I'm not drinking.
Come on, drink.
Being the only sober one
among drunks is no fun.
I'm more comfortable
being sober and boring.
It is not about comfort.
You just cannot drink.
The petty little miser cannot handle
a glass of Chaos Wine and chatters away.
I told you it's not that I can't.
I just don't want to.
Didn't you say you'd treat me
like a stranger?
We may be strangers in private,
but not professionally.
The lightweight who talks a big game.
I am choosing not to drink.
If you are that scared, let me.
Hand it over.
Who says I'm scared?
-What a man!
-One more!
You can drink just fine,
yet you put up such a fuss.
You should have just tossed it back
like that from the start.
Lord CEO,
you sure love playing hard to get.
Right, why take things so seriously?
I get to be this drunk because I am alive.
Worldly anguish,
pointless worries and the like
can all be washed away
with a single drink.
Once a gloomy day passes,
a pleasant new sun is bound to rise.
Gosh, why is it so cold?
Dawn is still a long way away.
And where am I now?
Where did everyone run off to without me?
And you wonder
why I can't take my eyes off you?
A stranger is speaking to me.
Do you know me? I do not recognize you.
You're drunk, Shin Seo-ri.
Drunk, my foot.
I am perfectly sober.
Here, look how perfectly sober I am.
I told you to watch it!
Watch that degenerate behavior!
"The moon rises, luminous."
"The beauty, how lovely."
"Gracefully entwining, unfolding."
"My troubled heart…"
"The bright moon rises,
revealing my beautiful love."
"My heart aches in longing."
Cha Se-gye.
I must go to Mount Halla,
-so lead the way.
-Why Mount Halla?
I have something to say there.
I must declare
that I shall cast myself away
and live as Shin Seo-ri.
Must you make that declaration
at Mount Halla, at this hour?
Silence!
Do you truly not know?
My Lovely Sam Soon, Episode 12.
Sam-soon cleanses herself
of her tedious past
and declares her new life
as Kim Hee-jin.
That very scene struck
a chord in my heart.
With Mount Halla so close at hand,
I cannot miss such a golden opportunity.
What are you talking about?
Shush. Let us go to Mount Halla!
I'm not going to Mount Halla.
Are you asking for palanquin fare?
Here.
When did you pick this up?
No! Stop! My token!
Are you nuts? Where are you going?
Why did you throw away my precious token?
I intended to cherish it.
You just said it was my fare.
Are you drunk?
Why would I pay with a rock?
It must be you who is drunk.
I stopped you going to Mount Halla,
even when you were freaking out.
Are you mad?
Climbing a mountain in the dead of night?
That's what I'm saying!
The sea is better than a mountain.
You said you liked the sea.
Just sober up a bit before we go.
Very well, then.
Cha Se-gye!
Look at that.
Hello.
Ms. Mo Tae-hee.
The sea has parted in two.
Maybe I drank too much Chaos Wine?
I told you yesterday. It's low tide.
It becomes a path at ebb tide
and an island at high tide.
It must be nice to be so smart,
knowing everything in the world.
Don't you think there's just too much
you don't know?
Yet there is one thing I know for certain.
How to endure life.
To ensure good memories
are not easily forgotten,
one must collect tokens like this.
I have tucked away the fond memory
of seeing the sea for the first time.
When life becomes unbearable,
I shall reach deep down
and pull out the memories
of those good times.
What if the good memories make you sad?
What then?
A memory both good and sad?
You must tuck it back away.
Since recalling it
will only make you weak,
you must replace it with new ones.
You…
feel guilty, do you not?
What?
It is written all over your face.
That you feel sorry.
That you regret losing
your temper earlier.
But it is quite all right.
That is how people naturally act
when they are frightened.
Even a man can easily become frightened.
You need not feel sorry.
No, I'm not sorry at all.
If I had to go back,
I would still chase after you
like a madman.
I'd do something foolish
and blow up at you again.
Even if you're disappointed in me,
as long as you're okay, I'll be relieved.
This man is hopeless.
I'm really sorry for being like this.
A foolish man
who cannot even apologize properly.
But I can't help it.
This is how I truly feel.
A bull-headed lone wolf
who only cares about himself.
Willful and self-centered.
Shameless enough to sell
his conscience for money.
So I'm warning you.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
I'm about to do something,
so if you want to run, now's your chance.
I'll give you three seconds.
One.
Two.
Three.
There are countless reasons
I must not fall for this man.
But there is just one reason
why I have.
You grabbed me first.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
"The moon rises, luminous.
The beauty, how lovely."
"Gracefully entwining, unfolding.
My troubled heart aches."
"The bright moon rises,
revealing my beautiful love."
"It tenderly stirs and blooms."
"My heart
aches in longing."
What?
-Such irreverence.
-Gosh.
A junior court lady who has only just had
her initiation is sneaking alcohol?
Your Highness.
What brings you here this late…
I came to chase away
the bird chittering through the night.
And I find a palace attendant who drinks
inside the palace
in defiance of the liquor ban?
Do you have a death wish?
No, it is not that.
This is…
This is not alcohol. It is medicine.
-Medicine?
-Yes, it is medicine.
I picked the ingredients myself
in the scorching summer heat to brew
this fine medicine.
Medicinal liquor for the ailing
is exempt from the ban.
Is that what you mean?
Then tell me, my companion.
What ails you to drink
this medicinal liquor?
Well,
you see…
I suffer greatly from suppressed anger,
so I use alcohol as medicine.
Rather than being consumed
by this rage within,
is it not better to drink
and stay alive?
That mouth of yours
is just too smart for its own good.
-Stop smiling.
-You complained when I looked too grim.
Now you scold me for smiling?
Yes, stop smiling.
You look ugly.
A deserted island?
I have not committed any sins.
Why have I been exiled here?
There's nothing we can do.
We'll just have to make
a cozy little life together.
I have no memory of that.
You will never be able
to take back what happened yesterday.
I really need to quit drinking.
Let's shoot him down
when he reaches the apex.
D-Day should be…
What's your relationship with Se-gye?
Se-gye and I are going to be married.
Goodness! Ma'am!
Mr. Cha, did you drive
under the influence?
Do what you must to keep her
out of the press.
Just stop doing anything for me.
If you keep making me waver,
I will shamelessly start hoping for more.
Subtitle translation by Justin S. Kim