ظآزThe world keeps changingظآز
ظآزA thousand years pass
in the blink of an eyeظآز
ظآزShoulder to shoulderظآز
ظآزWe stand above the worldظآز
ظآزOur identities switchظآز
ظآزThe world turns upside downظآز
ظآزWatch meظآز
ظآزStir up a stormظآز
ظآزLet's time-travel, broظآز
ظآزOur blood is boilingظآز
ظآزThe genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategyظآز
ظآزThe slacker general
is unmatched in battleظآز
ظآزThe business world is in turmoilظآز
ظآزThe court is rife with intrigueظآز
ظآزWe will conquer the worldظآز
ظآزThere's no escape for the traitorsظآز
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 5=
Are you trying
to rebel?
Impersonating the Emperor
is punishable by death.
The Princess has arrived.
Your Majesty,
it's you.
Why did you leave the palace?
Execute them all!
Please spare me, Your Majesty!
Spare me!
Mercy, Your Majesty!
Your lives are spared,
but you'll be punished.
Seal up this restaurant first.
Lu Ding
must be behind this place, isn't he?
Have the Ministry of Justice
summon Lu Ding.
Interrogate him thoroughly.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Take them away.
Mercy, Your Majesty!
I failed to recognize you.
Please spare me!
I tried to make a fair deal,
but you forced my hand.
Gu Bei.
From now on, this restaurant is yours.
You're Gu Bei?
That's me.
This beautiful young lady
must be Princess Xiao Ling, right?
What a smooth talker.
If I'm to marry
an uncultured brute like you,
I'd rather stay single forever.
First,
I never agreed to marry you.
Second,
I may not be smart,
but I have a bachelor's degree.
What's your education?
Education? Bachelor's degree?
I don't understand what you're saying.
You sound completely uneducated.
I'm a college student in the modern world.
Uneducated, you say?
What a joke.
You!
Your Majesty,
I have an idea
to determine
who is better educated.
This way, please.
Your Majesty,
this restaurant is also known as
Scholars' Tower.
After every imperial examination,
the top three graduates
come here to celebrate.
After a few drinks,
they write poetry.
That's why
this wall is called
the Wall of Zhuangyuan.
[*Top graduate in the imperial exam]
Her Highness and General Gu
may have a contest here.
Excellent idea.
Gu Bei.
Xiao Ling.
How about
a poetry contest?
What do you say?
Sure.
If I win,
I won't marry him.
I'll give up.
I don't want to marry you either.
Fine.
Until the incense burns out,
each of you shall compose a poem.
As for whose is better,
we'll leave it
to everyone here to judge.
Just recite a Li Bai poem.
That's such a clich├ر
in time-travel dramas.
Besides,
I never studied, remember?
"At the corner of the carved balustrade,
the moon shines bright.
She loosens her silken robes
as the evening breeze caresses them.
Leaning by the red veil,
she counts the moonlit flowers' shadows.
Little does she know
that spring has come for her."
Excellent!
That's good.
- Good!
- What a beautiful poem.
- Excellent!
"Quiet Night Thoughts".
[*A poem by Li Bai]
"Quiet Night Thoughts"?
Stop it.
I forgot poems from elementary school.
Reciting poems is boring.
Why is he playing the pipa like that?
ظآزThe sky is dim, like an evening drizzleظآز
ظآزI'm waiting for youظآز
ظآزAs the cooking smoke drifts,
I lift the blind to the rainظآز
ظآزOnly a window separates us,
yet it feels like we're oceans apartظآز
The sky is dim, like an evening drizzle.
I'm waiting for you. As the cooking smoke
drifts, I lift the blind to the rain.
Only a window separates us,
yet it feels like we're oceans apart.
Everyone,
that's a good one.
He's actually that talented?
I've underestimated him.
So this is what you're into.
I've got plenty of songs.
Changing the lyrics is a piece of cake.
ظآزWho plucks the old strings?ظآز
ظآزA gentle melody
that parts the dusk cloudsظآز
ظآزTime's scars seep through
the cracks in the bricksظآز
ظآزRevealing the wrinkles of bygone daysظآز
ظآزNot for an old promiseظآز
ظآزI write this poem
and await your returnظآز
ظآزWith a sweep of my brushظآز
ظآزThe inkstone bears
layers upon layers of ink marksظآز
Come on.
ظآزTo the east,
the lonely city endures through yearsظآز
ظآزBeacon fires rise to the sky
without endظآز
ظآزThe road stretches endlesslyظآز
ظآزTossed by wind and sandظآز
ظآزWho still holds the cup,
awaiting your return?ظآز
It's just a song medley.
Why is everyone so thrilled?
His lyrics have such beautiful imagery.
He even composed the music.
I gladly concede.
- Bravo!
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
Distinguished guests,
come on in!
Drinks are on the house today!
Great!
- Great!
Right this way!
Please.
Free beer!
Long time no see.
It has been a while.
- Don't show up in rags next time.
- This way!
- Congratulations!
- Thanks!
Came alone?
Where's your wife?
Greetings, Your Highness.
His Majesty said
your Xiaoyao Pavilion is impressive.
And this
membership system.
That's right.
The higher the membership,
the better the perks.
Is this enough?
You can apply for a membership.
You're our biggest patron.
Miss Patron,
this way, please.
All services we offer today
are complimentary for Your Highness.
There's nothing I haven't tried.
I...
Who is she?
She's full of herself.
Miss Hulv,
don't be rude to our guests.
Remember,
the customer
is god.
You!
Right this way, Miss Patron.
I'll take that.
Put it away.
Please follow me, Your Highness.
Your room upstairs is ready.
Enjoy yourselves!
Eat and drink up!
Enjoy!
Come.
Watch your step, Your Highness.
Not bad.
Just a moment.
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
Ow! That hurts!
That feels amazing.
Be gentle with Her Highness.
Easy with your hands.
This is incredible.
How did you think of this?
Life on the frontier is tougher.
If you don't have fun,
you'll get depressed.
A massage
while
eating.
His Majesty has never been treated
this well.
You know how to enjoy life better
than the Emperor.
He rules the palace.
I rule Xiaoyao Pavilion.
The two of us
have every angle covered.
Gu Bei.
You're so different from anyone I know.
Really?
Will you be my friend?
Uh,
who taught you that?
His Majesty did.
He said it's the highest courtesy
between friends.
Your Highness,
from today on,
we're friends.
It's getting late.
We're closed. Head back, please.
The guest's still here.
How dare a servant butt in?
Gu Bei,
you should discipline them.
A servant?
Seriously?
All right.
- Miss Hulv.
- We're closing.
Please don't be upset, Your Highness.
Head back first.
I'll send someone to the palace
next time.
Gu Bei...
I...
Don't push me...
Your Majesty,
Official Lu has always been
a dutiful official.
Whatever misunderstanding
there may be,
you shouldn't throw a senior official
into prison so hastily.
A misunderstanding?
Oppressing the people
and plotting regicide
are misunderstandings too?
I've known Official Lu for years.
I believe
he'd never do such a thing.
I vouch for him.
Please release him first, Your Majesty.
I'll investigate myself.
Fine.
If you want him released, you do it.
I
won't.
ظآزLet's time-travel, broظآز
ظآزOur spirit soars to the skiesظآز
ظآزThe brainy emperor
plots the strategyظآز
ظآزThe slacker general
leads the chargeظآز
ظآزSwords clash and
warhorses thunderظآز
ظآزLet the history
judge our deedsظآز
ظآزOur brotherhood is pricelessظآز
ظآزPeace across the
land, carefree at lastظآز
ظآزFunny moments never stopظآز
ظآزSilly blunders never ceaseظآز
ظآزYet through every up and downظآز
ظآزWe create miraclesظآز
ظآزFrom naive youthsظآز
ظآزTo legendary heroesظآز
ظآزThis journeyظآز
ظآزIs one we'll be proud ofظآز
ظآزLet's time-travel, broظآز
ظآزLet's createظآز
ظآزA legend of our ownظآز