♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 6=
If you want him released, you do it.
I
won't.
Your Majesty...
My apologies.
I suppose
Official Lu is cursing me in prison
for ruining
his and General Sun's plan.
How is that my concern?
Isn't it?
You've been defeating
that scoundrel.
I figured
you two had some kind
of corrupt deal going on.
You two aren't... What's the phrase?
In
kahoot...
In cahoots.
That's it.
Watch your mouth.
If you're not involved,
then drop it.
Whether he's guilty
is for His Majesty
to decide.
Enough of this.
One more thing.
Princess Xiao Ling has come of age.
General Gu has served with distinction.
I intend to marry Princess Xiao Ling
to Gu Bei.
Impossible!
Why do you disagree
with everything His Majesty says?
Do you have a contrarian personality?
Your Majesty,
I've admired Princess Xiaoling for years.
Please consider
my years of service,
and grant her hand to me.
I
have made my decision.
What are you doing?
Every scar I bear
was earned fighting for Jing.
Our founder
conquered the realm on horseback.
How can the Princess
marry a good-for-nothing?
If Gu Bei
can beat me in combat,
I'll gladly concede
and give up her hand.
He's way too skinny.
General Sun will kill him.
While guarding the border,
I took enemy commanders' heads
as easily as taking candy from a baby.
Not even an army could wound me.
What's the big deal about scars?
The real skill is never getting hurt.
I'm willing to duel General Sun
for the sake of the Princess.
Since it's a duel,
blades have no eyes.
Let's sign a death waiver first.
No.
What?
Are you scared?
Coward.
Let's do this.
This is my soft armor.
It'll stop any blade.
Wear it tomorrow.
It'll keep you alive.
You're giving this to me?
What about you?
I'm just lending it to you.
Let's get through tomorrow first.
No need for that.
With this,
all will be well.
What is this?
I call it
"Close Your Eyes Even When It's Bright"
powder.
Tomorrow in the duel,
I'll just blow a little in Sun's face.
He won't wake up for a long time.
Whoa.
It really works.
Xu's been exhausted lately.
He needs some rest.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Hey, Nan.
You even brought me a treat.
You've grown up.
If General Gu's soft armor doesn't fit,
alter it for him.
It's for His Majesty...
This is Qinghuan cakes
for His Majesty and you.
General Sun is a formidable fighter.
The armor alone won't be enough.
I'm worried about my brother,
so I came to discuss a strategy
with Your Majesty.
Uh...
Strategy for me?
Looks more like
you came to dote on His Majesty.
Do you like it?
I learned it from the imperial chef.
It's good.
A little sweeter would be perfect.
I'll make it again tomorrow.
I'll add more sugar.
Sounds good.
If Your Majesty likes it,
I'll make it for you every day.
Uh...
Really? That seems like a lot of work.
As long as you're happy,
it's no trouble at all.
Take your positions.
- Go!
Come on!
(Round One)
Do you know what this is?
I've never amounted to much,
but I spent all my savings
to buy you this silver hairpin.
Nan...
Consort Nan's life
is in your hands now.
Begin the match.
Wait!
Before we start,
I need to cheer myself up.
Get fired up.
Go, General Gu!
It's the signal we came up with
when we cheated.
(My sister)
(is in trouble.)
(Could it be)
(Gu Nan?)
Xiao Ling.
Go see if Gu Nan is in the palace.
That's enough.
Let's start now.
- Go!
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪