♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 7=
Wait!
You are both great warriors of Jing.
I believe this duel should go no further
than testing each other's skills.
Fists have no eyes.
A duel isn't meant to be restrained.
Your Majesty, let us begin.
Easy now.
Jing values martial prowess.
Having both General Gu and General Sun
is my great fortune.
A toast to you both.
We've had the liquor.
Are we fighting or not?
Your Majesty, are you stalling
because you're favoring General Gu?
Kidnapping the imperial consort
is punishable
by exterminating nine clans.
Once I become the prince consort,
Consort Nan will return to the palace
safe and sound.
If I win,
she dies.
If I lose,
Xiao Ling is mine.
Make your choice now.
You win.
I surrender.
General Sun wins.
Bravo!
Your Majesty, please eat something.
You haven't eaten all day.
Leave us.
Guard the door.
Let no one come near.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Sun Beiming has some nerve.
He dared kidnap an imperial consort.
Now he's shown his true colors.
He wants my throne,
bullies my friend,
kidnaps my consort,
and now he wants to marry you.
I'm going to kill
Sun Beiming.
There's another way out of this.
You
marry Sun Beiming.
Gu Bei!
You actually tell me
to marry that traitor?
Have you lost your mind?
Gu Bei,
Xiao Ling is my sister.
You only care about yours.
What about mine?
Aren't we trying to think of a way?
What other choice do we have?
Gu Nan is in their hands.
How can you be sure she is safe?
Answer me.
Answer!
Gu Bei.
I truly admired you.
I liked you.
Turns out
I was wrong about you
all along.
(Honor Learning and Confucianism)
Here's the gift registry I prepared.
(Wedding Gift Registry)
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
I won't neglect
Her Highness.
Where is Consort Nan?
Her disappearance
concerns me as well.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
I've ordered the Imperial Guards
to seal off the capital.
I'm sure Consort Nan
will be found soon.
Here's a map of Jing.
Bring Consort Nan back safely,
give up marrying the princess,
and I
will grant you a fiefdom.
You're free to choose your own territory.
Your Majesty,
what is this supposed to mean?
I won the duel.
I should be the prince consort.
Besides, I've admired
Princess Xiao Ling for years.
I've already prepared
the betrothal gifts.
You admired me?
Xiao Ling.
I'll marry you.
Your Majesty, my marriage is my choice.
Besides,
General Sun is a great warrior.
What more could I ask for
than a husband like him?
I'm not finished.
I'll marry you,
but on one condition.
Please name it, Your Highness.
On our wedding day,
I won't marry into
your general's residence.
The banquet and wedding night
must be held at my palace.
Enough. Step back.
As Your Highness wishes.
And one more thing.
After the wedding,
I must see Consort Nan
return safely to the palace.
I'll do everything I can
to bring Consort Nan back.
Well done.
You're finally
one step closer
to marrying Xiao Ling.
For tomorrow's wedding,
I've prepared a special gift.
It'll ensure everything goes smoothly.
As you command.
(Happiness)
Your Highness,
it's lively outside.
Why not join my men for a few drinks?
Quite the proud royal princess,
aren't you?
Let me make one thing clear.
Once you marry into the Sun family,
alive,
you're one of us.
Dead,
you still belong to us.
If you dare defy me,
I'll make you wish you were dead.
Look.
The whole capital is celebrating
my wedding.
General Sun and the Princess
must be enjoying their wedding night.
Lucky them.
Too bad we didn't get
to attend the feast.
- Cheers.
Why are you here?
My dear,
how do I look?
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor
plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general
leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and
warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history
judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the
land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪