♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 8=
Your Majesty, we've searched the area.
This place is under the heaviest guard.
Her Highness must be held inside.
Surround the place.
Break in.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Move.
- Let me go!
- Where do you think you're going?
Let go of me!
His Majesty won't spare you!
Let me go!
He doesn't even know
how much longer he'll live.
Since he's as good as dead,
why don't we...
Don't come near me!
Are you alright?
Your Majesty.
You finally came.
Don't be afraid.
You still owe me Qinghuan cakes.
With extra sugar.
Nan!
Fireworks!
They're beautiful.
That's Bei's signal.
They did it.
Do you like fireworks?
Mm.
Let's watch them first.
Why are you here?
My dear,
how do I look?
You...
You tricked me!
If we didn't,
how would you take the bait?
He wants my throne,
bullies my friend,
kidnaps my consort,
and now he wants to marry you.
I'm going to kill
Sun Beiming.
There's another way
out of this.
You
marry Sun Beiming.
Gu Bei!
You actually tell me
to marry that traitor?
- Have you lost your mind?
- Gu Bei, Xiao Ling is my sister.
You only care about yours.
What about mine?
Aren't we trying to think of a way?
What other choice do we have?
Gu Nan is in their hands.
How did you steppe people
get into the Princess's Residence?
Guards!
Your men are already under our control.
You've lost.
Just admit defeat, my dear.
Watch out!
Gu Bei.
You're hiding behind
a woman?
How pathetic.
The world doesn't belong only to men.
Women can wear armor
and win glory too.
You lost because of your brains
and your skills,
not because of your gender.
People laugh because I'm a woman.
They say if I were a man,
I'd be a great general.
Gu Bei.
You're the only one who understands me.
I may be a woman,
but I can still ride into battle.
I'm no less than any man.
If I die,
Gu Nan dies too.
Where is Gu Nan?
You'll never find her.
Everyone, stand down.
Then I'll leave her body intact.
In your dreams.
Impossible.
I hid her perfectly.
How did you find her?
Sun Beiming,
I gave you a chance.
The moment you tried
to force Xiao Ling to marry you,
you had already lost.
The Imperial Guards have surrendered.
Surrender now,
and I'll leave your body intact.
I've prepared a special gift.
It'll ensure everything goes smoothly.
Protect them.
Nobody move!
Everything goes smoothly?
So this is what you meant.
Even if I've lost,
I'll drag all of you to hell with me.
Winner, winner,
chicken dinner.
- Gu Bei!
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Nice one.
I call it the Pocket Blaster.
Good thing you caught my hint.
When you said,
"Winner, winner, chicken dinner,"
I knew you were telling me you had a gun.
Your Majesty.
Thank goodness you're alright.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪