( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
(Love has no age...)
(because it is constantly reborn.)
Butterflies?
I haven't felt butterflies in a long time.
What should I do?
Romance?
I guess I've been putting work
before romance.
Being alone became comfortable.
But now,
I can't keep putting it off anymore.
I want to feel butterflies again,
like I did in my 20s.
I want to fall in love.
Because I want a love
that gives me a dopamine rush.
I honestly don't think younger men
would turn me down.
I bought a house...
in one of the best neighborhoods
in the country.
He could just stay home
and be a house husband.
I can bring home the bacon.
I look much younger than my age,
and I'm very capable.
What worries me is
whether I'll actually find...
someone I'm attracted to.
Will I really be able to feel attracted
to a younger man?
I'll make them fall for me.
With just a few glances...
and a little playful banter,
they always fall for me.
Younger men tend to be
very straightforward.
Can't you just stay?
Should we spend the night here?
Do you think you can handle this?
If you're okay with it,
I want us to be together
even after filming ends.
But what would we actually do
in real life?
A romance?
From my perspective,
there's no attraction.
I don't understand
why you won't even try to see me as a man.
You really are young, aren't you?
This is the first time I've ever wished...
I were older.
What's wrong with a 12-year age gap?
Could this actually work?
I have a career too, you know.
Will I really be able to maintain
this relationship after the show ends?
You and I just don't work.
It's driving me crazy.
I came here to find someone I could marry.
(Mind the Noona Gap 2)
Hold on. What is happening?
This is way bolder than I expected.
It really is bold.
And this is only the prologue.
Even so, this season feels different.
- It's incredibly intense.
- Right.
Is it really that different?
If Season One felt like a calm lake,
this season feels
like a stormy ocean in Bali.
Wait. We should point out something.
Someone is sitting next to me
who wasn't here last season.
Could you introduce yourself?
Hello, I'm DinDin, the ideal younger guy.
I can give you that.
Honestly,
I think I got cast on this show...
because older women...
have always loved me.
A lot of them used to say,
"You're going to become irresistible..."
"once you hit your mid-30s."
And back then,
they always said I was too young.
- The older women said that?
- How old are you now?
I'm 36.
That's Korean age.
- So you're in your mid-30s now.
- Exactly. The irresistible age.
I've aged like fine wine.
When Season One aired,
the biggest issue
everyone talked about was...
the age gap between the older women
and the younger men.
People were obsessed
with the biggest age difference.
And the biggest gap was 13 years.
- That's...
- The biggest gap was.
That's huge.
- You mean, 13?
- That's a really big gap.
How much older were your exes?
Back when I was in my mid-20s,
I dated someone five years older than me.
She was already in her 30s.
So a guy in his 20s
dating a woman in her 30s.
That couldn't have been easy.
At first, the fact
that she was older made me...
really excited.
She used to drive me home in her car.
Just that alone gave me a dopamine rush.
One time while we were driving
on Gangbyeonbuk-ro, I literally screamed.
- I was so excited.
- That's adorable.
- You screamed next to her?
- I was like, "Yay!"
"Yay!"
- "She's driving me home!"
- That's cute.
"She's the first girlfriend
who's ever driven me home!"
That's how I was in the beginning.
But after some time had passed,
I realized we were just two people
in a relationship.
There are certain thrills
only older women can give you.
I see. So in a long-term relationship,
age doesn't really become a huge issue?
At the end of the day,
it's just a man and a woman.
Exactly. It's still just a relationship.
Regardless of age,
a relationship is still a relationship.
Emotionally, it's all the same.
- In the end, yes.
- But, you see...
the beginning is usually
the difficult part.
Older women tend to overthink
whether the relationship can really work.
But younger men just believe it will.
That's really how men think?
- Yes.
- The younger men?
Because we're men, after all.
They just believe it'll work anyway.
The women try to stay cautious,
but once they open up,
they fall hard.
(That's so romantic.)
Older women really fall hard?
Yes. They really do.
That sounds fun.
(What kind of drama will unfold
this season?)
(A spring day in April)
The weather is perfect.
If you meet the right person in April,
you're getting married before you know it.
- Right.
- Seriously.
- You just get swept away.
- Totally enchanted.
(The second Yeon House
for older women and younger men)
"Yeon House." It's been a while.
(Who will be the first to arrive
at Yeon House?)
She's here. The first older woman.
Just looking at her makes me excited.
She seems so elegant.
(Koo Ji Seung)
She totally looks like the type
younger men would love.
Whenever people ask me
what I love most in life,
I answer that it's the sense
of achievement I get from work.
I think work has always come
before romance.
Right.
I probably had opportunities
to get married before,
but I was never completely sure.
(She had opportunities but wasn't sure.)
But I've changed a lot now.
Now I want to experience romance
without overthinking everything.
It seems like she's finally made room
in her life for romance.
- Now that her career is more settled.
- Exactly.
I want to find someone
who can truly put each other first.
Where should I sit?
(The communal living room is still empty.)
She looks so young.
She really does.
The sunlight is way too strong over here.
(Blazing)
(While Ji Seung adjusts
to life at Yeon House,)
How is she feeling right now?
(a car arrives at Yeon House.)
(Is this the second older woman?)
(Or the first younger man?)
I think it's a man.
You can tell by the way he drives.
Was the driver a woman?
Her walk feels completely different
from Ji Seung's.
She seems confident.
(Park Ji Hye)
She looks like someone
who takes very good care of herself.
Younger men tend to be proactive.
I want a romance
that's bold and provocative.
I think I came here looking
for that kind of adrenaline rush.
Whenever I personally think
someone looks attractive,
they always end up falling for me.
So the guys...
should be nervous. I'm serious.
I'll never let my guard down.
Never.
Her charm is completely different
from Ji Seung's.
Younger men go crazy...
for women like her.
(Grinning)
I love her confidence.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
(The older women meet for the first time.)
They're so different.
- Totally different characters.
- They are.
Because the sunlight was so strong
over there,
- I moved here instead.
- Really?
Yes.
You're very tall.
(Glancing)
(Peeking)
They're checking each other out
already, right?
Definitely.
But they'll soon realize...
they have completely different styles.
Aren't you nervous?
I am.
About two weeks ago,
I wasn't nervous at all.
- I thought it would just be fun.
- Right?
But around five days ago,
I suddenly started getting really nervous.
I haven't been able to sleep since then.
Same here.
This is...
way more nerve-racking than I expected.
I've never been this nervous...
- in my life.
- Seriously.
This feels so different.
(Turning around)
Is someone coming?
Do you see anyone?
They're both nervous.
Seems like a woman.
(Choi Yu Jin)
Everyone is so pretty.
I'm usually easygoing.
But when I'm with someone
I'm attracted to,
I get super feminine.
I came to find a guy
who brings out my feminine side.
When it comes to love,
chemistry matters more than age.
I want a relationship
that gives me butterflies.
If you're in your 30s, you can relate.
- Hello.
- I'm so nervous.
- We were saying the same thing.
I'm so nervous.
She has a smiley face.
- Right. We're all feeling the same way.
- We feel the same.
(With Yu Jin joining them,)
(now there are three older women.)
I'm so nervous.
(Staring)
It'll be...
a fun week, right?
I think I'll be comfortable after today.
Me too.
I might not even want to go back home.
Ji Hye...
seems really charismatic.
She seems straightforward.
My first impression of Ji Seung was
that she seemed elegant.
Just imagining being there is suffocating.
I know.
(Older women with different vibes
are getting to know each other.)
(The fourth older woman is
arriving at Yeon House.)
She has a different kind of beauty.
(Yoo Ju Hee)
The younger guys will lose their minds.
I vibe better with younger guys.
I can be more honest with them.
I like that I can be myself around them
without holding back.
That's their charm.
I seem calm at first,
but when I get comfortable with someone,
I become more fun.
I think that twist is my charm.
She goes horse riding?
- What about it?
- That's amazing.
What do you think about women
who go horse riding?
I love them.
Some women who ride horses
even have their own horses.
- Hello.
- Where should I sit?
- Wherever you're comfortable.
- The sun is setting a bit.
- Yes. So it's...
- Hello.
(Glancing)
Ju Hee has a really pretty smile.
I really like people like her,
pretty and sharp.
At first glance, I thought she was pretty.
I didn't think much about her.
I was just looking forward
to meeting younger guys.
- They're so different.
- They are.
(All four older women are here.)
All older women have arrived.
Are we sitting too close together?
Just sitting with ourselves.
It'd be hard for the guys
to sit between them.
Should we space out
so that they can sit between us?
- Yes.
- There you go.
Good thinking.
- She thinks fast.
- Season Two is really something.
(Spreading out for the younger men)
I'm curious.
What's your type?
- I like handsome guys.
- That was really clear.
- That was a clear answer.
- That's important.
- You don't care about their height?
- I like monolids.
- Monolids.
- I don't like guys with double eyelids.
Same for me. I like monolids.
- Guys with fox-like vibes.
- Sharp features?
- I like a free-spirited vibe.
- Me too.
- We have the same type.
- They do.
- That's not good.
Oh, dear. This is not good.
You won't back down, right?
- "You won't back down?"
- That's quite direct too.
People don't say things like that
on other shows.
You don't really say that
when you've just met.
Back down?
- Back down?
- It sounds like you won't.
Shouldn't we leave that to the guy?
(Getting tense
while talking about their types)
We're in trouble.
(The first younger man is approaching.)
I can't wait to see them.
I don't think age matters.
If they only saw me as a younger man,
I wouldn't like that.
(Lee Si Won)
Oh, my. He's so handsome.
You didn't react like that to the girls.
Let's take a break here.
Her reaction is completely different now.
(Lee Si Won)
We exchange a few looks,
I talk to them a bit,
and then they fall for me.
- Her eyes are sparkling.
- Someone is coming.
(Turning)
- You're right. Someone is coming.
- We're all looking at him.
They're excited.
(Nervous)
My goodness.
(They've been waiting
for the first younger man to show up.)
(Staring)
- Hello.
(Scanning)
Hello.
(The older women stand up
as the first younger man appears.)
How should we sit?
- Sit?
- Hello.
Hello.
(Looking around)
Where will he sit?
- Has it been just the four of you?
- Yes.
(Naturally sitting next to Ji Seung)
They're sad.
It got more awkward.
(Smiling)
I was just amazed by his looks.
He looked like an actor.
He's handsome.
(Smiling)
(Si Won's appearance
changed the atmosphere.)
You were nervous, weren't you?
- I was really nervous.
- Right?
- Could you tell from my walk?
- I could tell you were nervous.
(Embarrassed)
He looks cute when he grins.
- He looks so different when he smiles.
- Completely.
Your voice sounds
completely different too.
(Laughing out loud)
I got goosebumps.
(But I really like him.)
- Here he comes.
- Really?
(They see a younger man
through the windows.)
The second younger guy is coming.
(Glancing)
It bothers him a little.
(The second younger man is walking
forward confidently.)
(Lee Jun Han)
I've only dated older women.
Really?
I never date people my age or younger.
I'm quite competitive.
I look masculine,
but I'll show I have a soft side too.
(Grinning)
He has such a smiley face.
Where have these guys been?
He's making eye contact.
He seems so nice.
He really does.
(Gulping)
Hello.
- Hello.
(While the room is hectic
as another younger guy shows up,)
Hello.
(who will Jun Han end up next to?)
He's bold!
He's moving further in.
(Boldly taking the center)
He just goes straight for it.
(Smiling)
(Nodding)
This is pretty embarrassing.
You smile like a baby.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Thank you. I can't move my neck...
- He does have a smiley face.
- Your neck hurts?
- My neck aches a little...
because I'm nervous.
(Smiley)
He looks so friendly.
(Nodding)
You all seem pretty relaxed.
- We've been here for a while.
- We talked a lot.
- Really?
- We did.
(Touching his neck)
Does your neck still hurt?
(Giggling)
My neck goes stiff when I'm embarrassed.
Your neck is red!
Is it?
I feel shy right now.
Try to stretch it like this.
(Jun Han has all the ladies' attention.)
Younger guys also have different vibes.
- Jun Han is easygoing,
- Yes.
- and Si Won is a bit cautious.
- Right.
But this could put Si Won on edge.
Yes.
You're really tall.
- Me?
- Yes.
I ate a lot.
- A lot?
- I ate well.
At what age?
Me? I've always eaten a lot.
- Seriously?
- For real?
You'll be surprised when you see me eat.
- Really?
You're a big eater.
So do you work out and stay in shape?
Yes, I like working out.
I can tell you do from your posture.
His body shows he worked out a lot.
(Squaring his shoulders)
You can tell how much he worked out
by the undone buttons.
- I can undo all of them later.
- I know.
(Glancing)
He was so down-to-earth,
and I felt he had a big puppy vibe.
I think they're called pecs.
The rounded muscles
from the chest to the shoulders.
I like those muscles so much.
So funny!
When talking about the first impression
on other shows,
most describe the looks.
- But she went with pecs!
- Pecs!
(Women even put things uniquely.)
This is so funny.
The lights are on.
(When the mood
and the lights are both on,)
(the third younger guy shows up.)
Love is...
the most important thing
for the rest of my life.
I want to meet someone
whom I can love more than myself.
Age doesn't really matter to me.
(Yoo Jin Woo)
- He's handsome.
- I feel like I've wasted my time.
I used to date those around my age
or younger.
So we treated marriage
like something distant.
I hope to meet someone I can marry.
Marriage?
He came to marry?
We'll see about that.
That's a lot of people.
He looks the most nervous.
His shoulders are completely stiff.
- Let's all clap our hands.
- Great idea.
I love the atmosphere.
Hello.
(Welcome to Yeon House.)
Thank you.
Hello.
- Hello.
You can sit.
Have a seat wherever you want.
Sorry?
- Do I sit anywhere I'd like?
- Yes.
(Reading the room)
(Glancing)
(Looking around)
No, don't sit there.
(In the end, Jin Woo stays where he is.)
I guess I got nervous before realizing it.
(Is this right?)
Of course, he would.
(The fourth younger guy
with confident steps)
I want to be seen as a man,
not a younger guy.
I'll be proactive...
and make the first move.
I've never lost the person I liked
to someone else.
Guys with that soft look are
popular these days.
(Lee Yun So)
I haven't dated someone older than me,
so I'd be excited if I find my love.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Sit wherever you'd like.
- Have a seat.
Okay.
Look at their eyes!
They're literally checking him out.
(Women's eyes go busy
as soon as Yun So shows up.)
How is it so different
from the first season?
(The older women and younger guys
have finally all gathered.)
They're not like the younger guys
from the first season...
- for sure.
- Really?
They're not.
Who stood out to you the most?
For me...
You're not choosing
your future husband here.
Pick someone who made
a good first impression.
For me,
it's Si Won.
- Si Won?
- Really?
So you're that type.
(No comment.)
(Oh, okay.)
Then, among the ladies,
who stood out to you the most?
For me,
it's Yu Jin.
- The cute one?
- Yes.
- The one with a bun?
- She had her hair tied up loosely.
So it might make her easy to approach.
I liked all of them.
- Come on!
- They're all charming.
I wish I could go somewhere too
with women like them.
I want to be treated like a baby.
Around the older women,
I can be like a puppy showing its belly.
- True.
- I love the way you put it.
For them, the moment I enter,
- I can lie down and act like this.
- You're right.
Did you introduce yourselves?
No, we were going to once you got here.
We were waiting for you.
So, you were waiting.
Do I go first?
My name is Lee Yun So.
- Yun So?
- Yun Sol?
- It's Yun So.
- I've never heard of that name.
Yun So.
That's a nice name.
My name is Yoo Ju Hee.
- Ju Hee!
- Ju Hee.
Yoo Ju Hee.
Ju Hee.
I'm Lee Jun Han.
- Ju Han?
- Jun Han.
- Jun Han?
Jun Han.
- Jun Han.
I'm Park Ji Hye.
- Ji Hye.
- Park Ji Hye.
- I'm Koo Ji Seung.
- Ji Seung.
That name suits you well.
- You're right.
- Doesn't it?
It's gender-neutral.
(Shy)
I'm Lee Si Won.
Si Won.
I'm Yoo Jin Woo.
- Jin Woo?
- Jin Woo.
My brother has the same name.
It's an honor.
- Yoo Jin Woo.
- Jin Woo.
I'm Choi Yu Jin.
Yu Jin.
- Choi Yu Jin.
(The older women and younger men
only know each other's names.)
So we're all eating here today?
Are we cooking something?
I think so.
Is anyone good at cooking here?
- Korean food.
- I can make Korean food.
I can at least cook doenjang stew.
- Really?
- I can grill meat.
- You can?
Great.
I can cook ramyeon.
There. We're done.
I can just stay still.
Anything.
I can make anything.
- Anything?
- Yes.
Even malatang.
Malatang? Really?
Really.
But guys usually don't eat malatang.
I can only eat mild ones.
You can't eat spicy ones?
I can.
- But it hits me hard the next day.
- You feel sick?
He's cute.
Jin Woo is kind of a delicate guy.
I see it.
You want to take care of him.
You seem like that type.
- He looks like he can't eat spicy food.
- What does that mean?
You look like you can't.
You don't think of me
as a younger brother, do you?
Just because I have the same name.
Jin Woo!
(Nice to meet you, Jin Woo.)
- I got a message.
- What is this?
(The first message is sent
to the older women and younger men.)
The first message.
What?
Why? What is it?
Right now?
Right now? The names?
(Please text the name of the person
who made the best first impression.)
Right away?
They have to make their choices
right away.
It felt too sudden for me.
I was a bit taken aback,
but since I knew exactly who I liked,
I sent the message without hesitation.
(Whom did they choose
for their first impressions?)
(Exploring Yeon House
after the first impression vote)
- Shall we check out the rooms?
- Shall we take a look together?
It's pretty.
- Right?
- It's so pretty.
What is this? Is it a heated pool?
There's a heated pool too.
The women's and men's quarters
are separate.
Look, the names are written over there.
(Nameplates)
- Choi Yu Jin.
- Right.
Great.
It's us two together.
I guess it's us two.
(They'll be living together in pairs.)
Great.
(Looking around the rooms together)
- How should we look around?
- Shall we take a look around?
It's so cute.
It's so pretty.
It's so nice!
It's a bedroom right away?
(Yeon House stands out
with its clean interior design.)
It's so pretty.
- The room is so nice.
- I know, right?
I wonder what the Talk Room is for.
Shall we go and check out the Talk Room?
- Who wants to go to the Talk Room?
- Shall we all go there and talk?
(A special space next to the common area)
There is a Talk Room.
(The Talk Room)
You need a passcode to enter.
(It's a private space for two.)
(Newly introduced in Season Two)
This is a new space
introduced in Season Two.
It's called the Talk Room.
The choice belongs to you,
so it doesn't bother me at all.
I hope you won't get hurt.
Hey, don't do that.
I felt betrayed.
This is what I think.
After all, it's only our second day here.
While I was there,
I kept thinking about you.
I'm sure...
things will definitely change
once we talk.
What's that?
We're talking.
How can the atmosphere be this different?
(Talk Room)
(What kind of stories will unfold here
in the future?)
Shall we go to our rooms
and unpack our bags?
- Unpacking?
- Let's unpack.
- Should we set a time to meet up again?
- Let's not do that.
Great.
- Don't do that.
- Let's take it easy.
You can't come out tomorrow.
- See you later.
See you later.
- All right.
(Ji Hye and Ju Hee, Ji Seung and Yu Jin)
(Si Won and Yun So, Jun Han and Jin Woo)
I think I'm going to pass out tonight.
- How many hours of sleep did you get?
- I only slept for two hours.
That's similar to me.
- Really?
- I slept for about that long as well.
I was too nervous.
Is there anyone among the men
who is your ideal type?
Are you asking that already?
In terms of looks,
everyone is so handsome.
Did you have someone in mind, Yu Jin?
Well.
- I'm not sure yet.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- She's keeping it a secret.
I think both of them are
intentionally holding back.
(Meanwhile, in Ji Hye and Ju Hee's room)
- Is there anyone you like?
- Sorry?
Is there anyone who caught your eye?
I'm not sure yet.
Really?
Do you have someone in mind?
I just chose the person who seemed
to have the best personality.
I really have no idea.
We should at least have a talk
or something.
- We haven't had the chance to talk.
- Exactly.
- Don't you think they seem quite young?
- Yes.
All of them, right?
I think they seem quite young.
- All of them.
- I was actually quite surprised.
The guys who sat over here and over there.
I thought they were K-pop trainees.
- They look so young.
- That's true.
They really looked like idols.
Right.
I wonder if the guys are
also talking right now.
- Asking each other who they voted for?
- Probably.
Of course.
(Yun So and Si Won's room)
Si Won, may I ask who made
the best first impression on you?
He's asking right away.
- First impression?
- The person you just voted for earlier?
For the text message,
I chose Ji Seung.
- Who?
- Ji Seung.
Really?
The person who sat next to me.
I cast my first impression vote
for Ji Seung.
The most memorable part was that...
she spoke very enthusiastically,
and when I saw her profile,
she was exactly my type.
I think her voice left
the strongest impression.
Who did you choose?
I chose Ju Hee.
- Ju Hee?
- With short hair.
Their choices didn't overlap.
I chose Ju Hee.
(Yun So's first impression vote
was Ju Hee.)
Honestly, when I first saw Ju Hee,
she seemed to have a great personality,
and her looks were exactly my style,
so I liked her.
(Si Won and Yun So's interests
didn't overlap.)
(The men gathered in the common area
first after unpacking.)
- Yun So, where was the meat?
- Here.
The men arrived at the kitchen first.
I noticed there were pork belly,
bacon, and ham...
inside.
(Just then, Ji Hye and Ju Hee
enter the common area.)
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hey.
(Spotting Ju Hee)
You're good at cooking Korean food.
- You're good at cooking Korean food.
- Yes.
From what I can see,
Yun So is definitely into Ju Hee.
Do you prefer kimchi stew
or doenjang stew?
- I prefer kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew?
But if we make kimchi stew,
everyone might get chili powder
stuck in their teeth.
That's charming, actually.
- Shall we pick it out for each other?
- Sure. Let's do that.
She's so cool.
She says getting chili powder
stuck in your teeth...
is charming and nice.
- Well.
- It's all fine for her.
She's chill.
It's not a big deal.
She's saying they have no time
to worry about things like that.
(Ji Seung and Yu Jin are here too.)
We're the last.
Hello there.
Hello.
I'm barefoot too.
- That's cute.
- So, it's stocked like this?
We don't really make it from scratch?
Is it pre-made?
There's braised kimchi too.
Then, let's make pork belly kimchi stew.
Great.
(The dinner menu was quickly decided
as soon as the ladies arrived.)
You said you're good at cooking, Ju Hee.
Yes. Should we take out the green onions?
You should be the head chef today,
and I will be the sous chef.
If you call us, we will take out
whatever you need.
Do you need anything right now?
Are you the main chef?
- Main chef?
- But isn't everything already made?
It's more like a pre-made meal kit.
Because...
(Disappointed)
it'll take too long
if we cook it from scratch.
Is it too bland?
No, it's just too sweet.
I think we should add something more.
(Yun So is sticking around Ju Hee.)
The broth.
(Broth tablet)
And...
kimchi broth?
(Stirring)
The ingredients.
It looks good.
(They're having a great time together.)
Yun So is good.
- He's marking his territory.
- He's good.
Yun So is like a reliable ox.
He seems very steadfast and dependable.
That works like magic.
(The kitchen is filled
with their own special chemistry.)
That must feel so good.
We're done.
(The two finished the kimchi stew
together.)
(Jin Woo silently gathers
the tableware...)
(and sets the table by himself.)
(Wiping)
(Doing the dishes too)
He's quite attentive to details.
I was going to do that.
- These need to be washed, right?
- Yes.
- I'll do it.
- You're so quick. Thank you.
It's nothing.
On top of his good looks,
he even takes the initiative
to do the dishes.
I can see a certain warmth in him.
That was quite impressive.
Ji Seung must have voted for Jin Woo.
Ji Seung?
(Did Ji Seung vote for Jin Woo?)
- May I help you chop these together?
- Sure.
I think this would taste delicious
with cream cheese.
- The candied walnuts.
- Right?
(Preparing desserts at the same time)
What is this?
You can try one of the pieces that failed.
Try this failed one.
Oh, my.
(Feeding him)
What?
He didn't even take it with his hand.
- That was smooth.
- He went straight for the bite.
What should we do with him?
He truly embodies
the charm of a younger guy.
Try this failed one.
(Si Won voted for Ji Seung.)
Yes, that's right.
You can just eat it straight.
(Jin Woo picks up a strawberry...)
(and heads somewhere.)
Have a strawberry.
Thank you.
- Have a strawberry.
- Thank you.
Would you like some more?
Oh, my.
During the dinner preparations,
it seemed like...
Jin Woo is showing some interest
in Ji Hye.
(Did Jin Woo vote for Ji Hye?)
Would you like some alcohol?
- Wine, please.
- Wine?
- Cheers.
- It's a small crowd.
(The first dinner at Yeon House
with everyone together)
That must be so good.
It's delicious.
How much can you all drink?
I can drink about three bottles.
- Three bottles of soju?
- Impressive.
- That's a lot.
- Which means he can actually drink four.
Right.
Here he goes again.
He'd probably throw up
and cry after one bottle.
You'd have to put him in a taxi
and send him home.
- You're talking about yourself.
- That's adorable.
You sound very confident.
I can drink that much,
but I don't really drink often.
I see. So you don't drink much.
Are you a drinker?
Me? No. Maybe once a month?
- Since you work out, right?
- Yes.
If it's once a month,
you're basically not a drinker.
- How often do you drink?
- I'm not much of a drinker either.
I can drink maybe half a bottle
to one bottle of wine.
I like wine too.
- Really? Do you prefer white wine?
- Yes.
- You drank white wine earlier.
- I'm not picky about the type.
Really?
I like wine too.
- Si Won is really handsome.
- He really is. I told you.
I think I also drink
once or twice a month.
So none of them are really drinkers.
I don't go out of my way to drink.
Hangovers got worse as I got older.
- As you got older?
- Older?
You're not serious, are you?
That's hilarious.
Am I not allowed to mention age?
Of course not.
(Giggling)
- I'm already tipsy. It's been a while.
- A message just came in.
- I got a message.
- Should we read it together?
Wait. They got a message.
Am I reading this right?
- What's going on?
- What does that mean?
I was honestly shocked
when I got the message.
What is it?
They all look shocked.
I didn't expect them
to reveal it publicly like this.
The mood suddenly turned awkward.
(The people who received zero votes
on the first-impression vote...)
(are Yoo Jin Woo and Park Ji Hye.)
They're announcing it like that?
They literally revealed
who got zero votes by text!
Really?
How are they supposed to recover
from this atmosphere?
Tell me about it.
(The ones who received zero votes
are revealed to everyone.)
Oh, no. They got zero votes.
I suddenly started feeling tipsy.
It still didn't feel real, though.
Seriously, I couldn't believe it.
I read it like five times.
It said nobody chose me
in the first-impression vote.
Look at her expression. It feels so real.
Why did nobody choose me?
Could this really happen to me?
That's brutal.
What am I supposed to do now?
I wanted to go home.
This is harsh.
(Another message is delivered.)
What now?
When I received the second message,
I was shocked again.
What did it say?
(After the zero-vote announcement,)
(Jin Woo and Ji Hye are given
a chance to talk...)
(1-on-1 for 30 minutes
with the person they like.)
They're immediately giving them a benefit.
It says to choose the person you like
right now.
(But only the first person to act
can take the opportunity.)
That totally caught me off guard.
All of a sudden?
The first-impression vote happened...
literally ten minutes after we all met.
So getting zero votes didn't really
mean that much to me.
I just focused on who I wanted to talk to.
Exactly. It's not that big of a deal.
This could actually become an opportunity.
(Who will grab this first-come,
first-served opportunity?)
This is so interesting.
Go now! Move.
Now!
Ju Hee, would you like to come
to the Talk Room with me?
- Me? Yes.
- Yes.
(Jin Woo moves quickly
and takes the opportunity.)
That was actually really brave of him.
(And Ji Hye misses her chance.)
I was too nervous,
so I couldn't ask anyone.
For older women, it's even harder...
to make the first move
in a situation like that.
Because this probably feels
very significant to them.
If I were there and got zero votes,
- there's nothing you can do about it.
- That's true.
I'd say, "If the vote happened right now,
the results would be very different."
And then I'd stare right into the eyes
of the person I liked.
That's such a good move.
That's really attractive.
- You can grab your coat.
- Okay. I'll get mine.
(Moving to the Talk Room)
Yun So looks upset.
(Peeking)
Yun So looks uneasy.
I didn't expect Jin Woo to ask Ju Hee out.
Earlier, we guys talked among ourselves.
He said he was kind of interested
in Yu Jin.
Then why?
(Did Jin Woo choose Yu Jin
in the first-impression vote?)
Did you guys tell each other
who you voted for earlier?
- Yes, we did.
- All of us.
- Really?
- You shared that?
- I voted for Ju Hee.
- Ju Hee? I chose Ji Seung.
I chose Yu Jin.
I heard.
(Jin Woo chose Yu Jin
in the first-impression vote.)
Yu Jin sat right across from me.
As we talked, I kept noticing her
without even realizing it.
We also made eye contact many times.
(While introducing themselves,)
My brother has the same name.
It's an honor.
My strongest first impression of her
was that she seemed very kind.
(But afterward,)
(Jin Woo subtly took care of Ji Hye.)
(And why has he invited Ju Hee
to the Talk Room?)
Honestly,
Ju Hee was the person
I'd talked to the least.
So I became curious
about what she was thinking,
and I invited her.
(He became curious about Ju Hee
because they hadn't talked much.)
Jin Woo said he wanted
to get to know everyone.
He's more cautious than I expected.
(After Jin Woo and Ju Hee left)
It suddenly feels so quiet now
that two people are absent.
- The mood got awkward.
- Really awkward.
- I'm so curious.
- I want to sneak into the Talk Room too.
What are they even talking about in there?
Did you ladies share
who you voted for afterward?
- Share? No.
- The person you voted for.
Did you guys share?
- Yeah, we all talked about it.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- You can do that?
You all know already?
- We do, yes.
- Really?
Are we allowed to share that information?
- They're so different.
- I'm so curious.
The women didn't share anything.
Is that so?
Really?
(Si Won chose Ji Seung
in the first-impression vote.)
(Who did Ji Seung vote for?)
I think she chose Jin Woo.
I picked Si Won
as my favorite first impression.
Really?
He seems so decent.
And I really like his clear eyes.
He has beautiful eyes.
That's why I chose him.
(Ji Seung and Si Won chose each other.)
- That's nice.
- Amazing.
(Who did Ji Hye, who received zero votes,
choose?)
I like masculine men.
Single eyelids and a personality
that feels approachable.
I thought he might actually be cute.
Then it must be Jun Han.
(Did she choose the bubbly Jun Han?)
I'm curious.
(Or the masculine Yun So?)
- I chose Jun Han.
- I told you.
He seems like such a nice guy.
The moment he walked in,
he started smiling.
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Jun Han caught Ji Hye's attention.)
I'm so shy.
I was curious about him
because he seemed fun to talk to.
Ji Hye chose Jun Han
as her favorite first impression.
(Ji Hye liked Jun Han at first sight.)
- Can you do that?
- I know.
(There's another person who chose Jun Han
in the first-impression vote.)
(It's Yu Jin.)
Jun Han turned out to be popular.
I voted for Jun Han.
As soon as he walked in,
I noticed how fit he was.
I wondered whether he works out a lot
or is an athlete.
And I thought
his smile was really beautiful.
My first impression was
that he had a very warm and kind smile.
(Based on first impressions,
who is Jun Han's number one?)
I'm curious.
(Is it Yu Jin?)
(Ji Seung?)
Who is it?
I feel like it's Ji Seung.
I voted for Yu Jin
based on first impressions.
Yu Jin?
We have similar smiles.
I like girls with pretty smiles.
You have such an innocent smile.
- I do?
- Yes.
(They smile in a similar way.)
They do have similar smiles.
(They were each other's number one.)
That's so nice.
They connected.
(Jin Woo and Ju Hee are headed
to the Talk Room.)
(Who did Ju Hee text
based on first impressions?)
I texted Yun So.
- They matched too.
- Yes.
That's interesting.
Yun So was the last to arrive,
but he wasn't too shy to talk
once he sat down.
My name is Lee Yun So.
- Yun So? That's a pretty name.
- Yun Sol?
(Even though Yun So joined them last,
he was relaxed.)
I was sitting close to him,
but I didn't get to talk to him much.
I want to talk to him.
(Ju Hee and Yun So were into each other.)
They liked each other's vibes.
(Without knowing this,
Ju Hee is going to talk to Jin Woo.)
It opened.
(What kind of conversation
will they have?)
Seriously.
- Should we sit like this?
- Just like this. What is this?
- We can't even face each other.
- There's some stuff in here.
I thought I didn't talk to you much...
- I know.
- because we were bust cleaning up.
Also, we were sitting far away
from each other.
- The whole time.
- Yes.
It's non-alcoholic, but it's pretty good.
It doesn't have alcohol in it, right?
You had some alcohol before, right?
Yes. I drank my beer quickly...
because I was thirsty.
Oh, my.
(That's cute.)
What's your type?
- I like a pale guy.
- A pale guy?
- A pale guy with puppy vibes.
- Puppy vibes?
What kind of vibe is that?
A guy who is kind of puppyish.
Doesn't Jin Woo give off puppy vibes?
I hope we have similar hobbies.
I'd like it if we shared the same hobbies.
Me too.
For example...
Yes?
I wanted to sit like this too.
Me too.
This feels a bit damp.
Wouldn't that make your heart pound?
Facing each other like that?
They're sitting like that
to get to know each other more.
That position is too straightforward.
It's like, "Here we go. Focus."
(Zipping down)
Why is he touching his neck?
What is he doing?
He's making flirty moves one by one.
- He's giving subtle signals.
- What are you talking about?
- Is he flirting?
- Yes. He's using it one by one.
(Shy)
Have you always had a bob?
I had long hair,
but I got it cut around January.
- That was recent.
- Yes.
How long was your hair?
It was so long, like down here.
It used to be this long.
Well, this is my first time meeting you.
It really looks good on you.
It suits you.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
What do you do for fun?
I go skiing.
I like horseback riding too.
I used to be
in the YMCA kids' sports team.
I was too.
A lot of people have been
in the YMCA kids' team.
- Right.
- I went to the YMCA for 2 to 3 months.
So, right now,
who's your number one today?
- Number one?
- Your favorite.
(Carefully asking what Ju Hee thinks)
Number one?
It might ruin the fun.
So, how about number two?
Number two?
Way to go!
- Jin Woo is doing a good job.
- That was cute.
Shouldn't I say his name?
Why not?
- I think I shouldn't.
- Why?
You can't say I'm the one?
I'll keep it a secret.
- A secret?
- I'll keep it to myself.
Okay. I understand.
That fuzzy feeling.
Small things make you giggle.
Let's toast.
This isn't alcoholic, right?
Why do I feel tipsy?
It's just zero percent.
This one is zero percent.
I guess I'm just getting tipsy.
For no reason.
That's so cute.
- Jin Woo is determined.
- He is.
(They got lost in the mood
and had a deep conversation.)
(Meanwhile, in the common space)
- Thirty minutes feels quite long.
- I know.
Hasn't it been over 30 minutes already?
Has it?
I wonder what they're talking about.
Indeed.
They're back.
Why is it so cold?
Is it cold?
- It's really cold.
- You guys look happy.
Yun So must've been so nervous
during those 30 minutes.
Did you guys have a good chat?
Yes.
Was the Talk Room nice?
They both...
- look flushed.
- I'm curious.
They look flushed.
Yun So is anxious.
(Once everyone gathers again,
they receive a text.)
A question card?
What is it? I haven't seen it yet.
It says there are question cards
under the table.
- Under the table?
- Underneath?
- Really?
- That's it!
That's fascinating.
- This?
- It sounds like fun.
Yes.
We take turns drawing a card...
and answer the question.
We set up a few things...
so they can open up more naturally.
We prepared question cards
to help them break the ice.
I like it.
- Draw a card.
- Okay.
I'll go first.
(Jun Han goes first.)
"Who do you think
will be the most flirty?"
(Curious)
Jun Han, please answer.
This is fun.
I like the question.
(Who do you think
will be the most flirty?)
(Ji Hye)
- Why?
- What's the reason?
- I feel like...
- Did you feel like I was flirting?
Sometimes, older girls say things...
that make your heart skip a beat.
Did you feel like I was flirting?
This is interesting.
No, I haven't.
Try harder.
"Try harder."
No, I haven't.
- Is that so?
- Try harder.
Should I put in more effort?
"Try harder?"
In what sense?
Your eyes make me think...
you'd be good at flirting.
Really?
- Does she have sexy eyes?
- Yes.
She has charming eyes.
Thank you.
(Glancing over)
Wow.
(Next up is Ju Hee.)
"When do you find a guy the sexiest?"
That's a hard question.
(Thinking)
- It's hard, right?
- Yes.
Yun So is easy to read.
I'm all ears.
He's cute.
I'm paying attention.
When he sees me struggling...
and helps me with it.
When he notices you're struggling?
Yes.
(Glancing)
(Yun So goes next.)
"Who do you think would be the sweetest
in a relationship?"
(Taking a quick look)
This is hard.
(Taking a deep breath)
Why is he pretending to hesitate?
I pick Ju Hee.
- Me?
- Yes.
Yes! Why are you pretending to think?
His head is turning little by little.
Actions come before words.
- I think you'll be so sweet.
- Is that true?
Jin Woo didn't look happy.
- Is he correct?
- I should answer, right?
- Answer?
- You don't really have to.
- Do you want to?
- Well, no.
(A subtle tension between the two)
"Who do you think is the best
at playing hard to get?"
It's the opposite question.
The best at playing hard to get?
For me, it's you.
- Me?
- Jun Han.
(Jun Han would be the best
at playing hard to get.)
- Jun Han?
Looking at it now,
no matter what comes up,
they're just picking the person
they're interested in.
- Right.
- Yes.
Jun Han?
- He might be good at it.
- Why?
- He looks like he would be.
- Really?
(Embarrassed)
- Looks like?
- He seems...
a bit...
- Slick?
- Yes, he has that vibe.
He looks like he dated a lot.
I'll take that as a compliment.
It is a compliment.
- I'll take that as a compliment.
- Right.
That's bothering her,
and it's on her mind.
What?
You should drink for this one.
Answering this?
(What is it?)
- What?
- What is it?
Don't drink. Just tell us!
What is it?
I'm curious.
"Is your first-impression pick
at your left or right?"
Wow, I wonder who it is.
(Roaring)
- Good question!
- Seriously!
(Ji Seung and Yu Jin on the right,
Ju Hee and Ji Hye on the left)
What a coincidence.
If one of the guys sat here...
There are women on both sides.
Yes, there are two on each side.
This is so tough.
I'm curious.
How are they sitting like that?
(Si Won sat between the women.)
He'll pull a killer move after answering.
She's on my right.
Si Won is cool.
He's a cool guy.
(Ji Seung is on his right
and is his first-impression pick.)
I see.
Look at Ji Seung. She's so excited.
(Those on the right are excited,)
Okay.
(while those on the left are disappointed
for no specific reason.)
(Did Si Won's first-impression pick...)
(get through to Ji Seung?)
(Bursting out laughing)
What is it?
"A partner who's kind as an angel
but boring."
"Or a partner who always causes trouble
but gives you a dopamine rush."
Why don't I get questions like that?
Ji Hye, answer this too.
Do it together.
- I want to answer such questions.
- Answer it together.
- I'm curious.
- For me,
it's definitely the former.
- Kind as an angel but boring?
- I choose the former.
I like a boring guy.
I can just be the funny one.
Right, you can.
I don't think she's funny.
Come on, don't say that!
- What's wrong with you?
- Ji Seung hasn't cracked us up yet.
- What about you, Ji Hye?
- The dopamine guy.
Okay, but I figured.
(Ji Seung and Ji Hye have
opposite personalities.)
- Two first-impression picks.
- Is it "Up and Down?"
(You have two first-impression picks.
Is your answer up or down?)
This is easy.
It is.
He should go with "down."
It has to be "down," so...
- He must pick it to go to Ju Hee.
- You're right.
You can be strategic with this.
So you have two first-impression picks?
But you are all charming.
He just picks everyone.
- You like all of them?
- Do you like them all?
Yes.
(Does Jin Woo really mean that?)
- He's really like a younger brother.
- I bet...
Jin Woo seems to have just reached
the legal age of adulthood.
Like yesterday.
(Quickly passing to Yu Jin)
- What will it be?
- It's so hard.
This is fun!
- It feels like a game.
- Yes.
(They can read each other's feelings
without pressure.)
"Who seems the most different
from his first impression?"
It's Yun So.
(Yun So)
(Surprised)
I think he is. He looks cold at first,
but he'd be really caring
once you get to date him.
- He'd be so sweet.
- Yes, he'd be warm, sweet,
and only have eyes
for the person he likes.
Thank you.
I think he would.
Interesting.
This looks like a good question.
- This one?
- Yes.
You want to get it, Ji Hye?
- What is it?
- Quick, answer it.
- What's the question?
- "A physical touch rookie"...
"versus a physical touch master."
A master, of course.
It's clear she's into dopamine.
She really is a mature woman.
Obviously.
I want to ask.
How good should you be to be a master?
You keep thinking about it
after you leave.
- How many times a day?
- Hye Jin, stop.
- That's enough.
- Why? It pops into your head,
- and you miss them.
- Just drink your soy milk.
Fine.
(The question time
for sharing honest feelings is over.)
- What time are you going tomorrow?
- Sorry?
For running.
Are you running tomorrow?
- I should start tomorrow.
- You are?
Are you running every day?
How far do you run?
Five kilometers.
Let me join you.
Are you okay with six minutes
and 50 seconds?
Yes, I can adjust to anything.
Okay.
Did you bring five workout outfits?
- I brought seven.
- Seven?
(Shocked)
- You're serious about it.
- I'm going all in on running.
I can run just twice.
I have two spare sets of workout outfits.
I'll lend you one.
You will?
Good idea.
Are you okay with...
- cropped zip-up and leggings?
- That's cool.
- Are you sure?
- I like it.
I also have two workout outfits.
I'll lend you some.
Gosh.
This startles me.
(A message arrives at the Yeon House.)
(Leave an anonymous Love QR
to your pick back in your room.)
Finally, a Love QR!
It's really happening.
It's suddenly getting tough.
This is fun...
because you just don't send texts.
You can also send videos, photos,
and voice messages.
- You can send anything.
- Right.
(Who will receive the Love QRs...)
(from the older women and younger guys?)
(Si Won and Yun So's room)
I'm dying to know who Jin Woo picked.
I wonder what he'll do
or what he's thinking about.
They both like Ju Hee.
Yes. Honestly,
- I don't get why he chose her there.
- Exactly.
- Suddenly?
- I think he kept her...
as his second choice.
He said all four of them were charming.
I guess he's keeping all options open.
He probably thinks
of meeting everyone at least once.
I should take photos now.
Can we take them here?
Well.
There's nothing to shoot.
- Then let's go out and take photos.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- Are you coming with me?
Yes.
(Clicking)
I can't wait.
This is quite fun to watch too.
I'll be right back.
Are you here for photos?
Where are you going?
(Taking photos without a word)
They're working so hard.
I kind of get it, though.
Wait. How do you get it?
What photos do I send?
(Meanwhile, the women)
Is it not what you expected at first?
It's a bit different for me.
- Me too.
- It's more like "Truth or Dare."
- Does it feel different afterward?
- Yes.
- If anything.
- Really?
(Have her feelings changed
after the question card time?)
- I had to think for around five minutes.
- Me too.
So when the guys...
picked so quickly,
I was really surprised.
I guess it's just this.
Don't think too much
and focus on this moment.
Choose the one
who attracted you more today.
- Today?
- Today.
(Maybe send it to the person
you were most drawn to.)
(Ji Hye and Ju Hee's room)
This is so hard.
Don't you think it's hard...
- since we still don't know yet?
- Yes.
- Right?
- We might have to wait until tomorrow...
to find out.
It's too early.
- They're so serious.
- Is it supposed to be this hard?
(Women are deep in thought unlike guys.)
Should this be this tough?
(A Love QR has arrived.)
It's the time.
(Go to the QR room
and find out the sender's feelings.)
(The secret space is finally open.)
Let's go. I can't wait.
(Prepared inside the QR Room is...)
(each participant's Love QR.)
(Scanning one's own QR...)
(allows them to check
the messages sent to them.)
(Did they manage
to connect with each other?)
That was the very place where
laughter and tears crossed paths.
Utilizing a QR code is quite innovative
because they can also send videos.
They could imagine all sorts of things,
wondering what it could possibly be.
(The one heading
to the QR Room first is...)
(Yu Jin.)
(Yu Jin received two votes
in the first impression vote...)
(from Jun Han and Jin Woo.)
(How many QRs did Yu Jin receive?)
(Yu Jin cautiously scans her QR.)
What could it be?
(Did she receive two votes
just like the first impression vote?)
Let's take a guess.
(How many guys would've voted for her?)
- How many?
- I say Jun Han and Jin Woo.
My prediction is that...
Jun Han might have changed his mind...
since it was interesting
to talk with Ji Hye.
- Do you really think so?
- Jin Woo also...
might have also chosen Ju Hee
instead of Yu Jin.
- I'm sure Jun Han voted for her.
- Really?
What do you think? How many votes
do you think Yu Jin will get?
She will definitely get
at least two votes.
- Does that include your own vote as well?
- My own vote?
If I include my own vote,
it would be three votes.
(How many Love QRs
did Yu Jin actually receive?)
- What?
- Maybe there's none. I'm telling you.
No way. Yu Jin definitely got some.
(You have received no Love QR.)
(Shocked)
See? I told you she didn't have any.
- How can this be possible?
- This doesn't make any sense.
- Then, what about my vote?
- Yu Jin was nice to everyone.
Jun Han was probably attracted to Ji Hye
because she casually tossed him attention.
- So, Jun Han cast his vote for Ji Hye?
- Jin Woo led...
- a one-on-one conversation earlier.
- Did he vote for Ju Hee then?
Yes.
I completely understand
the psychology of younger men.
(He has a Younger guy PhD.)
- DinDin, please teach me later.
- No problem.
I caught on to the situation immediately.
DinDin is absolutely amazing.
(Yu Jin did not receive a QR from anyone.)
Well,
all right.
Oh, no.
It's okay.
I can receive many votes in the future.
Yu Jin used to smile so brightly
before this happened.
(Glancing)
(Yu Jin ranked first in the first
impression vote but got no QR.)
- It's so shocking, seriously.
- How can this happen?
I'll be back.
(Jun Han got the most votes
in the first impression vote.)
He was the popular guy.
(How many Love QRs did he get?)
Wow.
Please.
(He's extremely nervous
checking his first Love QR.)
Please.
(Startled)
I think he probably received votes
from Yu Jin and Ji Hye again.
I also think he must have
definitely received a vote from Ji Hye.
(How many Love QRs did Jun Han get?)
(You have received no Love QR.)
- Hold on. Maybe it's not updated yet.
- That's ridiculous.
Jun Han didn't receive any either?
I guess it's something like this.
Since he seems too smooth and experienced,
the ladies might feel...
that he is not exactly the type
of younger man they expected.
Are you saying that the flutter has gone?
Then, who did Yu Jin vote for,
looking so disappointed
that no one chose her?
You're right.
What happened?
Neither of them has a reason
to be disappointed, then.
But they're both so disappointed.
Hold on.
(He checks his Love QR again
due to the unexpected result.)
(But the result stays the same.)
There's nothing.
I really never expected to get zero votes.
I was so shocked
as soon as I received the result.
I was devastated.
I think joking around too much
during our first meeting...
made me appear a bit insincere.
The ladies might have indeed
perceived him that way.
You look like a classic beauty.
Miss Pretty.
Can you kiss a boyfriend
who has just eaten green onions?
Everyone has a beautiful smile.
(Jun Han made light jokes
to get close quickly.)
I'm honored to be with pretty ladies.
(Did Jun Han's behavior
make him appear a bit insincere?)
Since I naturally have a playful image,
I thought I should use it
to show off my charms.
It backfired,
making me look too insincere
for a first impression.
I deeply regret making those remarks.
Oh, no.
(He looks back on the moments
he regrets now.)
Okay. Let's try harder.
They were the popular ones.
(The third one to check the QR is Ji Hye.)
(Ji Hye got no votes
for the first impression vote.)
(Can she get a different result
this time?)
She could get four votes.
(Trembling)
Since I received zero votes
during the first impression vote,
I was so scared to check the QR.
(She checks her Love QR
with a trembling heart.)
(You have received two Love QRs.)
- Two people!
- Congratulations!
See? You never know.
(Ji Hye was chosen by two younger guys.)
(Grinning)
I managed to restore
my self-esteem at that moment.
I realized that I still have
what it takes.
She's so happy.
(What's the first QR
that arrived for her?)
- What is that?
- "You must be tired. Sleep tight."
(What's this?)
Who can tell just from that?
I think he took a photo of the view
from his room and sent it to me.
(What is the second Love QR she received?)
Yeon House?
It looks like the signpost
at the entrance.
I really don't know who this is.
I have absolutely no idea.
I don't even have a clue.
Seriously.
(Snap)
My first impression of Yu Jin
was really good.
But visually, Ji Hye is much closer
to my ideal type.
Ji Hye said that dopamine is
what matters in a relationship.
Since Yeon House stands for dopamine,
I took a picture of the "Yeon House" sign.
It's a total dopamine rush itself.
(Ji Hye's second QR was a photo
sent by Jun Han.)
(Then who could have sent the first QR?)
Who could that be?
Si Won?
It's Jin Woo.
- I think it's Jin Woo.
- Yes.
Or is it Yun So?
(First Love QR)
(The sender of the QR is hard to guess.)
I'm just grateful if anyone sends me one.
I'm going to get to know everyone
one by one.
I want to talk to everyone a lot.
Among them,
I think I'll choose the person
who's the most fun, easy to talk to,
and has the best chemistry.
(The next guest in the QR Room is Ju Hee.)
(Ju Hee, who received
one first impression vote from Yun So)
(Did she receive a Love QR this time too?)
I think Jin Woo will be there.
No, there are two.
Jin Woo and Yun So went.
I also think Jin Woo will be there.
No, I think Yun So sent his vote here.
(You have received one Love QR.)
I think it's Yun So.
- It's Yun So.
- Yun So?
You're doing great.
(Smiling)
Perilla oil kimchi stew?
They cooked together earlier.
Right.
He took a picture
of the kimchi stew packaging and sent it.
I have absolutely no idea who it is.
Pardon?
What's wrong with her now?
But actually,
Yun So expressed his feelings
very directly only to Ju Hee.
- He didn't do that to the others.
- Right.
(Who is the younger man
who sent the kimchi stew photo?)
It's Yun So.
I sent my QR to Ju Hee.
I should send it like this.
There's some residual heat left.
(They struggled because the seasoning
in the stew wouldn't dissolve properly.)
We once put a seasoning ring
into the kimchi stew.
Since that feels like the starting point
for the two of us,
I took a picture of the seasoning ring
and sent it.
(It is a symbol of a new beginning.)
But the person involved doesn't even know.
- Why doesn't she know?
- Because she's not interested.
That makes sense.
(Is Ju Hee really not interested
in Yun So?)
(Where did Ju Hee's Love QR go?)
(Next up is Jin Woo, who got 0 votes
in the first impression vote.)
Now, how many QRs did he receive?
(Sighs)
- Come on.
- Zero again?
- I think it'll be zero.
- Something feels off.
I don't think he received any.
I have a feeling.
Maybe he received one from Ju Hee?
(Smirks)
(You have received no Love QR.)
Poor Jin Woo.
I already had a bad feeling...
because I didn't get
any first impression votes.
Something felt off.
Seeing the heartbreaking results,
I was down all day.
Oh, Jin Woo.
I think I'm only popular among flies.
I can't watch this.
(Jin Woo trying to crack a joke)
(Returning to the room
with mixed feelings)
(Sighs)
It's so sad to watch Jin Woo.
(Continuous sighing)
Starting tomorrow,
I think I should take the initiative
to talk more.
(The younger man Jin Woo strengthens
his resolve for tomorrow.)
He needs to shake that off quickly.
The older women didn't vote for him
at all?
Not a single one. Two men with zero votes.
(The sixth visitor to the QR Room,
the younger man Yun So)
I'm so curious.
(Who did Yun So receive a QR from?)
(Sighs)
Yun So could have 4 votes right now or 0.
(Taking a deep breath and scanning the QR)
Huh?
Scanning it one more time?
- There's none?
- It's Si Won, then.
(Are the remaining votes all for Si Won?)
(You have received three Love QRs.)
(Wow)
Three people?
What did Yun So actually do?
As expected, it's that.
- As expected.
- What is it?
Just being steadfast?
- Not showing off?
- Right.
Because he might be
the exact opposite of Jun Han,
who got zero votes.
Right.
"The others are a bit playful,
but this guy is steadfast."
There could be something like that.
Honestly, I really didn't expect it.
I was flustered that I got three,
but I'm grateful.
(What is the first Love QR?)
She sent a photo of workout outfits?
(Someone's workout outfits photo)
(What is the second QR Yun So received?)
"I'll look forward to the swimming pool."
They must have talked
about the swimming pool.
(Snickers)
(What is the meaning
of Yun So's laughter?)
(The last QR for Yun So)
"I want to go for a walk together."
"Go for a walk together." Who could it be?
(The last QR is someone
asking him out on a date.)
Congratulations, Yun So.
(Yun So received Love QRs
from 3 older women.)
I kind of expected Yu Jin,
but I really didn't expect the others.
Yu Jin seems to really love running,
so I think it's Yu Jin.
(The first QR
with the workout outfits photo...)
(was Yu Jin's message.)
Then shall we go
for a light three-kilometer run?
I can run just twice.
I have two spare sets of workout outfits.
Really? I'll lend you some.
Seriously?
That sounds good.
When we talk,
he's very witty.
I want to get to know him.
Do we have good chemistry?
I want to check that out too.
(The workout outfits photo
was Yu Jin's QR.)
The swimsuit one must be Ji Hye,
who loves dopamine the most.
I sent my Love QR to Yun So.
Shall I go first?
My name is Lee Yun So.
At first, I thought he looked very cold.
But...
Would you like a Coke?
(Spilling)
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Is that how you hand it over?
She finds it cute.
I saw a bit of his clumsy side,
so I was curious.
If we meet and talk,
I think I might find him cute.
He has those kinds of charms.
Please make sure to eat some rice.
I don't eat it.
- You said you don't eat rice.
- Yes.
He's cutting off carbs
and dieting right now.
So it sparked my curiosity,
and I thought it would be fun
to go on a date together.
("Yun So, I'll look forward
to the swimming pool.")
(It was the QR sent
by dopamine lover Ji Hye.)
(And the third Love QR Yun So received)
("I want to go for a walk together.")
Who is it?
"Go for a walk together"...
He can't figure out
who the last person is.
- Could it be Ji Seung?
- "A walk?"
Ju Hee?
I wanted to talk to Yun So,
so I sent my QR to him.
Right, right.
I wanted to chat while taking a walk.
They say it will be warm tomorrow,
so I sent the QR to suggest a walk
in the afternoon.
Right. You did well.
(The last Love QR was Ju Hee's message)
("I want to go for a walk together.")
(Ju Hee and Yun So)
(Both their first impressions and Love QRs
were directed at each other.)
(Then, who is the older woman
Jin Woo sent his Love QR to?)
(It was Ji Hye,
whom he had handed a strawberry.)
- Have a strawberry.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Right.
- Is it Ji Hye?
Giving her that strawberry took
a lot of courage,
even when she seems a bit cold.
(Jin Woo deliberating in his room for a
long time before sending the Love QR)
("You must be tired. Sleep tight.")
(He opened the door of his room
and took a picture.)
I sent the QR to Ji Hye.
Because...
She is the closest to my ideal type,
looks-wise.
So I want to spend more time...
with Ji Hye.
Isn't Jin Woo funny?
He picked Yu Jin for his first impression,
went Talk Room with Ju Hee,
and then said Ji Hye is his ideal type.
Gosh, he's so cute.
(So cute!)
From now on, I want Jin Woo
to keep his thoughts to himself.
He's so cute.
In case a new person might come.
(The 7th guest in the QR Room is
Ji Seung.)
(Looking around)
(Anticipation)
How do I do this?
I think these two sent it to each other.
There is no way they haven't.
It's certain.
(Ji Seung received
the photo of a wine bottle.)
It was a photo of wine.
I think that might be Si Won.
We briefly talked about wine in passing.
(Who is the younger man who sent
the Love QR to Ji Seung?)
Since we talked about our taste of wine
at the gathering...
I thought she might know it's me
if I send a photo of wine.
They've talked about the wine.
("Thank you for making me feel
at ease at the start.")
(A vague message,
hard to tell who sent it)
I haven't particularly tried
to ease anyone's nerves.
Still, I hope it's from Ji Seung today.
(The person who sent the QR
to Si Won was Ji Seung)
- Shall I help with something here, too?
- It's okay.
He was the first one
to strike up a conversation.
He seemed to pay attention
to even the smallest things.
Because of that, my nerves settled down
quite a bit.
I wish tomorrow would come already...
so that I can go on a new date.
They look good together.
(Constantly changing minds,
an unpredictable first night)
(Next to the lounge,
the deepest part of Yeon House)
(There's the Secret Room.)
There must be a hint.
To guess.
Oh, they can find out information
from there?
I think there will be some hints.
(A place that opens only
for the person with the most Love QRs)
(Open the drawer and guess the age
of the person you are curious about.)
(What you find out should
remain a secret.)
(The Secret Room has opened.)
(Who will be the first person
to open the drawer?)
(The one who enters the Secret Room is...)
(Ji Hye.)
Ji Hye.
(Ji Hye, who received 2 Love QRs
from Jun Han and Jin Woo)
(Which of the younger man Ji Hye wants
to know about?)
Who could it be?
(What will Ji Hye's choice be?)
(The second day morning,
the younger men's Choice Date)
(Today's date is first-come, first-served)
- First-come, first-served?
- First-come, first-served. I'm going.
I'm going too.
(The younger men leaving
without hesitation)
I left right away
because I wanted to secure my date.
(Knock, knock)
Would you like to go on a date
with me today?
Let's go on a date.
(Rekindling the excitement
they had forgotten)
(Building the first memory
between the two of them)
Your smile is really pretty.
(Their feelings are growing.)
We had a lot in common.
Have you dated a younger guy before?
Why do you ask?
Do you want to be the one?
It's so pretty here.
But you are prettier.
(Bold flirting
that only a younger man could pull off)
(Meanwhile,
a sports car is cutting through the road.)
I plan to go straight for it
without playing any games.
(The appearance of a new older woman
who will shake up Yeon House)
Everyone, sorry for the intrusion.
Dramaday.me