( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Pull up!
Pull!
During World War II,
the Imperial Japanese Army
marched into the Asia-Pacific.
The Thai government allowed
the Japanese to build a railway
from Thailand to Burma
for the transport of troops and weapons.
Chief, we lost contact with the soldiers
sent to retrieve the prisoners.
Right.
Bring them back, whatever it takes.
Yes, sir.
- What should we do. Help out!
- Yes.
Commander.
Why is the construction work
in your sector moving so slowly?
Forgive me, Commander.
We're short on labor.
I've already brought in
a number of natives to help.
Make them work harder.
Round the clock, day and night.
But I've already
pushed them to their limit.
Those men are idling.
Why aren't they working?
But it's their break, sir--
Stop giving them breaks.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Commander,
permission to round up
more service girls, sir.
Make sure to keep a nice one for me.
Yes, sir.
Back to the villa!
I've been tasked by the Japanese Army
to oversee the construction of the railway
across the border from Thailand to Burma.
Come on! Keep at it!
We need a large labor force
for the project.
Our workers are mostly prisoners of war
and ethnic locals
who live along the border.
‎You idiots!
- Wait!
- Come on!
‎Are you being lazy?
Get up!
You lazy-ass!
‎Get to work!
Get up!
‎-Hurry up!
‎-Hold on...
Faster!
‎Do it right!
‎-Hurry!
But one of the ethnic tribes
refused to cooperate
and declared themselves our enemy.
Arrest all of them.
So, Commander Nakamura
raided their village
and forced them to work for us.
- Find them! Don't let them escape!
- Where are they?
Their leader, Nortong, managed to escape.
‎Go find them!
Since then,
Nortong has repeatedly slipped
into our camp
and freed several of our prisoners.
Nortong is a dangerous malcontent
whom we want captured,
no matter dead or alive.
- Kill it!
- Yes!
What the hell's happening?
Keep moving!
We can't, sir!
Fuck!
You bastard!
Die!
What the fuck is that thing?
The soldiers we sent went missing.
The locals tell of a vile demon dwelling
in the mountains,
something resembling a monster
in the Japanese folklore
called "Omukade".
Boss,
we want to quit.
You have a contract.
You can't leave.
Go back to work.
Morning, sir.
Good morning, Akira-san.
A cigarette?
I don't smoke.
Is there anything I can do for you?
I need more laborers.
I've already rounded up
the whole province.
If you want more, I have to bring them
from another province,
and that'll cost more.
Not a problem.
I'm happy to pay.
Give me a few days.
I'll leave it to you, Boonchu-san.
My pleasure, sir.
Let's go.
- Who's this?
- Hey.
A new girl.
For the commander.
Alright.
Where's the girl?
Upstairs, sir.
You look tasty.
Where is it?
You'll fucking die.
Commander.
Ma-oo.
Where did you get that girl?
She asked for work.
I knew nothing about her background.
Never thought she could do
such a vile thing.
I have nothing to do with her.
Tell me where you found her!
Renja, stop!
No!
That's enough.
Chief!
A prisoner has escaped.
A British soldier.
The passcode.
Follow me.
Who's this white man?
Why do we have to help him?
He's an officer from our side.
We can't leave him to die here.
Hey, Sanor.
‎Hey!
Hey! Is the raft ready?
Yes.
Stay right there!
Drop your gun.
Please, sir.
If you let us go,
I'll give you
- all this money.
- I don't take bribes.
Take me with you.
This is my mission.
You're not part of it.
Are you sure?
My wage.
Shitty cig!
Take me with you now!
Adam, get the supply.
Move!
Maybe Nortong's the one
helping them escape.
Radio the Burmese troop
to intercept and capture them.
Is that your brilliant idea?
This is our job.
We have to finish it ourselves.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
A Western cigarette?
We'll have to go through this mine.
Does it stretch all the way to Burma?
This mine
was dug in the time of my father,
but it was shut down
when the war broke out.
Have you gone all the way through before?
Why are you so sure
it'll take us to Burma?
My father used to work here.
Then why isn't he here to guide us?
Don't panic.
My father's drawn me a map.
I can take you through it.
Let's stop here to eat,
then we'll continue.
Don't let me see your face again.
Die!
Don't kill them.
What're you waiting for?
I have to interrogate them first
to find out who's behind this.
Get them.
You!
Boonchu.
You betrayed me.
There were five of them.
Where are the other two?
- Follow them.
- Yes.
Ota, Ito.
Come with me.
Right.
Tie these two up.
Don't move.
Stay still.
Sanor.
Renja!
Found them?
No.
If you can't find them, stay here!
Find them.
Right.
‎Let's go.
Shit!
‎Look!
Goddamnit!
Shit!
Fall back!
Sato!
Ito!
Ota!
Ota.
I won't make it.
You'll be fine.
Good luck.
Long live...
the Emperor.
Help.
Help me.
Please.
What're you doing?
Help.
Help me.
Don't do it!
Damn you!
Sato!
Sato.
You knew, right?
You knew the Allies' planes
were going to bomb this cave.
You should thank me.
I saved your life.
If you'd been at the camp,
you'd have been bombed to shreds.
Bastard!
You're no different from me.
You said you were our friend,
but you betrayed the Thai people!
But soon you'll fucking lose the war!
No! We won't!
When the railway is completed,
Japan will be victorious!
Your railway was already destroyed
by the bombs.
You're war criminals.
You're no victors!
Tamaura!
I'm sorry.
Sato.
What happened to Sato?
- Wait, this...
- Sato...
We have to go.
Must be the white men's bombers.
- Sanor.
- What?
Did you know
they were going to bomb this place?
I didn't.
Boonchu only hired me
to take that white prisoner away.
They must've waited until he was safe
before attacking.
But why save only one man?
That's Boonchu's instruction.
The rest isn't important to us.
This fucker works for the Japs.
Sanor, you betrayed me!
The necklace.
The necklace!
Sanor.
Sato!
Chief,
if we lose the war,
do we have any choice other than suicide?
Chief, how can my wife and child live?
Keep your spirit up.
We're not going to lose.
The rocks have blocked all the exits.
We have to find another way out.
Right, sir.
Chief, I have an idea.
Let's blast our way out
with these dynamites.
We can't do that,
or we'll end up like Ota.
Ota...
What happened to him?
- Ota.
- Tamura!
Ota!
- Ota!
- Calm down, Tamura.
Ota!
What the hell is this?
Where's Ota?
Damn!
Sanor. What're you doing?
I'm going down to get the necklace.
Hold on.
What necklace?
My father made it for me.
Sanor.
I'll go.
Hold this.
Sanor!
I found it.
Who's there?
Who are you?
I'm out.
What turned Ravi into that thing?
Maybe this is what happened
to the miners who disappeared.
Have you heard anything about it before?
My father told me.
Why didn't your father come?
He's disappeared
since the last time
he broke the prisoners out.
But I believe that he's still alive.
Relax, it's me!
Fuck, it's Boonchu.
Fuck, it's not Boonchu.
Aim!
Stop!
Are you alright?
‎Are you alright?
We have to go.
Why are you siding with the Japanese?
Akira saved me when I caught malaria.
He then asked me to work for him.
But they razed our village.
Don't you feel anything?
Renja, you've spent too much time
with the Japanese
and become one of them.
I...
am on your side, Sanor.
What's this? Must be something big.
Maybe the molt of some reptile.
The Omukade...
There's light over there.
Sanor...
Don't move.
The Omukade is a monster
in Japanese folklore.
It hides in the bodies
of animals or humans.
We must get out of here.
Talk later.
- Renja.
- Watch out, sir.
The creature is inside him.
Why did you do that?
Legend has it that
smearing saliva on a blade
will let it cut through the monster.
- Come on.
- Wait.
The Omukade is afraid of fire.
But he's holding a torch.
Where have you been?
Do you know the cave entrance
has been blocked?
I do.
I'm looking for a way out.
Where's Boonchu?
Sanor.
Renja.
- Renja!
- Hey!
Sanor.
Stop!
Renja.
Be careful.
‎Huh?
Nortong.
Master...
Recognize this?
What are you doing?
Blow into it, and I'll come to you
whenever you get lost.
Right.
Sanor...
Run!
- Chief, run!
- Yeah.
Master.
Why are you here?
I was helping the prisoner escape
when the monster suddenly appeared
and killed everyone.
Good thing I fell into a hole
between the rocks.
It was too massive to slip through.
That's how I survived.
Where did you get it?
I found it.
Sanor must've dropped it.
My daughter is here?
Yes, Master.
But...
I have no idea where she is now.
That old creep,
why was he so angry seeing us?
Our uniform isn't the most loved
around here.
Should we take it off then?
The molt of the Tabongplum Centipede.
Rub it on your body,
and it'll think we're one of them.
Anything there?
Chief,
if we can't find an exit,
what will happen to us?
Then we'll rot in here.
In that case, we should go back to Renja.
He must have some ideas.
I guess so.
Master, how far is it?
The mine is deep under the water.
We have to dive through it...
to find an exit.
Why haven't you escaped then?
It's not as simple as it sounds.
Master.
Sanor's not far.
Master. Let's go find Sanor.
These centipedes are slaves
of the Tabongplum.
They're an ancient species dwelling here
through the centuries.
So huge and lethal,
they can fell an elephant.
Their venomous fangs
can incapacitate their prey.
Then they drill into the paralyzed flesh,
turning their prey into walking monsters
that serve them in turn.
Are they there?
Those cadavers we just passed
were once miners who worked here.
Now they've become god-knows-what.
Some of them were captured
and fed to the young.
I think
Sanor must have been taken here too.
The queen is hatching.
We must find Sanor now!
Sanor!
Luckily I put saliva on the sword.
What on earth are those things?
Same thing that happened to Boonchu.
Chief.
- Let's keep going.
- Yeah.
What the fuck!
Hang in there, sir!
Keep moving!
Tamura!
Chief!
My wife and child...
Please take care of them.
Renja.
Father.
Sanor.
Come here, now!
Come, child!
Get up!
Hurry!
Follow me!
Run!
Hurry!
Watch out!
Renja!
It's collapsing!
Run!
Renja!
Sanor!
Sanor.
- Sanor.
Sanor...
I don't want to see your face again.
Watch out!
Everybody loves and is ready
to protect their homeland.
In the face of invasion,
we must fight to the death
to save the home we vow never to lose.
Like the Omukade fighting
without any fear of death
to protect its nest.
If I could choose,
I would never want to be the invader.
But in reality,
I didn't have a choice.
Long live... the Emperor.
After Japan lost the war,
I was taken as a prisoner of war.
But that made me feel
the taste of freedom.
The future, once darkened,
has become brighter.
The wounds that all of us sustained
from the war slowly begin to fade.