( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
The first round is over.
Now we enter the second round.
If any guests wish to stop,
please leave Baihua Pavilion now.
You monsters!
You play with our lives like a game!
Don't you owe us an explanation?
Yes.
Give us an explanation!
Exactly.
You must give us an explanation today.
Yes.
This is your reward.
This is a Longevity Pill
extracted from a Demon Core.
Taking it will prolong your life
and cure your diseases.
For those without illness,
it can extend your life by seven years.
The reward for the second round
is the Purple Gold Pill.
Taking it will cleanse your marrow
and give you a new life.
Excuse me,
can it cure the chronic poison of the Qijue Flower?
It's Prime Minister Lin.
May I ask if it's your wife who is poisoned?
Yes.
As expected of Baihua Pavilion.
Gathering intel right under the nose of Great Qian,
you guys are really something.
You flatter me, Prime Minister Lin.
Taking the Purple Gold Pill can cleanse the marrow,
which is like getting a brand-new body.
Your wife's poison
is nothing to worry about.
Prime Minister Lin.
So you've known all along
the background of Baihua Pavilion,
yet you did nothing.
Your Ma...
Just call me Miss.
To answer you, Miss,
not only do noble families have shares here,
but Dowager Consort Hua also takes a cut.
I...
I had no way to touch them.
Prime Minister Lin,
go back.
The second round is not for ordinary people to challenge.
Keep your life
and serve the country well.
Forgive me, but I cannot obey.
My wife
doesn't have much time left.
Do you think passing the round
will guarantee you the pill?
I have to try anyway.
What if I order you to go back?
Then please, Your Majesty,
use the Shanhe Sword
to execute me.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
May the Emperor be well.
Ruling the lands,
reigning over the world.
This Lin Youtang is so annoying.
I have social anxiety.
You just had to expose me.
You may all rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
why did you come in?
Yes,
it's too dangerous here.
Baihua Pavilion used your lives as a threat
to force Her Majesty to enter.
They said three attendants were allowed,
but Her Majesty couldn't bear to put you in danger,
so she came to take the test herself.
Your Majesty risked your life for us.
We will follow you to the death.
Yes.
Everyone.
I won't tell you to give up seeking wealth in danger.
But this Baihua Pavilion
is actually a conspiracy
set up in Daqian by the enemy state, Beijing.
In this first trial,
I, along with Imperial Censor Lin Mo,
and Su Wuhui, Chief of Tianji Pavilion,
will do our best to keep everyone alive.
This...
But for the second trial,
if you insist on participating,
then life and death are up to fate,
and wealth is up to heaven.
We
can no longer help you.
Chancellor Lin,
where is the Zijin Pill?
I'll go get it for you.
My chances of passing
are definitely higher than yours.
Alright.
Given the circumstances,
there's no time for pleasantries.
I, Lin Youtang,
owe you two lives.
Your Majesty.
Everyone.
I, Lin Youtang, will be here
awaiting your triumphant return.
Please follow me
to wait outside.
Okay.
Let's go.
Old hag,
can you block it?
You brat!
Die!
Let me go!
The Xue family helped the Su family to the throne.
We just want some reward.
Why are you doing this, niece?
No!
Let me go!
Help!
Xue Qian!
Wancai!
Save me!
You dog.
You only get a dozen taels of silver a month.
Why risk your life for it?
Are these your last words?
Let me tell you,
except for the Shanhe Sword,
no weapon in the world can kill me.
I...
I can't use the Shanhe Sword anymore.
Then...
I'll kill you, the shape-shifting spiritual dog,
and then enjoy your master's body.
Wancai!
How are you, Wancai?
Su Ningxue,
look at him.
This is the beast you raised.
Too weak.
Let her go!
What's wrong?
Are you going to turn back to your original form to fight me?
You don't deserve it. No!
No!
Wancai!
You are a human,
not a dog.
It doesn't matter what he is.
I told you,
except for the Shanhe Sword,
no weapon can kill me.
But you can't use the Shanhe Sword anymore.
Let go!
Shanhe Sword.
She can't use it,
but I can.
Go to hell,
you disgusting family.
Lin Mo!
Why are you so late?
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Good thing you're okay.
Tonight, you and I
will be in this Empress Dowager's palace,
making a little prince.
Naughty.
You!
Why can you wield the Shanhe Sword?
We are husband and wife.
If she can use it,
of course I can.
What?
You seem a little dissatisfied.
If you're dissatisfied, just make a move.
You are just her guard.
No,
guardian beast.
Know your place.
Wancai.
Don't be rude.
What?
You want her?
I'll give you the Shanhe Sword.
Kill me,
and the Shanhe Sword is yours.
And she will be yours too.
Do it.
Although Lin Mo isn't likable,
he's definitely not
an idiot like you.
You didn't disappoint me.
Touch the bronze mirror
to enter the second level.
Your Majesty.
I will go in first.
Be careful.
Yaoniang,
did Liu Wancai just
enter the second level directly?
He is a shapeshifting demon.
The rules of the first level
pose no threat to him.
So the Tower Master
let him enter the second level directly.
So if we had just attacked you at the same time,
we could have skipped the first level directly?
Mr. Lin found out.
The first level
is my domain.
If you know the trick,
you can choose to skip it.
Unfortunately,
you didn't realize it.
That bastard.
It's fine.
Since it has come to this,
we just have to deal with the upcoming dangers.
Hold this,
and enter the bronze mirror.
Remember,
hold it tightly
and don't let go.
Hold it tight.
Hold it tightly.
Mr. Lin,
why do you keep staring at me?
The plum blossoms on your shoulder,
the dancer has them too,
only in a greater number.
Your levels
are inversely proportional to the number of plum blossoms.
Nothing can escape your eyes, Mr. Lin.
These petals represent the level of us hair demons.
Our true form
only has one plum blossom.
You have three.
The master of Baihua Tower,
Liu Ruyan,
should have one.
You're not the second-in-command.
If you really want to know, Mr. Lin,
you can find out for yourself.
This second level
won't be easy to pass.
You are right.
Going through the illusion alone
is indeed a bit difficult.
But it might not be for two.
Grafting,
activate.
It hurts.
Let go.
You,
why are you so strong?
Don't you want to have a child?
Didn't you ask me to hold it?
You can actually shift your position.
This cheat code is not bad.
You know about this too?
That day,
when you made the Minister of Revenue tell the truth,
I already guessed it.
As expected of a bookworm.
It seems
all karma
has finally come full circle.
Let's go,
break through the barrier.
A talent of a Qilin.
Unfortunately,
he cannot be used by us.
Hurry up.
They're out.
Prime Minister Lin.
I didn't expect you to be inside.
I'm so glad you're fine.
There is no problem with these people.
They are all citizens of Daqian.
You shouldn't have just brought the soldiers.
You should also bring doctors here.
Yes.
Prime Minister Lin.
I'll do it right away.
Coming.
You look like someone from a wealthy family.
Pick whatever you like.
Take your time.
You can't go in.
If it were a few years ago,
I would've killed you with one strike.
You should be glad
that Daqian respects the law.
Peasant.
Send a message.
The secret passage has been discovered.
Tell everyone to evacuate.
Who are we sending the message to, boss?
To my wife at home.
Send it to Beijing.
Sister,
take them down.
Go.
A perfect match,
and a prosperous family.
May you have a harmonious union,
and be of one heart forever.
An excellent match,
in perfect harmony.
Mutual respect,
and a blissful life.
Flying together,
and may you soon have a child.
Marital harmony,
and growing old together.
Supporting each other,
and staying together always.
Congratulations.