( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Let's make a deal.
You tell us all the rules and taboos,
and we won't attack you.
This girl is even more reckless.
Didn't you see
what happened to the one just now?
Cut the crap.
Make a decision quickly.
Otherwise,
we'll attack you together
and then meet up with him.
Great job, wife.
Fine.
But only for
the first level.
She actually compromised.
It seems
they are very afraid
of letting the four of you meet up.
Okay.
First,
after the guests take their seats,
no communication in any form is allowed,
including but not limited to words,
eye contact,
and any obvious physical movements.
If any of the above behaviors occur,
they will be considered communication.
Second,
the wine given by the shopkeeper must be drunk.
Third,
you must watch
the dancer's dance.
The wine given by the shopkeeper must be drunk.
If your wine is poisoned,
won't we definitely die?
Don't worry.
Our wine is just a bit strong,
it's not poisonous.
The wine won't kill anyone directly.
The rules
cannot be a certain death.
Otherwise,
the Heavenly Dao would not allow the Demon Domain to form.
Let's go.
Damn.
Lin Youtang,
you're into this too?
Who has heaven ever spared?
Dear guests,
today is our boss's birthday.
Please,
drink to your heart's content.
I wish you all
can leave here alive today.
This pot of wine,
I
will drink first.
What do you mean you guests aren't drinking?
Are you not giving our boss face?
He definitely has a way to deal with it.
My wife is protected by dragon aura.
She is invulnerable to all evil.
This trial isn't hard to pass.
Since you won't give face,
then there's nothing we can do.
Our wine here
is called Heart-Burning Brew.
After drinking it,
it feels like a raging fire burning the heart.
Let's see which of you
can withstand it.
My nation's dragon aura.
I can still deal with your mere demon wine.
Redirection,
activate.
Unless one has great perseverance,
few people
can endure the burning pain of Zhuoxin Brew.
What's wrong?
Is this the taboo of the demon illusion?
Damn it.
These demons brought in by Beijing
torture and toy with our Daqian people,
like making animals fight,
doing whatever they please.
Forget it.
I'll knock properly this time.
Lin Mo.
Open the door!
I need to talk to you.
Lin Mo.
Wake up, Lin Mo!
Who are you?
He's not here, miss.
This is the residence of the Vice Minister of the Court of Judicature and Revision.
Where did Lin Mo go?
Our master
went on duty yesterday morning,
and never came back.
They say he went to investigate a case.
Who are you, miss?
I'm his creditor.
He owes me money.
I'm here to collect it.
Then I'll wait for him here.
He won't be back anytime soon.
It's you.
Master Lin
went to Baihua Pavilion to hunt demons.
What?
To Baihua Pavilion
to subdue demons?
Him?
The one in Baihua Pavilion
is on the same level as the chief of Luoxian Town.
And he just went like that?
So why are you looking
for Lord Lin?
If I tell you,
can you take me to see him?
No.
Then don't ask.
Boss Chu,
you're here.
It's really tough for the Prime Minister.
He has no other means
but to take the demon wine head-on.
That explains
why he reached the highest rank.
Such willpower is naturally
beyond ordinary people.
This person has a strong murderous intent towards you.
And the killing intent is very familiar.
Could this person
be the one who hid in Baihua Tower
and tried to attack me?
Old man.
Do you think this person
is one of those chosen ones
blessed with fortune?
He's no bullshit chosen one.
He has some fortune,
but not much.
It's the fortune he got from his mother's side.
That's good.
Watch how I deal with him.
Yaoniang.
How can one cup of wine be enough?
Are you dismissing a beggar?
Bring two more cups.
Damn,
is he that arrogant?
Not enough?
How dare he speak?
What?
You said I couldn't interact with the guests.
You didn't say I couldn't interact with you, right?
Yaoniang,
serve the wine.
Since Mr. Lin wants to drink,
I
will respectfully obey.
Right,
pour a full cup for Brother Zhang
at my table too.
Getting stuck with such a troublesome disciple,
I have to clean up her mess as her master.
Yaoniang.
Pass on a message for me.
For this cup,
I'll finish it,
he can drink as he pleases.
No wonder he suddenly attacked someone.
Zhang Mu
really had the bad luck to sit at his table.
Damn,
a pay-to-win player.
Yaoniang.
Please tell Mr. Lin,
thank him for the toast.
I, Zhang Mu, will remember this debt.
After this,
we have plenty of time ahead of us.
It seems the drinking table
can also forge connections.
Perfect timing.
I'm giving you what I drank.
While it's hot.
Substitute skill,
activate.
Hold it.
I can't move recklessly.
This damn Lin Mo.
Once I get out,
I will definitely skin you alive.
It seems
they want to lure us into a trap.
We have no choice.
There are over a hundred Daqian citizens inside
being held hostage.
Your Maj...
Miss Su
couldn't bear to see the citizens slaughtered.
What 'Miss'?
Stop hiding it.
The Emperor is the Emperor.
How did you tell?
A Daqian princess dares to go to Luoxian Town,
can summon the Shanhe Sword,
and can mobilize troops?
I am also an emperor candidate, okay?
You are also an emperor candidate?
I voted too early.
Is it too late for me to switch sides now?
Take me into Baihua Pavilion.
I might consider it.
Goodbye.
Stop blabbering.
If you can't get out by noon,
my brother and I will have to fight our way in.
Fight your way in?
Baihua Pavilion is a demon domain with strict rules.
Don't you even have an attack plan?
Yes.
The plan is to attack.
Forget I asked.
Please have some tea.
Please enjoy the tea.
Thank you.
You are too polite, Miss Xiaoying.
You are all the young master's friends.
Taking care of you is my duty.
The Wanyao Banner is reacting.
Something is wrong with you.
Why is my Wanyao Banner reacting to you?
Miss Chu, are you still refusing to let me go?
What are you trying to do to my sister?
Boss Chu.
Let the past
be the past.
There are countless monsters in this world.
You can't catch them all.
I'm not interested in you.
You have another demonic aura on you.
It's of a high realm.
Have you been to Baihua Pavilion recently?
I'd rather die than go to a place like that.
Then have you
met anyone else recently?
I've been taking care of Miss Zhiwei recently.
Zhiwei.
Lin Mo has a new lover.
Zhiwei?
She's a girl who escaped from Baihua Pavilion.
Miss Wuhui has checked Zhiwei.
She's fine.
I'm warning you.
Don't pick on my sister one minute,
and trouble other girls the next.
I've been tolerating you for a long time.
Exactly.
Boss Chu.
Don't always be so aggressive.
Boss Chu,
considering our friendship,
please don't make things difficult for us.
[Purify]
Why is my temper so bad?
Yeah.
Why did I have murderous intent towards Boss Chu just now?
Your emotions were triggered by the hair demon.
Hair demon?
The demon illusion in Baihua Pavilion now
is a high-level hair demon.
She is very strong,
good at playing with people's minds,
creating illusions,
and stirring up emotions.
She's hard to guard against.
She relies on sucking human vitality
to improve her cultivation.
She can also transform others
into low-level hair demons.
The Zhiwei you rescued,
take me to see her.