( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Yaoniang,
keep serving wine.
He brought it on himself
by provoking him.
Mr. Lin,
this is somewhat personal.
The wine from now on
is no longer on the house.
Drink as you please.
Forget it then.
Looks like this trick won't kill him.
Kid,
you're really ruthless.
You show no mercy at all.
Reminds me of myself back in the day.
With only good wine
and no music and dance,
how can we fully enjoy ourselves?
This dancer
has an aura of decay.
Be careful, they suck out vital energy.
Try not to look at them.
If we don't look,
wouldn't that break the rules?
We have to watch the dancers' performance.
Right.
Then figure it out yourself.
Talking to a lady
shouldn't violate any taboos, right?
What a beautiful dance.
They are sucking out your spirits.
Everyone, don't look at them.
Close your eyes.
No communicating allowed.
You violated the taboo.
Keep playing the music.
Keep dancing.
There's nothing unusual here.
Is Chu Xiao'er just
being an alarmist?
Zhiwei seems very relaxed.
She doesn't look like someone who just lost a family member at all.
Maybe after seeing me,
she cheered up.
Bro,
who are you actually involved with, Qiaoyun or Zhiwei?
Usually, it's just the three of us drinking and chatting.
It's just that I talk to Qiaoyun
a bit more.
You have a refined taste, Miss.
Your calligraphy is excellent.
I grew up following my lady around.
So I gradually fell in love with it.
Are you here to see Lord Lin, Miss?
I'm here to see you.
To see me?
Do we know each other?
I hunt demons.
We don't need to be acquainted.
My banner just needs to know you.
It seems I can't escape my fate today.
I thought you would struggle a bit more.
Or
call them to help deal with me.
From the way you used a talisman just now
to easily calm their emotional fluctuations,
I knew that in my current state,
I'm no match for you.
You are very pragmatic.
That makes it easy.
How about
you enter my banner yourself
to save me the trouble?
Mr. Li.
Humans and demons walk different paths.
If you make a move,
there's no turning back.
She is a hair demon.
If she is truly the murderer,
I will personally kill her.
Until then,
I won't allow anyone to touch her.
If I use the Beijing First Prince's secret
and the way to enter the Baihua Pavilion master's room
in exchange,
Your Highness Chu Xiao'er,
can you spare my life?
Han Xiaoying.
Serve the tea.
Such a beautiful dance.
If you don't watch,
wouldn't it be a waste of my good intentions?
You like dancing so much, huh?
Come dance for me.
You...
You are...
Yaoniang.
I just put up a piece of paper.
No malice.
Not using force.
Just for decoration.
Add a rule to this place.
No harmful actions against
the dancers of Baihua Pavilion.
Effective immediately.
Bait and Switch.
Activate.
Lin Mo,
you bastard!
You set me up again!
Yaoniang,
someone triggered a taboo.
Is it ending like this?
I still have so much to do.
My lady,
I didn't expect
the most powerful minister of Nanqian
to die not on the path of politics.
Kid,
I see this person is surrounded by purple clouds
and favored by luck.
It seems
he is the child of destiny you mentioned.
What?
He is the child of destiny?
We can't let him die!
My mission!
Little girl,
he doesn't like your type.
Come dance for me.
I can
appreciate your beauty.
Do you have a death wish?
Fooling around at a time like this?
Dressed like this,
they shouldn't be able to recognize me.
Stop!
Where are you from?
Sir,
I just want to go to Baihua Pavilion
to drink some tea
and listen to music.
You are not from around here, are you?
What do you mean?
Still coming for a drink?
Baihua Pavilion is haunted by a monster.
Go,
go back quickly.
Monster?
Oh no.
I was careless.
The monster domain has opened.
Now it's not so easy
to get in.
That girl Xiao'er
must already be inside.
Shameless.
You can't play around at a time like this.
Can't hold it in?
This lecher
must be crazy for women.
You can play like this?
Yaoniang,
serve a pot of wine to each table.
Help me tell everyone,
follow my method,
and this level can be broken.
Congratulations, everyone.
The first round is cleared.
The taboo is lifted.
We are saved.
I survived.
Thank goodness.
We survived.
Young Master Lin.
No.
Censor Lin.
Thank you for saving my life just now.
Chancellor Lin.
You are too polite.
The future development of Daqian
and the moderate prosperity of all people
still need a screw like you.
Chancellor Lin,
don't be careless.
There are still many crises ahead.
Okay.
Xiaoying,
what are they talking about?
They are talking about the secret affairs of the Beijing Palace.
How does Zhiwei know
so much about Beijing?
Inside Lady Zhiwei's body
is a part of the Hair Demon.
That part
seals her experiences in Beijing.
What?
Then...
what about Qiaoyun?
I think it's better
for you to ask her yourself.
We two will go with you
just in case.
Let's go.
Alright.
I know everything I want to know.
You're on your own now.
If you dare to harm others to improve your cultivation in the future,
I will still come and destroy you.
Zhiwei.
Brother Li.
I know what you want to ask.
Let me answer for her.
She is Zhiwei,
but not entirely.
Every time the Hair Demon advances,
it sheds its shell.
And the shed shell
will generate a new consciousness.
After the main body finds a new host in the shed shell
and successfully merges,
it will devour the shell
to consolidate its own realm.
That is to say,
you are the new host of the shed shell.
When the main body intended to devour you,
you successfully escaped.
Qiaoyun saved me.
Brother Li.
Except for not telling you
that I turned from a mortal into a demon,
I never lied to you about anything else.
What are your plans for the future?
My sister is gone,
and the Song family is gone.
Now I am neither human nor demon.
With the matters here resolved,
I want to travel the outside world.
To think carefully about how to live from now on.
Use this to trick the barrier.
Boss Chu.
Where are you going?
Baihua Pavilion.
So unlucky.
Hurry up.
That's him.
Picked up by the Empress.
Can't believe he was raised to adulthood.
Yeah.
Looks like a decent human.
Ignore him.
He bites.
Wait.
Where is His Majesty?
Protect His Majesty!
Liu Wancai, save me!
Go quickly!
Master!
Save me!
Xue Qian!
You are courting death!
Let me go!
Get in!