( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Uncle.
Wuhui.
The late Emperor granted you the surname Su.
Do not disgrace
our Su family's reputation.
Please enlighten me, Uncle.
Without any breakthrough for so long,
your cultivation
has stagnated.
You haven't seen me draw my sword for years, Uncle.
How would you know my swordsmanship hasn't improved?
Cultivating one sword in a lifetime.
Thinking of one person in a lifetime.
Because of his appearance,
your sword intent
is messed up.
Uncle.
The way of the sword
is forged through fighting,
not through talking.
Interesting.
Then let me see your progress.
Please instruct me, Uncle.
Your Majesty.
No.
You are not His Majesty.
This is...
Song Qing, the previous Chancellor of the Imperial College.
Zhiwei.
Why is she here?
How can she wear mourning clothes?
Because Qiaoyun is a concubine's daughter.
Zhiwei is the legitimate daughter.
You can ignore all these NPCs.
Let's go straight to the person behind this.
Let's go.
Your father hasn't even been buried yet,
and you're here practicing calligraphy.
Isn't that a bit inappropriate?
Since you already know this is an illusion, sir,
why should I keep pretending?
I knew you weren't dead.
Tell me.
How do you want to play this?
Hurry up.
We're in a rush.
This level isn't a test.
Once I finish what I have to say,
you can leave the illusion immediately.
Did you choose to talk to us here
to avoid someone's detection?
However,
even here,
we cannot mention that person's name,
or he will sense it.
So,
I can only write it down.
Why do you want to avoid his detection?
Because the current situation of Daqian
is all thanks to him.
The foremost demon crisis
was also brought in by him.
Who is it?
I'd really like to meet him.
This wasn't in the book, right?
There aren't that many hidden plots.
If the updates hadn't stopped,
Daqian would have already fallen.
Unexpected,
but it makes sense.
You guys talk.
I'll look around.
Why are you telling us this?
Why should I believe you?
I am telling Your Majesty what I know.
As for whether you believe it
or what you will do,
I can no longer intervene.
Maintaining the illusion
must be very hard on you.
The love between Your Majesty and Mr. Lin is stronger than gold.
It cannot be broken by inner demons,
which makes maintaining the illusion even harder.
Tell me what you know.
The Song family
is a victim of that person's scheme,
as well as a pawn.
Perhaps
this is her best ending.
This cup of wine,
I will finish it.
The bride and groom
shall now enter the bridal chamber!
Wancai,
is that you?
Wancai.
We're finally together.
They all say humans and demons can't be together,
but I refuse to believe it.
Ma-
Master.
Silly Wancai,
why are you still calling me Master?
We're married now.
What should you call me?
Wi-
Wife.
That's right.
Husband,
let's be like this
and never be apart.
Let's live happily
ever after,
okay?
Thank you.
Between us,
why say thank you?
of course I should say thank you.
Because
we are not close.
Husband,
what's wrong?
Thank you.
Thank you for this illusion.
It let me experience the thing I dreaded the most
and the thing I looked forward to the most,
all at once.
I originally thought
no matter what the outcome,
I would sink into it
and be unable to extricate myself.
Now it seems
it's fine.
My Dao heart is quite stable.
Husband,
you're scaring me.
Don't be like this, okay?
Thank you for letting me completely understand.
My feelings for Su Ningxue
are not just some superficial romance
that can be compared to.
My thoughts are clear.
As expected of the Head of the Shadow Guards.
You don't care about Lin Mo's existence.
You are quite tolerant.
Why should I care?
Mortals only live for a century.
Compared to demons
and cultivators who live for thousands of years,
what is it?
You are too superficial.
In this inner demon stage,
you didn't play well.
Purple Gold Pill.
Come again.
Head of the Tianji Pavilion,
is this all you have?
Too weak.
This is not real.
This is just an illusion.
You are not Your Majesty.
Yes,
I am not real.
Then why
can't you beat me?
You rely on the Shanhe Sword.
That is not your power.
The power of ancestors
is also part of one's strength.
The first floor is completely dark.
It seems every floor
is an independent space of laws.
Such restless sword intent.
Su Wuhui.
If one falls, we both suffer.
I can't act recklessly anymore.
Liu Ruyan.
I am trapped in this Baihua Tower.
What exactly must I do
for you to let me go?