( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I need to know the truth
about Hijikata Toshizo.
He had the same look in his eyes as you.
What's the fun
in doing the sensible thing?
Doing what no one else
can is what makes you a badass.
It was the final years of Edo.
There were men who lived fiercely
and passionately by the way of the sword.
To become the strongest man there is.
What a coincidence. Same here.
I welcome you as the fools who are ready
to die alongside the Aizu!
They pressed on with unwavering resolve
against the tide of history.
This is the story of the last samurai
men who bloomed brilliantly
in an age of turmoil, and then fell.
Let us bloom with all our might.
SONG OF THE SAMURAI
APRIL 1862, TOSA
Man, Edo is amazing!
It was packed with people,
and the food was delicious.
And, what's more, there were
a ton of strong fighters, too.
But Toshi was
the strongest out of them all.
You just told us that story about Toshi.
That's the fifth time.
Is that true, Ukichi?
But still, Izo, since it makes you laugh
I'd be happy to hear it five or six times!
Hey!
Never mind all that.
Did you get a taste of this?
What? Do you eat pinkies?
You idiot! Edo has Yoshiwara,
the land's greatest pleasure district!
I'm talking about women!
I'm... not very good with women.
I've never seen or "tasted"
anything like that.
Hey, Izo!
Master Takechi is calling for you!
Assassination?
Keep your voice down, Izo.
But still, an assassination...
It's divine retribution, Izo.
Divine retribution?
We are to eliminate Yoshida Toyo.
Who is that?
You don't even know who Toyo is?
He's the ringleader in Tosa
who oppresses lower-class samurai like us.
He sides with the shogunate's plan
to open the country
a vile man who is leading
our nation to ruin.
Izo.
You, too, are a member
of the Tosa Loyalist Party.
Lend me your strength
to restore the emperor
and expel the foreigners.
No, I can't do that. Anything but that.
Izo!
You would really turn down Master Takechi?
But I don't like killing people.
I'm sorry.
- Hey! Get back here, Izo!
- Wait, Izo!
- Let him go.
- But, Master Takechi...
Well, wait and see.
Why would anyone do this?
Ukichi!
Ukichi.
They were making an example
of Ukichi's father!
He petitioned the domain
to lessen the burden of the labor tax.
And the one who gave the order
had to be Yoshida Toyo.
That damn Toyo!
How much more will he make us suffer?
Ukichi.
I...
will avenge...
you.
I'm sorry, Ukichi.
I'm sorry, Izo.
Yoshida Toyo, this is divine retribution!
Do you think a bunch
of Loyalist Party monkeys
can take me down?
Why?
Why...
Why did you kill Ukichi?
Another one, huh?
Ukichi...
looked up to me like an older brother.
What is this nonsense you're spouting?
You die first!
Impossible that a lowly samurai...
could be this skilled...
Izo!
You did it!
It's divine retribution!
You did it, Izo!
And that was the beginning
of Izo the Manslayer.
After that,
following Takechi Hanpeita's orders
he cut down one key shogunate official
after another.
So he was
a completely different man from when
he met my grandfather, Hijikata Toshizo.
A different man? That's putting it mildly.
When a man with a kind soul
is forced to keep killing brutally
do you know what happens to him?
He shatters.
Hold it!
KYO, ONE YEAR LATER
Surrender, Izo the Manslayer!
Stay away.
Don't come near.
Hey... Hey!
Hey, what's going on?
The Mibu Ronin are coming.
The Mibu Roshigumi?
Check out that cocky bastard strutting
at the very front.
Rumor is he killed Tanaka Shinbei.
- Hijikata Toshizo, the vice-commander?
- Yes.
Toshizo?
- Hey, they're coming.
- Yeah.
What's up, Toshi?
I feel like we're being watched.
A loyalist assassin?
No, it's probably nothing.
By this time, the Mibu Roshigumi had grown
and was split into two major factions.
The first was led
by Commander Kondo Isami...
One!
...with Vice-Commanders Hijikata Toshizo
and Yamanami Keisuke
the Shieikan faction.
- One, two!
The other was the Serizawa faction,
led by First Commander Serizawa Kamo
Vice-Commander Niimi Nishiki
and Assistant Vice-Commander
Hirayama Goro.
Don't tell me
they went out drinking again
last night and still aren't back.
Those bastards!
Incredible!
Mr. Todo sure is impressive!
How about that, Shimada?
SHIMADA KAI
Damn, Shimada!
Like a god of war!
Hey, Shimada! Don't get cocky, rookie!
I'm sorry. I got a little carried away.
Put those down, now! Put those down!
All of you, drop and give me push-ups!
Mr. Yamanami.
- 11, 12, 13
- 14, 15, 16...
You want to switch to the other faction?
Tell me why.
I wish to train under Master Serizawa.
They see more action,
and they're flush with cash.
Plus, it's fun.
They get to party almost every night.
- Exactly.
So that's the real reason, huh?
Well, yeah. That makes sense.
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
Are you serious?
Yeah, but..
on one condition.
Wake up, Gen!
It's starting again!
Yes.
Well, look who's all here.
Hey, it hasn't started yet, right?
It starts now.
Hey
come at me all at once.
If you can land just one strike on me
you can go to Serizawa's group
or wherever the hell you want.
Awesome.
Not confident, even four against one?
If you're that pathetic,
they won't give you the time of day.
Hijikata, mind if we add three more?
Yeah, I don't care.
That's seven men!
But even for Mr. Hijikata, that's...
Hey.
- On guard!
- C'mon, take it seriously!
What are you, scared? Hey!
- There are seven of us! We can win this!
- Yeah!
- Good luck.
- Yeah.
Get him!
What's the matter? Bring it!
Hey.
So, I take it you're all staying?
Whoa! Look at you go, Toshi!
That was pathetic, you guys. Gen.
What is this?
Hey!
I'll assist you.
So it's against you two?
Now this is getting interesting.
Dammit!
Hey, it's not a lethal blow.
Awesome!
Damn. He got me!
Man, what were you thinking?
What's the matter?
Are you that pissed you lost to me?
That's not it! You won the fight
against those guys, didn't you?
So why did you run them all off?
If they want to leave,
there's no use trying to stop them.
That's so like you, Toshi.
There you go again, being so nonchalant.
Do you know how many men
we've lost to them this month?
Pardon the intrusion.
You must all be tired.
Please help yourselves.
Perfect timing.
You're always so thoughtful, Aijiro.
Not at all. I'm honored
you remembered my name, sir.
What are you so tense about?
He's never this well-behaved around me.
Even in the last practice,
he mercilessly beat me down.
That's not right.
The one always beating me down
is you, Master!
See? He's usually got
a much bigger mouth on him.
What's this?
Bragging about your cute little disciple?
But
is this really okay?
For someone like me,
the son of a craftsman
to join the Mibu Roshigumi?
If you can't join our ranks
then we'd all have to quit on the spot.
Right, Toshi?
We're just farm boys ourselves.
Aijiro...
being a samurai isn't
about your social status.
It's about what's in here.
Commander Kondo, everyone...
I swear I'll make myself useful
to all of you!
Good. See that you do, Kojiro.
- It's Aijiro.
- Yeah, I know.
Thank you.
Man, that's something else.
That master-disciple bond, you know?
It gets you right here.
Seriously, I'm so damn jealous.
I want one of those, too.
What the hell do you want?
Hey, Saeki!
What are you doing skulking around here?
What about your patrol?
You're supposed to be on duty today!
Oh, that's right.
SAEKI MATASABURO
I heard he was out again last night.
You know, what's-his-name.
What was it again? Uzo? Muzo?
Izo! That's it, Izo. Okada Izo.
He was prowling Tominokoji last night.
Tominokoji?
You can just leave him to me.
If you don't dispose of thugs
like him quickly
a man can't enjoy his sake in peace.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
What's that supposed to mean?
Okada Izo is a manslayer, you know.
Or is he a "friend" of yours,
Vice-Commander?
In fact, isn't protecting him the same
as picking a fight with our Aizu patrons?
Saeki isn't wrong about any of this.
This isn't right, Toshi.
Saeki.
I apologize for the trouble.
But Toshi would never do anything
to endanger the corps.
You can count on that.
I need you to give it your all
as a Vice-Commander's Assistant.
Well, I can't exactly say no
to the commander, can I?
Well, then, I'll be off on my patrol.
Boss! Why is he the same rank as me?
Settle down.
Saeki's attitude isn't something
to be proud of.
But you've noticed it as well, I'm sure.
His killing intent is not
to be taken lightly.
We'll likely see more men of his ilk
joining our ranks from now on.
Yeah, we're getting more and more guys
with murky pasts.
It's increasingly difficult
to maintain control.
We may need to take some measures.
Looks like the master of this place
has agreed to our "donation."
Come on, have a drink.
Master Serizawa,
you should train us sometime.
It's always booze and women with you.
Our enemies will walk all over us.
Oume, go ahead and train him.
- Me? Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Are you...
really that strong?
You're always drunk off your ass.
I bet even I could take you.
I may not look it, but I've cut down
a Hokushin Itto-ryu master, too.
Is that right? Heh.
All right, I like your nerve.
I'll give you a lesson.
Try to kill me. Right now.
Hell, if anything
I'll even fight you bare-handed.
I'm the chief commander of the Mibu Ronin.
If you take me down,
you'll be famous overnight.
The Imperialists might pay you a fortune.
Or perhaps...
are you afraid of me,
even when I'm unarmed?
Don't you mock me.
Come on.
Hey, do you all get it now?
This is how I train.
Come try to kill me
whenever you want. Got it?
I'll follow your lead, Serizawa!
Pour it over my hand.
You're pretty damn good.
You've got some skills yourself.
We'll have another match, Toshizo.
Sure.
You. What are you doing here?
You're...
Okada Izo.
Izo?
Don't come.
You mustn't come.
Again.
A manslayer...
A manslayer like me...
has no right...
to show up
before Toshizo.
I guess it was after you all passed by.
He was rummaging through scraps
and other trash for food to eat.
Eating trash?
Yeah. It was a ghastly sight to see.
It was right here.
Will you let me know if you see him again?
Before the magistrate's office.
Got it?
Understood.
It's the manslayer again!
Move out of my way!
Hey, go on home now!
What happened?
Go home now.
Go home!
Toshi.
They both went down with a single strike.
As far as I know,
there is only one person capable
of a feat like this.
It's Izo.
I have to find him, and fast.
Do you have any leads?
No.
But he has to be close.
What will you do when you find him?
Cut him down.
Are you really sure about that?
If you fight Izo with a heartless blade,
you'll be no different than a manslayer.
If I don't do this now,
more people will die.
That won't do for you two!
That won't do.
Did you two meet just to kill each other?
Remember...
why you aimed to be the strongest.
You two were...
friends.
Right?
Before I'm his friend
I'm the vice-commander
of the Mibu Roshigumi.
Izo.
I've been looking for you...
Toshizo.
Hey.
It's been a while.
Toshizo.
What is it?
I'm...
I kept cutting down people on command.
And the men I fought
started to look like scarecrows.
Now
I feel nothing when I cut them down.
So, have you lost your heart?
Honestly...
I didn't want to meet you like this.
Don't.
I guess we have no choice, Izo.
Don't, Toshizo.
At least, I'll be the one to cut you down.
I am Mibu Roshigumi Vice-Commander...
Hijikata Toshizo.
Here I come!
I am Izo, the Manslayer.
No, you aren't.
Damn, you're strong.
Interesting.
You're still Izo, through and through.
From here on
I'm just Hijikata Toshizo.
You said it yourself, Izo.
"With wooden swords, we can fight
as many times as we want."
But I guess that's not an option now!
This is a fight to the death.
Our first and last duel.
Izo, after this,
we can never do this again.
There's no greater honor
than to fall by your blade.
I know you feel the same. Izo!
Damn, that hurts!
Hey! How does that feel?
Tell me, does a scarecrow bleed?
What you just cut wasn't
a scarecrow, was it?
See? You feel pain, don't you?
And the man I'm fighting isn't
a scarecrow either.
I'm fighting you! Okada Izo!
Hey, what was it we were striving for
Izo?
To become the strongest man alive,
wasn't it?
I don't need something like this
to duel you, Toshizo.
That's more like it, Izo.
All right.
You can continue
to fight with those.
Boss.
Toshizo.
Bring it on!
Yeah!
I am Okada Izo!
The strongest man in all of Japan!
I'm the greatest samurai in all of Japan!
- I won!
Looks like another draw.
Toshizo...
Man...
That was a damn good time.
Hey, Toshizo.
Someday...
we'll do this again.
No matter how much I boast of my strength
don't you dare run away next time.
What's wrong with you, Toshizo?
You're one to talk.
No matter where you hide,
no matter where you run
I'll find you
and beat the hell out of you!
Toshizo.
You're a real weirdo.
We just made this incredible promise.
So why are you crying?
Shut up!
You're the one who's crying!
What?
But why?
It's a promise, then.
I promise.
After that, Okada Izo was captured in Kyo
and extradited to the Tosa Domain.
He was imprisoned with Takechi Hanpeita
and the rest of the Tosa Loyalist Party.
Hey...
You...
A wooden sword.
Can you lend one to me?
A wooden sword?
What are you going to do with that?
Toshizo
is waiting for me.
is getting stronger
and waiting for me.
Then, on July 3, 1865
Okada Izo was executed by beheading.
They say he was swinging that wooden sword
right up to his final moment.
I can't believe it.
The man they called "Izo the Manslayer"...
Once in Edo and once in Kyo.
To think that was all it took
to forge such a powerful bond.
That's what it means to cross swords
with your life on the line.
Social status and personal beliefs
don't matter.
You just throw pure strength
at one another.
A battle like that is
every samurai's dream.
I'm envious of a bond like that.
It may
have been the last dream
either of them ever had.
Their last dream?
Sadly...
after that, the battles we fought
were a far cry from any such dream.
Hey, Hijikata, what are you doing?
The corps regulations.
To keep the riffraff in line.
That's just like you, Toshi. I love it.
- You really think so?
- Yeah.
We'll fight and clash
to keep the corps' rules in place.
- "The fight is on!"
- Make sure everyone stays in line.
You didn't have to tear it up, Soji!
I'm impressed you
wrote something so idiotic.
In fact, it's almost brilliant.
Kondo.
Never mind Hijikata's scribbles.
Use this.
Who does he think he is?
Now, now. Let's see what you've got.
"The Corps Code."
"One. Do not stray
from the Way of the samurai.
One. Desertion of the corps is forbidden.
One. You are forbidden
to raise money without authorization.
to involve yourself in litigation.
One. Do not engage in personal fights.
Anyone who violates these articles
must commit seppuku."
That's pretty harsh, isn't it?
Okita, this is no time
for such naive talk.
This isn't Shieikan anymore.
To restore order to the chaos in Kyo
the unity of our corps
is absolutely essential.
But still, seppuku seems extreme.
Yamanami.
What is it?
Are you against it, too?
Add two more rules.
"One.
Draw your sword and fight
until you or your opponent has fallen.
One.
If you fail to kill
and take a wound to your back
it is seppuku."
That means...
once you draw your sword, you must win.
Soji.
This is about resolve.
Without this level of resolve
you can't protect the things that matter.
I...
don't want to lose any more comrades.
That's true.
The stricter these rules are
the more justification we'll have to keep
Serizawa's rogue faction in check.
A just cause.
Yes.
At the very least,
it should slow them down.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
The Corps Code?
"One. Do not stray
from the Way of the samurai.
One. Desertion of the corps is forbidden.
One. You are forbidden
to raise money without authorization."
Yamazaki here can memorize anything
he sees and hears, down to every detail
and is able to recall it perfectly.
- A natural-born spy, huh?
- "One. You are forbidden
to involve yourself in litigation.
Anyone who violates these rules..."
YAMAZAKI SUSUMU
"...Seppuku."
The stricter these rules are
the more justification we'll have
to keep Serizawa's rogue faction
in check.
- This is obviously aimed at us.
- A just cause.
Those bastards.
We have to do something.
I like it. The Corps Code.
What?
But this business about committing seppuku
for breaking it, I don't like.
If we play this right,
we could use it to tighten the noose.
Is that so?
Hey, good work.
Money... Money!
"Half past six.
I'll be waiting at Shinkenji Temple."
Guess who?