Watch on kissasia.li
[Episode 2]
[Do not try this.]
The front door isn't locked.
Why do you always climb in through my desk?
This is my place. Which way I
come in is none of your business.
Nice one, Miao Jing.
I've been gone a few days,
and you've taken over my bed.
Didn't you say it yourself?
That you didn't want to live with me.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Copying you.
Fine. Go ahead and throw it.
But don't regret it.
Still so childish in middle school.
[Teng City No.2 Middle School]
By the way, class.
The date for our autumn trip is set.
It's this Friday at Joy Land Amusement Park.
[Class 5, Grade 7]
Grades 7 to 9 will go together.
We'll take the school bus together.
The trip fee is 20 yuan per person.
Five people per group, form your own groups.
Tomorrow morning, each group should
appoint a leader to bring the list to me.
Is that clear?
Yes.
Good morning, everyone!
Today, it's finally time for our long-awaited
autumn trip.
Remember, safety first.
Follow the teachers' instructions
and obey the park rules.
If you have any questions, you can
find your class teacher or come to me.
We'll gather back here at three
in the afternoon.
Keep an eye on the time and don't be late.
I hope you all have a great time.
Dismissed!
She ran off.
Why are you running?
I told you I'd take good care of you today.
Let go of me. I can walk on my own.
Let's do this one.
Give me the tickets.
Sir... Sir, I don't want to play anymore.
Don't move. The floor is electrified.
Sit down.
If you don't want to play, just
drive slowly and pull over to the side.
Buckle up.
- Yi, hit her!
- Ram her, Yi!
- Yi, from the side!
- Hurry, Yi!
- Hold on tight!
- Ram her!
- Go forward! Hit her!
- All stuck together.
- What's going on? Hit her!
- What's wrong with you?
- Yi, now!
- Yi, watch out!
- Hit her! Hit her!
- Yi, go, go, go!
- Yi, watch out!
- Yi! Yi!
- Overtake her!
- Yi, don't just stick to her!
Time's up. Please leave immediately.
What's wrong with Yi?
- Yi, are you okay?
- Yi!
- Yi! Yi!
- Yi, are you okay?
- What's up with Yi today?
- Yi!
- Yi! Yi!
- Yi! Miao Jing!
- Miao Jing, come back!
- Come back! Don't run!
- Come on, Yi!
- Yi, wake up!
- Yi, Miao Jing ran off! Yi!
- Yi! Yi! Yi, Miao Jing ran off!
Did you forget who's the boss in this family?
About going to No.1 High School,
don't even think about it.
"Raising a child without teaching them
is the father's fault."
A son must obey his father.
As long as I provide for you,
you do as I say.
Unless I'm dead.
I'm not even sure I'm your real father.
Remember this. I didn't fail your mother.
Your mother failed me.
Everything I'm doing now is for you.
The path I've paved for you is the best one.
Say something. Why are you not talking?
Where's that usual spirit of yours?
Aren't you quite the rebel?
Jing, you're back.
Uncle.
Go downstairs and play for a while,
then buy me a pack of cigarettes.
Okay?
Keep the change and buy yourself some snacks.
Go on.
Chen Yi. Come here.
- Here, Jing.
- Uncle, the blanket.
Okay.
Jing, spread this out.
Mom.
It hurts.
Chen Yi!
Chen Yi.
It hurts so much.
Chen Yi, I... I made you some food.
Careful, it's hot.
I thought you were afraid of me.
Being afraid is one thing,
but letting someone die is another.
I won't bother you anymore.
And about today...
I didn't see anything.
This is for you.
[Class 2, Grade 10]
Now, let's welcome
the principal and school leaders
to present certificates of honor.
[Teng City Experimental No.1 High School]
[Award Ceremony for Outstanding Students]
[Teng City Secondary Vocational School]
[Baihua]
Cheers.
Meet Mr. Li.
Everyone, this is Mr. Li.
A toast to us.
We've heard so much about you, Mr. Li.
Here's a gift for you.
You don't have to.
Take it.
Take a look and try it on.
T-This is too plain. Is there anything else?
Help me get this one. The one with the bow.
Okay.
Take a look.
This one is quite nice.
You can try this one too.
Your daughter has such a great aura.
In high school already?
She is at Experimental High.
One of the top students in the elite class.
A top high school?
- That's right.
- Good for her.
How old is she?
Sixteen. It's my birthday today.
What a coincidence.
There's a local custom.
When a girl turns sixteen,
her family will buy her a lucky charm bead.
Usually, it's a gold or jade bracelet.
For safety and smooth sailing in life.
Then let's get one. Please recommend
something with a good meaning.
- Sure.
- Jing, pick whatever you like.
This one.
She has slender wrists.
Bracelets look good on her.
- Jinx, behave yourself.
- Miss, would you like to see anything else?
- I'm at the intersection. I'll wait for you.
- How about this one?
This one has a good meaning.
Something urgent came up. I have to go now.
Here's the plan. You can take the bus back.
Be careful on the way.
Sorry. Something urgent came up.
Maybe next time.
Okay.
Be careful on your way back.
Anything catch your eye?
No, thank you.
Happy birthday.
All morning, we checked out several scooters.
[Changlong Seafood Restaurant]
That one's definitely a great deal.
No problem.
This is nice.
It's cheap to stock up now.
How much?
- I'll take a batch. How much?
- Wu.
Isn't this phone impressive? Just got it.
I'm more impressed by your new scooter.
We just got it two days ago. Check it out.
- Take care, Mr. Chen.
- Check it out.
Mr. Li, Ms. Wei.
- You're here.
- This way, please.
- Baihua Room.
- Park the car.
- Welcome.
- It's all been reserved for you.
How much was it?
This phone looks nice.
Thank you.
The latest client information.
How's it going?
Do we have enough people?
The power bureau's housing is almost covered.
The street-front block also looks promising.
You know what I'm capable of. Don't worry.
I know you've been working hard.
Mr. Zhai chartered a cruise tomorrow night
to reward all of you.
Bring your daughter along
and enjoy yourselves.
Business is okay.
- Not bad.
- Getting phones?
- Get a batch.
- Let's get a batch.
Yi, I just saw Miao Jing's mother.
- She's with...
- With her lover.
I'm going home. You go ahead first.
What about things here?
If you're out, won't the dock guys be upset?
The police academy's recruiting soon.
I have to focus on the exam.
What do you say, handsome?
I've got some legwork for you.
Think about it.
Don't say no to money.
[Happy Birthday]
Next year, I don't want to
spend my birthday alone.
When did you get back?
While you were making your wish.
You...
Are you free tomorrow night?
Yes.
Then stay home. Don't go running around.
I didn't say you could eat that.
It's too sweet.
Happy birthday.
Mom.
Did I wake you up?
Jing.
Have you been drinking?
Well, I had a business dinner.
Couldn't avoid it.
And I didn't celebrate your birthday today.
You don't blame me, do you?
Is he back yet?
I think he went to a party.
Good. Thank goodness he's not back.
He'd just pick a fight with me.
So annoying.
Let me tell you, I'm working so hard
to make money for the two of us.
So we can live better soon
and get away from this lousy life
of living under someone else's roof.
Do you know? I have good news.
I've become the top performer
at my new company.
I'm Diamond level. Impressive, right?
Tomorrow, our company will hold
its annual gala on a cruise ship.
I was thinking
of taking my little girl along.
Because they'll have seafood and cake there.
It'll make up for your birthday. Sounds good?
Give me a smile.
Okay.
All right. Time for bed.
I'll pick you up at school tomorrow.
We'll go to the cruise together.
Be good and sleep.
Go to sleep.
[Du Billiards]
Nice shot.
Your turn.
- Come on.
- You take the shot.
- Here we go.
- Watch this.
- Take your shot.
- All right. This one should go in.
So, what do you think?
Are you really not going
to Shen City with me?
Foreign trade has been booming there.
It's the land of opportunity.
There's good money to be made.
I'm not going. My friends are all here.
So you're giving up the dock business too?
You're really going straight?
From now on, the business around here
might depend on Officer Chen's mood.
Drop it.
Keep playing.
Since you're so determined today,
why did you even come here?
Mr. Zhai chartered a cruise tomorrow night.
Bring your daughter along
and enjoy yourselves.
Make some quick cash.
No one turns down easy money, right?
Fine.
I wish you a bright future.
Today is the last collaboration, work hard.
- Play a break?
- Okay.
Yi. Hello.
Han had a conflict with a boss in Teng City.
On this happy day,
we should certainly seek a good omen.
Don't worry. It's all Han's
business, none of your concern.
Just deliver it and your task is done.
It's safe.
Stay sharp there.
If you hit, hit hard, understand?
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Watch out.
It's best if nothing goes wrong.
Welcome to
the Green Life Annual Dealer Conference!
Let's give a big round
of applause to our top three sellers!
- Yes!
- Great!
Join Green Life and
earn 1.3 million yuan in three years!
- Do you want it?
- Yes! Yes!
To make life keen, you must wear green!
Join Green Life, win the future!
[Green Life Health]
When it's over, Li will treat us to a feast.
Perform well and make me proud, okay?
Mom, I want to go home.
Look at you, so timid.
Girls should see the world.
Go on in. Let's go. Come on.
I'll be counting on you two bosses.
- Thank you, beauties.
- Not at all.
Thank you for the opportunity, Li.
- Right. Drink up.
- Your sales this year...
- Hello, do you have antidinic?
- Yes, I'll get some for you.
- "It's only two million. Thanks." Listen.
- You're being too modest.
- Right?
- Right.
- We need to expand.
- Yes, expand the team.
Jing.
Come.
- Yes.
- It's her daughter.
Come here. Don't just sit alone.
Mom, I feel unwell.
Come on, they're waiting for you.
This is my daughter, Jing.
- Say hello.
- Hello.
- Good. She's so beautiful.
- Exactly.
Is she feeling unwell?
No way. My girl has always been tough.
Come on, recite pi for them.
Mom, I need some fresh air.
What grade is she in?
Grade 11, and she tops in her class,
very outstanding.
Mom, I'm in Grade 10.
Look at me. I'm forgetful.
You know, she takes Green Life
and has an increasingly better memory,
better than mine.
I need to take some too.
Hurry and recite it.
3.1415...
It's okay. She might be a bit nervous.
Don't be a killjoy. Come on.
Together.
I'm only responsible for the delivery.
What? If we're short-handed,
Han will be furious. Take it.
Brother. Yi. Help us for the last time.
- Little girl.
- Okay?
What's wrong? Are you seasick?
Poor thing.
Let me wipe your hands. Come.
This girl...
I can win her over.
He just delivers things.
He never does dangerous jobs like ours.
- What's going on?
- No problem.
Go!
Little girl. Look, I'm not a bad guy.
- I just want to help you.
- No need.
- Are you seasick?
- Don't grab me.
- Don't touch me.
- Are you seasick?
- Don't touch me!
Let me see. It's fine.
Smash it!
- Smash it!
- Hurry and smash it!
Let go of me! My daughter is still here!
Jing! Here! Mom is here!
Jing! I can't leave my daughter behind!
Let go!
- My daughter!
- Hurry up!
- Hurry!
- Quick, get on the boat!
- Jing!
- Hurry!
- My daughter!
Get down first! Hurry! Get on the boat!
Sit down! Start the boat!
- Sit down!
- Forget about your daughter! Hurry!
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
- No boat left.
- Miao Jing, get down!
Miao Jing, get down!
Get on.
Hold me tight.
Hold on tight.
Aren't you calling your mom?
No need. She's not worried anyway.
Thanks for today. Were it not for you...
Were it not for me, you'd have
bitten his hand off. He should thank me.
Get up, now!
Do you think she'll be okay?
So many men rushed in.
Go home and take a hot shower.
No, I must find her.
Come with me!
I forgot your coat.
I don't want to go home. It's too noisy.
Tell me what you want to do now.
I'm hungry.
Where do you want to eat?
Anywhere.
I want that too.
Wait until you're an adult.
I can't do anything with you.
Look! Fresh and delicious fruit!
Look at the fruit.
- A discount for two kilos.
- It smells so good.
The barbecue was too salty.
I want some fruit.
Little girl, what fruit would you like?
Do you want a bite? It's sweet.
You eat it.
Can we go home now? It's almost 1:00 AM.
There's a dessert shop on the next street.
I want seaweed and mung bean soup.
Aren't you afraid of indigestion?
Go home and sleep.
I don't think I can sleep without eating it.
Gosh! I can't get a hold of her at all.
What if something happened?
Are you nuts? My daughter is
missing. Why are you reading?
Are you nuts?
She's missing. Why are you reading?
Say something!
Who's that man fooling around with you?
Chen Li Bin.
I'm not married to you.
And we didn't make us official.
Even if I'm engaged with him,
it's none of your business.
Listen, it's me who raised your drag.
I won't be a cuckold, never ever.
If you don't want to continue,
take your drag and get lost!
Now you ask us to get lost?
Who begged me to bring my daughter then?
You said your wife died and you were afraid.
You asked me to bring her
for a complete family.
So you're not afraid now?
Chen Li Bin, don't pretend to be decent!
Come back soon.
Take this. Take this apple to eat.
Eat it yourself. Don't give it to others.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye, Mom.
Still here? Is going to school such a hassle?
You want clothes, right?
Just a Young Pioneer.
Look at how smug you are, right?
Here, wear this.
Auntie, it's my cousin's outgrown coat.
It's wearable.
Here.
Living off me, you're as greedy as your mom.
Jing.
Ming Zhen, what brings you here?
- Mom.
- I'll take you to our own home in Teng City.