Watch on kissasia.li
[Episode 1]
[Therapist's Office]
Chen Yi.
From our previous sessions, I could sense that
it was difficult for you
to talk about that period.
I imagine you must've felt lost and alone.
Sometimes,
painful memories are like a hazy, heavy fog
wrapped around us,
keeping us from moving forward.
If we have the courage today,
could we try together
to move a little closer to it?
Don't be in a hurry
to tell the whole story yet.
We can start with
what your body felt back then,
or with one clear image that stayed with you.
Don't be nervous.
Take a deep breath.
That part of your life is over.
The past can't torture you anymore.
You can go back to a normal life.
Think about your family.
Your friends.
And the person you want to see most.
It's been a long time.
Chen Yi.
[Hai City to Teng City]
[Lodging]
Where are you headed?
[Pickup Point]
Leaving now.
Where are you headed?
Miss.
First time in Teng City?
You're heading to
the new district for a hotel, right?
Fifty yuan. Come on.
I'll give you a discount, forty-five.
Sure.
Do you go to Zhongshan Road?
Get in.
Sure. Let's go.
Mister.
You don't look familiar.
I usually pick people up around here.
Really? I've seen you before.
No way.
You're so good-looking.
If I'd seen you, I'd be dreaming
about you at night, right?
But now that you mention it,
why do I feel like you look kind of familiar?
Miao Jing.
You're Miao Jing.
You've changed so much since high school.
You don't look like
you came from around here anymore.
You look like you stepped out of a magazine.
You've changed a lot too.
Me?
I haven't done much with myself.
Enough about me.
Are you going back to the hotel or home?
Home.
Yi.
Those young punks are causing trouble again.
Not sure if Fat Dragon sent them
to mess with us.
Who's watching outside?
Yong.
And they're harassing a young girl.
Have some fun. That's what hanging out's for!
My brother will be here soon.
What are you scared of? Why so shy?
If you're not playing, don't hog the table.
Yi.
You finally decided to come out.
Yong, this one's on me.
Tell everyone to clear out.
Yi just can't stand
seeing high school girls get bullied.
Right?
What high school girl?
How would I know?
That was years ago.
She was a model student.
Yi.
I'm telling you,
you'd better listen to our boss.
Otherwise, you'll get more than you can handle.
Yi. I was wrong.
Next time, wipe your mouth
before you talk business for someone else.
Go. Just go.
That was brutal.
Get out of here.
Go.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Yong.
Take her home.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
I don't even have your contact information.
An old classmate finally comes back
after all these years.
Reach out anytime you need anything.
- Take it.
- No need.
I can't take your money.
I can still afford to give you a lift.
It's too much.
Right.
You're back this time.
Does Yi know?
Hello.
Mr. Zhang.
Please hold on.
Yi, it's from Mr. Zhang.
He wants to talk to you.
Hang up.
I already answered.
Chen Yi.
Do you have time?
Play a frame with us.
I've got another friend here.
He used to be a professional snooker player.
Come make me look good.
You're too kind, Bin.
You know I haven't played in years.
This isn't kindness.
It's admiration.
Even when you're just messing around,
no one can beat you.
Mr. Zhang?
Bin?
Isn't that the entrepreneur from Teng City?
I think so.
Sounds like they know each other pretty well.
Then why did we have to take all that?
If he knew we were connected to Mr. Zhang,
would he still dare start trouble?
Do you know what our boss's nickname is?
Mr. Zhang really doesn't quit.
He's been turned down so many times,
and he still keeps calling you.
If he calls again, tell him I'm dead.
What did you just say the boss's nickname was?
Rabid.
Jing, where is the welcome gift
you brought for him?
This is my gift for you and for Chen Yi.
A drawing.
Look how good it is.
Look, all four of us together, so happy.
Jing, it's wonderful.
I love it.
I'm going to put it where everyone can see it.
Tu Li,
didn't I tell you not to touch my kitchen?
You're back.
Don't you get it yet?
All of this is fake.
Aren't you tired of playing house?
For the rest of your life, stay away from me.
I made soup.
Want some?
Why did you come back?
Do I need a reason to come home?
Is this your home?
Didn't I live here for more than ten years too?
How is it not my home?
[Jiang City to Teng City]
Come on, tickets.
Ma'am, wake up. Ticket check.
Why are you checking again?
How many times have you checked already?
What's wrong with checking more than once?
Miss, show me your ticket.
Miss, let me see your ticket.
Tickets, everyone.
Show him. Just show him.
Everyone's going to Teng City today.
Hurry up, miss. I told you to have it ready.
Where are you headed?
Teng City too, right?
Have your tickets ready.
Whose bag is this? Move it.
I'll charge you the fare in a minute.
Get your tickets ready.
Here.
Keep it.
Have your tickets ready.
Your ticket, please.
- Where are you headed?
- Teng City.
Teng City.
Then what's this?
- Get up, kid.
- No, no.
- She's over one point two meters.
- She needs a ticket.
- No.
She's not one point two meters yet.
She isn't tall enough.
What do you mean, she isn't?
I saw her just now. She's almost as tall as me.
Really? Just for one ticket?
You're going to smother her
and give her a heat rash.
- No, no.
- How could you?
You're dressed better than anyone,
so why are you dodging fares?
Who's dodging fares?
My child has a stomachache.
And besides, she's been sitting on my lap.
She didn't take a seat.
- Stop making excuses. A stomachache?
- I won't be in the way.
I've got medicine. Get up now.
I won't bother anyone.
Kid, get up.
Hurry up. Buy a ticket.
Why are you two so stubborn?
Come sit on my lap.
Dragging a family along and buying one ticket.
Listen, she's disturbing the other passengers.
I won't disturb anyone.
So loud.
- Why does checking tickets take so long?
- Fine.
I've never seen people like you.
Fine. Hold her if you want.
If she bumps into something, that's not on me.
Tickets.
If I haven't checked you, get them out.
Poor kid, being put through this.
Teng City. Keep your ticket.
This ticket is yours.
[Warmly Celebrating the Return of Hong Kong]
[Bus Station, Teng City]
Take a look.
Chartered ride.
Let's go.
Check it out.
Yi.
Look. That woman.
That old lady.
She's probably got something good on her.
Get back here.
We're heroes.
Robbing the rich to help the poor.
What part of her looks rich?
Take it. Some hero you are.
Helping the poor, are you?
We've been posted here for a whole week.
We haven't robbed a single person.
How about dinner at my place tonight?
We're cooking meat.
My family has meat tonight too.
Your dad had a change of heart?
Can we come?
You think it's for me?
That woman he met in a chat room
is coming here to stay with him.
But I'm not letting her
into my house that easily.
Little girl, who are you looking for?
Need a ride?
One look at her,
and you know she's from a rich family.
I'll go check it out.
Remember to back me up.
Did you get separated from your mom?
Are you here all by yourself?
I'm a good person.
I'll help you carry your things
and find your mom.
Is bullying people fun?
If you don't leave, I'm calling the police.
Right across the street.
Who are you?
She's my sister.
Are you going or not?
Where are your parents?
Are you alone?
My mom went to the restroom.
Leaving soon. Get in and we go.
Is that heavy? I'll carry it for you.
How do you know I'm not a bad person?
You helped me. You're not a bad person.
Where do you live?
I don't have a home in Teng City yet.
My mom will take me to our new home later.
You look easy to fool.
Jing.
Mom, I'm here.
[Well-Mannered:
So? Do you want to come take a look?]
[Rosy Sky: Sure.
I will come with my daughter in a few days.]
- Don't do this again.
- Sorry, excuse me.
Hello, is this...
Hello. Is this number twenty-seven?
Yes, this is it.
Thank you.
We're here.
Jing. Do you remember what I told you before?
Make him happy.
Do not fight with Chen Yi.
Be good.
Mom, I know.
I have to behave so
we can have a home in Teng City.
Come on, Jing.
Take a look.
You'll share a room with Chen Yi for now.
In a while, I'll rent the room next door.
You and your mom can move over there.
This is Chen Yi's bed.
I'll set up a folding cot for you at night.
Tonight, you'll sleep here.
Look. The pillow and quilt are all brand-new.
I bought them just for you.
Thank him. Hurry.
Thank you.
The light is good here.
You can do your homework here later too.
Your clothes and stuff can go in that wardrobe.
You two came all this way.
It must have been tiring.
I made you a whole table of good food.
All that's missing is the crucian carp congee.
I'll make it for you now.
- Wait here.
- You've done so much already.
I'll help. This is my specialty. Sure.
Jing, rest here for a bit. Hold my bag.
Jing, do you like the room?
I do.
This is such a feast.
It's the least I can do.
Here. Try my cooking.
Okay.
You're back.
This must be Yi.
Yi.
Where are your manners?
Say hello. Say hello.
Get up. This is Jing.
Say hello to her.
You say hello too.
Hurry. Say hello.
- Hello.
- All right, we're all family now.
Come on. Sit down and eat.
- Sure.
- Hurry.
Come on.
Miao Jing, sit.
Your son is so thoughtful.
He even bought fruit on his way back.
- Here.
- Don't just sit there. Show him the gift!
He'll be happy!
You brought a gift too?
What is it?
Jing really prepared a gift.
Great. Come on.
Go get it. Let me see what you brought.
It's in your schoolbag?
This is my gift for you and for Chen Yi.
A drawing.
Look how well it's drawn.
- Look. All four of us together, so happy.
- Yes.
It's wonderful. Really wonderful.
I love it.
Jing, it's wonderful.
Thank you, Jing.
Here. I'll put it in the most visible place.
Welcome home, Jing. Come, sit down and eat.
Wonderful.
It's so good. I love it.
Have some meat.
Try the shrimp too.
Sure. Come on.
I didn't know you were such a good cook.
I'm all right.
Mom.
That fruit was bought with money
Chen Yi got from selling stolen gifts.
I know.
You handled it well today.
You're actually pretty smart.
And look at Mr. Chen.
He really liked your gift!
We're new here.
We just have to put up with things for now.
Later, when I find a job,
the two of us will finally be settled.
Mom.
Are you going to marry Mr. Chen?
You little brat.
That's a lot of questions.
Eat first. You barely ate anything tonight.
Listen.
When you grow up, you'll understand.
People don't have to get
married to become a family.
Then what do they need?
Yi. Time to rest.
Well...
Jing.
Be good.
Come on in.
Remember this.
This is the dividing line.
Cross it, and I hit you.
Boss. A carton of Red Double Happiness.
Here. What are you laughing at?
It's pretty funny.
Last week, your son came in
and sold the cigarettes for cash.
Now, you're buying them back.
Are you two trading futures?
I'm leaving.
Jing, hurry.
Explain it to him.
You gave the cigarettes and liquor to Chen Yi.
Little snitch. All you do is tell on people.
Chen Yi.
When you do something wrong,
you face the consequences yourself.
Apologize to her.
My mom only had me. I don't have a sister.
Come on, we're all family.
No need to apologize. No need to be so formal.
Who says we're family?
You're outsiders staying in my house.
Chen Yi!
I've been too nice to you.
Stay just like that.
Kneel for one hour. Not one minute less.
Jing.
Didn't you say
you're really scared of that Guanyin statue?
I'll move it to the back room in a while.
- Consider it his apology to you.
- That belongs to my mom.
- You don't have to!
- Let go.
That belongs to my mom. Let go.
- Get out of my way.
- No, don't.
Put it back. Put it back.
Come on,
leave the kid something to remember her by.
Be safe.
Okay. Come back early.
What are you doing?
I'm fixing it for you.
I just wanted to fix it for you.
Let go.
Help! Help!
Chen Yi.
Help!
Jing.
Mom.
Are you okay?
Why did you go to the riverside alone?
Thank goodness someone saw you.
I just wanted to go there to get
some wet clay for the Guanyin statue.
Chen Yi could've pulled me up.
Chen Yi was there too.
He wouldn't save me.
I thought I was going to die in the water.
Mom, why do I always have to give in to him?
Jing.
I'm sorry. I made you suffer.
I know you're upset.
But right now, I still need Mr. Chen.
He can help me get a job
at the power supply bureau.
Let's put up with it a little longer.
I promise you, this is the last time.
If he ever bullies you again,
I will not let him get away with it.
Mr. Chen will be back soon.
We must not tell him anything.
Okay?
The two of us...
can't go back to Jiang City again.
Miao Jing. Miao Jing.
Wake up. Wake up.
Don't get your hopes up
She'll never be my mom.
And you'll never be my sister.
The moment you barged into my house
and broke the Guanyin statue,
you should've known we're enemies.
Don't get your hopes up either.
We're never leaving.
No matter what we are, we're going to
stay right here.
[Du Billiards]
Yi.
Isn't that Miao Jing?
She's here for you.
I barely know her.
Nice shot.
Chen Yi, take your time learning.
I'll take over.
Miao Jing.
What are you here to see Chen Yi for?
Bo, bill.
Chen Yi.
Yi, take the money.
Okay.
Five yuan.
Let's go.
Yi.
You've been coming in
more often these past few weeks.
Short on cash?
Of course he is.
Chen Libin's money goes to his daughter now.
Mr. Chen told me
to give you your living expenses.
He said if you're going to live at school,
go home and clean out your own things.
Mr. Chen will give you your living expenses
on time every week.
Don't make it sound like
I'm taking extra money.
I'm moving into the dorm,
and he won't even let me keep my things there.
Miao Jing.
Don't think I don't know what you're up to.
You don't get to kick me out of my own home.
Chen Yi. You're overthinking it.
I'm just passing on a message.
Now that I'm done, I'm leaving.