Watch on kissasia.li
[Episode 3]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're not as convincing as Wei Ming Zhen.
She's the one who actually looks fine.
If you feel wronged, just cry.
But after that,
you must remember why you cried today.
Don't act like everything's fine again
in a few days.
Waiting for your mom
to realize she let you down?
Stop dreaming.
I'm not.
If you say so.
You know what?
Not all parents know
how to love their children.
In this world,
plenty of parents don't know how to parent.
If you wait for them
to give you a place to belong.
Then all your life,
you'll only get to see these few stars.
The moment they don't want you to,
you won't even get to see these stars.
That doesn't sound like something you'd say.
You never used to talk like that.
Then what do you think I'd say?
"I'm used to being alone."
"This is my home."
"You're not allowed to stay."
Nonsense. I wouldn't say things like that.
Yes, you would.
Miao Jing. Have you thought about the future?
The future?
Studying and taking exams.
Isn't that what everyone does?
If one day,
my mom and Uncle Chen break up,
I don't even know where I'd go.
What future is there for me?
I applied to the police academy.
The police academy?
I've already submitted my application.
Miao Jing, don't pin your future
on someone else.
If you want to make something of yourself,
you have to rely on yourself.
Got it.
In a bit, I'll take you home a different way.
What way?
You'll see in a bit.
Don't be afraid.
It looks high,
but climbing up only takes a few seconds.
Come on.
Steady your feet and hold on tight.
Give it your all. You can do it.
I didn't expect you to be such a natural.
Go to bed early.
- Bro!
- You're winning! Hurry!
Swing your arms!
- Go!
- Yi is first!
First place!
- Go for it!
- You're the coolest! The best!
- So cool!
- 3:37.
- Awesome, Yi!
- Yi! 3:37!
What was the time?
Good. Much better than last time.
What was the winning time?
- How was the result this time?
- What's with you two?
- 3:51.
- What about the first place?
- 3:37.
- 37 seconds!
- You're in.
- Next time, try to get it under 3:30.
- Got it?
- That's asking a lot.
What about me, Coach?
What about me?
What's wrong with you?
I'm nervous.
- Chen Yi, run!
- Go for it!
Go for it!
Keep breathing!
Hang in there, Yi!
- Look!
- Sprint!
- Over there.
Yi, keep going!
- Go for it!
- Nice!
Nice!
- Go for it!
- Nice!
- Across the line!
- What's the time?
- 3:26, Chen Yi!
3:55 is the cutoff.
- Chen Yi!
- Yi!
- 3:26!
The physical fitness test's in the bag.
Your brother is amazing.
Do you know what this means? It's incredible.
He even lost a few seconds at the start.
How did she get in?
- She's from another school.
- We know.
- What's her deal with Chen Yi?
- I don't get it.
Look.
What's going on?
- 3:26.
- Who is she?
That's great!
Stop right there.
Yes?
Who are you to Chen Yi?
Why are you looking for him?
I'm bringing him study materials.
Then why are you leaning so close to him?
Don't think I don't know
you fan girls from other schools.
You're always throwing yourself at Yi.
You've got it wrong. I'm his sister.
Sister?
You're really good at flattering yourself.
Yi is an only child.
Where did this sister come from?
Exactly.
I'm not from your school.
If things get ugly, you'll be the one to lose.
If you like Chen Yi, then go after him.
The little sister is lecturing me now?
Do you even know who I am?
Being your sister is quite dangerous.
No... Yi.
This is all a misunderstanding.
- Let's go back.
- Bye.
Bye.
Miao Jing.
Be careful. I heard some people
from the vocational school are after you.
After me?
You know Chen Yi, right?
Everyone's saying
that he's claiming you as his sister.
The girls over there are fuming.
Anyway, just stay away for now.
And avoid those students.
Bye, I'm off.
I heard I've become famous at your school.
Yeah. So?
Being my sister makes you look good, right?
Yi.
What a coincidence.
Want to share a table with us?
Make some room.
Sharing a table sounds good.
Who are you?
I'm his sister.
Another sister?
- How many sisters does he have?
- Make room.
Sorry about that.
And who is she?
I'm his sister too.
Just how many sisters do you have?
Sis.
- What?
- I'm his sister.
I'm his sister.
- What are you doing?
- I'm his sister too.
So many... sisters?
That's all of them, right?
That's it.
Then I...
You're not my sister.
- That's not what I meant.
- She's not his sister? Goodness.
What are you two standing around for?
Let's go.
- My coke.
- Right.
When is the police academy exam?
The interview is right
after the physical fitness retest.
I've checked past interview questions.
They're not that hard.
Here's your reward.
How was it?
You don't think it's dangerous now, do you?
Bo had to ask around several classes
just to round up enough people.
Childish.
Alright, enjoy your food.
I'm leaving.
Good luck with the exam.
[2022 Police Academy Admissions:
Physical Fitness Retest]
Miao Jing.
Yes. Look at this question.
Yes, this diagonal line.
Miss. I need to use the restroom.
Go ahead.
- What's wrong?
- Something happened to Chen Yi.
Today is the academy's retest.
He went home for his identity document.
But he never came back.
I knocked on his door, but no one answered.
Lou, the locksmith, is sick.
He's not working. I don't have a key.
I had no choice but to come to you.
[Donghui Police Academy Admission]
At the test site,
Yong is keeping an eye on the situation.
We're running out of time.
Let's head back.
But what about your class?
I'll worry about that later.
Mr. Chen.
- Off work?
- Yeah, off work.
- You go in first.
- You're off early today.
Is the bike riding okay?
Yes, it was fixed well.
Whose bike is this?
It's Wang's from next door.
Wang's? What's up?
His tire blew out.
Yi! Are you home, Yi? Yi!
- Mr. Chen, you're off work so early.
- Yeah.
Let me tell you,
the spring onions we planted are growing well.
Is that so?
Yi, are you in this room?
Step back. I'm kicking the door in.
This is really good tea.
I'll bring you some another day.
Alright, alright. Thank you.
- See you.
Yi!
The knife!
- What's going on?
- Uncle Chen.
I... I was just careless.
- Did you cut your hand?
- I'm fine.
Alright. Stop that. I'll clean it up later.
Why are you back so early?
I wasn't feeling well this afternoon.
I have a fever, so I took half a day off.
A fever?
Then hurry up and take some medicine.
Go get an IV if it doesn't get better.
- Uncle Chen!
- Yes?
Could you lend me some money?
Yi. Move aside. Here comes the knife.
Your mom made so much money from Green Life.
Why don't you ask her for some?
You were willing to take us in.
We're already very grateful.
But I can't find my mom.
I have a fever, and she doesn't even care.
I really have no other choice.
Jing.
You've always been such a sweet talker.
If my son could learn even a fraction of that,
I wouldn't have to get so angry with him.
Tell me, how much do you need?
Whatever you can give is fine.
I won't spend it recklessly.
See! You're asking for a loan.
And I feel so obliged to lend you money.
Take this for now.
Let me know if it's not enough.
Uncle Chen, I...
I'm going to buy medicine now.
Go back to class once you're done running.
Don't linger on the playground.
It's not that I don't want to help you.
But the scheduled time for the test has passed.
It's against the rules to wait any longer.
I'm begging you, sir.
This opportunity is very important to him.
He's on his way.
Five minutes.
Can you wait for five more minutes?
Just five minutes.
I'm begging you.
Lin, let's wait for five more minutes.
I think this kid is a rare talent.
Thank you, sir. I'm so grateful!
Chen Yi definitely won't let you down.
I swear. Thank you, sir.
Thank you, sir. Thank you!
Kang, you're here to help your senior.
You might not understand.
The academy has strict recruitment standards.
It's not up to us to just wait.
Hurry. Go.
Give it to me.
Yi.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stop them.
Didn't I tell you to stall him?
Why couldn't you stop him?
You're back.
Wash your hands and eat.
[Name: Chen Yi
Forensic physical evidence examination fee]
Who said you could touch my stuff?
Why not?
You've had this planned, haven't you?
To apply for that police academy.
To get far away from me.
Then, go find your biological father.
Chen Li Bin, you have no right to control me.
Only my mom has the right to do that.
But she's dead.
This family has nothing to do with me now.
Do you understand?
Nothing to do with you?
I've raised you like my own son.
After you graduate,
you'll go straight to the power bureau.
Do you have any idea how many people
I had to beg to get this job for you?
Others would kill for this job!
How could you say that to me?
Are you even human?
You know I'm afraid of electricity,
yet you still want me to go there?
You're too weak to prove yourself.
So you kept tormenting and slandering my mom.
And now you're trying to ruin me.
When will you leave me alone?
You already changed my high school choices.
Wasn't that enough?
Do you want to do it again?
Chen Li Bin.
I really...
don't want to be anything like you.
Miao Jing. Miao Jing!
Come out for a second.
Something happened at your home.
You should go back quickly.
[Heartless Green Life! Give us our money back!]
Quiet, everyone. Everyone, please be quiet.
- We'll resolve any issues there are.
- Please.
Everyone, quiet down first. How about this?
You choose a representative. Okay?
Explain exactly what happened.
I want to sue Green Life.
They cheated us out of our hard-earned money.
Look at this. Look at this.
Look at this man. He ended up like this.
I worked so hard driving a cab for a month.
My back is about to break.
This is all I earned.
Just selling supplements earns that much?
It's too good to be true.
Recruitment is going well these days.
But you must remember to hide the ledger well.
Don't give it to anyone.
Relax, you rascal.
Miss. The road ahead is blocked.
We can't get through.
Why don't we take a detour?
Will everyone from Green Life be arrested?
In a place like Teng City,
many lost their life savings to scams.
They'll definitely arrest people.
Someone even lost his daughter's college fund.
Miss.
Did someone in your family get scammed too?
[Teng City First People's Hospital]
Mom. What's going on?
Uncle Chen had a brain hemorrhage.
He hasn't woken up yet.
How did he suddenly have a hemorrhage?
Yi had a fight with his dad.
I don't know what got into him.
He said he wanted to cut ties with his father.
His dad got so angry that he went out drinking.
When he came back,
the power was out in the hallway.
He took a nasty fall.
He hit the back of his head on the floor.
He lost consciousness on the spot,
and was rushed to the ICU.
One thing after another.
I just don't know what a mess this all is.
Do you know what a day here costs?
Three thousand yuan.
How can I afford that?
Chen Yi is unbelievable.
I called him, but he won't even show up.
This is his father!
With so much going on every day,
I can't even go home and change.
You go home first.
I'll stay and keep watch.
He's so stingy.
He even hid his bankbook.
No wonder he's a loser.
Jing.
Go to the power bureau tomorrow.
Get Uncle Chen's medical insurance sorted out.
But you two aren't married.
How can I handle his medical insurance?
Just say you're Yi.
Won't that work? You're so thick-headed.
Just say that.
Anyway,
I won't pay a single cent of this medical bill.
This is yours.
All right.
Thank you.
Here. Sign here, please.
Hello. How can I help you?
Please take a look at this.
[Health Insurance]
Wait a moment. I'll get you a form.
Young lady, are you going to sign or not?
Hurry up. I have things to do.
Are you signing?
There are people waiting behind you.
- I'll come back later.
- Let me see.
Okay. Here.
Next. How can I help you?
- I'd like to check my balance.
- Balance?
Your card balance is 206 yuan.
Sorry, at the moment,
the subscriber you have dialed is unavailable.
Please try again later.
The paperwork is done.
Yi. You're finally here.
Come here. Come and see your father.
He's been lying in there for three days.
He hasn't woken up yet.
He shouldn't have been drinking.
He was fine when he went out.
How could a single fall turn him into this?
What are we going to do now?
Yi, let me remind you.
You're father and son.
You shouldn't let a grudge come between you.
No matter what, he is your father.
Jing and I have been keeping watch
for three days.
Someone needs to be at the ICU at all times.
And his treatment's going to cost a fortune.
You need to start thinking about all this now.
Aunt Wei.
At a time like this?
You must have a lot of faith in me.
I'm just a student.
Where would I get the money?
Well...
Yi, let me remind you.
Your father and I are not married.
Didn't you say you'd take care of him forever?
He's not even dead yet.
[Sealing Strip]
Didn't I tell you to buy cigarettes?
Mints can keep you awake too.
Why are you staying so far away?
I'm not going to eat you.
Bo told me everything that happened to you.
Where have you been these past few days?
Internet cafes. Billiard halls. Arcades.
Teng City has tons of places to hang out.
Then where did you stay?
I put a bed in an empty warehouse
at my friend's repair shop.
I can sleep there anytime.
You didn't think I've been
at vocational school all these years, did you?
What about you?
What?
Three days ago, when you called me...
Turn on the defibrillator.
Defibrillator. Biphasic, 200 joules.
200 joules.
Preparing to defibrillate. Clear.
Charging.
Charged. Clear.
Ready to discharge. Three, two, one.
Resume compressions.
Pinch and compress.
Prepare for defibrillation.
Three, two, one. Go.
Continue compressions.
Who here is Chen Li Bin's family?
I am.
The patient is clinically brain-dead.
He still has a heartbeat,
but he can no longer breathe on his own.
If we continue treatment,
we can only maintain his basic vital signs.
There's no chance he'll regain consciousness.
The medical costs will be substantial.
That's the situation.
Time is of the essence.
You need to make a decision soon.
[Signature of the Authorizing Party]
[Chen Yi]
Don't worry.
He won't be a burden to you
for the rest of your lives.
Yong, Bo, and I took over a pool hall together.
We didn't have enough money at first.
But since he's probably not making it,
once he dies,
I'll use his savings to make up the rest.
It'll be just enough.
I'm cold-blooded, aren't I?
I know Wei Ming Zhen is after the bankbook.
I know who's been calling you lately.
The calls you keep ignoring.
But I don't care anymore.
I just want the payout and inheritance.
I'll let you and your mother stay
in the house until you come of age.
We've known each other a long time.
Let's not make things ugly.
Even if we're not family anymore,
we're still friends.
[The probability of paternity is 99.9999%.]