The two of you kissed.
Are you really not in a relationship?
It was just a kiss.
It didn't mean anything.
There were no feelings involved.
-What are you doing?!
-Let me go!
Stay still.
Lal!
Get out!
Okay, okay.
Calm down. I’m getting out.
Calm down.
Hey!
Ouch!
You think you’re so tough, huh?
Let go!
You!
You think you’re so tough, huh?
Do you want to die?
Korn, what are you doing?!
Let go. Let go of me!
Let go, damn it!
Let go!
Ouch!
Lal, don’t!
Don’t calm down, Lal.
Ouch!
Lal.
Lal!
Wine.
Wine, are you hurt anywhere?
Did he do anything to you?
I’m sorry I came late.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
You’re okay, right?
Lal.
Hm?
Can you please stop apologizing to me?
If you keep being like this,
how am I supposed to get over you?
Wine…
you love me?
Of course I do.
I love you so much.
I’m sorry
for saying that in the meeting room.
But the truth is, I love you so much.
I love you so much that I didn’t want to be
the reason you got fired.
That’s why I said those things.
I’m sorry, Lal.
I love you too, Wine.
Wine.
Will you be my girlfriend?
After everything I did to you,
you still want to be with me?
Of course I do.
I really do.
More than anything in the world.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Yes.
So, to sum it up,
this was a physical fight, correct?
No, that’s not true.
She did it in self-defense.
Who was defending whom?
Uh…
It was during the chaos.
I see.
But this all started
because he attacked our friend first.
He also tried to kidnap her
and assault her.
Hold on.
That accusation is going too far,
Ms. Jantra.
I simply saw that she was drunk
and got into my car.
I meant well.
I was only going to take her home.
With the GPS set like that,
is your house inside a love motel?
I just remembered that
the way to Wine’s condo…
was around there.
I was confused at the time,
so I pinned the wrong location.
It was just a momentary mistake.
I didn’t actually intend to go there.
Your impulse may have been temporary,
but being rotten seems to be who you are.
Who the hell are you insulting?!
Hey, sir.
She got into my car by herself.
How can you say I kidnapped her?
There’s a dashcam, right?
The evidence will show who’s lying.
Think carefully, Lal.
If other people find out about this,
the person
who will suffer the most is Wine.
Yes, Wine is the one
who suffered the most.
She was hurt,
harmed,
emotionally damaged,
and made to lose trust
in the people around her.
And worst of all,
she lost respect for herself.
Do you know how much
what you’ve done to Wine,
from then until now,
has destroyed one person’s life?
Am I really that terrible?
I haven’t even done anything to Wine.
Was Wine ruined because of me?
No, she wasn’t.
Ask Wine yourself whether I did anything
as bad as you said, Lal.
INCOMING CALL
Expecting someone like you
to come to your senses
was probably asking for too much.
If you still can’t be a good father,
a good husband,
a good boss,
or even a decent man,
can you at least be a human being?
Think about it.
If one day someone you love,
your daughter or your wife,
meets someone like you,
someone who does to them
what you did to Wine today,
would you still say what you just said?
I already told you.
I haven’t done anything to Wine.
You did!
Whether you did it or not,
you know the truth full well.
And do you know something?
You’re not the only rotten person
in this world.
In the future,
the people you love
will also meet someone like you.
And when that day comes,
you’ll understand how painful it is
to see someone you love get hurt.
You’re part of the reason
this rotten world exists.
But I don’t believe what Lal said,
the part about Mr. Korn
being unable to reflect on his thoughts.
Once becoming a father,
you should have some sense.
If you don’t want your child
to meet a certain kind of person,
then don’t become
that kind of person yourself.
Oops, I forgot.
Anyone can have a child,
but not everyone can be a father.
Jantra!
Hey, sir.
You’d better go calm down
at the police station.
Go.
Sergeant, please take him.
Go. Get in!
Everyone, please come to the police station
to give further statements.
You were taken into the car
without your consent,
and your friend followed to help you.
Then she got into an argument with him,
which led to a fight.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Did your friend start it?
No.
He drove his car at Lal first.
I understand.
In that case,
I’ll need you and your friend
to come to the station
to give further statements.
She’s not my friend.
Sorry?
She’s my girlfriend.
She is my girlfriend.
Sure.
I’ll call a car and follow you there.
See you.
Hey?
Why didn’t you go
with Numnim and the others?
Numnim and the others
already went with Jantra.
No wonder.
Where did you come from?
I went to the karaoke place,
but the staff said
you all had already left.
You came looking for me?
Yeah.
Why?
Well…
before this, the reason
I didn’t take any action
or do anything about you
wasn’t because I didn’t care about you
or your feelings.
I was just confused.
Confused about what?
I was confused about Wine.
Hey, but not in that way.
It’s just that
Wine was willing to resign
so she could be with the person she loves.
So I thought…
I would resign too,
so I could be with you.
Huh?!
I’m sorry for only saying this now.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Huh?!
Actually, I’ve been thinking
about it for a while.
But before this, I still hadn’t finished
helping Wine with her work.
Wine brought me in
to investigate the company, right?
But if I suddenly quit
just because I had a girlfriend,
I thought I would be a pretty bad junior.
But now that everything has been resolved,
I’m going to resign.
Huh?!
Hey, is that the only word you know?
Can’t you say anything else anymore?
Eh?
You suddenly came and said all this.
What did you expect me to say?
Well, say “okay.”
But you just started working here.
What about your job?
Who cares?
I can find another job.
But I can’t find another person
who makes me feel the way you do.
No, no, no.
We need to think this through
more carefully.
We need to consider the real costs,
the hidden costs,
and analyze all the risks that could affect—
Stop thinking.
If you don’t like me, just kiss me back.
I won’t.
I feel sorry for Korn’s wife and daughter.
When his wife brought their child
to the police station,
I couldn’t even bear to look.
Were you that sad?
I needed to poop.
I probably ate too much spicy salad.
Wow, listen to you.
Keep talking like that
and you’ll get backhanded.
No matter how sorry you feel
for his family,
Wine, don’t give in.
Take this case as far as it can go…
because someone like Korn
will never come to his senses.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, thank you both so much
for coming to help.
Lal, you already know.
When it’s not about work,
I always give it my all!
That sounds weird.
What?
Thank you so much.
I don’t know how I can ever repay you.
Just take care of my Lal for me.
Of course.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
I know you’re swooning,
but it’s time to go home.
Then we’ll get going now.
Mm.
Hey!
Bye.
Get home safely.
Bye-bye.
Let’s go back to our room.
Let’s go.
Everything is still the same.
I kept it all this way,
waiting for you to come back.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry for speaking to you like that.
It’s okay.
I know you did it to protect me.
I never knew what it felt like
to be loved properly
until I was loved by you, Lal.
It feels like such good love.
It’s the best love
I’ve ever received from anyone.
It makes me want to love you well too.
But I don’t know
if I deserve
this kind of good love from you.
Lal,
I promise
I’ll love you the best I can.
Me too.
I love you.
Lal, should we go back?
Why?
I don’t know what I’m supposed to say.
Let’s just go.
Hold on.
Just tell the truth, Wine.
Tell her everything that happened.
There’s nothing to be afraid of.
Right?
Come on.
Come.
Korn.
Korn, don’t.
About what my husband did to you,
Ms. Wine,
I’m truly sorry.
I’m really sorry.
We understand that this incident
must have caused you
and your family a lot of pain.
But we can’t soften our hearts either.
I didn’t come here to beg you.
I came here to tell you
to pursue this case to the very end.
What my husband did has made me
deeply hurt and disappointed.
As a woman and as a mother,
his actions are something
I truly cannot forgive.
I know
this must be
a very difficult decision for you.
But thank you.
Thank you so much
on behalf of your daughter.
There is nothing greater than parents
who protect their child.
Ms. Nan wants to see you.
She probably wants to talk about the case
and some other matters.
Got it.
Ms. Nan has already sent me
a calendar invite.
Don’t worry.
I’ll be there too.
If Ms. Nan does anything unreasonable,
the power of the moon will punish her.
But actually,
Ms. Nan might already be exhausted
from dealing with Medsai earlier.
I walked past the room just now
and thought it was World War III.
They were arguing so loudly.
Really?
I already got fired,
and as for the case,
we’ll proceed according to the law.
What else do you want, huh?
I think
you forgot to return something.
What?
For Numnim’s bubble teas
that you secretly drank.
You don’t need to waste your time
denying it.
The CCTV caught everything.
Fine.
It’s just that.
Here.
And where…
is the apology?
Huh?
Educated people apologize
when they do something wrong.
Seriously?
Over a bubble tea?
Exactly. It’s just a bubble tea.
Why didn’t you buy one yourself
in the first place?
Why are you making such a big deal
out of something so small?
Taking someone else’s things,
whether big or small, is still stealing.
Are you crazy?
I’m not.
Please apologize to Numnim.
Sorry.
Medsai,
I always ordered an XL cup
with extra pearls.
So what you gave me isn’t enough.
I need two more thousand-baht notes.
Here.
Numnim, treat me to grilled pork too.
Sure. Extra bacon set.
I want the family pork set.
The company will take care of everything
regarding the case,
including compensation
and mental health support.
We’ve already arranged a psychiatrist
and a specialized therapist for you.
Whenever you’re ready, just let me know.
Thank you.
Please know that we are ready
to protect your safety,
both physically and mentally.
As for your personal relationship
with our Head of Sales,
I can pretend
I don’t know anything about it.
Pardon?
Do you still want to work here?
But I already submitted
my resignation letter.
I can pretend
I don’t know about that either.
What about the COI rule?
People whose work is connected
or who share mutual interests
are strictly forbidden from dating.
What if the two people
work in unrelated roles?
Pardon?
One person is in Thailand,
and the other is in Japan.
That still counts as working
at different branches.
That alone would mean
their work is no longer connected.
There is an accounting-related position
open at the head office in Japan.
I think it would not be difficult for you
to learn the role.
With your abilities, especially after
you were able to investigate
and catch someone involved in corruption,
our company doesn’t want to lose
someone this capable.
I can refer you if you’re interested.
I heard that you’ve always wanted
to go to Japan.
Opportunities like this don’t come often.
A toast to our sales this month!
Great job!
Now no one can get in the way
of our bonuses anymore.
Yes!
What about Wine?
Isn’t she coming to celebrate with us?
Wine said she was going home to pack
and to tell her mother
about her resignation.
Since Wine made this decision,
it means she must really love you.
I feel guilty, though.
Hmm?
(Why would you say that?)
Hello?
(I’ll be home a bit late today.)
I want to keep talking
with my mom for a while.
(Sure.)
But I drank today,
so I probably can’t pick you up.
(Do you want me to call a car for you?)
It’s okay. I’ll get home by myself.
This might take a while.
(Okay. See you later.)
Wow, one couple has gone public.
Whoa.
Is there anyone here
who still isn’t dating?
You two.
Do you want to?
Nope.
Could I have the menu, please?
I already talked to HR.
Jantra said I can transfer
to one of the affiliated companies.
Then you don’t have to quit anymore, right?
Yeah. I’ll talk to my new boss next week.
Oh, then Wine should transfer too.
That way, she won’t have to
look for a new job either.
Actually, Wine already got an offer,
but she turned it down.
Eh?
What offer?
None of you knew?
No idea.
Mom.
Why aren’t you saying anything?
You gave up going to Japan
because you chose your girlfriend.
What else can I say?
Mom.
Well…
Well, I…
Do you know
how much money it takes to raise a child?
And do you know what I had to sacrifice?
I fought through everything alone.
No one helped me, not even your father.
I know.
You know, and you still chose this path?
Mom,
I’ll find a new job
that pays as much as my old one.
You don’t have to worry about expenses.
Even though I don’t have a job right now,
I’ll still send you money like before.
And what about your future?
Right now,
you may be choosing love over your future.
But what if one day
you break up with your girlfriend?
You’ll regret turning down
what you rejected today, Wine.
What’s wrong?
How did it go with your mom?
With my mom?
Same as always.
What do you mean, same as always?
She still doesn’t understand me.
No matter what I think or what I decide,
she always thinks I’m wrong.
Then…
what did you decide?
The fact that you’re asking means
you already know, right?
This is the country
you’ve always wanted to go to.
Why did you turn it down?
Because of you, Lal.
Wine, just knowing you sacrificed
your job for me
already made me feel guilty enough.
This is such a good opportunity for you.
Stop it, Lal.
Stop talking about this.
I’ve made my decision.
Wine.
Could you think about it again?
What exactly are you trying to say?
I…
I don’t want you
to sacrifice yourself for me anymore.
If it has to be like this,
maybe it’s better if we’re not together.
Do you even realize what you’re saying?
I didn’t mean it like that.
Then what do you mean?
If it were the other way around,
and you were the one who got this offer,
would you choose the job
and break up with me?
But I believe that if it were you,
you would make the same choice.
The choice where we still have each other.
Am I wrong to think that?
No.
Calm down first.
That’s not what I meant.
Wine.
I’m going back to my room tonight.
Wine, let’s talk properly first.
Don’t separate like this.
I don’t want to see your face.
Wine, I’m sorry.
Please open the door.
I’m sorry.
(The number you have dialed
is not responding.)
Can I ask you something?
I see Wine as my idol,
and I want to be like her.
But you don’t like me…
because you see me
as Wine’s replacement, right?
After everything we’ve been through,
you’re still thinking about that?
Yeah.
A little.
Can someone really like a person
just because they look like someone else,
or because they can replace someone else?
Maybe other people can.
But someone
who knows their own heart like me…
can’t do that.
Okay.
I understand now.
I’m sorry for asking over and over.
It’s okay.
If anything is bothering you, ask me.
Nothing is too small.
I want to love you properly.
Wine, open the door!
Wine!
Hey.
She’s not in the room.
Stop knocking.
It’s annoying.
She hasn’t come back?
I haven’t seen her.
If she had come back,
I would’ve heard something.
LAL
Someone’s calling.
Just ignore it.
It's Lal.
Aren’t you going to answer?
It might be urgent.
Can’t we just ignore it?
Just answer.
Fine.
Why is she calling me?
Hello, Lal?
What?
Wine is missing?
Um…
Have you tried checking Wine’s house?
Wine hasn’t come home.
Then, do you have any idea
where Wine might have gone?
I’ve called her,
but she won’t answer my calls.
Then try calling her girlfriend.
Well,
I’m her girlfriend.
Lal?
Yes.
I’m Wine’s girlfriend.
I don’t know where Wine has gone.
She came to talk to me about her job.
I simply gave her my advice as a mother
who worries about her daughter.
Then…
would it be alright if I asked
what you said to Wine?
Have a seat.
Yes.
Wine told me about the job offer in Japan.
I know that it’s Wine’s dream,
and it’s a good opportunity
for her future.
I once had an opportunity like Wine’s too.
But I chose love over my future.
And I made the wrong choice.
That’s why I don’t want Wine
to end up like me.
If you really love Wine,
you know what you have to do,
don’t you?
Yes.
I understand.
I finally understand
how Wine must have felt.
And I shouldn’t have said that to her.
She chose me
because she was sure of her own feelings.
She wanted to protect our relationship.
She didn’t choose me
because she hadn’t thought it through,
but she had already
thought it through carefully.
A future with me in it
was better than any other future for her.
I was the only one
who doubted her decision.
Thank you so much
for helping me understand
why she was so angry with me.
While I didn’t believe in her decision,
she trusted me the most.
I’m sorry for disturbing you so late.
Goodbye.
You don’t understand.
What you did today
will make Wine end up just like me.
Mom,
I can’t promise
what the future will be like.
But what I have to do right now
is show Wine that
she didn’t make the wrong decision.
I’ll excuse myself now.
Goodbye.
Tangkwa.
(I know where Wine is.)
Wine is at the beach
where we went for our company outing.
Wine!
Wine, where are you?
How did you know I was here?
Wine.
Are you really not going to let me
run away at all?
I’m sorry for saying those things to you.
I’m sorry too for running away like this.
We promised each other
that from now on, if something happened,
we would talk things through calmly.
But in the end,
I’m always the one who acts like this.
Let’s just say we each lost one point.
We’re even now, okay?
Yeah.
About Japan, you should go.
It’s okay.
We can have a long-distance relationship.
I go to Japan often.
I’ll see you there.
But it’s three whole months.
What?
Yeah.
Three whole months.
And Ms. Nan said that after I come back,
she’ll let me transfer
to the same company as Proud.
Wait.
So we had this huge fight,
and you ran all the way here,
just because of three months?
Three whole months.
You’re right! Three whole months.
Did you just say “just three months”?
No.
That’s not what I meant.
For me,
three months is long enough
to make me feel like I could die.
But…
the love I have for you
is bigger than that.
Even if you go
for three months or three years,
I won’t change my mind.
Such a sweet mouth.
How do you know?
Have you ever tasted it?
Next time you’re sulking,
can you just go somewhere around Sathorn?
The beach is way too far.
You really came all the way here.
But from now on,
I won’t let you run away again.
Did you pay them out of your own salary?
Yes?
With this much profit gone,
it’s no different from giving them
your own salary.
I love Wine,
but when is she finally going to Japan?
Soon.
Soon as in she’s leaving soon?
Soon as in my head is about to come off.
I get chewed out every single day.
Ms. Wine, this part…
Yes?
I’ll hold a meeting with the team
and help fix the problem here.
Thank you so much.
Here we go again.
I feel bad for Lal.
Lal, we can help fix it too.
It’s just this little thing.
If it’s just this little thing,
then you can do it alone.
You can help with your hands.
You don’t need to talk, okay?
I feel bad for Lal.
SEE YOU IN OUR ROOM.
Calm down.
What’s gotten into you today?
I’m punishing you.
You were really hard on me today.
I assume everyone has received the email.
Are you resigning because
you’re running away from your mistake?
No.
I feel guilty
for hiring someone like that
in the first place.
This is my first step
in taking responsibility.
It has been a great honor
to work with you all.
Even though it wasn’t for very long,
I truly admire your work spirit.
Likewise.
As for the job I hired you for—
I’m flying to Japan next week.
I’ve prepared all the case information
for you already.
If you need anything else,
please let me know.
I’ll send it to you.
Don’t worry.
I’ll do my very best with this case.
Thank you so much.
I’ll leave the rest to you.
I’ll get going then.
You can head back first.
I’m meeting a friend.
Hello, ma’am.
How many people?
Do you have a reservation?
Oh, Cheese.
My friend’s here.
That way, please.
Have you been waiting long?
I had a meeting with the lawyer
about the case.
You just crossed paths with her
a moment ago.
Where? I didn’t see her.
She’s probably gone already.
I’m hungry. Let’s order.
Yeah. I’m hungry too.
Excuse me?
I’m so jealous.
Lal is beautiful and hot.
Congratulations.
You finally have your own fox.
But I won’t get to see her for months.
Come on.
Japan is practically just down the street.
I’m more worried
Lal will keep flying over to see you
and forget to work.
I told you,
I’m trying to fight the case.
Sir, why won’t you give me a chance?
I have work experience at several places.
Let’s put it this way.
Win your case first.
With your reputation this bad,
no one wants to take the risk.
Sir.
Sir, please.
Sir!
Damn it!
Well done.
THREE MONTHS LATER
Nim, I’ll leave this to you.
Oh, alright.
Lal, where are you going?
I’m taking half a day off.
Aww, it’s today!
See you.
Bye-bye.
Hello, everyone.
Today, we have a new HR staff member
to introduce.
Hello. Hello.
I’ve just transferred here.
If you have any advice for me,
please let me know.
Hi. I’m Lal.
See you around.
Hello.
Do you have any advice for the newbie?
Well…
Just make yourself comfortable.
Treat this place like home.
Then I’ll sleep right here.
I’m kidding.
Just kidding.
Wow.
She can fight back.
We like that.
If you need anything, you can ask them.
Okay.
Though I’m not sure
how helpful they’ll be.
See you.
-Goodbye.
Lal is so pretty.
She already has a girlfriend.
And she loves her girlfriend very much.
Her girlfriend just came back from abroad,
so she’s taking her out.
What is her girlfriend like?
Well…
Let’s get back to work.
I’m here.
You’re 15 minutes and 48 seconds late.
There was a bit of traffic up ahead.
I checked the app.
The traffic wasn’t that bad
if you had left the office on time.
Well, I left a little late.
There was a new employee today,
so I stayed and talked to her for a bit.
Let’s go.
The traffic will get even worse.
Welcome back.
Let’s go.
You’re so sulky.
I waited for so long,
and it was so hot, too.
This way, please.
Hey.
Were you secretly taking photos of me?
Let me see. Do I look pretty?
Let me see.
Look.
Hey!
That’s ugly. Delete it.
Why?
You look beautiful.
Really?
Of course.
Seeing you act all cuddly like a cat,
who would’ve known
you could be as fierce as a tiger?
But if a tiger is this beautiful,
I’d gladly let her be fierce.
Stop it already.
What is it?
I’m so lucky I found you.
I think I’m even luckier
because we found each other.
LAL ♥ WINE