Watch on kissasia.li
Father...
You should be thrilled.
Father's back from the dead.
Mr. Hwang?
Am I drunk?
That was Father...
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
Did you see something?
You keep calling me Father.
Well...
Was that Chairman Na?
He really tried to kill you.
I don't think he'll stop with me.
The final target...
is you.
Figures.
He's cornered. He'll do anything.
No.
I'm talking about...
my target.
What?
No way...
Was that your doing?
Exposing Na Eun Se
to stop the Taeha Energy takeover?
Or wiping out Chairman Na's slush fund?
- Hey.
- Still, you saved Choiseong.
And you found your father's real killer.
You got your revenge.
So now I'll tell you what I want.
[Give me Choiseong]
What are you playing at?
I want payback for the life you ruined.
And for the record...
I don't negotiate.
How was it?
Facing Kang Jae Gyeong?
I was super nervous.
But it worked out somehow.
I did exactly what you told me.
Give Kang Yong Ho my regards.
Sir!
Sir...
Are you awake?
Where am I?
I was alive?
Sir!
After they declared you dead,
you suddenly started breathing again.
Jae Seong and I brought you here.
You were unconscious, so we didn't tell anyone.
You just woke up.
Give Kang Yong Ho my regards.
He...
He's in danger.
Not yet, sir.
You just woke up after months.
You need to rest.
There's no time.
Chairman Na will kill Jun Hyeon.
I have to find him.
No! This could kill you!
I already died once.
Sir!
Who did you say?
[Professor Min]
It's me.
Sang Jae.
Is it really you?
Then... Hwang Jun Hyeon is alive?
He's headed toward Yeongjongdo.
I think Chairman Na really took him.
Pull every string with the police
and prosecutors.
Tell them, unless they want
headlines with Chairman Na,
arrest him now.
Honey.
It's me.
I won't let him die this time.
Move. Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
Make sure he never comes back alive.
Go.
Finish it cleanly.
Grab him!
Get him!
Call the other side.
- What the...
- Hey!
- Get out!
- Okay.
Good thing Jae Seong moved fast.
Where is he?
- Hwang Jun Hyeon!
- They found him.
What?
He'll be okay.
Who did?
Where are you going in that condition?
How did you survive?
I had too much to live for.
I never got a proper apology.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
It sure is.
What is wrong with your children?
Do you know how many times
I almost died in your body?
You acted so mighty around me.
But your life was nothing special.
Why does everyone need you dead to survive?
Wait...
You remember everything
from when you were unconscious?
I know Jae Gyeong and Jae Seong
were behind my hit-and-run.
I need to see them pay for it.
Of course.
Can you do as I say?
I set a lot of things in motion in your body.
How can I trust you?
You'll cover for them and waver again.
That will never happen.
Everything is ready to take down Jae Gyeong.
What about the cameras?
They must've caught you.
Don't worry.
My friend Sang Jae will handle it.
So you do have friends.
I thought everyone just used you.
Still got that nerve.
Always telling the truth.
Yeah.
I raised my kids to sell out
even their dead father.
Who can I blame?
Not all your kids are like that.
Your youngest daughter.
Bang Geul is a good person.
How do you know her?
Buckle up. We're moving.
- This is Security.
- What about the CCTV?
A system error shut it down for a moment.
That may have caused the blackout too.
That was Father...
Na Byeong Mo.
You're under arrest for kidnapping and assault.
This is a waste of time.
Lock me up. I'll be out again.
Stop embarrassing yourself.
All your connections are gone.
What? You little...
Your daughter called.
She said she followed your orders.
She's turning herself in.
No... No!
My daughter would never
say something that stupid.
That's bullshit!
How dare you come after me!
[Villa Team]
Hello?
It's me.
Your father woke up.
- I'm coming now.
- He's not here.
Then where is he?
Yeah, I'm here.
Is Jun Hyeon really coming here?
Yeah, he's almost there.
You talked to him? He won't answer my calls.
Are you hiding something from me?
Hello.
Hwang Jun Hyeon!
Is this why you told me to stay out of it?
Do you know how worried I was?
I thought I'd never see you again.
Seriously...
It's me, Dad.
Wake up already.
You're starting to scare me.
Dad. I'm here.
Then Director Song's car went boom!
It was huge.
I'm here.
"Call me."
"You'll have to call the governor anyway."
He was acting so cool.
But honestly, it was kind of impressive.
He had the governor's aide and even Jae Gyeong.
I'm going to lead Strategic Planning.
Until you come back, I'll protect Choiseong.
Dad!
I landed a hit on Jae Gyeong!
If you'd seen it,
you would've said I did great.
So wake up already.
I'll introduce you to Hwang Jun Hyeon.
You'll probably like him. Like I do.
I mean, I don't like him that much.
No.
But I don't hate him either...
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Thank you so much for coming back. Jun Hyeon.
Thank you too, Bang Geul.
Did you hit your head?
Where did he hit you?
Here? Here?
He's going to pay.
- Let's go to the hospital.
- Wait.
I'm okay.
- I'm really okay.
- What do you mean okay?
You've never talked this sweet before!
I mean it. I'm fine.
Oh no. Why are you crying?
Let's go inside first.
You can eat right now? In this condition?
Sorry.
You're right. Koreans run on rice.
Ladies first? And manners?
You're definitely sick. Hospital after this.
Okay.
Is someone here?
Should I go in?
Hello...
I'll take that.
Excuse me.
Help me out here.
You're the smart chairman.
Figure it out. Good luck.
Enjoy your meal.
You punk... Wait!
What is going on?
Jae Seong and Professor Min...
When I started breathing again,
they thought saving me would set things right.
As for Hwang Jun Hyeon...
I just happened to run into him.
Well...
Anyway...
I'm glad you're okay.
You went through all that for a father like me.
I never did a thing for you.
Right.
Why did I bother? It's not like you'd thank me.
No, I meant...
I never thought I'd get to see you again.
I hated myself.
I thought this happened because I resented you.
I blamed myself.
Like it was all my fault.
Do you know why I named you Bang Geul?
You barely cried when you were born.
Every time our eyes met, you smiled.
So brightly.
Hey, don't cry.
I got it.
Right.
You always did.
All on your own.
Still, what kind of name is Bang Geul?
It makes me sound like some kid you picked up.
"Picked up?"
You're my own blood.
Jae Ni, Jae Yeon, Jae Ah...
Why not something like that?
Anyway..
This is real, right?
You won't disappear again, right?
Why is he so awkward?
Just hug her already.
My boy.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh my gosh.
Grandma...
Have you been okay?
Of course.
I've been spoiled rotten these days.
Come here, my boy.
You nagged me so much,
I've been taking all my medicine.
My joints are Ronaldo now.
That one does the cleaning.
That one does the dishes.
And that one does the laundry.
I've got nothing to do,
so I've been bored stiff.
How did you know it was me?
I'm not even in uniform.
I spent so much time with you,
I know just by your footsteps.
"My boy's home from work."
"Something good must've happened today."
I just had to be with you.
I'm sorry.
Let's get you fed, my boy.
- Grandma.
- Yeah, my dear.
Who are you?
- Have you been well, handsome mister?
Jun Hyeon.
I was so worried about you.
You've been through a lot.
Thank you.
You too.
Did you see him?
I kept thinking it was a dream.
But he was right in front of me.
This has to be a dream.
But then I heard his voice.
It really was Dad.
Thank goodness.
Thank you.
Get dressed up, Mom.
Let's go see Dad.
Thank you for looking after my grandma, sir.
Oh my.
What's with him?
They say near death really changes a person.
He's polite to me too. It's so weird.
I'm really okay, Bang Geul.
Why are you smiling so warmly? It's scary.
Yeah?
What kind of person did you turn me into,
Chairman?
I met Kang Jae Gyeong.
I told her I'm taking Choiseong back.
Really?
And she just let you go?
Well...
She's probably losing it right now.
She saw my dad.
Your dad?
Did she see Chairman Kang's ghost?
Not a ghost.
- He's real.
- What?
My dad is alive.
No way.
Come on.
- Manager Park!
- Are you okay, sir?
Sir...
Get some rest.
I'll bring Mom.
Father, it's Jae Seong.
I'm still too ashamed to face you.
Please forgive me for leaving only this letter.
I chased the chairman's seat
when I had no right to it.
I think I pushed you to this point.
If I had apologized to Jun Hyeon then,
and paid for the hit-and-run,
you wouldn't have suffered like this.
I regret it over and over every day.
I don't want to be a father my son
is ashamed of anymore.
I've set things up
so you can finish Jae Gyeong yourself.
Please stay well until we meet again.
Your eldest son, Kang Jae Seong.
My son...
You finally found your conscience.
Was this house always this big?
You're home.
It's quiet. Where's Kang Jae Seong?
He found a place and left with Yi Jun.
Il Jun went to Professor Min's family home.
And my husband?
Did you work all night?
I have to head back out.
You look terrible.
Eat breakfast first.
[Secretary Yeo]
Hold on.
Just listen.
You were right.
He erased the navigation history,
so I put a tracker on Professor Min's car.
He kept visiting a villa.
This is the injection
he took from the hospital.
The same drug used on your father.
Father is alive?
Mr. Hwang and Bang Geul knew.
Maybe Mrs. Jo and Lee Sang Jae too.
Kang Jae Seong called
an emergency board meeting.
To remove you as chairman.
So I was the outcast in this family.
Your husband's car.
Its last route.
Let's go.
Father came back from the dead.
As his daughter, I should pay him a visit.
Yeah.
It really is you.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you more shocked than I am?
How do you always make me the villain?
That day...
The day you cut Jae Seong's harp strings.
If I had scolded you then...
No.
If I hadn't been a father
who held back every word of praise,
because I feared your pride would ruin you...
Maybe we wouldn't have come this far.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
I think my greed made you far too lonely,
Jae Gyeong.
Come back with me.
It's not too late.
No.
It's too late.
If you're truly sorry...
then stay dead, Father.
Hide him until the emergency
board meeting is over.
Got it.
You can't take anything from me.
Where are you? Even without a warrant...
[Head of Legal, Choiseong Group]
this isn't good.
We can only help you if you turn yourself in.
Help me?
Do you know what I'm looking at?
To make me a murderer...
she made her living father look dead?
Where are you going?
Do you know where the board meeting is...
The main conference room? That way.
Hello.
That way.
You're acting strange.
No wonder Bang Geul's worried.
I'm sorry.
We'll help you.
Don't be nervous.
Own the room like Chairman Kang.
I know everything.
What you and Chairman Kang went through.
So you're Chairman Kang's friend.
I'm Lee Sang Jae.
Thank you for holding on this long.
Now it's time for your life to be paid back.
Excuse me, sir.
[Kang Bang Geul]
Hello?
Dad disappeared.
He disappeared?
And the one who caused all this
doesn't even show up.
Not that I expected him to.
When will he ever grow up?
I was planning to gather everyone anyway.
Let's have a meal after this.
Yeah.
We're fine, aren't we?
Of course.
Hello.
I'm Hwang Jun Hyeon.
I'm here on behalf of CEO Kang Jae Seong.
I move to remove Kang Jae Gyeong as chairman.
What's with him?
You got the biggest break in company history.
And now you're betraying her?
She's still grieving the late chairman.
This is why young people can't be trusted.
Even better.
Let's clear up all these ugly rumors
right here.
Still shameless to the end.
Let's start with
Choiseong Trading's hydrogen sale.
As I said, Taeha Group forced that contract.
We're preparing to reverse it.
Or was it to cut ties with Chairman Na?
This is the side agreement
she signed with Chairman Na.
Beyond the reported sale price,
Siren was to receive 100 billion won
and one percent of the hydrogen profits.
You know Siren as
Choiseong Chemicals' private equity fund.
Its real owner is Katherine Kang.
Kang Jae Gyeong.
What are you talking about?
Your money-laundering friends were pretty good.
They even sold the evidence
and cashed in twice.
Did you hire the launderers?
The ones who helped you set up Siren.
We have proof Choiseong Chemicals' funds
fed Siren for years.
I dealt with the man who killed my father?
That's absurd.
Not really.
Not if you wanted him dead.
Are you insane?
How dare...
How long will you stand in my way?
Still holding on?
Should I end it for you?
Oh my.
These people put a camera
in the room to frame me.
Na Byeong Mo and Na Eun Se killed my father.
If I were guilty, I'd be arrested.
This is a plot to remove me as chairman!
Was it also a plot when you framed your father
for your hit-and-run?
Don't accuse me without proof!
That's already over.
Jae Seong turned himself in.
What?
I stood by as Jae Gyeong
tried to suffocate him with a pillow.
That's why he fell into a coma.
Why?
To cover up the hit-and-run.
We fabricated evidence
and deceived the victim, Mr. Hwang.
We even made him hold a fake press conference.
All of it was planned by us.
You're all insane just to take me down.
I built Choiseong into what it is. Trust me.
We're acquiring Taeha Energy.
Not just hydrogen,
but the global battery market will be ours too.
The late chairman's top-five dream is
within reach.
Will you let rumors destroy us?
No matter how I look at it...
you're not fit to be chairman.
That's what your father asked me to tell you.
Seeing ghosts now?
What could he possibly say?
Who said I'm dead?
Honey?
I knew you suspected me.
I couldn't let him be lost to you again.
[Chairman Kang Jae Gyeong]
Stop playing chairman.
Jae Gyeong.
It's not over...
It's not over.
No.
Jae Gyeong!
Chairman! Chairman!
- Oh my!
- Chairman...
Why did you save me?
Why?
[Two Years Later]
She draws the same thing every time.
She doesn't even know her name.
She erased who she was.
Her mind rejects it too strongly.
She won't forgive herself easily.
Honey, I'm here.
But she still remembers one person.
The person she loves most.
Aiden, Logan!
It's been five hours. Let's go home.
Aren't you hungry?
Can they not hear me?
How do you win every single time?
It's okay to lose.
Your dad likes losing more.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Oh.
Their competitive streak is no joke.
They won't let anyone go home until they win.
The other parents keep looking at us.
We're totally blacklisted.
Blood will tell.
We were never that bad.
They're worse than me and Jae Gyeong...
It's okay. You can say it.
Il Jun, I mean...
Logan will have to see his mom someday.
Right?
He just needs a little more time.
I worried when you left to care for the boys.
But you sound happy. I'm glad.
It suits me perfectly.
I feel at peace.
What about Korea?
You haven't come back once in two years.
I'll bring the boys this break.
They keep saying they miss your cooking.
Your views blew up again, huh?
You're a superstar now.
[The Chairman's Table]
Hi, guys.
It's Mrs. Jo from "The Chairman's Table."
I finally got my Gold Button.
I owe this honor to my one million chairmen.
Thank you.
Today's dish is Shepherd's purse ramyeon.
[Looks good!]
[Choiseong, make it a meal kit]
[Did you see the Choiseong news?]
What news?
After a series of scandals,
the Kang family left management.
Choiseong is now run by professional managers.
Despite public concern,
it has grown remarkably.
It offers a new model
for Korea's chaebol system
long ruled by family succession.
[CEO Lee Sang Jae, Choiseong Trading]
Especially...
CEO Lee Sang Jae now leads Choiseong Trading.
He rose through Choiseong
from new hire to Strategic Planning MD.
After Taeha split off,
Choiseong acquired
its core business, Taeha Energy.
With Choiseong Rotem,
Trading now leads hydrogen mobility...
Don't you have work?
Did you come here to read that to me?
I'll yank that MD plaque off your desk.
Come on. An MD's not a manager.
I, MD Park Bong Gi, have it all under control.
Everything is running smoothly.
You said you were swamped.
You kept begging me for new hires.
New hires are Team Leader Kang's job.
Oh, right.
She said she's cleaning house first.
At Taeha Group.
[Choiseong - Taeha Bio]
[M&A 3rd Meeting]
A Middle Eastern investor is interested
in our Alz7 dementia patch.
They're offering 500 million dollars,
so I told them we're talking to Choiseong...
Isn't it a scam?
Sorry?
Your natural compound missed
the required level in the report.
You know the MFDS could suspend
production over that, right?
That's not true.
Phase 2 trials ended without issues.
So Phase 3 is the buyer's problem?
You fake the numbers, sell it high,
and walk away?
Do you think we're stupid?
You're using this M&A to make a profit.
Taeha almost fell apart.
Choiseong is taking it in
and protecting employee jobs.
Don't gamble with people's livelihoods.
Thank you.
New hire orientation...
[Strategic Planning]
Strategic Planning is the core of Choiseong.
It's produced many great people.
Including me.
For projects, make sure you get
your bonuses and incentives.
Don't let your bosses steal your ideas.
Protect your worth
and negotiate a higher salary.
Got it?
Then... is that rumor true too?
Which rumor?
That the Choiseong gave their shares
to employees as bonuses
and donated the rest to society?
One last stop.
[Anyone at Choiseong can become chair]
It's true.
A company owned by its employees.
A place where you earn as much as you work.
The lifelong job
we only heard about in stories.
If you want it, we can make it real.
That's not for new hires like us.
Actually, it is.
It really happened.
A legendary new hire almost became chairman.
[Anyone at Choiseong can become chair]
Go in now!
Pass it!
Shoot!
Good! Stay focused!
Don't lose heart!
Alright.
Pass it to Yong Seong!
Come on, Yong Seong!
Goal!
Good Job!
Grandpa Boss!
Your shot was great today.
Your passes were beautiful.
I booked the galbi place nearby.
Go eat up.
Five servings each!
Work hard like your coach, okay?
- Yes, sir!
- Go on.
You're here.
Hey. What are you wearing?
Look who's talking.
Young seventy?
Let's go.
You're coming to
Hae Chan's send-off next month, huh?
Of course.
He's our first player going to the EPL.
He'll make us a top club.
I knew he was different from day one.
His thighs were this big.
I'm the one who recommended him for his shots.
You're right.
- You're something else.
- You just noticed?
You're seeing my grandma today. Try to smile.
Your grandma doesn't like me.
I was her grandson and guardian. Everything.
Grandma likes you.
She wants us to be family.
She's waiting for us with a whole feast today.
"Family?"
Who?
I thought I was meeting your girlfriend today.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
So... what happened was...
One second.
I told her not to come...
What?
I'll just grab my bag and be right back.
Wait here.
That punk...
Something's off.
A movie poster shoot will begin shortly.
All staff, please gather by the front seats.
Why isn't she answering?
No way...
It can't be.
My daughter's way too good for him.
She's Choiseong's ace.
I need to set him straight first.
Caught you!
Men and women need boundaries!
In broad daylight?
Have you no shame?
Chairman Kang! Calm down!
How dare...
Dad, calm down first.
My back...
Are you okay?
Are you okay, sir?
I told you it'd take time
to get used to the robot legs.
Do you know me?
You know my dad?
Oh my gosh.
This is insane.
Not again... yeah?
- What's with her?
- What's going on?
Why am I over there?
Oh my.
Is that a mask?
Why is it so realistic?
Are you... my twin?
Or my doppelganger?
Doppelganger...
Doppelganger.
What's wrong with my voice?
What did you do to me?
So... here's what's going on.
- Are you okay?
- Are you alright?
We're out of time.
We have to go.
Oh, wait.
- I'm not her.
- Right.
I'm the real one!
See?
See? It's me.
It's me!
Right.
He's the real one.
Look at my moves! It's me!
- Yeah, great moves.
- Let's go.
- Great moves.
- Hurry.
No, I'm telling you!
I'm her!
The Trading affiliates...
Sorry.
How dare!
I'll do it again.
How do I do this?
Pre-tti-ful!
- What?
- Again.
"Pre-tti-ful!"
Gwang Bang Geul is...
"Gwang" Bang Geul?
The mother and daughter
coughed up all their slush funds.
- I'm really sorry.
- Why?
Please...
Be happy.
Thank you.
I shouldn't have joked around.
Let's go!
Manager Park, we were close, huh?
What did you do to me?
Someone's laughing.
Thank you so much.
We love you.
Mr. Lee Jun Young.
You worked so hard for this drama. Love you.
One last smile.