( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I always told myself
that nothing is more important than my future.
For this competition, we are very lucky
to have both the class president and the top student.
Taking time off from your studies to compete together.
I believe you two will make a great team.
Since it's you two, I probably don't need to remind you,
but for now, I want you to be on your best behavior.
Just like you always have.
Don't cause any scandals
that could get us disqualified.
As for you, Nalin,
regarding your scholarship application to study abroad,
I'm putting my hopes on you.
But I have to be honest with you.
You have to win.
How is it?
Was it tiring taking the long way around?
Not at all.
I'm the one who doesn't want anyone to know we're dating.
I'm sorry.
It's totally fine.
I understand.
I know it would affect your scholarship.
Yeah.
We should stop.
Or else I won't be able to hold back.
But...
if you want to do more...
It's okay.
Hey, someone might see us.
Let them see.
Our dream is about to come true anyway.
The director will approve the scholarship next week.
Wait a minute.
I have something to tell you too.
Well...
My mom is letting me study at the same place as you.
She even said we should live together
so she won't have to worry.
Hey, that's great!
Mink.
Let's celebrate our 3rd anniversary together.
Yeah!
What are you two doing?!
Mother Superior, please discipline these two students
with the same standards you use for everyone else.
Otherwise, there might be complaints.
Nalin.
About your scholarship...
I'll have to suspend the consideration for now.
Mother.
I kissed Nalin first.
She didn't consent to it.
Please punish only me.
It was me.
I've always had feelings for Nalin.
I don't want to be the reason
my friend can't achieve her dream.
Nalin.
Is this true?
Hello, Mink.
The room is amazing. I can't wait for you to move in.
Hey...
I don't think I can go anymore.
Well...
My mom found out about us.
And she can't accept it.
She's so mad
that I lied about us just being close friends.
But I understand her.
She also said...
the reason we like each other
is because there are no boys at school.
Right now...
my mom has already found another school for me.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Then... what about us?
What are we going to do?
While you're over there,
take good care of yourself.
If we break up,
you won't have to worry about anything back here.
No. I won't break up with you.
Even if you disappear, I'm not breaking up with you.
Even if we never see or talk to each other again,
I won't break up with you, Mink.
Can we please not break up?
I don't want to break up.
Here.
I saw this and thought of you, so I bought it.
I think...
I like you.
I'm sorry.
I don't feel that way about you.
Well...
I kinda figured.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
But...
I won't be able to stop my feelings for you anytime soon.
But I'll try not to cross the line.
Okay?
Even if you wanted to, I wouldn't let you.
Wow, is this the same person from school?
Different person.
Let me pour you a drink.
Welcome drink!
No, thanks.
How did you get here?
Goi invited me.
Are you happy in Class C?
Drink?
No, thanks.
Guys...
We shouldn't be drinking.
Should we go home?
Aw, man.
I don't wanna go yet.
Oops. Sorry.
Sophie.
I forgot to ask.
Did you like my birthday present?
It was me.
I'm the one who told Ms. Thip.
And she told your mom...
that you and Amy were making out.
What the fuck are you talking about?! What the fuck did you do?!
- Sophie, calm down!
- Why did you do that?!
Hey, calm down!
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
Stop, stop! That's enough!
I'm gonna kill you!
Enough!
Get up!
Let's go home with me.
What's wrong with you?!
What does this have to do with me?!
What's that noise?
Stop, that's enough!
Stop!
That's enough!
What the hell is your problem?!
Sophie, stop! Enough!
What the fuck is wrong with you?! What did I ever do to you?!
Enough, stop it!
That's enough, stop!
Calm down.
Where the fuck are you going?!
Hey.
I was just about to wake you up.
Got a headache?
Yeah... a little.
Is this your house?
Yeah.
Here.
Wear this for today.
We're probably the same size, right?
Did you bathe me last night?
No, just changed your clothes.
But... if you changed my clothes, you must have seen...
Changed your clothes...
I didn't think anything of it.
Oh...
Uh...
So... how did I end up here?
Where the fuck are you going?!
What the fuck is wrong with you?! Why are you hitting my car?!
What the fuck is your problem, bitch?!
Earn!
I really don't get it.
Why is P'Som so obsessed
with getting me to do a face-reveal content.
Yeah.
I don't really get it either.
So I punched her once.
I doubt she'll dare show her face now.
Thank you.
Hello? Hey Earn. You're awake?
I know what you were trying to do last night.
But let me tell you to stop trying.
Because from now on, I'm not making any content with you anymore.
Thank you for everything.
I'm done talking to you.
That was badass.
Is this the Earn I know?
So fierce.
Well... I've been meaning to quit for a long time.
We learn from the pain, right?
But...
Even though I have no idea how to make money from now on.
You'll figure it out.
Stop it!
Sophie, stop!
You do know that violence is unacceptable in this school, right?
And your romantic affair with Wadtawan?
Amy and I are nothing to each other.
Good.
Considering your past good behavior,
I will give you a light punishment.
You're stripped of your role as the student council president.
And I will appoint Shisha, the runner-up,
as the new president instead.
Sophie.
I'm sorry.
I know you must feel awful.
But I really didn't mean to steal your position.
Stop the bullshit.
I really didn't mean to.
You can slap me again.
I'll let you.
I'll transfer the money for the clip.
The princess has become a commoner.
Whoa, are you okay?
Why are you...
so pretty today?
You're so drunk. You drank a lot, didn't you?
I'm not drunk.
Okay, if you're not drunk, what number is this?
What are you doing here?
Waiting for me?
Yeah.
Why?
Oh, well...
[Transfer Successful: 40,000 THB]
I know you have to pay back the seniors in your circle.
I didn't want you to be in trouble, so I'm lending it to you first.
And don't worry, I won't ask for it back in front of our friends.
I won't tell anyone either.
You can pay me back slowly.
Just a little bit every month. I'm okay with that.
Thank you.
But I don't want to borrow money from anyone anymore.
I think I'll try to find a way myself first.
Alright then.
But if you ever need it, let me know right away.
Mhm.
By the way, what happened last night? Tell me.
I woke up this morning and couldn't remember anything.
You don't remember anything at all?
Well...
Nothing really.
Just a little chaos.
Okay.
Hey.
I thought you were waiting for me!
Wait up!
Hello, sweetie.
Mom, you said you'd call me often.
Mom's been busy.
Aren't you busy with your new friends at school too?
No, just the usual.
Anyway, never mind.
Oh, Mom, I have a question.
What is it?
Are people's words trustworthy when they're drunk?
Whoa...
You've been a Bangkok girl for just a bit,
and you're already sneaking out to get drunk?
Nooo.
Remember the party I told you about?
I only drank a little. I wasn't drunk at all.
But my friend drank and got really drunk.
So I'm calling to ask for my friend.
Just a friend, right?
Uh-huh...
A real friend.
Let me tell you, drunk people are more honest than sober ones.
Really?
Yeah.
I've never seen a drunk person lie.
[#FakeRichGreenCheerleader #APT]
[Owes almost 80k in total to the whole school.]
[If she owes you, go get it back before it's too late.]
[That's just in school. Who knows who else she borrowed from outside.
Looking rich with other people's money lol]
How do you explain this?
I really did borrow it.
But I had some problems back then.
And now I've paid everyone back.
You know this ruins the school's reputation, right?
I know.
But if you're only worried about the school's reputation,
why don't you punish the person who posted it?
Or is it because you don't want to...
since Shisha is your favorite?
I don't have favorites.
And if you hadn't caused trouble first,
would anyone have shared this?
Don't let this happen again.
Otherwise, the school will have no other choice
but to expel you.
[Som: The face-reveal content with YUMIVERSE you asked for...]
[I can't do it anymore.]
[Don't you want the money?]
[I do.]
[Then make it happen.]
[What if you just get to see her face, but no clip?]
[Fine. But you only get half the money.]
What do you want?
Hey.
Talk to me nicely.
I'm actually here to help you.
A lot of seniors in your circle are starting to gossip
that you're in trouble.
Many of them must have asked you for their money, right?
If they want their money back, I'll find a way to pay them.
You don't have to rush to pay me back.
But with others...
I think if you don't pay them back soon, it's going to be a big deal.
How about this?
I think I can help you.
Just...
come have dinner at my place tonight.
And a lot of your debt to others will disappear.
I'll find the money to pay you back soon. Just leave.
What are you thinking about?
You look spaced out.
Nothing...
I was just wondering how I'm going to pay for my tuition.
Hey.
Now that you don't have to make content with Teacher Som anymore...
That means...
you have time to tutor a lot more students.
Don't overthink it.
I'll help you find more people.
Belle, have you seen this?
People are sharing it in the group chat.
I think...
I like you.
Could it be Goi...?
Did you film me?
So what?
Are you going to slap me?
Go ahead. Do it.
If you think people don't look down on you enough already.
Hello, Mother.
Hello.
Have a seat.
I must apologize to you, Nalin.
For making you come all the way here to talk about your matters.
Are you not feeling well, Mother?
I'm sorry for bothering you.
It's alright.
I've heard everything from Teacher Thip.
Let's talk about your matters.
First of all...
I haven't been a good enough teacher.
And I even caused trouble.
Teacher Thip probably told you already.
So I think I should...
Hold on.
In what way do you think you haven't been a good teacher?
When it comes to teaching,
you've done an excellent job.
And the students' test scores...
are very satisfactory.
I didn't follow the conditions I promised you.
Instead of telling you...
like I promised.
Probably the letter S.
About Earn doing sex content...
I think she must have her own reasons.
I even helped cover them up.
And another important thing...
that I failed to do...
was keeping a professional distance between a teacher and a student.
Are you talking about Belle?
At the very least,
Belle has changed for the better.
For this,
I should be the one thanking you.
I want you...
to keep taking care of Belle like this. Can you do that?
You must have seen the clip, right?
I think Belle must be throwing a fit right now.
No.
Belle isn't throwing a fit.
She's gotten much better.
And that's because of you.
Just now, before I arrived,
Teacher Thip called to tell me that
Belle went off on the friend who filmed the clip.
A lot of people gathered to watch.
Do you know
how Belle... got back at her friend?
Listen up, everyone.
This bitch, Goi, is the one who filmed the clip
to make everyone misunderstand
that Teacher Nalin and I were about to kiss.
I really don't get it. Are you just a problematic kid,
or do you just have too much free time?
Why do you like getting other people in trouble?
Using violence on you would be a waste of time.
I just want everyone here to know.
All of you.
This bitch sells out her friends.
If you ever accidentally tell her anything, I guarantee you...
she'll tell the whole fucking world.
Are you going to have any friends left after this?
As Belle's aunt,
I must thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Even without me,
Belle would have definitely kept improving.
Especially if she knew
how much her aunt worries about her.
Mother...
Please don't think I'm overstepping,
but there is still time.
To show Belle how much you love her.
I'll give you your medicine now.
Excuse me.
This might sting a little.
Many years ago, I was diagnosed with cancer.
But I was treated and it went away.
At that time, Belle was still at her old school.
I never let her know about it.
But now...
it's back again.
And it's in the terminal stage.
Mother...
I don't have much time left.
So I thought, at the very least,
I want to live to see Belle graduate high school.
I want you to help me.
I'm begging you.
Even so...
what happened at my house,
it would be hard to deny responsibility for it.
Teacher Thip definitely won't let it slide.
If you're worried about that,
don't be.
I've already made a deal with Teacher Thip.
You won't face any disciplinary action.
Mother.
When do you plan to tell Belle?
Have a seat, Teacher Nalin.
You probably already know
that you're still a teacher here because Mother Superior asked for it.
Yes.
And because of this, I've become the Deputy Director.
Acting Director.
While Mother is recovering,
I have to take care of this position's responsibilities as well.
Let's get straight to the point.
Because there are still many important things to do.
Mother Superior already told you, right?
About the central board coming to inspect our school.
Someone from the central board whispered to me that
the inspector will come disguised as the new guidance counselor.
But it seems like they are...
deliberately messing with our school.
I heard that
if they find anything inappropriate,
they could even order the school to be closed.
I see.
And what do you want me to do?
You can call me "Deputy Director". Get used to it.
Okay.
Teacher Thip.
Mother Superior has told me everything.
About you covering up the students' bad behavior.
You can't do that anymore.
Because we're on the same team now.
I hope you understand.
Don't worry, Teacher Thip.
I definitely won't let my students cause any trouble.
It's not just the students who shouldn't cause trouble.
The teachers shouldn't cause any either.
Right?
I asked your classmates for these and kept them for you.
Them fighting over it, so I was afraid you wouldn't get one.
Thank you.
I feel bad. You aren't even in 11th grade yet.
But you have to collect these for me.
Am I taking care of you too much?
You can tell me. I don't want to make you uncomfortable.
Not uncomfortable at all.
But...
you have to let me take care of you in return, you know?
[Congratulations]
Are you proposing to me?
Do you want to marry me?
Where can we even get married?
Well, if we can't do it here,
we can just go somewhere else.
If this place isn't for us,
we'll go get married somewhere else. Anywhere.
As long as I have you.
What a smooth talker.
For this...
you deserve a reward, right?
One kiss.
Just one?
Please?
No.
Get well soon, buddy.
By the way, the extra donation money you transferred,
did you put it in the donation box?
Yes, Doctor.
I wish there were more people like you two.
A lot more cats would be happy.
Oh, please, Doctor.
Just Nano alone is stubborn enough.
I didn't ask you to get involved.
Well, I'll help out next time too.
So we can have another healthy cat.
But treating them isn't enough, we have to find a home for them too.
So, next time, please help me announce it to find a home for this one.
Okay.
Aww. Who's getting a new home soon?
About the money you owe the seniors...
I saw there's an influencer flea market next week.
There's no booth rental fee either.
Hmm.
Do you want to go sell more stuff? I'll go with you.
Oh, I have nothing left to sell.
But thank you for always helping me out.
I already paid back all the seniors.
Huh?
Yeah.
The modeling pay that was delayed finally came in.
So I used it to pay everything off.
Wow, that's great.
We should celebrate.
Sure.
My treat.
It's okay. I'll treat you.
Why couldn't you keep your position as the student council president?
Did I not raise you right?
What did I do wrong?
Why did you turn out like this, huh?!
Sophie.
What did I do wrong?
I'm a bad mother, right?
I don't know either.
I'm not you.
But you must have done something wrong.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have grown up to be like this.
Are you satisfied now?
You heard what you wanted to hear, right?
Everything is your fault.
I never got to be myself.
Here. I'm being myself now.
I'm being exactly who you raised me to be.
Do you see it now?!
Sophie.
Why don't you keep slapping yourself?
Amy isn't even your child,
and you could do it in front of her.
Once I leave,
you can do whatever you want.
Sophie.
Sophie, come back!
Sophie!
So.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry for bothering you.
You don't need to apologize.
Honestly, you can bother me anytime.
It's just...
I couldn't imagine...
if I didn't have you...
how I would get through today.
I have a girlfriend now, So.
That doesn't matter.
I can be whatever you want.
As long as I have you.
You're home pretty late.
I was helping my friends clean up the grandstand.
I wasn't going to scold you.
Actually, I'm glad you're finally using the iPad I bought you.
I saw it sitting in your room unopened for so long.
So I bought you a keyboard for it today.
They said it makes typing as fast as on a laptop.
Try connecting it. I didn't even get to test it when I bought it.
To see if it really types that fast.
Dad...
The iPad isn't with me right now.
My close friend really needed money urgently.
And since I wasn't really using it...
I decided...
to sell it.
But once I get the money back, I'll buy a new one for you.
You're exactly like your mother.
Always taking my money to give to other women.
Your mom lied to me countless times.
Sometimes claiming you were sick.
But in the end, she gave the money to another woman.
Are you planning to be a deviant like her?
What the hell are you talking about?
Mom isn't like that.
She is exactly like that.
The reason you had to come live with me...
is because your mom...
was going to take a million baht
to open a cafe for that Pim woman.
That's not true! Mom was afraid the loan sharks would hurt me.
Then hear it from her yourself.
Haven't you told her about that one million baht yet?
I did, but your daughter just wouldn't believe it.
Well, she caused some trouble.
Who in their right mind sells the iPad I bought for them?
And says they gave the money to a friend.
She's just like you.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Make sure you explain that million baht to her clearly.
And go get my iPad back.
Long time no see.
Visiting the school?
Oh, actually...
I'm the new guidance counselor here.
Someone from the central board whispered to me that
the inspector will come disguised as the new guidance counselor.
And what about you, Nalin? What are you doing here?
I'm a French teacher.
Really?
That means we'll get to see each other often then.
Actually,
I had something I wanted to reach out to you about.
I just couldn't find the right time.
About your wedding, right?
You knew?
Yeah.
I heard it from a friend.
Congratulations, Mink.
Finally, here...
women can actually marry women now.
The law passed faster than expected, huh?
Yeah.
I thought I'd be the one getting married before you.
But it turns out you beat me to it.
I'm really happy for you, Mink.
But I'd really love for you to come to the wedding.
During our high school years,
besides a few close friends,
it was just you...
who I felt was truly important in my life.
But...
if it makes you uncomfortable,
that's completely fine.
I understand.
Thank you.
I'll...
think about it.
This place has changed a lot.
If you need anything, just ask, new teacher.
Since you started teaching here, have there been any issues?
Are kids these days still like we were?
Like secretly crushing on each other.
Secretly doing things they shouldn't.
Or rebelling against the school rules like we did?
There's nothing like that here.
Because here...
[Hello, YUMIVERSE.]
[We met the other day, Earn.]
we teach all of our students...
[Which foundations are you raising funds for this month?
I want to help.]
[Will you be my girlfriend?]
to be well-behaved.
Hello, Earn? I think I like you.
Why are you only telling me this now, Belle?
All this time, you tricked me into helping you scam money?
Tell me! Speak up! My mom helped you...
I went out of my way to help you too. Why are you so selfish?
Mink.