[Sin and Love]
[Episode 2]
Police!
Is anyone in there?
Sung Ho, you're still here.
Officer Kwon was looking for you.
I covered for you.
Got it.
I'm leaving first.
As expected,
you're a bad guy,
Sung Ho.
You
have changed a lot.
How so?
Your stamina
is much better.
What are you doing?
Looks like you've earned a lot of money.
Why do you say that?
'Cause it doesn't seem like you.
True.
I really want to leave here
as soon as possible.
Have you thought of me
in the past 5 years?
Why are you asking me that?
Tell me.
Every day, all day—
you were all I could think about.
You don't mind if I take off
this police uniform, do you?
Mm.
Take it off for me.
You've lost a lot of weight.
Yoo Sehyun.
Give me a sec.
Yeah, shoot.
Now?
Got it.
I'll be right there.
You're hiding something from me, right?
It has nothing to do with you.
Sung Ho.
You are a cop,
and I am a nightclub owner.
From the very beginning,
we were never from the same world.
And that kiss just now?
It meant absolutely nothing.
Five years
is enough time to change a person's fate.
I won't be like before,
having only you in my eyes.
Because I'm no longer
the person I used to be.
Sung Ho.
Do you know what's
the most invaluable thing in the world?
It's feelings.
You wear that police uniform,
standing in a glamorous world.
Full of justice, perfect, and clean.
While I am just
a nightclub owner.
A person struggling
to survive in the shadows.
From the very beginning,
we were never from the same world.
Don't come here anymore.
You get in the way.
Oh, right.
It was the same in high school.
Your parents were the school's sponsors.
And I was just
a student who couldn't go to school
without a scholarship.
Yoo Sehyun!
Say whatever you want, I don't care.
But if you break the law,
I will definitely arrest you.
Kwon Hyukjae.
What exactly do you want to do?
Sung Ho.
I'm sorry.
Mayor Li.
You must become the president.
Because I have
bet everything I have on you.
Minho, it's time to get off work.
You can take off your police uniform.
Yes.
How about we play a game?
Hmm?
Hit me.
Harder.
I'm telling you to hit me harder.
Harder. More.
More!
Use some force.
Damn it.
Can I come in?
Come in.
Are there
any special instructions?
There are many things suspicious
about those nightclubs in Gangnam,
but there is no solid evidence.
Keep an eye on them.
Report to me if there's anything.
Yes, understood.
Also, Sung Ho...
You and Yoo Sehyun
from the Gangnam nightclub,
were high school classmates, right?
Yes, we were classmates.
But we haven't contacted each other
since then.
We just ran into each other today.
Ran into each other?
But I heard
you two used to be very close.
You even dated.
That was all in high school.
It was just playing around.
We have nothing to do with each other now.
Sung Ho.
You just came back.
You must separate
public and private matters.
Understand?
Officer Kwon,
are you familiar with Yoo Sehyun?
We met before
when I was investigating a case.
Don't take it to heart.
Go back and rest.
Minho,
Yoo Sehyun is the informant
I planted next to Sung Ho.
Keep a close eye on him.
Got it?
Yes.
Go.
Bastard.
Were you happy to see Sung Ho yesterday?
How far do you want me to go?
You told me to see him, so I did.
You told me to distance myself, so I did.
But how far do you intend
on bossing me around like this?
Damn it.
Sehyun,
you are now the boss of Gangnam Palace.
Okay?
And Sung Ho is
a line you must never cross.
If you dare to cross it,
you both will die.
Got it?
It's been 5 years.
It's already the 5th year.
You promised me.
Huh?
That as long as I hold on for 5 years,
you promised I could return
to the police force.
You also promised me
I could return to Sung Ho's side.
That promise still counts.
But Sung Ho came back—
that is the variable.
What if you let your feelings
get in the way?
Hmm?
Please don't touch Sung Ho.
If you promise me that,
I will keep doing this.
What are you talking about?
Hey.
I
had no intention of touching him.
Besides, there's no value in doing so.
Don't let those pointless feelings
ruin everything.
Understand?
Oh, one more thing.
You know Kim Minho, right?
He is my informant
I placed next to Sung Ho.
You should also watch your words
and actions.
Hello?
Sung Ho.
Can't recognize my voice?
I'm Yoo Sehyun.
Yoo Sehyun?
How did you get my phone number?
Let's meet at Gangnam Palace.
Let's talk properly when you get here.
What do you want?
Sung Ho,
aren't you curious
why I suddenly disappeared 5 years ago?
Stop trying to test the boundaries.
You are a club owner, and I am a cop.
I have nothing to say to you.
Nothing to say?
Why I gave up my dream of becoming a cop
and chose to run a club—
come if you want to know the reason.
I'll tell you everything.
Fine,
I'll go.
8 PM. I'll wait for you.
But if you dare to mess with me,
I won't let you get away with it.
The truth from 5 years ago...
[Sin and Love]