( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
SOLD OUT ON YOU
Mechoori.
Can I stay here?
What?
Can I stay over?
I know what I said, but I didn't
think you'd actually come over at this
hour.
Well. I came over for you. To help
you sleep.
Oh, I can't say anything around you,
but what about work?
I needed to come to Seoul anyway.
I have a lot to do before signing
-the contract.
-And you're sure everything's okay?
I'm fine, everything okay with you?
Should I go?
No, everything's fine. You know that.
Where's your bedroom again?
Oh, Mechoori. Wait! Let me straighten
things up a little. It's a bit of a mess.
Follow me.
What is that?
You haven't been able to sleep this
whole time. I'm going to do this until
you fall asleep. I find it works well.
Stop doing that. You need to sleep too,
don't you?
I'm gonna sleep once you're asleep,
I'll use the couch.
What?
Uh, what-- Why? Because my couch--
It's really small, the bed can
easily fit both of us.
I'm fine with the couch.
Try to sleep.
It's just, the couch is really
uncomfortable, and this bed is really,
really cozy.
Good night.
You're not saying…
You're going to stay in Korea, are you?
Because of that home shopping host?
Ms. Ye-jin.
Hey, neighbor! I'm glad to see you.
You can call me, Mr. Seo. I've decided to
get my job back after all.
Crossing every finger for you.
Feeling better about it already.
Don't forget to eat well, it's really
crucial. I can send you a list
of all the best restaurants in the area.
Get it.
Uh, no, no!
Going for a run around the park.
QUAIL EGGS
SPICY RADISH SALAD
So salty.
This rice was just milled yesterday.
So it should be fresh.
I appreciate it.
I think I'll take one myself.
These quail eggs here are more fresh.
They're better when they have
rough shells, you know?
Are you a chef of something?
No, but I know a bit about quail eggs.
Thanks for the tip.
I'll take one as well.
Thinking of having some ssambap for
lunch?
The snacks at home are too salty. So I
thought…
Wrapping them in vegetables might help.
Ah, no. Too much salt. What happened to
low-sodium?
I know, right? Have a nice day.
You too.
-Huh?
-Oh?
After you.
Oh, no.
Ah! Oh, no.
Guess we're neighbors. Do you live alone?
Ah, no.
Well, who ever you live with is lucky to
have someone who cooks for them.
I imagine same for you.
Was my cooking really that salty?
Was it?!
That was so--
Wha-- Ye-jin.
-Would you mind giving this a taste?
-Ah. sure.
It's incredible! Wow.
Is it really? What a relief.
Did you go for a run with Mr. Seo?
No, we ran into each other while
I was out.
So, you're the one who helped Ye-jin,
right? You're Mr. Seo, hmm?
I've been wanting to treat you to dinner,
but I'm afraid you won't like it.
No, it looks so delicious.
I can tell you're a master chef just from
your touch.
How did you know?
I'm a cooking teacher down at the
cultural center.
I knew it! I've never had an in-law
with such knife skills.
Uh, am I an in-law?
Oh, my bad!
-Almost forgot the onions.
-Right, onions.
I've got-- Here you go.
Don't just hover around us. Have a seat.
Uh, yeah.
This boy's made of glass.
-Okay.
-Wow! That looks so good.
Yeah. Thanks so much for this.
Pass your plate, I'll serve you.
Oh, it's okay. I'll do it.
Oh, okay. Someone else then?
Ah, thank you very much.
Here you are. Enjoy. And if it's too
salty, add some rice, or some veggies.
You can make a wrap.
It's not too salty at all. Is this
umami that I'm tasting?
Precisely. Umami.
Hand me your plate.
Thanks.
Fill it up, please.
-Eat up, now.
-I'm not sure he likes spicy food.
Ms. Dam Ye-jin.
I'm just fine. Please eat.
This is delicious…
Sir.
Oh, is it? Seems you like it.
Yes, sir. Yeah, the umami's good.
Well, great. Wow. I see Mr. Seo knows how
to enjoy food properly.
I learned this is the only way to eat it.
That's right. Well, you need the
lettuce to cut through the fat.
Well, you young people have such big
appetites.
-Mechoori.
-Oh, slow down, slow down, okay?
Thank you for cooking.
You're welcome. Uh, oh, uh-- You should
really slow down. Make sure to chew.
Uh, why were you stuffing your
face so much? I thought it was too salty
-for you.
-The umami.
Man, it was amazing.
Does your father often come by and
bring you food he's made?
Not just often. Always.
I bet it takes a lot of effort to
prepare that food, but you didn't
eat any.
Yeah, I know. He means well, I guess.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
Hyun-ki. May I ask you something?
It has to do with Dam Ye-jin. Did she
not know about the Good Morning Cream?
Dam Ye-jin was-- She was brought onto the
project barely a week before Good
Morning Cream.
What?
I think I know why. She wanted
to take this opportunity. Even though
she knew was green.
Myeong-hwa, I remember the time you left
college all of a sudden. No one
could find you anywhere for a whole year.
There were rumors. Rumors at school that
Song Myeong-hwa had disappeared.
But then, I suddenly remembered him.
That man I had introduced you to, Dam
Seok-gyeong.
I went to the theater where we saw
that play together, got his address,
and went to his house to see if he
was there. He was.
I couldn't believe my eyes when I
saw you and your child.
When I first saw Dam Ye-jin, it was clear
as day that she was your daughter.
It was like I was looking at you
thirty years ago.
Myeong-hwa, Ye-jin had more drive
than anyone else there.
It was because her mother was right there
alongside her.
You really tried all these?
Of course. This room here is a
lot like your mushroom farm. Sloppiness?
Silly mistakes? Not on my watch. I'm not
someone who has to use acupressure
points in order to sweat.
I'm sorry for how long I've ignored
how hard of a worker you are, but you
really are.
Hey, it's okay. I also used to judge
everyone at first sight.
I'm sure it was exhausting.
Since we're here in this room, I might
as well be honest. Thing is,
this confident person you see before
you wasn't always there. I grew
into this person to prove myself to my
mother.
SONG MYEONG-HWA WINS THREE AWARDS
WITH BLUE PARADISE AND STAR OF THE YEAR
Every Sunday, at eight p.m., I would
call this number here, right on the
dot. I was able to just to be a
normal girl talking to her mother and
not to a star.
I'll remember that number till the day
I die.
So I'm guessing that your mom gave it up
five years ago?
No, earlier than that. I can't
imagine how the number got assigned
to you. Such a weird coincidence.
Dam Ye-jin. The first time I
answered your call, do you know why I
stayed on the phone with you?
There was something in your voice.
I'm not sure if I should say this…
But it was clear that you missed
your mother. It sounded like you
missed her a lot.
-I think you should--
-That was just my meds talking.
I wasn't being myself.
Because I don't even hate Song Myeong-hwa
any longer.
It actually looks better on, don't
you think? I think it fits well.
Right here. Yeah.
Ye-jin had more drive than anybody
else there. It was because her
mother was right there alongside her.
Ye-jin… Would never do that.
Think it over again, Myeong-hwa.
Hmm, make sure that the pockets don't
-bulge out though. You see that right
-Oh, okay.
-Here?
-Yes.
-How's that?
-Good. It's great. We can wrap it up.
Okay.
RAW MATERIAL SUPPLY CONTRACT
CONTRACTOR: GOJEUNEOK BIO
CO-CEOS: LEE HAE-SEOK AND KANG MU-WON
-I'm glad to be working with you.
-Yes, we're looking forward to it as well.
Mu-won, you look very sharp today.
Shall we take a photo?
Let's do it.
-Yeah.
-This wall should be good.
GOJEUNEOK BIO
Yeah, it's great. I like that. Hae-seok.
No, thank you. You two go ahead.
-No point, then.
-Just forget it.
Yeah.
Just the same as you always are.
Oh, thank you.
-Alright, good to go.
-Mu-won.
Hae-seok should be in the center.
Come on.
Hurt my feelings, why don't ya?
Can you just move over there? That's it.
There-- There we go. Here. That's it.
Better. Huddle in. Big smiles, everyone.
Okay.
Okay, everyone ready? One, two, three.
Wow. I came this close to crying. I was
going over the H.O. documents. You must
have had to do everything from scratch
while in Thailand. You should be proud.
Oh, I had the exact same thought
whenever I heard about Gojeuneok.
You two are sticking together and
are clearly doing great.
Yeah.
Great job. Really. Great job.
What's the matter with Hae-seok? He's so
quiet? This guy used to talk all
day long.
Believe it or not, this is an improvement
over how he used to be. A massive
improvement.
Oh, wait. I got it. He doesn't like being
in the spotlight. I can read him like a
book. C'mon, bottoms up, let's celebrate.
-This is a good day. Here we go. Cheers.
-Yes, cheers. Here.
Wow. Seriously. Just sitting here, wow,
reminds you of the old days, doesn't it?
How back in the day, the four of us…
Wow, I must be drunk.
But you know, gotta give credit to
Woo-su.
For?
Bringing Hae-seok on the team. You
remember? He was practically
freaking out that a genius was
joining the company.
How could I forget?
Hey. Where's Hae-seok going?
He's top of the department. Of course
he's gonna have his pick of any company.
Yeah, true.
I'm so jealous.
OPEN RECRUITMENT
DEVELOPING FOOD-GRADE COSMETICS
MADE FROM 100% FOOD-GRADE INGREDIENTS
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry, um, welcome. Please,
come in.
This says it's food grade, does that mean
you can eat it? How do cosmetics not
have at least some chemicals? Silicone,
parabens, or…
Uh, did you just…
I made all of these myself. So I
should be able to trust them. Would you
like to try one?
APPLICATION FOR EMPLOYMENT
SUBMISSION BOX
Word was…
All the top pharmaceutical companies
were trying to snatch you up.
His hands were shaking when he made
you an offer, so when you accepted, he
was so grateful. He'd always tell that
story every time we'd have a drink.
Woo-su.
What a guy, that Choi Woo-su.
You're here.
Just need a minute.
Just hold me like this for a minute.
What's wrong? Was someone mean to you
today? Just tell me who it was and I'll
beat them up.
Uh, okay. Uh, Mechoori, how much did you
drink?
Not much.
Okay, careful. Uh, careful.
You rest here. I'm gonna go get you
something to drink.
Hey, how much longer are you gonna
call me Mechoori?
What name would you like?
You know. That one.
Which one?
Uh, come on, you know.
I have no idea what you're saying.
Matthew. Matthew.
Okay, but why do you want me to
call you that when your real name's
so nice? Is Matthew the name you
used abroad?
Som-yi would call me that.
Mister. You're really here. Why you
hiding over here? Are you playing hide
and seek?
I found you. Mister, aren't you cold?
Here, drink this.
People say you're weird. Because you
don't talk. But, I don't mind.
MATTHEW AND HIS FRIENDS
MY FRIEND IS SICK
Wanna look at this?
This is my favorite book.
There's nothing written in it. But you
don't need words to know what
they're saying.
Mister, can you talk at all? If I tell
you my secret first, will you tell me
yours? I promise to keep your secret.
I don't have any friends to tell anyway.
Cause I look like this.
Do you really not have any secrets?
That's boring. Can you tell me what they
call you? Do you even know your name?
If not, I could give you one.
Matthew. Oh, that's it. My Uncle Matthew.
If it wasn't for Som-yi, I don't
know what would've become of me.
Because of her…
I finally felt comforted. That little
child saw me.
Som-yi has a lot of affection for
you. You know that.
I really owe my life to Som-yi. Yes.
She saved me.
Past the intersection, second block,
under the red sign.
Ugh, every sign around me is red.
Oh!
-Is he a flasher?
-Oh, my!
Maybe.
-It's always the handsome ones. They're
-Good-looking boys.
-Always doing something shady.
-Ridiculous.
I've obtained some information.
What is it?
Gojeuneok Bio has rejected the vice
president's offer and signed a
contract with a company called H.O
Cosmetics.
My sister must be absolutely furious.
Oh, I'm sure she is. She's not
someone who'd sit back with
something like this. I was bracing myself
for her to grind me down, but…
Okay, and?
And your sister did nothing.
But she's definitely pulling some
strings. She's been doing strange
things, keeping me out of the loop,
going off on her own, probably more.
What? Has my beauty left you speechless?
Is that it?
You are pretty.
What do you need?
I was wondering, are you working
tomorrow?
No, not tomorrow. Why?
How do you feel about a staycation?
What? You're having a staycation with
Mechoori?
Thanks for the announcement.
Sorry, I can't help it. I'm so excited.
That's huge.
It's no big deal, it's nothing.
We're just staying at a hotel.
You packed? Are you all set?
What? All set for what?
Well, technically, it's a staycation,
but think of it as boot camp. Swimsuit,
evening outfit, gym outfit, and a hotel
lounge outfit. Bring all of them. Or you
might regret it. This is war,
don't forget that. And stop eating.
Ah, come on. You're being ridiculous.
Am I? Then why are you blushing, huh?
What?
-What's on your mind?
-Nothing.
TWC.
What a workout, my blood sugar's
crashing.
Wow. Has protein with very little flour.
I'm obsessed with them. Just like
Mr. Lee. So delicious. Want one?
They have a ton of flavors.
Ta-da! Ta-da! I like the cheese one.
You got so many.
Try one.
So? Why are you so busy?
I won't be here tomorrow.
Oh, that's right. You're taking
tomorrow off. Is there a lot to do
-at the farm? Should I join?
-No. That's okay.
Sung-mi, seriously. I'm fine, I don't
need to prepare. This isn't my first
staycation.
Okay. I guess it is our first date, so,
it's just good manners.
Something's missing.
Sorry, are you Dam Ye-jin? Oh, I'm a fan.
You're so gorgeous.
Oh, thank you so much.
Are you looking for a gift? Or
something for yourself?
It's for me. I need something that'll
make a guy's heart race, and I can't
look too excited, or that I'm
desperate, or that I gotta have a
spotlight on me. Also, it has to be cute.
Do you have something like that?
What about this one here?
I'll take it.
Okay.
Why'd you pack so much stuff?
Women always overpack.
Are you feeling okay?
I should go.
The necklace looks great on you.
Just to be clear. I didn't get it for
this occasion, okay? I just
think fashion is all about accessories.
So I got it in order to complete
today's outfit.
Hello, welcome.
-It's really nice.
-Isn't it?
-What is your name, please?
-It's Mechoo--
Lee Hae-seok.
One moment, please.
Ah, yes, there you are. You're in 507.
Tap your key card once you're in the
elevator, and press the fifth floor.
Oh, and here's 508.
Thanks.
Here's 509.
-Great.
-And here's 510.
Okay, thank you so much.
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
What made you book so many rooms?
Hey! Can we get an early check-in?
I need an early check-in! Check-in, hey!
Ah, Dam Ye-jin.
-Mechoori!
-Oh, hello.
Mechoori!
-It's everyone.
-This is so great, I'm so excited!
We're here!
What exactly is going on right now?
I thought this was a staycation.
Yeah.
I'm bringing the village too.
Didn't I tell you? It's for all the
villagers.
-Got it. I see. Hi, everyone, how are you?
-Hey.
It's so nice to see you here.
I've already checked us all in. Let's go,
okay.
-You mean we're going to the room already,
-No way. There's so much to see.
We can't do that.
Mechoori? We came all this way.
We have to do some sightseeing first.
Well you can find everything you could
ever want in here.
Sweetie, I meant to ask you, is your
office very far from here?
Would you mind showing us around
the area?
-Oh, yes, please. We'd love to.
-I love HIT! Can my sister and I come too?
Please?
-Uh. Som yi.
-Yes, right now, let's go.
-A great idea! Let's all go.
-Everybody?
My wife even put on her finest dress for
this occasion.
Dam Ye-jin doesn't have a show today.
Can't do it, I'm afraid.
What are you saying?
We can't? Really?
No, come on, we came all this way to
see that.
Oh, that's no fun.
We want to see the broadcasting station.
I was so excited.
Oh. that's so unfair.
Hi, Mr. Hwang. I was wondering if
Goblin could be run today?
Okay. I'll take that one.
DAM YE-JIN: HIT HOMESHOPPING
EXCLUSIVE HOME SHOPPING HOST
Wow, there it is!
Is that Dam Ye-jin?
-Woah!
-She looks totally different!
Oh my goodness, look at her! Wow!
Looks like me.
Of course. Dam Ye-jin is prettier
than you!
She's an absolute angel! There's no
way she's human. She must be an angel
-who fell from the sky!
-Oh, so beautiful.
-Wow. Oh!
-It's beautiful.
Jin-yi. Come with me.
Oh, my, my.
This is it! This is the thing I showed
you the other day.
2025 HIT HOMESHOPPING OPEN RECRUITMENT
FOR ROOKIE HOME SHOPPING HOSTS
Come on, let's head in.
-Look at that! Let's go! Come on! Oh, I
-Let's go! Hurry, everyone!
Can't wait!
-Let's go.
-Did you apply already?
Why in the world would I apply?
Oh, I'm so sorry. Thank you.
Oh. You're from Deokpung.
-Ah, yeah. Right.
-Aren't you?
Oh, thank you.
Are you applying for this?
-Ah, no.
-Ah, you should.
Uh, hope to see you later. Oh, my
name is-- Is Ki-hong. So…
Yeah, my name is Ki-hong. Remember that.
-What do you think? Yeah? Thanks.
-I like it. It's pretty.
-She really looks great.
-Ms. Dam.
Huh?
What?
Sorry, I know this is last minute. But I
could only find one model on such short
notice. I think it might look weird
with just one.
Today, I'm introducing the Steady
Collection by Solen, a renowned
designer for menswear.
This collection is completely
wrinkle-resistant, so it always
looks tidy.
He looks great.
Made with 3D printed fabric that
allows airflow so even those who tend to
run hot will be able to stay cool.
Oh, it's washable too, so it can
be tossed right into the washing
machine. On top of it all, it even
blocks UV rays. This jacket is one of a
kind.
Thanks to our customers' overwhelming
response, the brown jacket you're
MY HUSBAND WOULD LOOK JUST LIKE HIM
I SHOULD BUY IT
-Are you worried about the fit because you
-Wow, I didn't think we'd get anything
-have a larger build? The great
-out of him. Would you look at that.
Thing about the Solen jacket is
this piece doesn't taper at the waist,
like other jackets. That way…
Even if you were to fasten it, like this,
the fit stays perfect with tons of
room left for all sizes.
What's going on with that guy?
Come on. That's enough, guys.
He looks so cool, doesn't he?
Sort of.
I gotta get one of those. Hey, help
me with this. Okay?
-I'll use mine.
-Okay.
So cute.
Run those two stills back to back and cut
together the pared-down versions of
scenes three and five.
Three and five. Got it.
Great. He's so cute.
Mr. Park!
Sung-mi! Hi!
This is for you. You looked so handsome
in it earlier.
Oh, what did I do to deserve this? Uh,
actually, I got one already. I bought it
today.
But, uh, all these items you keep buying
and showing me, are you buying them
'cause you need them?
No, I bought them because I wanted to
increase your sales.
I didn't ask you to buy anything,
this must have cost a fortune. I mean,
why blow all that money on this?
Oh. I-- I-- I just…
I wanted to find some reason that
would let me message you. And besides,
these items, they didn't cost a lot.
I buy things so I can see a smile
on your beautiful face.
Well then, you must've bought the hotel
staycation too.
Absolutely.
Would you like for us to go together?
Going somewhere?
Just making a delivery.
I'd love to assist you.
Hey.
Dressed up like that?
Is that a problem for you?
Just don't get on my nerves.
Should be nearly there, right?
-Here we are.
-That wasn't so bad.
Oh, coffee's fine. It's fine.
Can you please be careful.
I'm sorry.
Grandmother, it's me! I have coffee, come
outside.
Ae-ra, you're here.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
You grandfather had a bit of an
accident on the bedding. I want to
clean him up, but I can't move him.
I'll help you.
Let me do it.
Good morning, sir. You must be so
uncomfortable. Don't worry. Let's get
you to the bathroom. Okay. Ma'am, may
I use this cloth next to the blanket
here?
Yes, of course. Go ahead.
Great, thank you.
So, which way should I go?
-Right that way.
-Ah, perfect.
But you have such nice clothes.
They'll be ruined.
It's okay, I'm fine.
Please don't forget to take your blood
pressure pills. I'll be back at ten,
okay? For physical therapy.
I hope she doesn't forget to take her
medicine.
I should buy them new clothes. No. I'll
buy them a whole brand new outfit.
Ae-ra, could you tell me what styles
they prefer?
Just get whatever.
My name is Mu-won. And Mr. Mu-won
doesn't do whatever.
Your watch is gone. Did something happen?
I threw it away.
What? You threw away a watch that
expensive?
I didn't think you liked it, Ae-ra.
Oh.
But it looks like you are very
interested in my watch.
I don't know the first thing about
watches, but I once knew a guy with
that watch who really made my skin crawl.
Why are you following me? This is your
staycation. So go take care of the
villagers.
Are you angry?
Uh, no. No, I'm so grateful that you
used my staycation package for
such a nice purpose.
Uh, there appears to have been a
misunderstanding.
Our staycation has only just begun.
-What?
-It starts right now.
Wait.
GALLERY FESTA
Right.
-Pretty good, huh?
-It is.
Good, I'm glad.
Oh, you're choking.
Mechoori. Read this passage. This one.
Do you feel better?
-What do you mean?
-You know you were pouting earlier.
I wasn't pouting.
Your lips were pursed like this.
Hey, stop it.
I think I'll go home to Deokpung
tomorrow. I'll bring back the villagers.
You're all leaving? But Mr. Park can
drive there.
I want to take them, I'll do it.
How come you always try to do
everything on your own? Is that why
you slouch? Cause you're carrying so
much?
It's a genuine question. I really
mean it. You should relax. And live
in the moment a little bit, just for
yourself.
Have you been thinking about developing
cosmetics again?
Remember that photo I saw?
It was the first time I had ever seen
you smile like that.
And if I can get you to look like
that again, I promise to do what it
takes. Just like you did for me. Just
think about it.
Hmm? What? You're not saying no.
Usually you have no problem saying no.
Okay. That's it for today.
Whenever you have any worries or
fears, I'll carry them for you instead.
Might not seem like it, but these
shoulders are pretty strong.
Thank you.
Did you buy it?
Michelle! This is bad! Your car…
-Wait, what?
-Your car…
What should I do? You have to go now!
You have to go right now at this minute!
-It's cold out.
-Right now! We have to go now! Hurry!
Oh, my God. Move!
Hurry, hurry! This is bad. This is
really bad. What do we do? Mama mia!
What's going on?
I drove as carefully as I could,
under the speed limit. Even so,
the second that the car was parked,
I saw this!
I was determined to get you a
sandwich that had arugula. Arugula that
had been picked from the garden!
So this sandwich is the reason you ran in
shrieking? The big emergency is
-a sandwich?
-Yeah.
It's awful, because your food is the
company's fuel. The fuel that drives
L'Etoile. Your food is its power source!
-Listen to me.
-Yes.
Are you crazy?
What is wrong with you?
I have a reservation at a restaurant
nearby. Let's go there instead.
Have you lost your mind?!
Uh, in that case, I'll make you a new
-sandwich myself.
-You idiot! Idiot!
Just a minute!
I can't believe it!
I promise you, if you waste my
time again, I will throw you out myself.
Yes. I'm sorry.
Get me a coffee. Very, very hot.
Yes, ma'am.
Ah.
Cool foam only, got it?
Oh, yes. A very hot coffee with
cold foam. Uh, how do I do that?
I'll get it, never mind!
DEOKPUNG COMMUNITY CENTER
-Thank you for driving!
-That trip took a lot out of me.
Yes, thank you.
Oh, Mechoori.
Thanks to you, I got to have an
experience I'll never forget as long as
I live.
Those two, though? Do something
about them. Good luck.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Ah, thank you.
-Let's go.
-No. I don't want to live with you.
Na Som-yi.
I'm gonna live in Mechoori's house now.
Come on, now.
Okay, fine. I don't care.
Did you fight with Jin-yi again? What
happened, Som-yi?
I can't live with her anymore.
I'm so sad, Mechoori. I wasn't
allowed to eat at the buffet, I
couldn't have anything. I went all
the way to Seoul. I asked for
a small bite, but she just said no over
and over.
SOM'S VARIETY SHOP
Hey, Jin-yi. Uh, she fell asleep.
So, I'll put her in her bed.
The last rent payment.
Last payment, really?
Som-yi and I are moving to Seoul.
Isn't that a bit hasty?
It's not.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
Her doctor recommended a larger
hospital for Som-yi. It's in Seoul.
It's too far to go back and forth.
I can take her there myself, Jin-yi.
You're doing it again.
Som-yi loves being here, you know that.
She's class president, she's made
so many friends.
That's why it's important we go right
now. So her memories of this place
are only good. I've thought it over, and
this is the right thing to do.
Leaving before she finds out everything.
Then I should be the one to leave here.
You should stay put. I'll explain
everything to her.
What will you tell her? That the
cream you developed is the reason
her face is like that?
Som-yi has to learn the truth, Jin-yi.
-No, she doesn't have to.
-Jin-yi.
We'll talk later.
Hello.
Help me, please! Som-yi-- Som-yi's
missing.
What?
I went to work, she was still asleep, but
when I got home, she wasn't there.
What do I do? Her phone is off. She
must have heard us talking about
everything, what do I do?
Stay there.
Attention please, this is a Deokpung
One-ri announcement. Our Som-yi
has still not come home yet, and her cell
phone is off too. If anyone has
seen her or knows her whereabouts,
we please ask that you immediately
contact the shop.
-Som-yi!
-You found her?
Not yet. She's not here. Let's look
over there.
-Yes, okay, okay. Som-yi!
-Som-yi!
-Som-yi! Som-yi, where are you?
-Na Som!
-Na Som-yi!
Go that way!
Okay. Na Som-yi!
Som-yi!
Som-yi.
Mechoori.
What's wrong?
Mechoori. I know everything now.
Som-yi.
Forgive me.
I'm so-- I'm just so sorry.
I already knew. Because you would
apologize every day. You'd always
bring me presents from Seoul. You cooked
for me. You always cut my fruit.
You came to my sports matches.
Mechoori, are you really leaving? I heard
you tell Jin-yi that you were leaving us.
Are you leaving me like my mother and
father did?
It's not like that, Som-yi.
I'll be here till you go to college.
Until you find out what you want to do
in life…
And you've been cured for good. I won't
leave you.
Okay. You have to stay here.
Yeah. I will.
Please swear.
Yeah, I swear.
Sweetie, Mechoori will find her,
I'm sure. I just know he will. Som-yi is
fine.
It's all my fault. Why did I bring her
here? What was I thinking?
It'll be okay, sweetie.
Don't beat yourself up over this,
it's not your fault. Don't cry.
Jin-yi.
I'm so sorry.
No, I'm sorry. Oh, I'm so sorry.
Jin-yi, can't we just keep on living
here? I would-- I'd like to keep
living here, please.
Yes, of course. Let's do that.
You did it.
Oh, Mr. Cha!
Uh, what have you heard about the
Asian market entrance plan?
The Asian market?
Oh, please, what are you talking about
now? We can't get the raw materials--
How would we? How?
Exactly. What is my sister thinking?
What's her goal?
One we start developing, this'll look
very different. With more equipment.
Develop what? What're you saying?
That I'm trying again. Making cosmetics.
Mechoori.
I made a promise to Som-yi. I'm going
to make it. I'll make the perfect
cream for her.
I'm gonna try to give it my all.
Ms. Michelle, thank you so much
for coming.
I was curious. You told me, "I'll help
get rid of that thorn in your side"
What did you mean?
Gojeuneok Bio. I'll put a bow on
it for you. It'll be all yours.
SOLD OUT ON YOU
THANK YOU TO MR. SEO HYUN-WOO
FOR HIS SPECIAL APPEARANCE
That day, why didn't you show up?
-Go to bed.
-I'll sleep out here.
Gojeuneok Bio's first cosmetic
product will be a regenerative cream.
This is the cream I made. What do
you think it should be called?
Noori Cream.
I've brought something for Dam Ye-jin's
Only One.
Noori Cream is the hottest new
product among retailers everywhere.
You like it that much?
Lee Hae-seok. I'll make sure he
never sets foot in this industry again.
THIS VILLAGE GREW MURDEROUS MUSHROOMS
GIVE US VICTIMS OUR SKIN BACK