SOLD OUT ON YOU
When I told you I'd bring Gojeuneok's raw
materials to L'Etoile, that was
a temporary fix. I thought you understood
that.
So, what're you planning to do then?
A new product is being developed by
Gojeuneouk Bio.
They're producing cosmetics now?
Yes.
What? You think this is funny, huh?
About five years ago, there was a
huge scandal. It shook the entire
country.
It was known as the Good Morning Cream
scandal.
Lee Hae-seok was actually Good Morning
Cream's developer and creator.
It's a mistake if it only occurs once,
but a second time, that's not a mistake.
That's on purpose. This time…
I'll wanna make sure he's never seen in
this industry again.
I'm home. Mechoori.
Oh, you're back.
What's all this?
I have homework to do. Regulations
have changed a bunch, and with new
manufacturing methods, I gotta read up
on a lot.
Aren't you sleepy though? You worked
all day.
I'm not.
I have something to do as well.
Hey, focus.
You look pretty, even at home.
Ah, it's already so late. Aren't you
gonna sleep?
Uh, after I'm done with this.
Hmm, you would tell me to go to sleep.
I'll go easy on you. Just finish
that up and go to bed.
I will. Night-night.
Night-night.
You said you were gonna wrap things up
for the night.
Um, you can't fall asleep?
No, I can't.
I stopped taking the sleeping pills
actually.
You went off your medication? Why'd you
do that?
Just 'cause. Seeing you face your past
helped me look inward too. I want to
do what you did.
I thought my own past was holding me back
in life. But I'm what's holding
myself back. I'll overcome insomnia and
cut the meds too. Just watch me.
That's good and all but, you should
take your meds. And tomorrow, talk to
your doctor. It's better to go easy,
-given that you're--
-No.
Especially not after I lost so much
sleep over it.
Let's head to bed then.
I told you, I can't fall asleep.
You don't have to light the candle for
me tonight. Hurry up and go to bed, you
must be tired.
I'm gonna sleep here.
Okay. Are you relaxed?
Yes.
Okay.
You get it? Slowly relax your face,
then your shoulders, your arms,
and your legs.
Imagine you're floating like a jellyfish
in the ocean.
Uh, jellyfish, do you mean-- What am I
supposed to do?
A sports therapist developed this.
It promotes sleep. With this
technique, you can fall asleep in
two minutes, if implemented correctly.
That sounds like fake news. I'm so wired.
Focus.
Swim like a jellyfish. Think like
a jellyfish.
Alright, I'm a jellyfish now.
Close your eyes. And imagine what I'm
saying. Right now, you're lying
in a canoe, floating on a calm lake
on a warm spring day. You look up at the
blue sky.
Yes.
I'm feeling very tired.
That's it. Good.
Check out the shoulders on that
bodybuilder over there. Do you come here
often? Hey, where are you from?
Stop!
What's wrong? I'm imagining like
you said.
Don't think, you hear me? Let go. Allow
yourself to just be. And let go.
Things were just about to get
interesting. I'm swimming back
over to the lake now.
The lake's dried up, so you can't go
there now.
Imagine pitch black darkness. You're
softly swinging on a black hammock.
Is it just the two of us?
Stop playing around.
Well, I'm just curious. I mean, how
exactly would we lie next to each other
on a hammock? Hmm?
Didn't I warn you?
Don't think. Just focus.
You should rest. You're leaving early
tomorrow, right?
I'll stop thinking.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
What's happening? A coffee addict like
you is turning down coffee?
I'm quitting coffee.
I'm determined and I know I can do it.
Is it good?
Hey, guys. Can we move to the shade?
It's so hot over here.
I mean, doctors recommend you
have fifteen minutes of sunlight a day.
What is this, some sort of infomercial?
Thanks for the pro tip.
I'll soon have my own show again.
I need my body to be ready.
Dam Ye-jin's Only One show? So we're
going back to the weekend prime time
slot?
You two better start sleeping and
eating well. Know what that means?
Hello? Sung-mi? Am I making sense?
-Yeah! We really did it! We did it!
-Ah, you're hurting me!
We did it!
Ah! You have a product for it, right?
No, not yet, but I will. You'll love it.
Wow, that's gonna take forever. Let's go!
Let's go!
WHITE FLOWER
NOORI MUSHROOM EXTRACT
So this is the raw material
extracted from white flower
noori mushroom using a new method, right?
This formula heals body wounds much
faster.
You see this going up, right? Using this
as a core ingredient boosted recovery
rates by well over fifty times. We could
make a brand new cream that does that.
Listen to me. If you need anything,
anything at all, request it okay!
Anything at all! Request it!
Oh, you guys are working super hard.
There you are.
Remember that cafe we used to love eating
at? It's still in business.
Oh, it's so nice that it's still around.
Anyway, perfect timing! We're just
about to celebrate.
Why? Special occasion?
Get this. Gojeuneok Bio's first cosmetic
product will be a regenerative cream.
Oh.
Mr. Lee here developed a new raw
material using the white flower noori
mushroom. How should I put this?
He killed it.
I just love him so much, I could kiss him
right now. Was that to much? Okay.
Anyway, PTBA.
Prepare to be amazed.
Yeah, wow! Well, congrats, but you guys
should think this through. Your raw
materials already outrageously
expensive, and with processing
costs on top of that, the price per unit
will go up a whole lot. Then it won't
be competitive in the market.
Respectfully, I don't agree. Money's not
the only reason I'm here.
How cute, Mu-won. Kid, you got no clue,
huh? A business makes profit its top
priority.
Ah, there I go again interfering.
I'm sure you both can handle
this without me. Let's sit and eat.
Sit, sit.
Mechoori!
Good evening.
Is this a special occasion? Such a fancy
place and you're all dressed up.
Have a seat.
Oh, my God.
Is this what I think it is?
I have a proposition for you, Ms. Dam
Ye-jin.
Hold on. Oh, you should've given me
some sort of hint. If I knew this was
gonna happen, I would've dressed up
in something fancy, but I kept
thinking "no way." Are you serious?
I want to formally purpose a partnership,
Ms. Dam Ye-jin.
A partnership?
HIT HOMESHOPPING PROPOSAL FOR PARTNERSHIP
GOJEUNEOK BIO REGENERATIVE CREAM
I wouldn't have been able to develop this
cream without you.
I'm proposing we work together
to complete this.
Never stop doubting me, questioning me.
I'm certain your help will give me
reassurance I need.
-Let's make sure to get there early
-Did you print the materials I sent you
-because of the traffic tomorrow.
-yesterday?
This way, please.
What are you looking for?
Just something I need to check.
Ah, but that's a lot. You're not
gonna check all of it, right?
I don't really have a choice. You know?
Mr. Lee, allow this humble servant
to help you a little.
Okay, say what you're looking for.
I want to see outcomes from the study
by Seohan University on major medicinal
mushrooms and their antibacterial
effects.
The paper you mentioned is, "Research
trends of ingredients proven
effective and safe for sensitive skin".
According to antibacterial tests on
five types of skin disease-causing
microorganisms, the MIC was found to be
nineteen point seven two micrograms per
milliliter.
Okay. Honestly, I really liked
the seventh sample too. I think
we're almost near finalizing.
-We can't be sure of that yet.
Copy that. Let's keep up the energy and
continue.
Let's keep going!
Let's go.
I adore it, but…
It scares me when she says that.
White flower noori mushroom has a unique
fragrance, which might be of concern.
When a product has a strong scent,
reactions tend to split. And that
impacts our sales directly.
So mix in artificial ingredients to
dilute the product and make more money.
I'm talking about the product's
marketability
Fight.
Isn't our ultimate goal to have maximum
outreach so more people can use the
cream and benefit from it?
Reactions to scent are subjective,
aren't they? Nobody's the same.
Still.
Will people actually smell this and say
that it smells good?
Without additives, we can show
the natural approach to our cream.
I have a better idea. It would be
more wise to go with a timeless scent
like citrus, marine, or sandalwood.
Let's discuss what the best way--
Ms. Dam Ye-jin, you better…
As Gojeuneok's cream developer, I know
what's best better than anybody.
Lee Hae-seok, sir. Listen. Let's add
another reason for customers to
pick this product. Why do luxury cosmetic
companies incorporate fragrances?
Because smell elicits emotion and brings
comfortability.
Once they feel the cream's benefits,
even the scent you strongly dislike,
will become pleasant.
Lee Hae-seok, sir. Aren't we meeting to
provide feedback today? You're not
open to hearing any opinions at all.
Ms. Dam Ye-jin. I'm open to your input if
it improves the product.
So you're saying my input is helpful?
I'm not so sure.
Let's break for a few minutes.
Let's reconvene in fifteen.
The cream is still gonna launch, right?
Something might explode before that ever
happens.
What about our show though?
Seriously!
Oh, there he is.
Oh, he's all alone. They must still be
fighting! Where's Dam Ye-jin?
Wait, I don't think he's alone.
What?
Come on. Can't you loosen up a bit?
You're so rigid.
-Okay, I'll try.
-This is a warning.
So we were the only ones taking this
seriously. Let's go.
-Honey potato!
-Cherry tomato!
Cherry tomato is on a quick break.
-Oh, really.
-Did you eat?
I have.
-What did you have?
-I had janchiguksu.
Oh, that sounds so yummy! Now I
want some!
Hmm, viscosity hasn't changed. Yeah,
still got a funky scent though.
Mr. Lee. The results of the pilot
test also matched the sample.
PILOT TEST
SAFETY EVALUATION REPORT
Thank you so much.
We appreciate your work.
Well done. So is the cream's name
chosen yet? We should pick one so
we can start on production.
I'll ask this naming expert I know.
You sure you cleaned it up?
Yes, I already cleaned it.
-You're saying this is all organized?
-Oh, stop. I told you, I did.
I don't think so. It looks the same as
yesterday.
-I did clean. Go away.
-Som-yi.
Mechoori! Hi!
You're back from school?
SOM'S VARIETY SHOP
Som-yi. Here.
What is this?
It's the cream I made for you.
Wow, really? What did you make it with?
White flower noori mushroom and some
other things. Som, what should we
name this cream of yours? I want
you to be the one to pick the name.
Name.
Noori Cream.
Noori Cream?
Hey, Noori Cream? That's so tacky.
I learned at school recently that
noori means the entire world. So it
carries the idea that the entire
planet will use this cream. Isn't
that cool?
Noori Cream. Beautiful.
Did you hear that? Mechoori, could I try
putting this on?
Then, why don't we both use it.
No way. It's all mine. I have to
wash my face and put it on!
Noori Cream's gonna be the next
big thing. You even got her to
go wash her face.
Jin-yi.
She requested I give you this.
Who did?
The deadline for HIT's open recruitment
is midnight.
I hope you get a chance to spread
your wings.
How long are you gonna keep that up?
I've been waiting forever for
this moment. I have to make this special.
What was that?
Stay still.
Here.
-Are we there yet? Can I open my eyes?
-Just a bit more.
How about now?
Turn around here.
Hurry and say three, two, one!
Three, two…
Where's…
It's you. I've been dying to see you.
You look amazing.
-Do you like it that much?
-I do.
You're crying? You're actually
crying over this?
Of course. I know what you had to do
to make your cream a reality.
Great job. I knew you could do it.
I'm lucky to have your encouragement.
That's what I needed most.
Come in.
Director.
Hi, there.
You've waited for so long. Here's the
first item for Dam Ye-jin's Only One.
Gojeuneok Bio?
The material supplier for La Fin Essence,
right?
Right. It's their first cosmetic
product and you know how picky they are.
You're sure about this?
I'm sure of it.
Thanks for all your hard work.
I'm honored.
Okay.
All of you who worked tirelessly to
make Noori Cream…
Do you know what your minds have in
common with my credit card here?
We don't!
-What is it?
-I wanna know!
-They're limitless.
-Oh, that was a good one.
Today, eat as much as you want. Make sure
to drink up, okay? Noori Cream! Drink up!
What are you doing? That's alcohol!
I can drink alcohol again. Thanks to
someone.
I'll help myself.
Mechoori, this one's really delicious.
Try it.
You should eat some then.
You have some first, come on.
I'll eat if you do first.
Ah, seriously. Then…
-I'm going.
-Really?
-You try it first.
-Well, I guess I picked the wrong seat.
Hello. How's it going? I didn't
feel like it.
It's good, right? I have something
better for you.
Potatoes.
I miss my Potato.
Sir, can I please have another beer here?
Young miss, I think you've had enough.
Time to go home.
Hi, cherry tomato. You look pretty.
Sweet potato, what're you doing in Seoul?
Mmm, you said you missed me.
Yeah, but you, came all the way here just
because of that? You know, I think you'd
actually drop dead if I asked you to.
So cute. Park Kwang-mo's so cute.
So cute. So, so cute. You're so cute.
Cute, huh? You know there's a lot more to
me than just my cuteness.
G-- Uh, got it?
So cute!
-Oh?
-Huh?
Mr. Seo.
If seems to rain often. At least whenever
we're together.
I know, right? You know they say I'm
a good luck charm when it comes to the
weather. Maybe you're the one
bringing all the rain, Mr. Seo.
Why didn't you show up that day?
You know, since it's raining and
all, I feel like it's a good time to
talk about that.
If you believe in fate, why don't we
just meet tomorrow? Right here?
I wanted to be there. It had been
so long, since anyone looked at me
with such a sparkle in their eyes.
If I want to be there by twelve, maybe I
should get up at ten? Uh, no,
I'll wake up earlier to be safe.
ALARMS
I wanted to get a good night's sleep and
meet you there fresh-faced.
But when I woke up, it was already
evening.
The dosage of my new medication
was just to strong.
I see.
It's all in the past, I know, but I don't
want you to think it didn't matter.
I really had a wonderful time. And when I
struggled, I thought about the
memory that we shared that day.
Thank you for, uh, remembering them so
kindly. I think that's how I'll remember
the time I spent with you too. Thanks to
your honesty, and getting to see how
hard of a worker you are, I know
which way I have to go.
I'd like to thank you. Working together
introduced me to a person even more
interesting than the person I met under
that umbrella.
Really?
Do you know the word impromptu?
It means doing something without any
planning or any sort of hesitation.
That's beautiful.
Yeah, it is, but it's actually tough
to do. And with that, do you want to do
an impromptu walk? Let's go this way.
Come on, stranger.
GOJEUNEOK BIO
NOORI
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
Have a nice day.
-We're hosting a lucky draw event with
-Have a sample. This will change your
-life, ma'am.
-various prizes including Noori Cream
Have a sample.
And discount codes you can use during the
show launch.
This is why people say, "It has to be Dam
Ye-jin."
Noori Cream's so hot right now.
They're all going crazy for it. Everyone
only shares good feedback and praise.
They say you've got an amazing knack for
-finding hidden gems like…
-Hold up, now.
You should share such valuable info
in a lot more detail, please.
Oh, 'kay. Well the pre-launch event for
Noori Cream, almost five hundred people
applied to participate even though
there's only thirty spots. Man, I was
sweating bullets trying to pick
the winners.
So when do we get the reviews?
Oh! In two weeks. I'll compile them and
share them with you both as soon as
they're released.
Okay.
We need to use the reviews as inserts, so
make sure to get photos for all of it.
Yes, sir!
Here are your salted butter rolls
from France, ma'am. And I see you're
already drinking your coffee.
It looks like you are very photogenic,
my friend.
What?
Show him.
He passed the secretary interview with
that photo. Not bad, right?
Take that with you. You'll be needing it.
You're very tall.
Here goes.
Block this.
What are you looking at?
Isn't he cold?
-I'm not cold.
-Mr. Cha!
-What happened?
-Oh, I'm sorry. I blew my cover.
Wait. Did they beat you up?
Ah, it's all good. I'm fine.
You're bleeding, what are you saying?
But I think I snuck something from under
Ms. Michelle's nose.
Oh, uh, I'll find something in
the dashcam footage. Even if it
takes all night, I swear. And by the
way, it's almost impossible to
track Michelle now. What are we gonna do?
-Mr. Lee.
-Hmm.
There's something you need to see.
The person claiming to be a victim
is Ye Min-a, a beauty creator, who's
got an inflammatory skin disease. She's a
famous content creator and
her allegations are provocative, so it's
spreading rapidly through social media.
This is just a claim from one person.
It could be from something she ate.
We spent months testing this product.
No way. It can't be.
I have to call someone.
MR. MECHOORI
Hello?
Dam Ye-jin, you saw the post, right?
We're looking into it as we speak. So…
I'll call you back.
What's wrong? Mechoori.
ANOTHER GOOD MORNING CREAM INCIDENT?
RETURN OF THE CONTROVERSIAL RESEARCHER
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE MUST TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR HARBORING LEE HAE-SEOK
Mechoori.
Since last night, a bunch of
people barged in, and made a total mess
out of the village.
What should we do? I thought you should
at least know.
STRONGLY OPPOSE THE SALE OF THE CREAM
WE ARE THE VICTIMS
Oh, God! What should we do? Oh, God.
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY!
GET OUT!
Gojeuneok, my ass.
Over there, over there.
-Let's hurry.
-Okay.
I'll give them a piece of my mind.
LEE HAE-SEOK,
YOU MADE POISON, NOT CREAM
Wasn't a cream, but a poison? Jin-yi,
who are those people?
Let's go inside, okay?
It looks like they're headed towards
Mechoori's house?
Go inside, okay? Just go inside.
CRIMINAL LEE HAE-SEOK OUT
SUFFER FOR ALL YOUR LIFE
You all better tell us where he
is. Open up. Where is he?
-What if someone gets hurt, huh?
-Come on, let's please just talk this out!
Tell him to come out while you can!
You people know everything, don't you?!
Seriously?
-Let's talk this out.
-He's here.
He's here, that bastard.
Ah, Mechoori?!
You've got some nerve, asshole.
You've been hiding out here. You ruined
my kid's skin.
Look, look at my face.
Look at me with your eyes, you dick!
I need you to fix it. Just fix it.
My child's face, and all the lives
you've ruined! This is all on you!
What should we do then?
This solves nothing, okay?! Someone is
gonna get hurt! Let's be civil and talk!
Are you okay, Mechoori? Everybody,
calm down, so we can talk! Let's calm
down and talk.
Because of the cream this bastard
made, my child couldn't put on a
normal tee-shirt. On the hottest day
of summer!
I'm sorry.
Oh!
You're sorry?! You try putting it on,
bastard!
Come on, let's talk about it.
Get out of my way, dammit!
Oh, Mechoori.
Oh, God, Jong-il. Oh, God. Are you hurt?!
Hey, I think he sprained his back badly.
-Are you okay?
-Hey, are you okay?
Ugh, why'd you have to get in the
way like that?
Hey, listen up! Stop, moron! Is this
the time to be pointing fingers? Huh?
Get outta here! If you don't, I'll-- I'll
call the police. Get out! Get out!
Let's just get out of here. Come on.
Get out now! Now!
-Come on!
-Get out of my sight!
Your old boss took his own life to pay
for this. What are you gonna do?
Uncle, are you okay?
You evil bastard!
You're a damn criminal.
Oh, God! It hurts. Hold on.
Get out of here already!
You think you can stand up?
STRONGLY OPPOSE THE SALE OF THE CREAM
CRIMINAL LEE HAE-SEOK OUT
-Be careful!
-It hurts!
-What do we do?
-I can't believe it!
He doesn't look good.
Alright, are you okay? Let's get
you inside.
I'm so sorry. I need to get rid of
this trash first.
You've already got enough troubling you.
Just leave it, okay?
Just let him do it! He said he'd do it!
Um, the banner stuck to the community
center. I'll go and remove that.
Don't you worry.
And what if you get hurt as well?
All the green houses are covered
in graffiti. Let's just go clean that up.
I'll be fine.
How'd this happen to us all of a sudden?
Our small peaceful village of all places?
Just stop it already!
I'm sorry.
Before I cause more trouble,
I'll clean things up quickly and
leave here.
Why are you all just standing there?
How could you all act so coldly like
this? Huh?
You shouldn't be talking to us like
that! You heard perfectly well what
they said earlier! You're still taking
his side, even after all of this?!
Is there…
Anyone here who hasn't been helped
by Mechoori even once?
How can you call yourselves human beings?
How can you even ask us that, Sang-geum?
How could you side with Mechoori
over your village? We've lived with you
for thirty years.
God, Sang-geum! Why does Mechoori mean so
much to you?
That's not what I meant. I don't
mean that.
I need you to understand just what he
means to me.
He reminds me of my child. The child
I buried deep in my heart a long
time ago. It's because he reminds
me of the child I buried deep
in my heart. He reminds me of my child.
It's because he reminds me of my child.
Bong-chan.
I don't know what to tell you, I'm always
hungry. You're food is so good.
I used to have a son.
He was a good son, who only ever worried
about his mother, even though I
didn't do much for him.
Sang-geum, this is bad. The ship,
Bong-chan. The ship he was on
flipped over.
That day was his birthday.
I never even got to make him a warm
birthday meal. I shoulda-- I should've…
Bong-chan?
After having felt guilty my whole life,
on the day I decided to visit
Bong-chan's grave, I saw Mechoori.
Hey, hey.
Young man. Goodness, it's such a
cold day. Let's get you inside.
It's cold out here.
Mechoori! I brought potatoes for you.
After feeding him to my heart's
content and spending time with him…
-I realized how foolishly kind he was.
-I'm dying.
Just like my son. Mechoori!
-But that foolishness…
-That's perfect! Way to go!
We got our TV back. Yeah!
See you tomorrow! Goodbye.
Made a spring breeze…
Blow through my hair.
And through the entire village…
I thought the heavens were so cruel.
For leaving me here all by myself
alone. Alone. But maybe they did it
so I could hold your hand, my dear.
Great job today.
-And this happened.
-No way, no way!
So what did you do? What did you do
after that?
Her hair was curving so badly to
one side, it looked like it was
pasted to her head. I couldn't
do the show with her.
You're kidding.
I wouldn't have been able to either,
really.
Ms. Ji Yun-ji.
Congratulations on the sell out.
Can we chat for a second? Won't be long.
Why did you come here like this?
I want to take you out to a nice
restaurant.
The Noori Cream's trial participant
list ended up being a huge help.
So I'm done helping you now, right?
Please don't contact me again.
You didn't really think you could
just get rid of me that easily? Do
you, Yun-ji?
Please, Mr. Son! Who would buy Noori
Cream after this? With public
response so awful, surely this should be
more than enough.
Noori Cream's never been my goal, Ms. Ji.
A huge incident occurred and Lee
Hae-seok's responsible.
And now…
I must end him.
What's the emergency?
I found out who Ms. Michelle has been
meeting with in secret.
Who the hell is this guy?
Why would Chang-ho…
Do you have any idea why my sister
and Mr. Son Chang-ho met?
One thing's for sure, H.O. cosmetic is
purchasing Gojeuneok Bio's raw
materials, but why that is, isn't clear.
Right now, L'Etoile is planning to
expand to Asia, but I noticed La Fin
Essence is part of their main
products list.
La Fin Essence?
Yes. Strange, right? It's been
a long time since they ran out of
those materials.
NUAMER WITH UNITED PASSION
MAKING NUAMER'S BEAUTIFUL VISION A REALITY
H.O. COSMETICS CLIENT LIST
NUAMER
Who are you?
You should go. This place closed down
a long time ago.
By any chance, is Son Chang-ho
someone you know?
Who?
I heard that H.O. and Nuamer signed a
contract and were collaborating on a
project until late last year.
Research, cooperation, strengthening
technological capabilities, blah, blah.
What a smooth talker, yeah? We fell
for it completely and signed
the contract, only for them to steal our
proprietary technology!
What about the patent? Did you
register it?
How could small business owners like
me and you, afford all the procedures
and costs?
But you must surely have research and
development data, so you can prove
your case.
We tried filing all kinds of
lawsuits, but we got slapped with
a countersuit and lost everything.
And by then, they had already
prepared their own research and
development data.
H.O. cosmetics has an internal R and D
known for aggressive investments
from what I hear.
Who told you that? They don't spend money
on their own products and won't!
They copied our product, and switched
out the raw materials. Then they
went and sold it at a much higher price!
Wait, did you mean that…
Did you just say that the raw materials
were switched?
Yes. He told us that our raw
materials were too expensive,
and suggested we use cheaper ones to make
a profit.
A business makes profit its top priority.
They're saying Woo-su…
That he swapped out the ingredients.
Looks like you've also gotten tangled
up in one of Son Chang-ho's schemes.
Be careful. He wouldn't hesitate to
use violence to get exactly what
he wants.
Ah, Ms. Ae-ra. You closed the store.
Uh, yeah. I turned off all the machines.
I was craving your cappuccino so
I came here. Shame. I can come
back another time.
Oh, um, I can still make drinks.
Oh, delicious.
Is something wrong? You're not being as--
Well, corny as usual.
Ms. Ae-ra, have you ever seen a different
side to someone you were close to?
It makes you wonder who the person you
spent all that time with really was.
Were they always like that, and I just
didn't see it? Ah, this is so tough.
What's so tough about it? Whoever
deceives is the bad one. And the
other one…
Suffers.
Don't let a bad man like that get to you.
That man has got no idea whether
or not I-- I'm rotting away inside
or not.
That bad man? Was he the guy who wore
the same watch as me?
Yes.
When I feel this way, I warm up
my insides usually. Wait here for a bit.
Let me make you a nice cappuccino.
HE MADE ANOTHER COSMETIC PRODUCT?
HOW COULD HE BE SO SHAMELESS?
HIT HOMESHOPPING SHOULD CANCEL
THE LAUNCH SHOW FOR THIS GARBAGE
MR. MECHOORI
HIT MERCHANDISER
HWANG KI-HONG
Ki Hong, what's up?
Ms. Dam. About Ms. Ye Min-a, real name,
Chu Min-a, she was one of the winners of
the pre-launch trial event.
And just her, but all six of the alleged
victims.
Isn't that a bit weird? The pop up
event handed out plenty of samples, but
not a single person there claimed any
issues after.
Let's check the lot numbers of the cream
the testers used and have them retested.
Here. These are the test results that
were delivered by express.
There's absolutely nothing wrong with the
cream.
Ugh, seriously!
Not a single person is picking up their
phone. Is this some kind of joint
REVERSE VIRAL MARKETING
DELIBERATELY SPREADING NEGATIVE PUBLICITY
We need to expose what's going on.
But even if we claim it's fine, no one's
just going to believe that.
Oh, no.
-Hello?
-It's me. Na Jin-yi.
Oh, Jin-yi?
Hurry, hurry.
I want to help Hae-seok.
My sister's skin is practically a
litmus test strip. She has a condition
called chronic atopic dermatitis,
so her skin reacts right away to even
the most minimal of irritants.
She's been using this sample of
NOORI CREAM IS SAFE TO USE
Noori Cream every day, but she
hasn't shown any symptoms.
I can apply it like this, and I swear
it doesn't itch at all.
This right here shows the safety
test results from an agency appointed by
you can see in our test results.
That means there wasn't a single
problematic ingredient found.
It's about what you asked me to find out.
The person who came into contact
with Ji Yun-ji was Son Chang-ho,
CEO of H.O. cosmetics, which is
headquartered in Thailand.
STUDENT REPRESENTATIVE OF
HAIST INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY
CHIEF RESEARCHER OF THE USU
Also, another thing…
Seo-a. Go on up. Go up, love.
To the side. Move to the side.
Oh, Ms. Song.
Ah, Ms. Song.
What brings you…
Well, looks like we have a lot to talk
about, Ms. Yun-ji.
Do you need something from me?
How exactly do you know Mr. Song
Chang-ho?
Good Morning Cream's presenter was gonna
be you, up until about a week
before airing.
Mom!
Yes, Seo-a.
I'd like to ask you a difficult favor.
I too have to protect my girl.
Thank you so much, Jin-yi.
Don't mention it, I only had the
courage to do it because of Som-yi.
Ah, I should've mentioned that Mechoori
sponsors the victims' alliance
every month.
Well, Mechoori will be very grateful
for what you've done.
Ms. Dam.
Can I talk to you? I just need a second.
Hae-seok. It's been so long.
It's really been a minute. Are you
doing well?
Uh, I came because I missed Woo-su.
ARTICLE 3
UNIT PRICE AND ORDER
So. That rumor…
From five years ago…
About a bribe taken by a show host…
That was me.
What is this? Blackmail? Some kind
of set-up? Really? So what if I have
a kid? I'm just a home shopping host!
Seriously?
Calm down. I'm suggesting we help each
other.
Given your standing in the company,
you can get a product placed on a
show while skipping the process for
internal review.
Get the Good Morning Cream onto
HIT's prime time slot, and you'll
be paid. We'll compensate you
and make the money untraceable.
If you want your products on the show,
do it the proper way.
Ms. Ji, shouldn't you be scheduling
a surgery for Seo-a?
Chang-ho, I'm asking you for the
last time. Please tell me the truth.
Please tell me the truth. I won't let
you take the fall alone. I'll take
responsibility with you.
I won't let you take the fall alone.
I'll take responsibility too. Maybe I'm
the reason you ended up like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dam. I had no right to do
that. I hid the truth just so that I
could survive.
I'm too late, but I have something to
give you.
AUDIO RECORDINGS
It's all in there.
The Good Morning Cream incident. How it
started.
CEO SON CHANG-HO
Hae-seok, what are you doing here?
Explain.
What do we have here?
-What is this?
-Don't play dumb. Explain.
I think you're the one that should be
explaining. So what's this all about?
Did you do this to Woo-su too?
Hae-seok. I think there's a
misunderstanding, but keeping this up,
whatever this is, will upset Woo-su,
who's now in heaven.
Shut up. Don't taint his name with lies.
Hae-seok, don't you get it? Woo-su
deceived you too, face it. That's the
truth!
Hey, you said that there was nothing
wrong with the product.
What if someone sees us? Shh!
You promised you switched the ingredient
to cheaper ones and nothing more.
You're blaming this on me, right now? Ms.
Ji Yung-ji, why are you acting so
innocent now? Did you think you could get
paid that much without any risk?
Of course not, you had your concerns and
passed it on to your colleague. Come on,
be honest. Did you really not know? I
asked, did you really not know?!
This is the truth.
And also why Woo-su killed himself.
Chang-ho. This is the thing you said
you'd handle when I went on a
business trip to Jeju, right?
Um, what are you talking about? When the
hell did I say that?
Chang-ho, be honest with me. I'm asking
you, okay?
Hey, listen. I know that you're
on the brink right now, but you're
out of line.
You bastard, you switched it!
Is there any proof of that?
You-- No, it wasn't you. Right? Say it
wasn't! Say that it wasn't you, bastard!
It wasn't, right?!
How could you?! Tell me it wasn't you,
you bastard!
Chang-ho. It wasn't you, right?
SOLD OUT ON YOU
THANK YOU TO MR. SEO HYUN-WOO
FOR HIS SPECIAL APPEARANCE