THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
EPISODE 8
Yeah, dig there. Right there.
That, that rock there...
Okay, the wind and rain are getting worse.
Everyone, evacuate
to the barracks for now.
Fall back!
- Fall back!
Hey, fall back!
- Careful, careful!
- Everyone, move out carefully!
Look after all your comrades, got it?
- Hurry, hurry!
- Hurry, let's move!
My glasses!
My glasses, my glasses!
GANGLIM
Are you okay?
Kang Seong-jae!
GANGLIM OUTPOST
GANGLIM
- You okay?
- Are you all right, sir?
It'll take more than this for me,
Hwang Seok-ho, to...
I'm fine.
Wait, wait, wait...
I think my arm is broken.
I think it's broken.
No, if you think it's broken,
this won't do.
You gotta pull it harder, see?
- That's how a broken arm sets.
- I said
I think it's broken. I think.
- So it's not actually broken?
- Right.
Jeez.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Why would I do this on purpose?
I've got no reason, Company Commander.
The way you jumped in
to protect Kang Seong-jae...
I really thought I was watching
a scene from a movie.
I, Hwang Seok-ho...
As long as I can protect the men
I won't go down even with broken bones.
Still, you were being reckless.
What if it had hit you in the head?
I'd just need to wear a cast
and I'd be fine...
But if one soldier gets in an accident,
it becomes a huge headache.
Goodness.
That's our Company Commander for you.
No matter what happens
never take your eye off the prize.
My "prize"?
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey, why are you getting so serious
over a little joke?
I mean, to our Company Commander,
promotion is everything.
So the safety of the soldiers
is your meal ticket, isn't it?
Shouldn't you be more concerned,
Master Sergeant?
Your juniors have made Sergeant Major.
Will you retire as a Master Sergeant?
I should pull this harder. Really hard.
What's wrong with you two?
- Stop it.
- It hurts.
Company Commander, we have a huge problem.
The rain is so heavy that
it washed out Ganglim Bridge.
Wait a minute.
If the Ganglim Bridge is blocked...
we can't get out of the outpost.
That's right.
Goodness...
we're in real trouble now.
What's with all this chaos
all of a sudden?
I've never seen it
rain this hard in my life.
This is due to the abnormal climate
caused by global warming, sir.
Have you considered
you're the weird one for worrying?
I'm sorry?
Oh, wait! Isn't that the chicken coop?
The chicken coop?
Wait! They're not supposed to fly.
GANGLIM OUTPOST
ISOLATION DAY 1
GANGLIM
THOROUGH VIGILANCE AND FLAWLESS MISSIONS
What... How...
- Damn...
- What... What do we do?
- I don't know, just get inside.
- Yes, sir.
Are these all the ingredients
we have left?
The storage shed flooded,
so there's not much that's usable.
Today was delivery day
so we'd used up most of what we had.
If the Ganglim Bridge is cut off
that means we can't get any ration.
It looks like today's going to be tough.
We'll be resupplied soon,
so let's just hang in there.
Why don't I have service?
What's wrong with it?
Salute.
The distribution box is completely shot.
Since the power's out,
the communications relay is dead too.
- And cell phones have no service.
- Company Commander.
We moved ingredients from the fridge
into coolers for now...
But I don't think they'll last very long.
Master Sergeant.
How many combat rations are left?
We only have a three-day supply
of combat rations.
The regulations only call
for three days' worth.
Three days.
We'll hold out for three days.
Sir?
The Battalion Commander won't give up
on Ganglim easily.
Based on his infinite trust in me,
he'll be sure
to handle this quickly.
Without a doubt.
MILITARY COMBAT RATIONS
We just finished training
and now we're back to combat rations?
Corporal Joo Sang-uk...
is it true we can't get any supplies?
The Ganglim Bridge is out,
so we can't do anything right now.
Damn it.
What if things aren't fixed
when we run out of combat rations?
What do you think will happen?
We'll all just starve to death.
I don't know either.
I'm sure they'll fix it soon.
I mean, it's not like they'll let us
starve to death, right?
Class Change Quest Round 2.
Typhoon on a Meal Tray.
Find hidden cooking ingredients
and serve a meal.
Maintain the Mess Hall
Satisfaction Rating above 50.
Failure to do so
- will terminate The Chef's Path.
- What...
What am I supposed to do
with combat rations?
Man, changing my class is so hard.
GANGLIM
Attention!
No matter how fearsome nature may be...
we will never be broken!
Unbreakable spirit!
We will show them the power of Ganglim!
Carry on.
With both his arms broken...
what does he mean "unbreakable"?
Still, I thought he was pretty cool.
Hello, Do-yeon.
- You're here.
- Yes, I'm here.
- Se-chan.
- Yes, hello.
I'm not your principal, so why are you
bowing at 90 degrees? I'm your wife.
- Please, relax.
- Oh, relax.
- Relax, relax. Treat me like a friend.
- Okay, I will.
What's wrong with me?
GANGLIM OUTPOST
ISOLATION DAY 2
The rain stopped...
but why do I feel so drained?
If you ask me, it's these combat rations.
Hey, how much longer do we
have to eat this stuff?
I'm already sick of it.
I'm starting to miss the shit soup
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun used to make.
Pick something worth missing.
Even so...
the combat rations are better.
Isn't that obvious?
These are combat rations
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol boiled himself.
If we keep serving combat rations
aren't the guys
going to burn down the mess hall?
Mess Hall Satisfaction Rating
is decreasing.
Please be cautious.
Isn't there some way
to make these combat rations taste better?
Seafood paella.
A traditional Spanish home-cooked meal.
What?
How am I supposed to make paella
in a situation like this?
Find the hidden ingredients
to complete the paella.
OBJECTIVE: THREE SEAFOOD ITEMS, TWO SPICES
Seafood?
First seafood ingredient acquired.
BIG AND FRESH WHELKS
KOREAN FROZEN SHRIMP
Second seafood ingredient acquired.
What are you so happy about?
Well...
It's nothing.
Well, Corporal Kim.
I'm going to need some seafood.
What are you talking about?
Where would you find seafood around here?
Wait.
Master Sergeant's... squid?
Jeez.
Wait...
Where did he get that?
I gave one I found in the warehouse,
and he's been at it all day.
What's everyone staring at?
Get back to your duties.
I told you I'll let you know.
Don't you trust me, Hwang Seok-ho?
We'll be out of combat rations
by tomorrow.
Come on, Company Commander.
I'll try to get the power back on
at the outpost
so why don't you stop messing around
and do something productive for a change?
The Battalion Commander
is going to send support to Ganglim
so let's just wait a bit.
All right? Don't worry.
Are they gonna bring us supplies
from the Korean War?
Get out.
We're gonna starve at this rate.
I said, get out.
Fine, have it your way.
Do whatever you want.
Good grief.
I never should have given him that thing.
- Jeez.
- Salute.
Goodness.
I've never faced
a disaster like this before.
No.
I, Hwang Seok-ho, will get this done.
Did you see the Company Commander's legs
shaking while saying everything's fine?
I'm so scared out of my mind.
Tell me about it.
We'll all starve to death
waiting for a rescue.
All because we're stuck
with a lousy commander.
Salute. Private First Class Kang Seong-jae
reporting to the admin office.
Yeah. What's up?
Is something wrong at the mess hall?
Master Sergeant.
Can I have the squid, please?
What?
Well, will you look at this kid.
What, did you get a whiff of it? Here.
Not this, I need a lot more than this.
What are you talking about?
SQUID
You know the domestic ones
are rare, right?
Thank you.
But...
this one too.
I don't know what kind of masterpiece
you're trying to make...
You better not let
this squid's sacrifice be in vain.
Got it?
I'll make something delicious
that meets your expectations.
Go on.
Yes, sir.
I said, go on.
Salute!
ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICE
All seafood ingredients acquired.
SQUID, BIG AND FRESH WHELKS,
KOREAN FROZEN SHRIMPS
3 SEAFOOD ITEMS: WHELKS, SHRIMP, SQUID
2 SPICE ITEMS
SPICES ACQUIRED: 0 OF 2
First spice acquired.
TASTY CURRY
MILDLY SPICY
- I see.
- Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
What are you up to now?
I'm trying to make paella
with the combat rations.
- Pa... what?
- Well, it's...
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol,
are we having combat rations again?
You punk.
When your senior cooks, you eat.
What's with all the complaining?
We've been eating combat rations
since the last training.
- Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Can't you make something delicious,
like those fried rice balls?
Hey!
He already said he's making
some paella or whatever
- so just shut up and wait.
- What?
Paella?
Isn't that the Spanish dish
that's easy to make but delicious?
Oh, really?
You squeeze a bunch of lemon
on the seafood...
It's like...
one of those fancy foreign dishes.
But no matter what, our rookie...
- can't pull that off.
- Right.
Lemon juice. Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
That's right, I need lemon juice.
Where are we gonna get lemon juice?
We don't even have lemons.
Just wing it.
You're going to spoil the other guys.
- Lemon...
- Hero.
Use the "Comrade, help me" skill.
COMRADE, HELP ME! LEVEL 1
Wait.
I know just the guy.
Yes?
Salute...
Salute! Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol,
reporting on official business, sir.
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
What's this about?
Could I have some of that lemon juice
you were drinking the other day?
My lemon juice?
What are you talking about?
That lemon juice's for my detox to enhance
my combat abilities.
It's not something
I can give away to anyone.
You seem busy, so I'll help myself.
Thank you. Salute!
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol!
Kim Kwan-cheol! Kim Kwan-cheol!
That's mine!
Hey!
WHEN THE BROTH REDUCES, ADD SEAFOOD
AND SIMMER THEN ADD LEMON JUICE
HEALTHY LEMON JUICE
It is time for the evening meal.
Go ahead and have your meal.
Man, I'm so hungry I could eat anything.
Anything but combat rations.
It's combat rations for dinner too, sir.
Give me a break.
You should at least eat a little.
This army life really sucks.
Olé!
Perfect! This is delicious!
Paella made from combat rations.
Delicious.
Perfect! This is delicious!
- Perfect! This is delicious!
Thank you.
Mess hall satisfaction is increasing.
Oh, delicious!
Charge!
One, two, three!
GANGLIM OUTPOST
ISOLATION DAY 3
Do your worst, typhoon.
We will be victorious!
- Yeah!
Man...
A meal from Kang Seong-jae
really gives you a boost, huh?
- Yeah!
Finally, the power's back on.
The fridge is working now, too.
I bet the new supplies
will get here soon, right?
We're running low on ingredients too, sir.
Hey.
Now, is the power working okay?
Yes, the fridge's working properly.
Yeah, that's what I like to see.
Hey, Kwan-cheol.
You helping your junior out?
- Yes, sir.
- Keep up the good work, all right?
Work hard
and I might even get you off
overnight guard duty.
Come on, sir, don't mess with me.
- I'm serious, man.
- Really?
Just kidding.
- Hey, Mr. Kang.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Follow me.
All right.
- Hold on.
- Yes, sir.
All right.
And...
last but not least...
Here.
LIKEABILITY
LIKEABILITY 100%
New colleague has been added.
Master Sergeant Park Jae-young.
Aren't these your most prized possessions?
In an emergency like this
you squeeze blood from a stone, right?
I figured you'd need these more than I do.
Isn't the supply truck coming soon?
We're out of combat rations after today.
Comms are back up
so the truck should be here soon.
YEONJU-SI TYPHOON RELIEF SUPPLIES
BONGGIL TRADING
Salute!
Is the damage assessment
for each unit complete?
The recovery is being delayed.
What's the status on Ganglim?
Still no contact?
There's a problem with the Ganglim Bridge
but don't worry too much, sir.
Every unit keeps a week's worth of
combat rations for situations.
It's probably nothing...
but maybe because Seok-ho is there...
I have this uneasy feeling.
I understand how you feel,
Battalion Commander.
There's not a single sane person
stationed at Ganglim.
Hello.
- Salute.
- You're here.
Well, now, look who it is.
If it isn't our esteemed governor.
- We appreciate all your hard work.
- Of course, sir.
Did you make it home okay
after our game of golf the other day?
- That day, I...
- OK, taking the picture now.
One, two!
Wait, hold on.
4TH COMPANY COMMANDER, HWANG SEOK-HO
Oh, my apologies.
RESPECTED BATTALION COMMANDER
Battalion Commander! Battalion...
What...
Why isn't he...
RESPECTED BATTALION COMMANDER
Sir! 4th Company Commander,
Hwang Seok-ho, reporting.
- Battalion Commander, sir...
- Is everything all right?
I heard from the Support Section Chief.
That each outpost has a week's
supply of combat rations.
Well, Battalion Commander.
There's been a misunderstanding.
What are you talking about?
Well, you see...
The only combat rations we had
were a three-day supply.
And we've already used up most of that.
Why are you just reporting this to me now?
- I'm sorry?
- I told the Regimental Commander
that everything was fine at Ganglim.
Now how am I supposed to tell him
we're out of combat rations?
- I...
- Jeez.
Just hang in there.
But how are we supposed to...
That's why you need to file
your reports properly!
RESPECTED BATTALION COMMANDER
Battalion Commander.
Battalion Commander!
We're starving!
How cute.
Gosh, I'm so bored.
Now what in the world does that mean, huh?
- What's the big idea?
- Come on, this is ridiculous!
All the support went to civilian aid.
What can I do?
So let's just monitor
the situation for a bit.
Goodness, that Lee Min-gu... That jerk!
Civilian aid, my foot.
We're about to starve to death.
I'm gonna go up that mountain
and forage for some greens myself.
- Just letting you all know.
- Hey, don't be ridiculous.
So, what? You want us to sit back
and starve to death?
- Jeez, seriously!
- Master Sergeant!
GANGLIM OUTPOST
ISOLATION DAY 4
What's on the menu today?
We're out of combat rations.
All that's left is the ramen, sir.
Then is there any kimchi?
We're out of kimchi as well, sir.
Just shut up and eat.
Now's not the time to be picky.
Come here.
Why's he always yelling at me...
Thanks for the food.
There was barely any food,
so there's nothing to clean up.
Hey, but what are we gonna eat now?
We finished all the ramen, didn't we?
Yes, sir.
Well, we're screwed now.
Damn it...
Does anyone have a secret stash?
Hero.
Well... there is one thing
that comes to mind.
Actually, it's probably a bad idea.
Why?
What is it? Spit it out!
BARRACKS 1
YOON DONG-HYUN
If Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun finds out
we'll be in trouble, won't we?
Oh, come on.
We're about to starve.
Is this really the time to be scared?
Don't we need to get our hands on
anything we can eat?
Right, exactly.
We need to look out for ourselves first.
There's nothing here, damn it.
CHICKEN BREAST BEST SET
Ah, screw it!
There!
Let's eat!
We're saved. We're saved!
BLACK PEPPER CHICKEN BREAST
You have acquired a cooking ingredient.
CHICKEN PORRIDGE: ADD SALT, PEPPER,
AND FINISH OFF WITH SESAME OIL
SEASON WITH PEPPER
Decent chicken porridge.
DECENT CHICKEN PORRIDGE
COULD'VE BEEN SOMEONE'S SOURCE OF PROTEIN
GANGLIM OUTPOST
ISOLATION DAY 5
Is this for real?
We've gone through all our supplies.
All that's left is rice.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Pyo Ji-yong.
You got anything in your barracks?
What would I have?
Come on, don't be like that.
Just give me some.
Hey, what are comrades for?
We're supposed to share,
especially when times are tough.
Freeze.
What was that? That sound from your
military biscuit pocket?
Hey, what are you doing?
The hunger must be making you hear things.
No, that was the unmistakable crinkle
of a snack bag.
I swear, I have nothing. Nothing.
Why are you doing this? Really!
- I swear, I have nothing!
- I heard it! Right here! Look.
This is my last one.
Just one bite. Just one bite.
Just one bite, please. Come on.
- I can't! No!
- Please!
No way.
CHOCO PIE
No!
Freeze!
What do you all think you're doing?
Company Commander, this is a serious
problem on our hands.
You should speak with the
Battalion Commander and recommend
we evacuate the outpost.
And just how are we supposed to
evacuate the outpost?
The Ganglim Bridge is out.
We can't get in or out.
Right.
Then I'll go out
and find something. All right?
If I bring something back,
won't Seong-jae figure something out?
Didn't I tell you no?
It's too dangerous! The rain just stopped.
But we can't just sit here
and starve to death.
- We have nothing to eat right now.
- Then I'll go with you.
We can't just stand by and do nothing.
No. I'll go with him.
With the Company Commander's condition
you have to stay and protect the outpost.
That's enough, everyone.
Absolutely not. I said no.
I, Hwang Seok-ho,
will absolutely not allow it.
I'll contact the
Battalion Commander again...
How long are we supposed to sit and wait?
They care about themselves, not us.
Company Commander, you frustrate me.
That's how we get...
stabbed in the back.
What did you just say?
Stabbed in the back? Frustrating?
- Master Sergeant.
- What, was I wrong?
We got stabbed in the back.
All of us got stabbed
in the back, didn't we?
Regardless of anything else...
we can't let the soldiers starve.
Fine. Do as you please.
But if anything goes wrong...
I, Hwang Seok-ho
will hold you personally responsible.
Don't go too far
and make sure you're back before sunset.
All right.
- Pull this down.
- Yes, sir.
Now, now, Outpost Commander.
Don't you worry.
Who do you think I am?
I'm Park Jae-young,
Master Sergeant of Ganglim Outpost.
I can't let our soldiers starve to death.
Deputy Outpost Commander, don't get hurt.
Yes, ma'am. Don't worry.
By the way, is the Company Commander
doing any better?
Master Sergeant! Deputy Outpost Commander!
You have to come back safely.
Master Sergeant.
Troops, attention!
Salute the Master Sergeant!
- Salute!
Salute!
I'll be back.
Kang Seong-jae!
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae!
Get a fire going in the cauldron.
- I'll be back before you know it.
- We love you, Master Sergeant!
Over the desolate mountains and rivers
- Let's go.
- The snow-covered
Front line we march on...
Oh, man.
Okay, grab on.
Jeez.
Well, this is strange.
What's wrong?
I'm sure this was the right path.
Maybe it's because the typhoon
swept through here?
It all looks the same.
Hey.
Haven't we been climbing
that tree for a while now?
I think we have.
Jeez, it's like we're being haunted
by a ghost.
We just keep going around in circles.
A... a ghost, you say?
Did I ever tell you...
how the previous Master Sergeant died?
No, you haven't.
Well, the thing is...
He was on patrol one night...
and it was probably somewhere around here.
Someone from behind kept...
Never mind. It's nothing.
Master Sergeant, we should head down
before it gets any later.
The Company Commander is probably
waiting for us too.
I'm kidding! Kidding, kidding.
The last Master Sergeant is alive.
Why would you joke like that?
The soldiers are starving.
This is no time for games.
Let's see.
Okay, look.
The sun is over there,
so we have to head that way.
Are you sure it's that way,
Master Sergeant?
My gut tells me so.
I think your gut is the reason we're lost.
Let's go.
Wait up!
We haven't eaten much,
so we have no energy.
Hey, talking a lot makes you hungrier.
Just be quiet.
Master Sergeant.
When on earth are you coming back?
VIGILANCE IS OUR MISSION
GANGLIM OUTPOST
What are you guys doing?
If we do this...
won't someone from above
see us and rescue us?
YEONJU-SI TYPHOON RELIEF SUPPLIES
BONGGIL TRADING
You must've been swamped leading
so many men for civilian support.
Thanks to you, Battalion Commander
I'll be able to hold my head high.
Isn't it a soldier's duty to be
the first to step up?
If I can be of help to you,
Regimental Commander
I should take the lead on anything.
On the next promotion list...
your name will be on it,
Battalion Commander.
Really?
I know you've been anxious about it...
so I'm giving you a heads-up.
You had a tough time last year
because of Major Im.
And I was worried
things would be difficult for you.
But seeing you break through
it all like this...
I'm so relieved.
Better days are coming.
Let's just hang in there.
Take care, sir.
Salute!
Are they gonna be okay?
I think we need the Master Sergeant here
as soon as possible.
This is exactly why
I was against this! See?
What now?
I mean...
What if they get stranded
in the middle of the night?
Then I'll go out and find them, sir.
You want to get stranded too, Cho Ye-rin?
- Sir, you can't take that off now.
- I, Hwang Seok-ho
value the safety of the outpost soldiers
over my own two arms.
But, sir...
I'll go find them myself. In my place
I need you to take command of the unit.
Master Sergeant!
Attention!
Salute the Company Commander!
- Salute!
He's not returning the salute.
As you were.
Master Sergeant Park Jae-young
has completed our mission.
We gathered balloon flower roots,
mushrooms, and mountain greens.
Now we just need to get this
to Seong-jae...
What in the world happened?
You weren't answering!
What?
Weren't you the one who said,
"Do as you please"?
Don't tell me you were worried about us.
It's not that I was worried.
I distinctly remember telling you
it was dangerous after the rain.
The Master Sergeant was incredible, sir.
He was zipping around the
mountainside like a flying squirrel
then suddenly back here again.
What would you have done
if something had happened?
Do as you please.
You're an absolute mess.
There he goes again,
bitching about something.
He bitches when I leave.
He bitches when I come back safely.
If I were him, I'd have made Major
instead of wasting time bitching.
The Company Commander may talk like that
but he was really worried about you two.
But the Company Commander
took off his cast.
Yeah.
I guess it's all healed.
He's the type to do whatever
he wants, right?
Probably just took it off
when he felt like it.
- "Do as you please!"
- Welcome back! Great work!
Heave-ho.
CHAMNAMUL
GRADE A
SHEPHERD'S PURSE, BALLOON FLOWER
SHIITAKE MUSHROOM
GRADE A
OYSTER MUSHROOM, COASTAL HOG FENNEL
- Wow.
- What is all this?
Did they raid the entire mountain?
This is incredible.
How did they get all of this?
MOUNTAIN GREENS BIBIMBAP
PROFICIENCY
NAMUL COOKING LEVEL 7
Your namul cooking proficiency
is increasing.
- I think you can take them out now.
- Right.
SAUTE SHIITAKE AND OYSTER MUSHROOMS
IN PERILLA OIL
FRESH MOUNTAIN GREENS BIBIMBAP
Fresh mountain greens bibimbap.
CAPTURING THE VIBRANT
COLORS OF NATURE
Company Commander, it's time to eat.
The Master Sergeant said an injured person
needs to eat well to recover.
I think that's why he pushed himself
so hard to go to the mountain.
- Great work.
- Goodness.
- Enjoy your meal.
- This smells amazing.
Wow, this looks so good.
You all worked hard.
- Now, enjoy the food.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm not hurt.
- Master Sergeant.
- Yeah, eat up, eat up.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Yes, enjoy.
Man, you must still be full.
Are you waiting for the Company Commander?
Oh, me?
Why on earth would I wait
for the Company Commander?
- Come on, let's just eat.
- Salute!
At ease.
Company Commander.
Please come this way.
Here you are.
I was wondering
what all the fuss was about...
but it looks pretty good.
All right, everyone, let's eat up.
- Enjoy your meal.
Go on, mix it all up and have a taste.
Since you're such a picky eater,
I have no idea if you'll like it.
Oh, come on. Stop it.
- If you don't like it, don't eat it.
- No, that's not...
All that hard work for nothing.
And yet he's sure wolfing down
that bibimbap.
This is good.
Look at you.
You're licking the spoon
clean and pretending you don't like it.
- No, I just said it was good.
- You're pretending.
I was just trying to say that...
Thank you for the meal, Master Sergeant.
Enjoy your meal, Company Commander.
I, Hwang Seok-ho...
have something I'd like to say
to all of you.
Like this bibimbap
I never doubted
that our Ganglim would become one.
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger,
as they say.
The rain may have trapped us
and made us suffer
but today, with this bibimbap,
we will become even stronger.
I, Hwang Seok-ho...
propose a toast
with this bibimbap.
When I say "Ganglim!"
you all say "Forever."
Ready? Ganglim!
- Forever!
Hero. Mess Hall Satisfaction Rating
has increased.
MESS HALL SATISFACTION RATING
CURRENT STATUS 100
As ingredients with their characters
mix together
to create one delicious bowl of
bibimbap...
we grew dependable and passionate
when we were together.
Man...
I'm on leave...
and time is still crawling by.
It's weird, but I think
I was more comfortable back on base.
Hey, you idiot!
What is this crazy fool saying?
There's so much fun to be had.
Get a grip, Dong-hyun.
Yeah, get a grip.
Enjoy your meal.
That's weird.
The taste seems different than before.
Is it because I'm just used to
Kang Seong-jae's cooking?
No, no way. Ugh!
The military has launched civilian support
operations in Gangwon-do
which was hit by Typhoon Crow.
Oh, boy. You're all working so hard,
aren't you?
- Goodness.
- They will support the civilians.
However, with major roads
and bridges washed out
supply routes and access
to some areas and military units
have been severely disrupted.
According to an official
the government and military are mobilizing
all available personnel
to accelerate recovery efforts
but due to the widespread damage
caused by the typhoon
they are facing significant difficulties
in resolving the situation.
Up next...
Master Sergeant.
Do you have particular tastes in alcohol?
Tastes? If it's expensive,
I'm just thankful.
Whoa, it's blue.
You got any snacks to go with this?
I have something I really like.
Star Candy.
You think I want to be doing this?
I'd love to stand up to my superiors too.
But...
as for me, Hwang Seok-ho...
I graduated dead last
from the Military Academy.
That's a well-known fact
for anyone in uniform.
You're supposed to let it dissolve.
Some of them come from
three generations of soldiers.
And some are
ridiculously good at kissing up.
- So what am I?
- Yeah.
I mean, how bad must it be...
for me to keep liquor
I don't even drink in my room?
Hey, if you had such good stuff,
you should've brought it out earlier.
Because you always drink makgeolli.
Hey, you just don't get it.
Once you acquire the taste,
nothing is better than makgeolli.
See? This is why I didn't want
to give you any.
"Do as you wish."
- Do as you wish.
- Yes.
- As you wish.
- Jeez.
But why do you...
always choose to do
the things you're told not to?
With due respect, Company Commander
aren't you the one who forbids everything?
Someone said...
that you have a surprisingly
fiery temper...
and they were worried you'd get hurt
if left alone.
Are you sincerely
worried about me?
Because I made a promise.
I made a promise
to not let anyone get hurt.
But it's not easy.
It's all my fault.
Me too. I'm just as much to blame.
Since I don't have any power yet. Well...
What can I do?
Come on.
Power's something you make,
isn't it, Company Commander?
Look at what happened today.
The camaraderie we couldn't build
finally came together.
Come on.
Have a drink.
Yes?
Salute.
Oh, Seong-jae. What is it?
During the last training exercise, ma'am.
I happened to...
overhear Captain Lee Min-gu on a call.
A call? About what?
He said...
the Outpost Commander
won't be able to do anything now...
and that if you became a nuisance...
he would take care of it.
What's that supposed to mean?
I heard him mention your name,
Outpost Commander.
Oh, you're talking about
Cho Ye-rin, right?
Should I just take care of her?
No, you must have heard wrong.
Why would Captain Lee Min-gu
say something like that?
Stop thinking about it
and get some sleep.
Yes, ma'am.
Salute.
OUTPOST COMMANDER'S OFFICE
GANGLIM OUTPOST
Did you see that?
The power of Hwang Seok-ho!
- I am Hwang Seok-ho.
- Good work.
- Hwang Seok-ho.
- All right, good work.
Hey, you worked hard.
But was it really possible
to restore the Ganglim Bridge so quickly?
That's because...
Yeah, yeah, knock it off. That's enough.
- How's it looking, Seong-jae?
- Yes?
We'll be able to eat properly now.
- Yeah!
Salute! Are you all right, sir?
Hey, Yoon Dong-hyun.
Why are you back so soon?
That hurts, Master Sergeant.
I've appeared to resolve the crisis, sir.
Should I prepare the meal right away, sir?
Don't be so dramatic.
Yeah, I missed your shit soup. Let's go.
- Kang Seong-jae, you ready?
- I'm ready, sir.
Let's move out.
Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Yeah!
Now I feel like
I'm in my own skin again.
You know?
- What is it, kid?
- No...
- It's nothing, sir.
- Look at the state of this place
while I was gone.
How am I to discharge peacefully
with things like this?
You must've had a hard time
because of that punk Kwan-cheol.
Don't worry. I'm here now.
- Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Thanks for the food.
Enjoy your meal, sir.
What's this? What's going on with you two?
Did something happen?
Ah, aren't we colleagues
serving in the army together?
You've gotten soft,
calling your senior a colleague.
Hey, Kim Kwan-cheol.
What did you do to Kang Seong-jae?
What are you talking about?
Do I have to worry about a junior?
You two smiled without me.
You smiled again.
You had it tough with the typhoon.
I'm glad no one got hurt.
How did you get through it?
By demonstrating leadership skills
I learned from you
I, Hwang Seok-ho...
was able to overcome the crisis.
All right.
The Master Sergeant foraged for greens
and mushrooms in the mountains
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae
cooked with the combat rations
so we were able to endure.
What happened?
- Well, sir.
- Everyone could have been in danger!
Aren't there regulations
to prepare for these situations?
What were you thinking,
not knowing the proper regulations!
I'm sorry, sir.
SAVORY SESAME OIL
DISASTER SITUATION ENDED
You have completed
the "Typhoon on a Meal Tray" Quest.
INTERMEDIATE COOK
Changing class to Intermediate Cook.
STAMINA
A NEW PROFICIENCY HAS BEEN ACTIVATED
By changing class to Intermediate Cook
you can now cook five-star dishes.
THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
Are you talking about Officers' Mess, sir?
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae
will showcase his cooking.
Complete a five-star dish
for the Regimental Commander.
I don't think a cook from an outpost
can do anything here.
I guess you have to be this good
to be a soldier in the Officers' Mess.
If it's not a five-star dish
- it won't satisfy Regimental Commander.
- Are you going to leave like this?
Sorry I'm late.
Can't you see we've already eaten?
At this rate,
the quest will be a complete failure.