( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
The second single
will be released soon.
This time,
you must crush that annoying traitor
and get first place!
Stop shouting. Calm down.
How can I be calm?
It'll be your fault if we lose again.
You got deceived by that scammer
just because she's a bit pretty.
How gross!
She did no real harm.
She caused real harm everywhere!
She stole our members'
personal information
and now she even knows
our current situation!
She knew we were poor to begin with.
Shut up! Why did you treat
that jerk to hot pot?
That's our money. It's frustrating!
Stingy.
Don't call me stingy!
Okay! I give up... Gosh!
If we lose to TORINNER
and that detestable Park Ji-soo
next time
I won't be able to pay off
the 500 million debt.
Then, the bad guys will capture me,
and I'll become fish food!
My condolences!
Stupid Azuma!
Get first place at all costs! First!
Or MAMA's Best New Artist Award
will be nothing but a pipe dream.
We'll aim for MAMA's
Best New Artist Award.
We can win it!
Yes!
This time, we'll make it to MAMA.
You and SEVEN SEAS failed
to fulfill that dream.
You'll take NAZE to MAMA, right?
Yeah.
This time
I'll take them to that dream stage.
Look at all of those.
This is Mr. Kamiya, the director of
the Japan branch of Bouquet Music.
- Good morning.
No need for the formalities.
Artists like you two
don't need to be so polite
to an ordinary guy like me.
Have a seat.
I apologize for making you come
all the way here.
Today, I'd like to talk to you
about TORINNER
as well as the roadmap
we've planned for the group.
Our CEO, Mr. Choi Ki-young,
has high expectations for TORINNER.
He's considering
a huge global development
that's beyond
the other agencies' imagination.
After the release
of their second single
they will release a full album
in July
and they will be holding a world tour
including US stops.
After that...
I can't reveal who it is
but they will be
having a collaboration
with a world-famous artist.
Wow!
In November, they'll receive
MAMA's Best New Artist Award.
I can safely say
everything will go as planned.
MAMA? You mean that MAMA?
That's right!
The MAMA Awards.
It is the biggest K-pop award
ceremony known worldwide.
All K-pop artists long
to stand on the stage there.
Am I right, Kun?
TORINNER will stand
on the MAMA's stage...
- It's not decided--
- That's right!
After all, we...
Bouquet Music, are going all out
to support TORINNER.
Our company's principle is
to give artists
the greatest respect and love.
That's especially true for extremely
talented people such as you two.
What do you say?
Have you decided to join TORINNER?
No.
We came here today to turn you down.
Is that so? Why is that?
The reason we've made it
this far is that
we've learned many things
from Mr. Azuma.
We trust Mr. Azuma very much, so...
I see.
You two are very honest.
But...
If you continue to trust Mr. Azuma
you'll regret it.
This is an article in a tabloid
five years ago.
Azuma abused the group
he was training back then
so he was banned from the industry.
There was no uproar
since his agency pulled some strings
but lately, people get bashed
horribly for past incidents.
What will happen if a similar article
sees the light of the day again?
Don't forget that NAZE is currently
on the rise.
What about your mother's
medical expenses
and your little brother's
living expenses?
Humans need money to survive.
Is this article true?
Those kids aren't interested at all!
All this dawdling is
the reason you were fired!
As instructed, I infiltrated NAZE
to create chaos
and asked Turn and Kimkun
to join TORINNER.
Good work.
As it happens, we also have
two rotten apples in TORINNER.
We'll swap them.
No.
I don't think they'll agree
to join TORINNER.
Hey, what are you talking about?
You call them losers and leftovers
but they've united
under Producer Azuma
and formed a family-like bond.
If you make two TORINNER members quit
and add the two NAZE members
it'll upset them
and have the opposite effect.
It would be smarter not
to steal the NAZE members.
You're just a mere producer.
How dare you talk like that?
Ms. Park, are you saying
you oppose my plan?
No, this is just a realistic analysis
of the situation.
Thanks.
Not many people will
voice their opinions to me now.
We need to cherish talents
like her...
Mr. Kamiya.
You're right, Mr. Choi.
Well, then.
From now on,
TORINNER's chief producer...
will be Mr. Kamiya.
What?
Ms. Park, you'll assist him
and continue to train the group.
I'm in all this trouble
thanks to you.
I'm a businessman
and I don't want to do creative work.
Still...
Since I'm in charge now
I need to train them again
from scratch into cash cows.
Here he is.
Come in.
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Kamiya.
I'm Seso Weekly's Kazamatsuri.
Please have a seat.
I'm asking you...
Why did I have to treat
that liar to hot pot?
What are you here for?
You're blathering on and on.
What's wrong with coming
to have dinner?
Why do I need your permission?
This is my home.
Besides, you're one to talk!
You got totally deceived
by that scammer. How gross!
What do you like
about that ugly woman? How gross!
The song Ms. Park bought
is awesome, isn't it?
I wouldn't have been able to get it.
Besides, I like her. She's pretty.
Like her? Pretty?
Anyway, you're too careless!
Nowadays, information is everything!
She now knows
our members' special talents
and what they can't do.
- She won't resort to cheap tricks.
- You're too naive!
That's why we're losing to TORINNER,
you third-rate producer!
Come again, you third-rate CEO?
You're the only one
who would be so rude to me!
You're the only one!
Third-rate CEO?
- What... Hey...
- You little...
Wait...
- Wait! Come on...
- Unforgivable!
Can an adult intervene?
I can't ask them...
Excuse me, Ms. Nam.
How long have you and Mr. Azuma
been in a relationship?
Wait, why are you asking that
out of nowhere?
Nothing! There is no specific reason.
Let me think. About 10 years.
Ten years?
I mean our relationship
as colleagues.
No, that's not what I mean.
I mean your romantic relationship.
Let's see...
- About 15 years?
- 15 years!
Why is it even longer?
I mean, I think of him as my lover
only in my mind.
I've been in love with him
since university.
That's not what I'm asking.
Did you two actually date?
What? Minase,
are you in love with Azuma?
Yes...
What? No, I'm not.
You're better off
not dating that guy.
He can't take care of himself,
and nobody knows what he's thinking.
Wait. I mean, it isn't like that.
I respect Mr. Azuma as a producer.
Is that so? But...
He can be quite romantic, you know?
I wonder if he still has it.
That one thing
filled with our fond memories.
"That one thing"?
What is that?
If Azuma still has that
then maybe he still
has feelings for me.
What are you talking about?
I can't tell you.
What was she talking about?
Wait, what is it?
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Your moves are not sharp at all!
I told you to always pay attention
to the fans.
Can you beat TORINNER like that?
Do it once more!
- Yes, sir!
It feels like Mr. Azuma is
taking charge
for the first time in a while.
Yeah, he's taking this seriously.
This suits Mr. Azuma more.
- Younki, Kaisei, drink your water!
- Yes, sir!
Yes, sir!
- Run faster!
- Yes, sir!
About 30 seconds left.
Let's keep this up!
- Okay!
- Mr. Azuma!
Park Ji-soo:
Let's talk about the contract.
Excuse me, Mr. Azuma.
Are you perhaps keeping something
important somewhere in this house?
What? Why do you ask?
I have nothing valuable.
I thought so.
You got banned from the industry,
and you're in debt.
Why would you have anything valuable?
That stings.
Still, there are things that aren't
valuable but important to me.
What do you mean?
Well, things that contain memories
with the people I cherish.
Like Kun's.
What? Oh, right.
My mom made me this.
We all get stuff like that.
For me, it's the love letters
I received in the past.
- What?
Or stickers I got
from the girl I liked.
So boys do tend to cherish
fond memories they share with girls.
I need to check.
Right, I also keep things to
remind myself of the mistakes I made.
Like exam papers with bad scores!
That's just hiding it. You were
going to destroy the evidence.
Where did you learn that?
In Japan, we stuff those
in snack cans.
Yeah, you're right!
I used to hide important stuff
in snack cans.
I see! They hide important things
We do that in Korea too!
We hide it under the bed,
but our mothers end up finding it!
But there aren't any beds
in this house.
What about Thai people?
We hide it above Buddhist altars.
In Japan, people commonly hide
stuff under the floor
under the roof,
and in the toilet's water tank.
Under the floor, under the roof,
I'll check those places first.
I keep my fond memories
I've made with NAZE, too.
First, our TGC entry badge.
Next, the bandana I used back then,
which I haven't washed.
And also, the sock at Melody!
- What?
- Wash them!
"Your body is a mirror
of your habits."
What's that? Never heard of it.
It's a popular saying in Nagano.
That's too obscure!
- What are you doing?
- Put them back!
Put them away!
We've become a great team.
Right. I was so worried
when I first arrived at this house.
Right back at you!
It's all thanks
to your help, Mr. Azuma.
That's right. We couldn't have
done this without you, Mr. Azuma.
Say that after you get first place.
- Okay.
- You're right.
Okay! Let's get first place together
with our next song!
- Yes!
- Let's do this!
- Let's do it!
We'll get first place!
- Eat up!
- Okay!
Go ahead.
It's freezing.
- What's the matter?
- Sorry, we'll be a bit late today.
Something happened back home.
Me too.
Let's go, then!
- Okay!
- Let's go!
See you later!
Bye!
Snack cans...
All right...
Snack... cans!
There we go...
No way!
I don't see snack cans anywhere.
It's... a snack can.
TO MR. AZUMA JUN
We're here. What now?
I want to stay in NAZE.
Me too, but...
If that article
about Mr. Azuma spreads...
We'll have to disband.
We're here.
Wait, aren't they NAZE?
I'm going to the restroom.
Me too.
- Are you okay?
- Hey, are you okay?
- Yeon-woo? Yeon-woo!
- Yeon-woo!
- Are you okay?
- What's wrong? Hey!
Are you okay?
Yeon-woo?
You're late! How dare you slack off?
Come on. Hey, stand up!
You're in the way!
Hey!
That's enough!
This is not practice.
What?
You can quit if you want, you know?
Hey. If you want to put on airs
and act like an artist
do it after you earn some money!
I have an important
business meeting now.
You guys had better
practice properly!
Yeon-woo!
Hey, Ryo. Are you okay?
- Why are you here?
- Ms. Park asked us to come.
Anyway, that old man is so nasty!
Does Ms. Park know?
She's suffering the most right now.
What?
They want to get rid of Nicc and me
and replace us with you two.
And if that doesn't work,
they'll swap us back again.
To them, we're disposables
that can be thrown away after use.
It's not right
to fire TORINNER members
just to take in the NAZE members.
They are not robots.
They have a bond
that they forged together.
That's why they look cohesive.
We should continue
with the same members.
Are you saying this
just because you're a super-famous
producer known worldwide?
Our job is
to properly execute any orders
from Mr. Choi. That's all.
Do your job as instructed.
That's all you're expected to do!
This is the only way
for your beloved TORINNER to survive.
Good, I've been expecting you.
Thank you for coming
all the way here.
Wait, you'll be one of us
starting today, right?
We refuse!
What's the matter?
You must've seen the signing bonus.
Now you don't have
to worry about your family.
Don't be ridiculous!
You were absolutely horrible
to TORINNER!
I see...
Have you met them?
You use the power of money
to trample on
other people's feelings.
We can't work with you.
We'll follow Mr. Azuma.
Are you really sure about this,
you brats?
Don't regret it.
It's over for Azuma.
The same goes for NAZE, too.
Hey, you.
I'm in a very good mood today.
I'll give this to you.
Thank you.
You're funny.
So funny!
TO MR. AZUMA JUN
This should be the place.
Good morning.
Now, for today's morning news.
A music producer who used violence
and abused his power in the past
and caused a controversy
is suspected of doing the same
to the popular boys' group, NAZE,
as reported by multiple magazines.
This producer used
to train SEVEN SEAS
a global boy group that was
active in Japan and Korea
and he used violence and forced them
to attend intense training sessions.
He was speculated to be the reason
behind the group's disbandment.
Now, he is criticized for allegedly
repeating the same coaching style...
It must be Choi Ki-young.
Why is he going this far?
Who knows?
I have no idea how I pissed him off.
It's high time I leave.
Wait! Just tell them it's all false!
We'll be stuck with the mudslinging
for months if I do that!
If that happens,
NAZE won't be able to win.
Choi Ki-young must've been
waiting for the right time.
So that I'd think
leaving is the only way.
If I stay, I'll be in NAZE's way.
This is a crucial time for them.
But...
What am I supposed to tell the boys?
They won't accept it easily.
- This is a lie, right?
- Have you heard anything?
Nothing.
But many people commented they could
tell it was fake right away.
That's right.
I'm sure Mr. Azuma isn't like that.
But at this rate, we...
The most important thing now
is to get first place
with our second single.
Stop overthinking
and get on with our practice.
I agree.
It's over for Azuma.
The same goes for NAZE, too.
Hey.
I am really sorry.
It's not something
you need to apologize for.
I'm the one to blame for it.
It's not my place to say this
but please don't lose.
Of course.
We won't lose.
This moment is crucial to NAZE now.
Choi Ki-young did strike
at the perfect time, though.
I'll disappear.
But that's exactly what Choi wants!
Still, there is no other way
to protect them.
Right?
I enjoyed myself
more than I expected.
At first, I thought they were
completely hopeless.
But now, they've become a team
that's good enough to compete
with elite groups like TORINNER.
They worked hard for it.
Really...
They did a really good job.
I never imagined
they would improve so much.
I abandoned everything
and couldn't find my life's purpose,
so I was wasting away my life.
The seven of them
were the ones who made me
want to live my life to the fullest.
That's why...
I won't do anything
that will waste their efforts.
That's the one thing I must do.
I'm very sorry
that I couldn't stop Choi.
You'll be in serious trouble
if anyone finds out you met with me.
Thanks for coming.
I met you
and came across that great song.
And now, NAZE has grown
even stronger.
NAZE is strong now, you know?
I'll help NAZE climb to the top.
That's my last job.
One, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
We weren't in sync just now.
Concentrate!
- Okay!
- Yes.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four...
There's no need to hesitate.
That's right.
Crush them.
Minase!
What happened?
Hey, what's wrong, Minase?
What's this?
RIKU, LEADER OF SS, DIES BY SUICIDE
Suicide?
"It has been discovered that Riku,
leader of the popular idol group SS
passed away four years ago.
His family says he committed
suicide after being tormented
by Azuma, who abused his power."
IT'S HORRIBLE! SO CRUEL
A PRODUCER WHO KILLS PEOPLE
It says Riku is dead!
- He's dead?
- The one from SS?
K-pop is an industry that involves
the shaping of personalities.
He tramples on
the dreams of young people
who want to become stars
and uses his authority as a producer
to control them with violence.
As someone in the same industry,
there's no way I can forgive that.
I was told that
Azuma has disappeared.
To where?
His whereabouts are unknown.
You don't know where he is...
Whatever shall I do?
As his former colleague,
I'm very worried about him.
I hope nothing bad happens to him.
Don't you agree?
At this time of year
the snow must have
piled up high enough.
What did you just say?
It's nothing, sir.
Excuse me.
Hey!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Hey, don't take photos!
What?
- You took photos, right?
- I did!
They entered without permission.
Seriously...
I'm scared.
They found out where we live, too.
Where did Mr. Azuma go?
Guys, what are your opinions?
It's true that Mr. Azuma is strict.
But...
He isn't someone
who would use violence
to force us to listen to him.
I agree with you.
I do, but...
The leader of SS...
His family said he killed himself
because Mr. Azuma abused his power.
There's no room for doubt, is there?
Kun and I...
were invited by Ms. Park
to transfer to TORINNER.
- What?
Are you betraying us?
- Both of you are leaving?
- Just hear us out.
We turned her down, of course.
But some arrogant man
came and told us...
that it's over for
both Mr. Azuma and NAZE.
What? What does that mean?
That guy had the article
about Mr. Azuma's past.
Does that mean
that guy framed Mr. Azuma?
It's possible.
Can't we do something
to help Mr. Azuma?
But it has caused
such a huge commotion.
What can we even do?
I...
want to protect NAZE.
I think that's also
what Mr. Azuma wants.
- Please let them perform.
- I'm sorry.
I will get in touch again.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Mr. Azuma!
Where have you been?
Mr. Azuma...
I am really sorry.
I...
found Riku's letter at your home.
Mr. Azuma, everything is ruined
since you left.
What's this?
UONUMA CITY, NIIGATA PREFECTURE
AONO RIKU
"Aono Riku"?
Riku from SS?
What he wrote bothered me.
So I went to the address
on the letter.
That was when I met Riku's family.
Leave!
He said Riku killed himself
because of you.
He said...
you killed him.
That's right.
I pushed him too hard.
And it killed Riku.
Azuma, that's not true!
Ms. Nam.
Let's talk.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five...
- Mr. Azuma!
- Where were you?
- Where did you go?
Don't slack off!
You bunch of useless losers.
Do you think you can afford
to waste even a single second?
You're running out of time
for your comeback, fools.
Fools? What do you mean?
What? I told you not to talk back.
Do you want to get fired?
Don't think we can be
like friends forever.
Go on. Start now.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
What was that?
What are you trying to do?
Five, six, seven...
So useless, all of you.
How can you guys
call yourselves idols?
Stop! Stop! Stop!
- Once more.
- Yes, sir.
- Why can't you do something so easy?
- One, two, three, four...
- Stop. Once more.
- Yes, sir.
You all should quit!
I feel embarrassed watching!
Stop. Once more.
Six, seven, eight.
Once more. Hurry up and begin.
We've been practicing
since this morning.
We'll get injured
if we don't take a break.
The performance of a top artist
lasts over three hours.
You need the stamina of an athlete.
You must know that. Right?
You guys have no right to rest!
That's enough!
Why are you talking like that?
Come again? What did you just say?
I said that's enough!
Kun!
Don't act so cocky
towards your producer.
Producer? Don't be ridiculous!
You abandoned everything and ran away
when you were in trouble!
You use violence
when things don't work out for you!
How can you call yourself a producer?
What did you just say?
We won't follow a horrible person
like you. Get lost!
- Mr. Azuma!
- No!
- Don't do this!
- Stop!
Please!
Stop!
Mr. Azuma, please!
Mr. Azuma, stop...
I have an obligation
to protect the boys.
I cannot continue to work
with a violent man like you.
Quit your job as producer at once
and never appear
in front of them again!
Fine by me.
Not like I can afford to fool around
with leftovers like them forever.
And that's my line.
Don't ever appear
in front of me again.
Kun!
I'm sorry!
Mr. Azuma!
It's okay. It's okay.
I...
I am only here because of Mr. Azuma.
It was all thanks to Mr. Azuma!
That's why I could do my best.
But now...
There's nothing I can do to help him!
I'm sorry!
It's enough.
- It's enough. Let's go back.
- I'm sorry!
This time...
It was supposed to be our turn...
to protect Mr. Azuma.
But we can't do anything.
And yet, to protect us, Mr. Azuma...
he intentionally...
He intentionally abused us...
- So you could tell, Kun?
- I'm sorry.
Mr. Azuma, I'm sorry.
Ms. Nam.
Let's talk.
- No.
- I am NAZE's producer.
My job is to take the best course
of action for NAZE, right?
But not that.
What do you mean?
What do you plan to do, Mr. Azuma?
NAZE will be criticized if I stay.
So, I'll disappear.
What?
Of course you can't do that!
Besides, the boys aren't going
to accept it!
I'll make them think my past is true.
- Work with me.
- But...
If you do that
you won't be able
to see the boys again!
That's what I want.
Besides, they'll be fine without me.
Nam is here, too.
And they've got you.
He was acting all cool.
Mr. Azuma smiled back then.
When?
When I lunged at him.
It was for a split second,
but he had a slight smile.
That was when I...
He knew I would realize
what he was doing.
It felt like he was telling me.
I want to debut as early as possible!
Your dream can't fill your stomach.
I'm a fool.
Even if you say it's a dream,
I still can't give up.
I'm a fool, so I want to dream
a foolishly big dream!
For a group of losers like you
it's impossible to become
that 1 in 100,000.
Impossible. It's absurd.
But if we're doing it,
might as well aim to go global.
Mr. Azuma gave up everything...
to protect us.
We must not...
let his efforts go to waste.
I will...
NAZE will...
definitely climb to the top!
Yes.
I would like to report something
regarding Mr. Azuma
the producer who was embroiled
in a controversy a while ago.
Two days ago, we suddenly
couldn't get a hold of him
and his whereabouts are
still unknown to us.
This is a serious breach of contract.
As a result, we decided that
as of today, we will cancel
our contract with Mr. Azuma.
Oh, wow! NAZE's new song is so cool!
I agree. I'm going to stan them!
Still, I'm really happy
for NAZE's members.
I can't believe that Azuma abuses
his power over these young guys.
He's really horrible!
He's a demon! The devil!
The new song is amazing!
I'm so glad that guy is gone.
- Right?
- Let's root for them.
I know them from the news.
Isn't NAZE great?
I know! Who's your fave?
Their producer abused his power
and used violence.
- NAZE.
- NAZE?
They're admirable. I like them!
VIEWS
TOP 10 WEEKLY SALES RANKING
First place.
First place...
RANKINGS WILL BE ANNOUNCED
AT 10:00 A.M.
LOADING...
Mr. Azuma...
Congratulations, NAZE.
We are all fools
so we want to pursue
an even more absurdly big dream.
Now, it's our turn
to help Mr. Azuma dream.
Is that idiot
really not going to come?
Let's do this!
NAZE TO MAKE ITS WORLD DEBUT IN MAY