( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Wait.
Let's watch from a distance first.
If you dare to find a girl behind my back,
you're dead.
Sir,
I'm just running a small business.
Please don't make things difficult
for us weak women.
Bribing a court official.
According to the laws of our dynasty,
that's thirty blows of the cane
and exile to the western desert.
You see,
I was confused.
Confused.
I have something to ask Lady Qiaoyun.
Call her to see me.
So he's here to investigate.
At least you have a conscience.
Qiaoyun.
Qiaoyun, she...
She...
Where did Qiaoyun go?
Speak.
To be honest,
Qiaoyun is no longer at the Baihua Pavilion.
Some time ago,
the manager said
she wanted to redeem herself
and has returned to her hometown.
You said Qiaoyun redeemed herself?
Who paid for her?
The manager didn't say.
I don't know where she got the money.
Even her maid ran away with her.
Then why did you lie to me that she was receiving guests?
Warrior,
men are competitive.
I just wanted you to spend more money
on other girls.
So he's helping his lovelorn brother
get back at them.
How dare you, Lin Mo.
Using power for personal gain.
Let's see how I punish you when we get back.
It's understandable.
Since Qiaoyun has redeemed herself,
I won't bother her anymore.
Let's leave it at that.
Master Lin,
I've caused you trouble.
The monster threat in Baihua Pavilion is right under the Emperor's nose.
We can't let it grow.
I need to find some clues.
Since we're here,
let's not rush to leave.
Let's look around.
Dammit.
Okay.
You guys look around.
Go.
Take your time talking.
Take your time.
Which girl has Young Master Lin set his eyes on?
Tell me.
I'll help you check her out.
Strange.
Why should I feel guilty?
I didn't do anything.
Why is she always so aggressive
and I have to cower?
No.
I have to stand up for myself.
Okay.
Then I'll have to trouble Miss Su
to help me pick carefully.
It just so happens that my mansion
is missing a
beautiful concubine.
Lin Mo.
Are you asking for a beating?
Get back inside!
Ouch!
Go back!
Help me!
I didn't do anything.
Ouch! Wait.
Ouch.
It hurts!
Slow down.
What are you doing?
Just now,
at least two groups of people were going to attack you.
More than that.
I sensed
people from three directions
exposing their killing intent.
I...
Who did I offend?
The new policies we implemented
have offended too many people's interests.
Then,
can we know
which family those people who attacked me
belong to?
Even an idiot can figure it out.
The imperial court has nationalized the salt industry.
The price of salt has dropped significantly.
Who would be the most furious?
It's the Zhang family of Yunan.
How do you know?
Qiaoyun's father
reported the Minister of Revenue, Li Xian,
for colluding with the Zhang family,
taking bribes,
and inflating salt prices.
That's why he ended up dead.
Then let's start with the Zhang family.
Wifey.
You...
Who is your wife?
You need to find Su Wuhui quickly
and have her use the Heavenly Secret Talisman to find Qiaoyun.
She is the breakthrough to deal with the Zhang family.
Such little tricks.
I can do them too.
Why is there no reaction?
You're out of practice, aren't you?
If the person is too far away,
they cannot be tracked.
I see.
Miss Su,
try Qiaoyun's maid.
Her name is Zhiwei.
Zhiwei.
I'll try again.
Found her.
In Fengming City,
near the county office.
Let's go.
You don't practice orthodox Taoism properly,
but dabble in these unpresentable evil arts every day.
What kind of potion did my eldest brother give you?
In the Beijing royal family,
who doesn't secretly collude with the demon race?
Only you, Chu Xiao'er, are an exception.
How did you know my whereabouts?
Baihua Pavilion.
Baihua Pavilion is an intelligence point under the First Prince.
It's time to collect some reward from my brother.
Every victim
has been drained of their essence,
their hearts ripped out,
and there's a trace of demonic aura left on their bodies.
It seems
it can be confirmed as the work of a demon.
This is already the sixth case.
Do these people have any common characteristics?
The drunk homeless man you found earlier
might be the first victim.
It seems the demon's first crime
was somewhat clumsy.
The others are both men and women,
all over twenty-five or twenty-six years old.
The oldest
is no more than forty-five.
These people are from different social classes,
I really can't find any commonalities.
If it's just to improve its cultivation,
then it probably wouldn't be picky,
or only target the lower-class commoners.
Don't move.
Behave.
Who is she?
This girl
has been wandering around the entrance of our county office for days.
She was spotted by the runners again today.
No demonic aura,
no cultivation.
An ordinary person.
Why did you come here?
Do you have a request,
or nowhere to seek justice?
Prime Minister Lin.
With the current situation,
don't you have anything to say?
Mr. Zhang,
what do you want me to say?
Not to mention the Empress nationalizing the salt industry
and then drastically reducing the price,
leaving us with almost no profit.
There's also the Tui'en Order.
My brothers and sisters
have already started getting restless.
Prime Minister Lin.
I came this time
representing the aristocratic merchant guild,
to discuss with you
how to respond next.
Do you know why just now
I stopped you from attacking Lin Mo?
Isn't it because you, Prime Minister Lin,
don't want to bring trouble upon yourself?
After all,
you are also in this Baihua Pavilion.
Yes,
that's only one aspect.
Do you also know...
Who was the woman that just dragged him out?
Could that woman be
Her Majesty the Empress.
The guard beside her
is named Liu Wancai.
Liu Wancai?
The Commander of the Shadow Guards?
Yes.
Moreover,
the Empress now holds the Shanhe Sword.
If she decides to strike,
people like you
won't survive for dozens of breaths.
The Zhang family
will just be the next Xue family.
It seems
that in this capital,
using force
is exactly what the Empress wants to see.
In our future actions,
we must not be too radical.
That's right.
Regarding the Tui'en Decree,
although we can't stop her from enforcing it,
you can reduce
the number of your siblings.
It's not like you haven't done it before.
Chancellor Lin.
Let's not talk about business today.
Let me toast you.
Come.
Please.
Judging by your scent,
the cosmetics you use
shouldn't be cheap.
Why are you wearing rough clothes?
If you have unspoken difficulties,
why don't you tell us?
Maybe we can help you.
I pay my respects to Your Majesty.
Long live Your Majesty.
You are the Empress.
You may rise.
Remember to keep it a secret.
I obey the decree.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Benefactor Lin,
you're really amazing.
Feng Yong,
are you used to being the prefect?
I am terrified, Your Majesty.
Miss Zhiwei.
Brother Li,
where have you been?
I went to Luoxian Town to be a bodyguard.
The boss paid me a lot this time.
I figured after this job,
I'd have enough money to redeem Qiaoyun.
But when I came back,
Qiaoyun was gone.
Miss Zhiwei.
Qiaoyun wouldn't leave for no reason.
And you,
disguised yourself
and hid near the Jingzhao Prefecture Office.
What exactly happened?
Brother Li,
you must avenge my lady!
What did you say?
Qiaoyun?
What happened to her?
My lady
was killed by a monster from Baihua Pavilion.
Miss Zhiwei,
I am from the Great Qian Dynasty,
Lin Mo, Deputy Minister of Dali Temple.
I'll take this case.
Tell me everything you know.
Leave no detail out.
Okay.
Song Qiaoyun!
Song Qiaoyun,
open the door!
You're a prostitute,
yet you want to act like a chaste woman?
You don't sell your body or your skills.
What do you want?
Free food and drinks?
You spend all day with your low-class lover,
having fun in there,
don't you?
Do you think this is still your Song Residence?
This madam is going too far.
Forget it.
We'll be able to leave in a few days.
Just endure it a bit longer.
Get out here right now
and serve the clients!
Still not opening the door?
You must be having fun with your lover in there!
You can say whatever you want about me,
but don't you dare insult him.
You don't deserve to.
Baihua Brothel actually produced a chaste woman.
Are you still that
daughter of the Chancellor of the Directorate of Education?
Enough, Yaoniang.
You don't need to mock me.
I'm buying my own freedom today.
It's no use coming to me.
You need to find the boss.
Fine.
Then I'll go find the boss.
The boss is in the attic.
You'd better go during the day.
She doesn't see guests at night.
Sister Qiaoyun.
Didn't Yaoniang say not to
see the boss during this time?
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
I don't want to stay here for another moment.
The boss is eating.
She's not asleep yet.
Let's give her the money and leave.
Boss!
Didn't I tell you
not to disturb me at this time?
Song Qiaoyun.
Your recklessness has doomed you
and your maid.
This heart of yours,
I will gladly take it.
Zhiwei.
Sister Qiaoyun.
No.
Hurry.
Run.
No.
Qiaoyun.