( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
That's how things happened.
I tried to find Brother Li but couldn't.
I was afraid of exposing myself if I reported to the officials.
It seems
the culprit behind the recent heart-digging cases in the capital
is the master of Baihua Tower.
Judging from the wounds on the body,
the killing method
is rough and stiff.
It doesn't look like an innate demon,
but rather a human
who took a demon core to transform into one.
The killer is very smart.
The crime scene is far away from Baihua Tower.
And she didn't attack the guests,
clearing Baihua Tower of suspicion.
Your Majesty,
I will deploy troops immediately
to encircle and suppress Baihua Tower.
Liu Wancai has already gone.
You set up a cordon around the area
and evacuate the civilians.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let's go
to Baihua Tower.
Wait.
I need to go to Dali Temple.
I need to confirm something.
My lord.
Here are the records you requested for the former Chancellor,
Song Qing's service record,
and his confession after being convicted.
He hanged himself in prison.
He had two children,
one legitimate daughter,
Song Weier,
and Song Yuner.
Song Weier, Song Zhiwei...
Song Zhiwei is Song Qing's legitimate daughter.
Qiaoyun is the illegitimate one.
Could it be that
she disguised herself as Qiaoyun's maid in Baihua Pavilion
to protect herself
as a safeguard?
Keep this matter
to yourself.
It's trivial.
Exposing it
might just make the girl feel guiltier.
My lord.
I promise to keep it a secret.
His Majesty has personally gone to Baihua Pavilion.
I believe there will be results soon.
It's not that simple.
After Zhiwei
escaped from Baihua Pavilion,
the exposure of Baihua Pavilion's affairs
was inevitable.
But they didn't take any action.
Don't you think
it's unusual?
You mean...
Seeing Zhiwei escape,
they should have either fled
or disbanded Baihua Pavilion.
That would be the normal course of action.
But they are operating as usual.
Either they have someone backing them,
or
they have a grand scheme.
We have investigated everything we can.
I need to confirm it in person.
Let's go.
Okay.
What's going on?
Master.
If we attack by force,
the commoners inside won't survive.
Wow.
Not even pretending anymore.
Taking hostages now, are we?
How many commoners are inside?
Nearly a hundred.
They are all Fengming City citizens
spending money at Baihua Pavilion.
Those who can afford to spend here
usually have unusual statuses.
They really gave us a tough problem.
Not even hiding their demonic aura.
How arrogant!
If you touch me,
ten commoners inside will die.
Wuhui.
Fall back.
Mr. Lin,
you're finally here.
My name is Yaoniang.
Today is our boss's birthday.
Please
attend the banquet.
Invite me to a banquet?
Am I close to your boss?
Of course.
Back then, Mr. Lin
even had a marriage contract
with our boss.
Liu Ruyan?
Her?
This isn't in the book.
Wait.
Did you read the book carefully?
It's Emperor Ruyan!
I am a Silver Tier reader!
That was indeed an early foreshadowing.
The later story hasn't been updated yet.
The plot has indeed completely changed.
Mr. Lin,
please enter Baihua Pavilion for the banquet.
You can bring three companions.
I'll be waiting for you.
By the way.
Our boss also said,
the soldiers should
retreat ten meters away.
Otherwise,
every two hours,
a guest will be killed.
Pass my order.
Retreat ten meters.
Yes.
It seems
they want to settle it with us
in this Baihua Pavilion.
Honey,
Liu Wancai,
Su Wuhui,
Li Dashan and I will go in.
Yes, Master.
I will definitely protect you.
In your dreams.
Li Dashan,
you and the other two brothers go back to guard the Mo Residence.
Beware of sneak attacks.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Don't be capricious at this time.
They are trying to lure you in.
I know.
They have such confidence.
They didn't close the door or run away.
They blatantly use witchcraft to harm people
and challenge my authority.
They must be supported by Beijing forces.
If I retreat,
I am not worthy of being the empress.
Inside here,
it's no less than a second Lin Residence.
It's full of danger.
I won't allow you to have any accidents.
That day,
you risked your life
and went into the bronze coffin to find me.
Now,
I won't let you take risks alone.
Why are you talking to me like an ancient person?
You always ruin the atmosphere.
Okay.
When you are stubborn,
no one can beat you.
Let's go.
Together.
You have to protect me.
Your Majesty.
Benefactor.
Return in triumph.
Triumph.
Location:
Baihua Tower, Fengming City.
Monster: Hair Demon.
Weakness: Unknown.
Mission: Eradicate the demon.
This time it's a Hair Demon.
Subdue the Child of Destiny.
Child of Destiny.
Kid,
this monster is very powerful.
You guys need to be careful.
Welcome, Young Master Lin.
Please take a seat, everyone.
Are you guys okay?
What's wrong with these people?
Breathing is normal.
They are conscious,
and not under an illusion.
Then why are they all sitting so upright
and not talking to anyone?
Could it be that
these guests are not dead?
Please take a seat, Young Master Lin and your three companions.
The banquet is about to begin.
They are afraid of violating the taboos,
so they don't dare to make a move.
It seems
we need to know the taboo rules here
to play with them.
Magic isn't restricted here,
nor is my cultivation sealed.
To hell with the taboo rules.
Let me take down this madam first.
Liu Wancai, don't!
I forgot to tell you,
violence is strictly prohibited here.
Otherwise,
you will end up like him.
This is also a taboo.
Please take your seats, you three.
We are about to start.
Wait.
Don't sit down yet.
Why do you keep insisting
that we take our seats?
What if we don't sit?
The guests here won't answer me.
And they don't communicate with their tablemates.
This means
talking and communicating are taboos here.
If you violate them, you will be punished.
As for the other empty seats,
the seating is obviously irregular
and uneven.
They are clearly not reserved for guests,
but the original guests
have disappeared.
The missing guests
disappeared precisely because
they violated the taboos.
Exactly.
But we have been talking all along.
Why haven't we violated the taboos?
That's because we
haven't taken our seats yet.
Once we sit down,
it means we accept their rules.
Not bad, kid.
I wanted to see
how you would break into this demon tower.
I didn't expect you to figure out the rules so quickly.
You're a formidable young man.
Young Master Lin,
is indeed a genius
who became a top official overnight.
With such insight,
I am truly
impressed.
You are right.
After taking a seat,
guests are not allowed to talk.
That is the rule of this round.
Yaoniang,
how about we make a deal?
What's going on?
So many soldiers.
They are not even hiding their demonic aura.
They want a direct confrontation.
Brother,
you are being reckless.
It's her.
Miss,
this area is under martial law.
Please go back early.
My lord,
what's happening ahead?
Why are there so many soldiers?
The government is handling a case.
Unauthorized personnel shouldn't ask.
Go back early.
Go find Lin Mo.
He definitely has a way.
Mother.
My son,
what is it?
Mother,
Baihua Pavilion has shown its hand.
She just came back from Luoxian Town.
Others will definitely make a move.
Mother,
the Empress has already found out.
According to the spies,
the Empress and Lin Mo,
along with Su Wuhui and Liu Wancai,
her two trusted aides,
have all entered Baihua Pavilion.
How long have they been in there?
It must have been
sixteen to eighteen hours.
Heaven is truly helping our Zhang family.
Several hours outside
is only one hour inside Baihua Pavilion.
Su Ningxue,
you are truly fierce.
Baihua Pavilion threatened the lives of the guests,
only allowing the few of them to enter.
The Empress left the soldiers outside to guard,
and only took three people inside.
She certainly has the courage and responsibility of the late Emperor.
What a pity.
You, Su Ningxue, are not my daughter.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't mind you being the Empress.
Mother,
there is also some bad news.
My cousin Zhang Mu and Minister Lin
are also in Baihua Pavilion.
They seem to be hostages now.
What?
Zhang Mu is there too?
Please calm down, Mother.
I will find someone to figure out a way right now.
There's no need.
Once this demon realm is opened,
unless a winner is decided,
it is very difficult to break its rules.
Mu,
I hope heaven will bless you.
I wonder what kind of deal
Young Master Lin wants to make
with me.
Tell me all the taboos of the first level.
We will
play with you.
Young Master Lin,
do you take me for a fool?
You don't have to take a seat.
I don't mind waiting.
The flow of time in the Hundred Flowers Pavilion
is already different from the outside world.
It's much faster here.
How much
faster?
One hour here
is equivalent to three or four hours outside.
But the flow of time for our bodily functions
remains the same.
Which means,
if we keep waiting,
these guests
will soon die of starvation.
Exactly.
We have Qi-Restoring Pills,
but these commoners don't.
I see.
How vicious.
However,
it's not a big problem.
Kid,
it's best not to use
this parchment roll now.
This parchment roll is effective
for half an hour.
It should be used at the most critical moment.
You haven't found the master of the Hundred Flowers Pavilion yet.
If you use it now,
she will realize the rules have been altered
and prepare in advance.
Let's change the stakes.
You tell us all the rules and taboos,
and we won't attack you.
This young lady is even more reckless.
Didn't you see
what happened to the one just now?
I know Liu Wancai's temper best.
He doesn't get angry easily.
You used tricks
to provoke his emotions
and force him to act early.
It was just
to force us apart,
right?
Liu Wancai was teleported somewhere else.
That's right.
He should have been teleported
to his own level.
You three
really make me look at you in a new light.
Cut the crap.
Make a decision quickly.
Otherwise,
we will attack you together
and then teleport to join him.
Wifey.
Awesome.