( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
The light is on.
Should we knock?
What do we say if we knock?
We just tell the truth.
We are doing this for our benefactor's safety.
Let's take a peek first.
It might be awkward if it's someone we know.
Makes sense.
This...
Isn't this too wild?
Sounds like more than one person.
Look at him.
The princess of Daqian is his lover.
And he has several more in this house.
Look at the gap between you two and him.
Are you done?
I'm different from our benefactor.
I only have love and devotion for Qiaoyun.
Boss.
Is there a possibility,
that the pony you can't bear to ride,
someone is riding it hard,
and whipping it?
You...
You sons of bitches!
You want to break up the gang, right?
Master!
Master, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll drive these two bad women away right now.
Come with me.
Lin Mo,
come back with me to see my lady.
Why are you so nosy?
Lin Mo,
give that thing to me quickly!
In your dreams!
Alchemist of Beijing,
Tianji Pavilion invites you for tea.
Let's see if you have the ability to do so.
Master.
They all force you.
Only I feel sorry for you.
Stop!
Don't!
Ladies.
If you don't stop,
this bed is going to collapse.
It seems like a four-person game.
Let's go.
It's none of our business.
Help!
Someone is going to die!
It's our benefactor calling for help!
I don't care anymore!
Go in!
Benefactor Lin!
Are you okay?
Lin Mo.
You can run, but you can't hide.
We have plenty of time.
Hanging out with him won't be peaceful.
Think it over carefully.
Where is your boss?
The previous boss.
Waste of breath.
Young master.
Come.
Xiaoying.
You go back first.
Let me be alone for a while.
Is this the side effect of recklessly changing the rules?
Why is it the three of you?
You.
Didn't you go to Baihua Pavilion
to look for that Qiaoyun?
Did you find her?
Benefactor.
Don't mention those two words again.
What is going on?
Fortune hides in misfortune.
The breakthrough lies in Baiyong.
To overcome this crisis,
you must unite as one.
There is fortune in misfortune,
but misfortune can also hide in fortune.
Your Majesty returning safely this time
is truly a blessing.
But you should still be even more careful.
Breaking the Baiyong deadlock.
I don't quite understand it.
But the latter part
should refer to me and Lin Mo.
This bastard
is quite useful at crucial moments.
Master,
I'm back.
So?
Is Han Xiaoying up to no good?
Yes.
I knew it.
That manipulative bitch is restless.
Master,
there's more.
What?
The nerve!
She dares to steal from me.
Go,
investigate more,
and report back.
Yes.
Are you saying
that Qiaoyun has been acting out of character lately,
taking clients overnight,
and refusing to see you?
There's nothing wrong with this tea, right?
We're even now, right?
I am now Han Qingyun's sister,
Han Xiaoying.
Let the past
be the past.
That's very gracious of you.
I'll drink this tea first.
That's more like it.
We're all on the same side now.
Li Dashan,
let me ask you.
From the time you entered Baihua Pavilion until you left,
you never saw Qiaoyun at all,
right?
How can that prostitute be so heartless?
My brother truly cared for her.
That's right.
Every time my brother went to see her,
they only talked.
He never crossed the line.
The drinks and overnight fees,
he still paid in full.
Even though he often used my money.
You didn't need to say that.
By the way,
Xiaoying,
let me ask you something.
Based on your experience,
and I mean all of your experience,
if a woman and her old lover
are deeply in love,
but suddenly one day,
she turns against him without warning
and refuses to see him.
In this situation,
what do you think the reason might be?
One possibility
is that she has met Mr. Right,
who makes her fearless of death,
and makes all other men in the world
look like nothing but dust to her.
Impossible.
Qiaoyun looks,
well, she looks
just average.
Besides,
when it comes to singing and dancing,
she knows nothing.
Lao San,
you shouldn't judge a book by its cover.
That's not fair.
She has been reading and writing since childhood,
and has excellent calligraphy.
People who go to Baihua Pavilion
don't care about that.
What about the second possibility?
She has something she can't talk about.
Mr. Feng,
go ahead.
Qiaoyun is the daughter of a criminal official.
After she was sent to the Music Bureau,
she was temporarily transferred to Baihua Pavilion.
Although her father is dead,
his influence is still there.
Like those officials and such,
anyone with a little connection
dares not mess with her.
What's more, Qiaoyun only sells her art, not her body.
So no one pays attention to her anymore.
Only a reckless guy like my brother
would seek her out to drink and chat.
You guys don't understand.
Actually,
Qiaoyun is a very lonely girl.
So,
if she refuses to see you,
it doesn't necessarily mean she has a new lover.
There might be another reason.
Benefactor.
Then what's the reason?
How would I know?
You have to ask her directly.
Please help me, benefactor.
I just want to know her attitude in person.
Get up.
Sit properly.
Stop calling me benefactor.
It's so awkward.
I can only try.
I don't know if my new identity will work.
Li Dashan thanks you, Young Master.
These three reckless kids are clinging to me.
I might as well let them help me find
clues about nearby demons.
It's been a while since I got a mission reward.
By the way.
Recently, there are demons killing people in Fengming City.
Every victim
had their heart ripped out.
Help me investigate secretly.
As soon as you find any clues,
tell me immediately.
Never act on your own.
Young Master.
Yes, sir.
Somehow I got three more underlings.
It seems my intimidation as an emperor is not enough.
Everyone acts so arrogant.
Sword, come.
Interesting.
This is...
the Shanhe Sword!
His Majesty is recognized by the Shanhe Sword.
How many years has it been
since the Shanhe Sword appeared?
Even if the late emperor wanted to hold the Shanhe Sword,
he had to pray
and kneel.
His Majesty can directly summon the Shanhe Sword!
His Majesty rules the world
and commands the land.
Our Great Qian
will prosper!
This attitude is acceptable.
Please rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
My dear ministers,
I assume you already know
about the Luoxian Town incident.
Within our Great Qian,
such a tragedy actually happened.
Do you have nothing to say?
I am ashamed.
The Demon-slaying Army is less than a hundred miles from Luoxian Town.
They can get there in half a day on horseback.
Feng Yong, as the governor,
actually has no right to dispatch troops.
Minister Wang,
why is this?
Your Majesty,
the Demon Quelling Army
is the main reserve force of our Daqian
to resist foreign enemies and demons.
Unless it is an emergency,
they cannot be mobilized casually,
unless
there is a handwritten edict from Your Majesty
or an order from the Ministry of War.
Bullshit.
Luoxian Town is almost becoming a devil's den.
If this is not an emergency,
what is?
Your Majesty,
I am a minister of the country,
and I must exercise my power according to the law.
Otherwise,
the country will be in chaos.
You are so stubborn.
Fine.
I won't waste my breath on you anymore.
Pass on my decree.
Wang Ke, Minister of War.
Due to your dereliction of duty,
Luoxian Town was overrun by demons.
Also, because you rigidly adhered to dogma
and stubbornly refused to adapt,
you missed the best time for rescue,
causing the tragic deaths of countless people.
You are punished for multiple crimes.
Men,
throw Wang Ke into prison,
to be executed after autumn.
As for his family,
the men will be exiled,
and the women sent to the Jiaofang Division.
Lord Wang,
if you don't want to leave with dignity,
I can help you with that.
Anyone who dares to plead for him
will be considered an accomplice
and punished equally.
Yes.
In this novel,
Daqian is a deeply corrupt dynasty.
Su Ningxue is tyrannical and despotic.
To change the fate of certain death,
the court's discipline must be revitalized.
This is so hard for me.
Lord Lin.
How are things?
Have you been well these days?
I didn't expect
you to be the Deputy Minister of the Dali Court.
Status is not important.
Serving the world
is what matters most.
Yes.
I read some of the files.
The cases are truly appalling.
The Dali Court
indeed has a heavy responsibility.
was established by the Empress.
Do you still think the Empress is incompetent and tyrannical?
Merely establishing the Dali Court
doesn't prove anything.
I know.
Because of what happened in Luoxian Town,
you resent the Empress.
She actually has her own difficulties.
Actually, I know all this.
Daqian
is still being coveted by Beijing.
Internally, noble clans are in power,
and powerful ministers dictate.
Her decrees don't even leave Taiji Palace.
The Empress has barely been on the throne for two years.
She is completely stripped of power.
I didn't expect
you to see through all this.
So what?
No matter how they fight,
the commoners are the ones who suffer.
This empire belongs to her.
If she can't solve it...
Who else can solve it?
Who says it can't be solved?
Be prepared.
Reform
usually comes with bloodshed
and sacrifice.