( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
My dear Minister Lin.
You always look sleepy.
Did you not sleep well last night?
Your Majesty.
I did go to bed late
last night
because of official business.
Then Minister Lin,
you must take good care of your health.
I
will need your help
to implement the new policy.
New policy?
I learned from the Luoxian Town case
this time
that not only are there demons causing trouble,
but also a group of
domestic forces sucking the blood of the people,
which are the noble chambers of commerce
and the aristocratic industries.
Does the Empress dare to take action against them?
Does she no longer want the throne?
Take the Lin family's salt industry for example,
the cost is obviously low,
but it is sold to the people at an exorbitant price.
It's these noble families
that monopolize it behind the scenes.
With such matters,
I don't want them to continue running rampant.
So implementing new policies
is urgent.
Your Majesty,
how do you plan to reform?
If the methods are too forceful,
you may
face unbearable opposition.
Please think twice, Your Majesty.
Lin Youtang,
let me ask you,
is this empire the empire of the Five Surnames and Seven Clans,
or my empire?
What's wrong with Her Majesty?
Is she confronting the noble families?
What should we do?
What can be done?
Your Majesty,
please forgive my insolence and presumption.
I do not want to deceive you.
Speak.
I pardon you.
Your Majesty,
as long as you do not anger the noble families,
this empire
is your empire.
Lin Youtang,
how insolent!
As the Prime Minister of the country,
how dare you be so rebellious!
Prime Minister Lin,
apologize to Her Majesty at once!
It's fine.
My lords,
when you studied to pass the imperial exams,
you more or less
had their help.
However, Minister Lin,
your answer is wrong.
This world belongs neither to the prominent families
nor to me.
This world
belongs to the people.
Your Majesty is right.
Yes.
Your Majesty is absolutely right.
Your Majesty,
Beijing is eyeing us covetously,
and demons are running rampant.
It is truly unwise to antagonize the prominent families further.
Of course, we can't be too radical.
My reforms are very mild.
I believe they
will like them.
May I ask who came up
with this new policy?
Of course,
Her Majesty came up with it.
As for me,
I am responsible for perfecting the specific steps.
I didn't expect Her Majesty
to have such a grand strategy.
She wants to change this country
more than anyone else.
But
it takes time,
and talents like you and me.
Lord Lin.
Her Majesty's move
is an overt scheme for the ages.
However, in the future,
there might be a drawback.
What drawback?
Prime Minister Lin, you may speak.
Your Majesty.
In your Decree of Favour,
it stipulates that all children, legitimate or illegitimate,
can all inherit land and family property.
This
can indeed greatly divide
the overall strength of the powerful families,
making it hard for them to unite.
Your Majesty's brilliant scheme,
I
am in complete awe of it.
However,
in the long run,
as those children have more children,
the land they receive will become less and less.
If this continues...
I know what you are going to say.
You worry that in the long run,
they will prey on the common people again.
And then carry out massive land annexation.
Right?
Your Majesty is wise.
Isn't there a second volume?
The solution
is right in this second volume.
So,
this policy means
no more poll tax.
Instead,
whoever owns more land
pays more tax.
This can also force those heirs
to divide their family businesses
to avoid monopolies.
Coupled with opening mutual trade,
encouraging merchants
and fair competition,
it will stimulate domestic capital circulation.
The core principle
is to redistribute resources and wealth.
Lord Lin.
I am willing to serve His Majesty
and Lord Lin faithfully,
doing everything in my power
until death.
Finally got it done.
Not bad.
The signs of national ruin are no longer evident,
but danger still lurks everywhere.
Brother.
Xiaoying,
what brings you here?
I brought you some food.
Why are you sweating so much?
It's a bit hot in here.
Lord Lin,
has my sister caused you any trouble?
No.
Once I find a new place,
I'll have her move out.
We won't bother you anymore.
Brother,
I'm not going anywhere.
Didn't you promise Mo Xiaolan
to protect Master Lin?
Besides,
the master needs a maid to wash his clothes and cook.
Sister,
I know how you feel.
But don't forget,
Lord Lin's lover
is a member of the royal family.
So what?
Even a princess can't serve the master
hand and foot every day.
Alright.
Those houses of mine
need some life in them.
Just stay there and don't worry.
Li Dashan and the others moved in a long time ago.
I have things to do.
I'll get going.
Master,
where are you going?
I'll go with you.
You can't go to that place.
I'm leaving.
Where is he going?
It seems to be some Baihua Pavilion.
What?
My husband really has some skills.
He handled these old foxes with just two booklets.
It seems this method is feasible.
Your Majesty,
may I ask,
who came up with this new policy?
I gave the general direction.
Lin Mo perfected the specific details.
Alright.
I am tired.
Go back and take your time reading it.
Secretariat,
draft the specific regulations.
It will be implemented on a chosen date.
I obey your command.
Dismiss the court.
Farewell, Your Majesty.
Long live the Emperor.
What are your orders, Chancellor Lin?
Before this matter is officially announced,
it must be kept strictly confidential.
Yes.
Don't tip off the aristocratic families yet.
If word gets out,
those family heads
will be assassinated by their children first.
Yes.
I will keep it strictly confidential.
Go to Yonghua Palace
and tell Consort Hua about this.
Yes.
I will do it right away.
My Empress,
who gave you such an unparalleled strategy?
No one is guarding you this time, right?
Auntie.
Someone asked me to give you this just now.
Little girl.
Remember to call me sister next time.
What's wrong with this old guy now?
The spring water has finally increased.
Your Majesty,
although the national crisis has been resolved,
danger may lurk within good fortune.
Please do not be careless.
I know.
Uncle.
Why don't I
see Wuhui today?
Recently, there are monsters in the capital
harming the people
and eating their hearts.
Wuhui is investigating overnight.
I have sent her more men.
Let's go.
To Lin Mo's place.
Master.
Lin Mo
is not at home.
Where did he go?
He went to
Baihua Pavilion.
You bastard.
Are you itching for a beating again?
Come out, everyone.
Hiding in the bushes
must be uncomfortable, right?
Princess Xiao'er.
Knowing the letter was forged,
you still dared to come.
I was just curious about
what you want to do.
Princess Xiao'er, please hand over Shamo Zu,
so that we
can go back and report.
Will everything be fine if I hand over Shamo Zu,
or are you going to
silence me as well?
Your Highness Xiao'er,
we are just following orders.
I have no intention of fighting my brother for the throne.
I even hid all the way in Daqian.
Can't he show some mercy?
Your Highness Xiao.
Ever since you went to Luoxian Town
to scheme for the Shamo Ancestor,
there was no turning back.
All right.
Then it's a fight to the death.
Everyone,
give His Highness a quick death later.
Do not humiliate his royal body.
This is...
The Yinsha Bride of Luoxian Town.
The Shamo Ancestor has indeed fallen into your hands.
These evil spirits
were all refined by this banner.
They are extremely powerful.
Let's attack together.
Don't hold back.
Keep one alive to talk,
and kill the rest.
I will activate the Yin-Yang Reversal Array
to greatly weaken the evil spirits.
Time is limited.
Finish them off quickly.
What?
A slingshot?
Such a child's toy.
You must meditate for this array
to change the surrounding power of Yin and Yang.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
you can't use it.
Damn stinky Taoist!
If you don't activate the array,
I can't hold on much longer!
Brother,
give some money to the procuress.
Just say we want to see Qiaoyun
without delaying their business.
Second Brother,
why don't you use your money?
My money is saved for you to marry a wife.
Baihua Pavilion
Monster: Unknown.
Weakness: Unknown.
Hint: Unknown.
Mission: Eliminate the monster threat.
Wow.
Those that make it to the quest board are all great monsters.
This Baihua Pavilion is something.
This is...
I am the Chief Minister of Dali Temple.
I'm here to investigate a case by imperial decree.
Please cooperate.
Are you sure he went in here?
The Shadow Guards
saw with their own eyes
that he, Li Dashan, and another person
went in together.
Once I figure out the spinning machine,
all these prostitutes
will go to the factory to make clothes.