( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Spells
can kill people.
What do you mean?
Spells
can really kill people.
When did you learn it?
Three years ago.
Niu Dali raped me.
After the neighbors found out,
they gossiped about me.
The gossip was suffocating me.
I didn't dare to step out of the house.
I could only lock myself indoors all day.
Usually,
my father had to go out for work.
Being a famous shaman in the village,
she was often not at home.
That day,
I noticed Dad's pants were torn,
so I went to Mom's room for a needle and thread.
But normally, I am never allowed inside.
After entering the room,
I saw a dusty little wooden box.
I blew the dust off
and opened it.
Inside, apart from a few straw dolls,
there was a record of an ancient spell.
As long as you know the target's name
and get their hair,
you can use this spell.
Kill the other person
with the Mind-Losing Curse.
So,
you are here to confess today.
Fan Le
and Niu Dali,
you killed them both using curses.
And my father.
Come with me.
You are just soiled goods now.
You are going to the brothel with me
to get some money back, Mother.
Come with me. I'm begging you.
Begging me? Go to hell!
Are you okay, Mother?
Mother, get up. Let's go.
Xuanli!
Let me go!
That night
was the first time I used the curse.
The next day,
I received news of my father's sudden death.
At first,
I thought it was just a coincidence.
So I hid this box
and didn't dare to touch it again.
Until a few days ago,
when Niu Dali was released.
How have you been lately, sir?
Not bad.
Thank you for visiting me so often, sir.
It's getting cold.
Put on some extra clothes.
It's you.
Bitch.
Back then, you pretended to be a decent woman,
valuing your reputation of chastity.
You insisted that I knocked you out,
which caused me to suffer in prison.
Now that I'm out of jail,
I never expected to run into you in this brothel.
What happened?
You ended up in a brothel as a prostitute?
It's a pity the law only gave you three years,
while it ruined my entire life.
Speaking of those three years, it makes me furious.
Calm down, sir.
Is there a misunderstanding? Let me tell you,
I'll make you pay me back properly today.
Let me go!
Then,
why did you kill Fan Le?
After Niu Dali left, I used the curse again,
but Fan Le saw the whole process from outside the door.
So Fan Le went to Niu Dali's house,
not to return the money,
but to verify if Niu Dali was dead.
If he was really dead,
it meant killing with curses was real.
But I don't believe curses can kill.
I didn't believe it at first either.
I thought even Niu Dali's death
was just a coincidence.
Until
I learned about Fan Le's death.
I felt both joy
and guilt.
They all deserved to die.
But I am
also a murderer.
So I came
to turn myself in.
What a bizarre way to kill someone.
I'd like to try it.
Try it?
How are you going to try it?
Kill me with your curse.
If I don't die,
it proves you're lying.
Name.
Hair.
Are you really going to try it?
Seeing how confident she is,
wouldn't it be terrifying if it's true?
Don't jinx it.
Speak less.
Don't worry.
Jueming.
Jueming!
Jueming, what's wrong?
Jueming.
Are you okay?
Jueming!
Stop it.
Stop!
Jueming, I just started shaking the rattle drum.
If the drum beats fast, the heart beats fast.
If the drum stops, the heart stops.
You really do have this ability.
Good.
You have the motive,
and the means to commit the crime.
Men,
come here.
Escort her back to the county office.
Come, pinch his philtrum.
I'm fine, really. Quick, pinch his philtrum.
I'm really fine.
What's wrong?
What is this?
Fan Le took Zhao Xuanli's money.
He should have hidden it at home,
but we searched the whole house and found nothing.
Perhaps he felt it was too conspicuous at home
and hid it elsewhere.
The curse in the wooden box was taken from her maiden home.
If Zhao Xuanli can kill with curses,
then her mother probably can too.
That makes sense.
Su Lang! Father,
Quickly send someone to arrest Zhao Xuanli's mother too.
Official business. Step aside.
Hurry.
What's going on? It's quite scary.
What are they doing?
Zhao Xi,
Niu Dali,
and Fan Le.
I killed them all.
Where did you sell Xuanli?
You should at least tell me where.
Tell me.
Where did you sell Xuanli?
Let go.
Yichun Brothel.
You are her own father.
Do you think
I wanted to?
I worked so hard to raise her.
I thought she could marry into a good family,
and get me a better bride price.
I didn't expect
her to be such a burden.
I...
If I didn't sell her to Yichun Brothel,
who else would want her?
Are you speaking human?
When you're out there,
don't you also talk nonsense?
I went back to my room,
made a straw man,
took his hair while he was fast asleep,
and put a curse on him
to cause his death.
As for Niu Dali,
he was the one who hurt my daughter.
I've wanted him dead for a long time.
But I just couldn't see him,
and couldn't get his hair.
You wanted to get his hair.
There is a record of her visiting Niu Dali in this visitation log.
Is that true?
So that day,
you went to...
I went to get his hair.
That room.
Niu Dali.
Niu Dali!
Who is it?
I brought you some food.
Come and see.
Hurry up and eat while it's hot.
Do we know each other?
Yes.
I am Zhao Xuanli's mother.
Niu Dali,
you ruined my daughter's chastity! Someone come!
I will make you pay with your life! Guard!
Someone is trying to kill me! Come out! I will kill you!
Niu Dali!
Go! I will make you die a horrible death!
Niu Dali! Kill her!
You will die a horrible death! This crazy woman!
Right, I remember now.
That did happen.
The officer on duty that day told me about it.
So that means you
didn't get his hair that day.
If I had gotten it, I wouldn't have waited until now.
That day,
Niu Dali went to Yichun Pavilion,
and I happened to see him.
So I found someone to get close to him
and take his hair.
Using the same method,
I ended his life.
What about Fan Le?
He shouldn't have blackmailed my daughter.
When I got home,
I used the same spell to kill Fan Le.
That's strange.
Before you,
Zhao Xuanli just confessed that she was the real murderer.
She used spells to kill three people.
She learned her spells from me.
Besides a name and hair,
you also need
to sacrifice your own blood.
She didn't know this at all.
So she thought her spell succeeded.
Actually, I completed the spell at the same time.
I am the real murderer.
How can you prove that Zhao Xuanli's spell didn't succeed?
You took the lives of those three.
Because I created the spell.
Do you really believe in spells?
Don't you believe it?
If you don't believe it,
Zhao Xuanli
is not the murderer.
If you do believe it,
then I am the murderer.
Newcomer,
what's your name?
Refusing to speak, huh?
You look quite pretty.
Such a pretty face,
it'd be a pity
if it gets ruined.
Drag her over there.
Put her up there.
Once you enter my place,
even if the King of Hell doesn't want you,
you'll have to beg him to take you.
Are you going to use illegal torture?
If you really killed someone,
it won't be that easy for you to die.
Later,
I will personally change it for you.
That dress.
Boss.
Mother!
Get in.
You...
I have confessed.
I killed him.
It has nothing to do with my daughter.
She was wronged.
You can let her go now.
Don't let this dress
soil my daughter's body.
Xuanli,
how are you...
At your age,
you should be married and have children,
living a life like other women.
Blame me for being too cowardly back then,
making you end up like this.
Live well after you get out.
Here they come.
Freshly baked hot sesame cakes.
Here, smell how good they are.
What a fragrant sesame cake.
Here,
you and the young lady share one. This is too big for me.
Jueming, let's share one.
Have you ever encountered such a bizarre case before?
When I was young,
it was a spectacular scene with flags fluttering and drums beating.
I followed Chief Catcher Qin,
and there was no magical case we didn't solve.
Then in your opinion,
between Zhao Xuanli and her mother,
who is the real culprit?
You lack vision.
You always ask such specific questions.
Let me tell you first.
I found this shaman to be truly miraculous.
What do we care about most in our line of work?
Coming and going safely, right?
So that day,
I wore plain clothes to the temple to pray
and ask for a peace amulet for everyone.
Right after I finished praying and stepped out of the temple,
I saw that shaman standing there.
Our eyes met.
I suddenly felt a special connection.
I walked over,
and she immediately told me what I prayed for
and what I asked for today.
That amazing?
Let me tell you,
when I went out to pray that day,
I didn't even tell your mother.
How do you think she knew what I was going to pray for?
Right?
So,
this shaman
is really magical.
Chief Catcher Su,
Actually, for this shaman to know what you prayed for
is very simple.
Because she has many followers
who pretend to be commoners and blend in.
Then when you kneel on the cushion and pray,
they will listen closely
to what you are praying for.
When you come out,
the followers will tell the shaman.
Then the shaman met you.
Judging by your outfit,
you must be a master.
I have been waiting for you for a long time.
Waiting for me?
If it were someone like me,
I wouldn't say my prayers out loud.
I'd just recite them silently in my heart.
How would she know?
Right.
That's also very simple.
There are so many pilgrims going to the temple every day.
She just needs to catch one or two
to make a fortune.
Oh no.
I'm doomed.
I bought so many of these peace amulets from her.
You each have one, right?
I gave them all to you.
I have one for myself too.
I've been fooled.
She completely scammed me out of my money.
Constable Su,
peace amulets are for peace.
It doesn't matter who sold them to you.
What matters is our intention.
Right.
So according to what you said,
you don't believe the shaman has the ability to foresee the future.
You don't believe she can kill with curses either.
She can't.
Neither can Zhao Xuanli.
That's not right.
When Zhao Xuanli cast the curse that day,
you were clearly in pain.
Does it still hurt?
I was pretending.
I just wanted to test her
to see if she really believed her curse could kill.
If she was lying herself,
when I felt sick,
she would have shown a hint of surprise.
But her expression was calm at the time.
This shows she really believes she knows curses,
rather than lying.
You brat, you're quite sly.
I don't believe that in this world
curses can kill people.
But what if they do exist?
Isn't it too dangerous for you to do this?
Then I wouldn't die either.
She said it herself.
The curse requires a name and hair to match.
It has your hair,
and the name Jueming written on it.
Since you are so certain
that Zhao Xuanli is not the real killer,
why did you take her to the government office?
To show the suspect, of course.
Fan Le took Zhao Xuanli's money,
so he must have hidden it at home.
But when the four of us went to his house that day,
there was no money in the house.
This shows one thing:
someone must have arrived at the crime scene before us.
We need to find this person.
So Zhao Xuanli's mother was just taking the fall for her,
and she isn't the real killer either.
Then the real killer must be related to Zhao Xuanli.
Let's go right now
and investigate all the social connections
of Zhao Xuanli's family.
Wait for me to finish this bowl of porridge!
Solving the case is more important. Let's go.
Then take a pancake.
Here, take a pancake with you.
I'll go buy you a hot one,
fresh out of the oven.
Safety comes first,
and cases can wait.
You always forget that.
The porridge is cold. I'll go heat it up.
No,
why do I feel like Zhao Xuanli is the killer?
Her mother is a sorceress,
just a fraud.
Her father is a gambler.
How good can a child raised by them be?
The law is based on facts.
We can't just rely on subjective assumptions.
How about this?
Let's think again.
What do these crime scenes have in common?
The victims' pupils
were all dilated.
There was a fallen bucket next to Niu Dali's body,
and there was a fallen kettle next to Fan Le's body.
This shows they experienced extreme thirst before they died.
With these symptoms,
it's highly likely they were poisoned by datura before they died.
The suspect poisoned them.
Once poisoned by datura,
one will experience blurred vision,
extreme thirst,
a rapid heartbeat,
and hallucinations.
They most likely chose to commit suicide while hallucinating.
I got it.
What are you doing? Where are you going?
To test the poison.
How do you test the poison?
Hey.
This is the datura flower.
What are you doing?
Taking a small amount simulates the poisoning.
After I pass out later,
remember to pour licorice and mung bean soup into my mouth.
Aren't these mung beans?
Isn't that a stove?
Mother.
What's wrong?
Are you all right, Jueming?
Mother,
I missed you so much.
Don't be afraid.
It's all right.
As you two know,
the men who come here are either looking for pleasure
or entertainment.
They might be intimately involved with the courtesans,
even acting desperately in love.
But to have them commit murder for anyone?
That is absolutely impossible.
Does she have any special regular customers?
There is one.
He always asks for Zhao Xuanli.
He also came to ask me about redeeming her
and how much money it would take.
I just gave a random number,
and he noted it down.
What is his name?
Jixiang,
a laborer at Jinxiu Silk Workshop.
He came today.
I told him Zhao Xuanli went out early in the morning.
So he left this wooden box with me
and said to give it to Zhao Xuanli when she returns.
A wooden box.
You're awake.
You're finally awake.
You scared me to death.
Look at how many bowls of mung bean soup I've fed you.
And you also had so much licorice.
I was really afraid you wouldn't wake up.
Thank you.
You scared me.
Do you want some more?
Are you okay?
Are you still hallucinating?
Did I say any nonsense
or do anything stupid?
No.
By the way,
The effect of this Datura flower
can temporarily incapacitate a person.
So it's impossible for him
to commit suicide.
I see.
Why didn't I think of that?
Did Zhao Xuanli's father die at home?
Where are you going?
You haven't fully recovered yet.
Hurry up. The lord is looking for you.
Hurry up.
What's the matter, officers?
Tell the lord what you saw.
Speak.
A man was knocking on the door just now.
He left when he saw no one inside.
What does he look like?
About this tall,
and thin.
With somewhat small eyes.
I was just about to look for you two.
I found a suspect here.
His name is Jixiang.
He went to Yichun Brothel to look for Zhao Xuanli.
And he even asked the madam
how much it would cost to redeem Zhao Xuanli.
Jixiang?
Yeah.
He came looking for Zhao Xuanli today.
Found she wasn't in the room.
Xiao Li, come here.
Coming.
Not only that.
Back then, when Niu Dali assaulted Zhao Xuanli,
he was the one who reported it.
We found out Jixiang works at Jinxiu Silk Workshop.
So we went to the workshop.
When I saw him,
I realized he was the one who reported the case three years ago.
Let's go to Xiao Li's house for a few drinks after this.
Okay.
Officers.
Someone is raping a young girl.
Where? Over there.
At that time,
he said he was on his way home,
saw Niu Dali's beastly act,
and hurried to report it.
But just now,
when he learned that Zhao Xuanli and her mother both turned themselves in,
he seemed very surprised.
How is that possible?
Killing with curses?
Officers, you actually believe that?
Of course we do.
She confessed,
and explained the details of the crime very thoroughly.
I suspect this Jixiang developed feelings for Zhao Xuanli.
He just committed the murder for her.
So I used talk about believing in curses to trick him.
Alright, you don't need to say so much.
Her mother is definitely an accomplice, no doubt about it.
We can go back and close the case.
It's just that,
these days,
there are all kinds of ways to kill.
We've checked carefully.
When Fan Le and Niu Dali died,
he was working in the silk workshop.
So he didn't have time to commit the crime.
Constable Su.
Where is Zhao Xuanli's house?
Here.
Constable Su.
Did Zhao Xuanli's father also fall here back then?
Right here.
I know the suspect's method.
Call Zhao Xuanli and her mother back.
I want to recreate the crime for them.