( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Be careful.
Did you think of anything?
The suspect left no clues.
We can't analyze it through kinship
or who benefits most from the victim's death.
Even if I really guess who it is,
if he doesn't commit another crime,
it will still become an unsolved case.
Come.
That's the guy. Let's go.
Boss.
Give us three baskets of steamed buns.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Back then,
Constable Qin also tracked the case to here.
Later, the murderer stopped committing crimes,
so there was no follow-up.
If you can guess who the suspect is,
we will send someone to keep a close eye on him.
Enjoy your meal, you three.
Okay.
And the plan I proposed before,
it's worth a try.
Let me go.
Stop it. Go.
My lady.
Are you okay?
Behave yourself.
Raise your head.
Uncle Liang.
How could it be you?
Why did you kill so many people?
Everyone says you love your daughter dearly.
How could you harm Liang Chuyi?
Because Liang Chuyi saw the mask he wore when committing the crime.
You also killed Su Xiang.
Why did you kill Su Xiang?
Brother Liang.
Su Xiang.
Did you see the masked man?
No.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help Constable Qin catch the masked man.
He is right over there.
He won't get away today.
These people,
these women,
you killed them all, right?
Why?
Let me go.
Constable Su.
Why did you kill innocent people?
Constable Su, the red strings on them,
those spells,
what do they mean?
Don't move.
I'm cold.
Bear with it.
You can't even stand this little hardship.
Back when I gave birth to you, I suffered so much.
When I finish drawing the spell,
you are not allowed to wipe it off.
Drawing this wealth-attracting spell on your body
is like having a wealth-attracting boy possess you.
This way,
when I go out to play leaf cards,
I will have good luck in gambling.
How did I lose?
It shouldn't be.
How could I lose?
At that time,
before my mother went out to play cards,
she would always draw spells on my back.
Can't you understand human language?
I told you not to put on clothes.
Can't you understand?
When she came back,
If she lost money,
she would beat me up.
I told you to get dressed!
Mom... I told you to put them on!
Stop hitting me! Put them on!
It hurts! Put them on!
If she won money,
she would bring me food.
Mom won a lot of money today.
I brought you some steamed buns.
They're still hot.
Thank you, Mom.
For the next few days,
neither of us will go hungry.
I didn't know if the spell had anything to do with her gambling.
All I knew was that
I completely hated that symbol back then.
Before you were even born,
your father ran away.
I was all alone,
with a huge belly,
risking my life to give birth to you.
But
our life
is getting worse day by day.
I'm leaving.
Mom, where are you going?
To get married.
Take me with you.
If I take you,
I won't be able to leave.
You haven't drawn the spell on my back today.
Draw it now.
You'll win money once you draw it.
Mom.
Please take me with you.
Please don't abandon me!
Don't blame me.
If I don't leave now, I'll never be able to.
Let me go! Take me with you, Mom.
Let me go!
In the end, my mother still abandoned me,
leaving me all alone in the world.
After she left,
I lived a life fighting with wild dogs for food.
Whenever I walked on the street
and saw women like her,
I wanted to strangle them with a red rope,
so they wouldn't have to suffer in life anymore.
Then I'd take off their clothes
and draw that old spell on their backs.
Su Xiang
lived in the West Market.
Every time she went to the East Market government office,
she would take my ferry.
Over time,
we became friends.
That night,
she found out about me.
Having no other choice,
I killed her.
Even now,
I still remember
the last thing she said to me before she died.
Brother Liang.
I know
I probably can't get away.
I hope
I am
the last person
you kill.
The last
person.
From then on,
I never killed anyone again.
I married a wife,
had children,
and lived a normal life.
Then why...
To kill Sister Qiuhua.
Qiuhua went to the dock every day
to collect the boatmen's dirty clothes.
That day,
Qiuhua,
let me help you.
Uncle Liang.
Qiuhua,
you come here to wash clothes every day.
The water is so cold.
Don't hurt your hands.
I won't be doing this laundry work anymore.
Why?
A wealthy merchant has taken a fancy to me.
However,
the condition is that I can't take Zhen'er with me.
I thought about it for a long time.
It's a rare opportunity.
Qiuhua, you're going to abandon Zhen'er and leave with the merchant?
I've suffered my whole life.
I don't want to...
I don't want to suffer anymore.
At that moment,
I remembered my mother who abandoned me.
I felt the urge to kill again.
But what I didn't expect was
that Chu Yi found the tool I used to kill Qiuhua.
I had no choice
but to kill her too,
using the same method.
Suxiang,
Qiuhua,
Chu Yi,
I killed them all.
I am a sinner.
I am guilty.
Jueming Envoy, listen to my order.
The cold case is solved.
The yamen hereby rewards you with five strings of cash.
Because this is an extra bonus,
you can use it to buy whatever you want.
I still feel that this case
was solved too smoothly.
Isn't smooth good?
It's too strange.
Uncle Liang had already silenced Liang Chuyi.
Why did he still try to harm you?
Because
killing again
made him addicted.
He used to be that kind of person.
The blood of a villain flows in his veins.
His nature is evil.
Okay.
Let go of me.
It's red.
Logically speaking,
when we caught him,
his reaction should have been panicked.
But he acted too calm.
When we went to his house,
his daughter had died in his house.
When he held her and cried,
that reaction
didn't seem fake.
You're confusing me.
What exactly do you mean?
I mean,
this case is not simple.
There must be more evidence behind it.
Honglian,
don't go out these days.
Especially at night.
Staying at home is safer than anywhere else.
I actually think
Home is more dangerous than anywhere else.
If he forces you to do anything else,
I'll throw him in jail.
Freshly bought mutton.
Smell it.
Smells good, right?
Add it in
to nourish your body.
Isn't Qiuhua's case solved?
Why can't we go out?
Jueming thinks the killer
is someone else.
I don't know if he's right,
but it's better to stay home.
Qiuhua had such a hard life.
Raising Zhen'er all by herself.
She finally found true love,
but then she got consumption.
Her condition kept dragging on.
She didn't have much time left anyway.
Let me do it. Be careful.
Although Qiuhua had a hard life,
she doesn't deserve any pity.
She was going to abandon Zhen'er to enjoy a good life.
How could that be?
Qiuhua wasn't that kind of person.
Besides, Wang Mang would definitely accept Zhen'er.
Wang Mang?
What do you mean?
The two of them...
Qiuhua didn't tell anyone else.
She only told me.
She often washed clothes for Wang Mang,
and over time, they fell in love.
And Wang Mang liked Zhen'er very much.
It's a pity that Qiuhua got kidney consumption.
Even if she wasn't murdered,
I'm afraid she...
Honglian.
Is what you said true?
I...
I have to go back.
The case is wrong.
Look.
These victims,
their hair was all very neat.
But Qiuhua's hair
was very messy.
And Liang Chuyi's hair
was neat again.
Moreover, these suspects...
Twenty-seven years ago, their targets were all young women.
But Liang Chuyi and Qiuhua,
they were both older women.
Why is that?
There's a new development.
Constable Su.
Any clues?
You two guessed right.
Old Liang's little grandson in the country
has gone missing.
When did he go missing?
He disappeared the day after he went back to the country.
I remember Old Liang said
his little grandson has asthma.
With this disease, he needs to have medicine on him at all times.
Wrong.
I was just at Honglian's.
She told me
Qiuhua had severe kidney consumption.
Her lover wasn't some wealthy merchant.
It was Wang Mang.
It all makes sense now.
Someone deliberately kidnapped Old Liang's grandson.
We must search all the pharmacies immediately.
Whoever buys asthma medicine regularly
is the biggest suspect.
Go.
Go upstairs.
Dad, careful.
I searched all the pharmacies nearby.
The owner of this pharmacy told me
someone recently bought a large amount of Shegan Mahuang Decoction
and Dingchuan Decoction.
And this person,
his right shoulder is lower than his left.
Are you okay?
He looks like a porter.
And coincidentally,
this pharmacy
is very close to
Qiuhua's house.
I've had asthma these days
and need medicine.
Uncle Liang's grandson is unconscious upstairs.
Save the child quickly.
He's fine.
I gave him a soothing soup and he fell asleep.
How did you find me?
Uncle Liang told you?
Uncle Liang did as you said.
Indeed, he committed all the murders 27 years ago.
But Qiuhua and Liang Chuyi now,
they were killed by you.
In all the previous murders,
the suspect would carefully dress up each victim.
This detail
is generally not noticed.
I also used this point
to confirm he is the killer of my sister.
Every day since my sister died,
I've blamed myself
and hated myself.
From that day on,
I only have one reason to live,
and that is to avenge my sister.
Later,
I went to Constable Qin to ask about the case.
Since the case was not solved,
out of guilt,
he told me all the details.
The masked man's route was from the pier to the East Market.
He suspected the masked man lived at the pier.
So I've been a porter at the pier since I grew up,
wanting to meet more people
and praying to meet him again.
By chance,
I found a wooden stick on Uncle Liang's boat.
I asked him what it was for.
Uncle Liang told me it was for self-defense
and driving away water snakes.
But that stick
was very similar to the one I saw that night.
Considering Uncle Liang's age matched the killer's,
I started paying attention to him.
I observed that
whenever it rained,
Uncle Liang would go home early.
I checked the boat departures on the day my sister died.
Although it didn't rain that day,
the government opened navigation
and sealed the port.
None of the boatmen went out.
The only thing that didn't match
was that Uncle Liang is right-handed,
while the suspect injured people with his left hand.
So I started testing him.
Once I deliberately fell into the water from his boat.
In the most critical moment,
he reached out his left hand.
Afterwards,
I told Qiuhua the whole thing.
But Qiuhua told me
The government won't accept an old case
without evidence after so many years,
based solely on personal guesses.
Brother Mang.
Before I got sick,
you said you'd marry me.
Is it true?
Of course it's true.
Do you want to bring the real killer to justice?
I dream of it.
I have a way.
What way?
You,
kill me.
Nonsense.
I'm telling the truth.
I won't live long anyway.
Strangle me with a rope.
Imitate the exact modus operandi of the killer from back then.
Then watch Uncle Liang's reaction.
If he is the real killer,
when everyone is talking about
how the killer from back then is striking again,
you try to get information out of him.
His reaction will definitely be different from others.
Then you can report him to the officials.
Say he
killed me.
No.
I can't kill you.
Is there a difference
between living one more day
and ten more days?
If the real killer doesn't strike again,
you'll never catch him.
But I want to help you catch him.
This is the last thing
I can do for you in my life.
I'm dying anyway.
I want my death
to be more meaningful.
I hope
you can help me take good care of Zhen'er.
Can you?
If you don't agree,
I'll die right in front of you.
If you just stab him to death,
he'll never repent.
Bringing him to justice
is the real punishment.
I can't kill you.
I heard that
before a person dies,
hearing is the last sense to go.
So,
please say you love me
in my last moments.
I love you.
Zhen'er.
When everyone started discussing
whether the suspect from back then struck again,
only Uncle Liang said no.
Because in the previous cases,
the victims' hair was tidy.
But Qiuhua's wasn't.
Her hair was messy.
You were extremely shocked when you heard that.
You didn't want to just let him go.
So
you thought of a crueler method.
You made a mask like the one the killer wore
when he killed your sister.
You killed Uncle Liang's youngest daughter.
You killed Liang Chuyi.
They kidnapped his little grandson
and threatened him with the boy's life,
making Uncle Liang take the blame for murdering his own daughter.
Suxiang,
Qiuhua,
and Chuyi.
I killed them all.
Am I right?
Wang Mang.
Have you lived up to Qiuhua's request?
Be good, Zhen'er.
Your mother is gone.
Uncle is leaving today, too.
Take good care of yourself.