( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Constable Qin.
Same MO again.
How many is it?
The third one.
The body was found by the night watchman,
but he didn't see the suspect's face.
Also strangled to death.
There was a fierce struggle before death.
The time of death should be the Hour of the Dog tonight.
By the way,
I remember the night of the first murder.
Was it raining too?
Yes, it was a rainy night.
The suspect always strikes on rainy nights.
The victims are all young women,
and none were sexually assaulted.
After suffocating to death,
they were tied with red ropes
on their backs,
had the same talisman drawn
and were left at the scene.
Constable Qin.
The victims this time are all adult women.
In cases like this,
we all know
the culprit is usually a rapist or a thief.
But all the female victims this time
weren't sexually assaulted.
Instead, they died a tragic death.
I think
this suspect must have a huge grudge against women.
To be able to strangle someone to death with a thick hemp rope
and commit three murders in a row without being discovered,
the suspect is likely a single person,
physically strong,
and an adult male.
Around 20 years old.
Look, everyone.
From the three locations where the bodies were found, we can be sure
that the suspect
is extremely familiar with the route from the city gate to the back alley,
and then to the South Market Pier.
Then
we can narrow down the scope
and focus on investigating single men living alone in this area.
Understood.
Don't worry, Constable Qin.
We'll take action right away.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Recently, on any rainy night,
we must increase patrols
and send more constables
to prevent the suspect from striking again.
I know.
Bring me my sword.
At that time, we deployed more manpower
and searched door-to-door.
Single men living alone
became our prime suspects.
It was raining continuously then.
Whenever it rained,
we would patrol the whole city at night.
But after searching for several days in a row,
we found nothing.
I remember it was sunny that day.
Constable Qin judged that it probably wouldn't rain again that night.
Also, because we had been patrolling during the day
and on duty at night for days,
everyone was exhausted.
Constable Qin prepared a banquet
for us to have a good drink
and relax.
But who would have thought,
the killer struck again that night.
It's like this again. The same as last time.
It's him again. It's terrifying.
I don't understand.
It didn't rain last night.
Why did the killer change his habit?
Rain might be a condition for the murder,
but not a necessary one.
The suspect always commits crimes on rainy nights.
It's highly likely
that it's related to his line of work.
Because of the rain,
he gets off work early and goes home,
giving him time to commit the crime.
Let me in!
Who are you?
He's the brother of the victim, Wang Chun.
He was present during the attack
and identified the killer as a man,
though he didn't see the face clearly.
What's your name?
Wang Mang.
Officer, Wang Chun is my older sister.
I heard she died a tragic death.
But
I still want to see her one last time.
Aren't you afraid?
Wang Chun is my sister.
I wouldn't be afraid of her no matter what.
How tragic.
Officer,
my sister was murdered.
Please, you must catch the killer.
I'm begging you.
Rest assured,
we will get justice for your sister.
It's been so many years,
and these cold cases remain unsolved.
If the killer from back then was never caught,
it's highly likely he'll strike again.
But we can't rule out
a copycat killer.
We can't just assume it's the same person
just because the MO is similar.
It must be the same person.
Look,
this red hemp rope,
the strange binding posture,
and the mysterious talisman on the back.
It's exactly the same as the original suspect.
You said Wang Mang saw the suspect back then.
Is he still alive?
He's alive.
Take me to him.
We've reached the pier.
It's just ahead.
Wang Mang.
Wang Mang, come here.
Constable Su.
Constable Su, any news on the suspect?
We haven't found the suspect,
but we have some other news.
Come, let's sit down and talk.
Constable Su.
Today, we found a female corpse in the East Market.
The victim's name is Qiuhua.
The killer's MO
matches the one used to kill your sister, Wang Chun.
Why are you smiling?
For all these years,
my biggest fear was that he had settled down
and would never commit another murder.
If that were the case,
I'd never get the chance to find out who he is.
So every night I've been thinking,
as long as he dares to strike again,
I'll definitely have a chance to catch him.
When Wang Chun was killed,
you saw the suspect.
Can you tell me the details of what happened back then?
What happened that day,
I will never forget.
Brother, why have you become so unreasonable?
You lied to me, sister.
You promised that if we sold all the radishes,
you'd buy me sugar-coated haws.
Mother is still sick at home.
We barely have enough to eat.
Why do other children have food
but I don't?
I worked harder than them.
Come, get up.
All right.
Come here.
Mang.
I'll buy one.
I won't eat.
You are the best, sister.
There are five haws on a stick.
We can have two each.
And save one for Mother.
Mang, slow down.
Here you go, little boy.
Thank you.
I want this one.
Sister!
The masked man held a wooden stick in his left hand.
He should be left-handed.
About six feet tall.
If I had listened to my sister
and gone home with her
instead of buying those sugar-coated haws,
she might not have died.
Then why didn't he kill you?
Wang Mang.
Yes.
Constable Su, I'm going to work.
Okay, go ahead.
If the suspect was seen by him,
it's highly possible that the suspect's dominant hand has changed.
So this can't be used as a characteristic of the suspect.
It was lucky for him to survive.
It wasn't luck.
First,
he didn't see the masked man's face,
so naturally he wouldn't be silenced.
Second,
look.
The victims are all women now.
Is it possible that women are his target
and he is not interested in men?
This masked man,
does his family sell masks?
I thought of that too.
Back then,
I checked all the vendors selling masks.
There were no suspects.
For so many years,
I've been thinking.
Every time after committing a crime,
the culprit would pose the bodies
in all kinds of strange postures.
And he used cinnabar
to write strange spells on the victims' backs.
There must be a purpose.
I've heard of
a ritual
that can resurrect people.
Could it be that the culprit
held a ritual to resurrect
his dead loved ones?
If it was for resurrection,
why did he wait 27 years to commit crimes again?
Right.
Maybe 27 years ago,
he successfully resurrected his loved ones,
so he stopped.
And 27 years later, someone close to him died again,
so he wants to do it all over again.
According to what you said,
more people will die.
Let go of me.
Let me go.
This is the archive room.
Are all the case files here?
Of course.
Don't mess around.
The file we are looking for is over there.
See?
These are the files left by Head Catcher Qin from his cases.
Head Catcher Qin had a characteristic:
he never forgot any case he handled,
and he would record them in complete detail.
Come, look.
Head Catcher Qin was a meticulous person.
Not only did he have an extraordinary memory,
but he was also skilled at drawing.
He would draw the crime scene every time
for future reference.
These were all drawn by Head Catcher Qin.
Of course.
Do you still remember how Qiuhua looked when she died?
Yes.
Find a portraitist to draw another one.
I want to compare them.
I can draw that too.
Head Catcher Su.
We found another body at the East Market crossing.
The MO is the same as before.
It was done by the same person.
This is Uncle Liang's house.
Alright, arrange some people to set up a defense outside.
Yes.
Uncle Liang.
This is Head Catcher Su, Coroner Li, and Envoy Jueming from the yamen.
Let's go in and take a look.
Alright, let's go check the body first.
The deceased is named Liang Chuyi,
Uncle Liang's only daughter.
Liang Chuyi.
She was married
and they had a daughter together,
who is over eight years old this year.
The deceased is wearing only a red bellyband on her upper body.
Her whole body is entangled with red thread.
Her head and hands are suspended,
and her legs are kneeling on the table,
like a puppet.
Her face is pale
and her eyes are scarlet.
On the deceased's back,
there are incantations drawn with cinnabar.
The livor mortis is quite obvious.
The time of death is more than eight hours ago.
There is a strangulation mark of about one cun on the neck,
appearing purplish-red.
The initial judgement of the cause of death
should be strangulation leading to asphyxiation,
and then posed in this bizarre manner after death.
Although it looks similarly bizarre,
the method is somewhat different.
Look, the body is in a kneeling state of atonement.
Although her facial expression is in great pain,
the corners of her mouth
are forced into a slight smile.
Dying in such pain,
why would she smile?
There is a wooden stick in her mouth.
It should be that inside the oral cavity,
a wooden stick was used to prop open the corners of the mouth.
After being fixed for a period of time,
the muscles would form a rigor mortis in the new position,
thus maintaining this smiling appearance.
Let me go.
Did Qiuhua have a wooden stick in her mouth?
No.
The deceased's body
has the smell of medicinal herbs from boiling asthma decoctions all year round.
Did she suffer from asthma before she died?
Uncle Liang.
I need to ask you a question.
Did your daughter have asthma?
My little grandson does.
Is your grandson at home?
Yesterday,
I took my grandson to the countryside.
My son-in-law happened to be working outside.
So my youngest daughter was home alone.
This morning,
when I came home
and opened the door,
I saw my daughter's body.
I just saw her...
She knew peony cakes are my favorite,
so she went to the street to buy some for me.
Chuyi,
Chuyi...
They died so tragically.
We must catch the real killer as soon as possible,
so they won't have died in vain.
This is how Liang Chuyi and Qiuhua looked when they died.
Jueming,
take a look.
Based on the current clues,
the victims were likely stalked by the suspect for a long time.
After figuring out their home addresses,
he made his move when they were alone.
Yes.
That's what Chief Qin said back then.
This masked man
targets the area from the East Market to the dock.
He strikes after the curfew,
targeting women walking alone.
After succeeding,
he drags the bodies to their homes
or a pre-set location,
and then arranges them like the crime scene.
At night,
he operates exclusively at the dock
and the East Market.
Since he targets women walking alone,
I'll be the bait
to lure him out.
No way.
That's completely impossible.
It's too dangerous.
I actually think Miss's idea makes a lot of sense.
What's there to be afraid of with me here?
I'll follow her to protect her.
As soon as the suspect appears,
I'll catch him immediately.
Nonsense!
Shut up.
Don't bring this up again.
This is absolutely out of the question.
It's way too dangerous.
That's how things went wrong back then.
Chief Qin tried it.
Who was the bait?
Yeah, I never heard you mention it.
That was a few days after Wang Chun died.
At that time, Wang Mang
sat at the yamen gate every day,
urging us to crack this case quickly.
Everyone, list all the livelihoods
that close up when it rains.
Everyone name one.
Farmers. They can't work on rainy days.
I thought of one too.
Fishermen.
If the rain is heavy,
they won't go out to fish.
Coachmen. The roads are muddy on rainy days,
making it hard for carriages to move,
and horses can slip easily.
You're right.
Boatmen.
Water levels rise on rainy days.
The currents get faster.
No one would take a boat.
Traveling merchants,
flatbread stall owners,
and street peddlers
will all suffer damaged goods due to slippery roads in the rain.
So they close up shop.
You're right.
But if that's the case,
the pool of suspects is too large.
No matter how important finding the suspect is,
it's not as important as filling your stomach.
What's this delicious food?
Big meat patties!
Don't fight over it.
Get me one. There's enough for everyone.
I'll have one.
I'll take this one.
Smells good. Try it.
I'll pass.
No matter how urgent the case is, you need to keep your strength up.
Otherwise, how will you catch the suspect?
I don't even know where the suspect is right now.
By the way,
did you see a child when you came in?
Take this meat patty to him.
He must be hungry.
Who is he?
We must focus our defenses on this area.
Su Yu'an.
Hey.
Okay.
Okay, I'll take you there.
Here, take this.
And this.
Oh, this is for you.
It contains mimosa and nightshade.
It helps with sleep and calms the nerves.
Just outside.
Let's take it to him.
So that's the whole story.
I see.
Yeah.
By the way,
you shouldn't go out much lately.
It's really too dangerous out there.
You just said
the masked man only targets women walking alone at night.
How about this?
Let me be the bait.
That way, you can ambush him from the dark.
Wouldn't that be faster?
How can we do that?
It's too dangerous.
Think about it.
A group of constables like you
walking around with lanterns at night...
Only a fool would come out to commit crimes.
But if you hide in the dark,
as soon as he appears,
you can catch him red-handed.
Still no.
It's too dangerous.
Wait.
By doing this,
aren't I also trying to help Constable Qin
close the case as soon as possible,
so he can get a good night's sleep?
Still no.
It's too dangerous.
Wait.
Then spit out my meat patty!
You ate my food,
so you have to listen to me.
You wait outside.
Wait for my news.
I told Constable Qin about Su Xiang's idea.
At first, he didn't agree either.
But we couldn't resist Su Xiang's repeated pleas.
At that time,
we were all eager to solve the case.
I
had the same idea as this brat.
I thought Head Catcher Qin and I could follow behind Su Xiang.
In case the culprit appeared,
we could jump out and protect her.
So,
we chose a night after rain.
But unexpectedly,
it was on that very night
that something happened.
Oh no!
The criminal struck over there.
Let's go quickly!
Miss!
Wake up, miss!
You guys, split up and search.
Yes, sir.
Miss!
Miss, wake up!
Oh no.
Su Xiang!
Take good care of her.
We deployed our men
and searched the whole night.
Until early the next morning,
we finally found her.
Make way, make way!
I forgot to close the door last night.
I came to open the shop early this morning.
When I opened the rice shop, I saw it.
So I immediately reported it.
Head Catcher Qin.
How could this happen?
Here, this is for you.
It can help you sleep and calm your nerves.
How could this happen?
How about this?
Let me act as bait.
That way, you guys can lie in ambush.
Wouldn't you catch him faster?
It's all my fault.
Maybe we alerted the enemy.
After Su Xiang died,
that suspect never committed another crime.
But this case,
I have never let it go.
The sachet shop where Su Xiang worked,
is it still there?
It's long gone.
There must be more clues.
Let's check again.
Let's walk the route from the East Market to the pier once more.
The deceased, Zhang Xiaoqiu.
21 years old.
The youngest daughter of the winery owner.
Lived in the East Market.
Her body was found by a dry well in the East Market.
The victim, Wang Qiuhua,
aged 32.
A washerwoman at the dock.
Lived in a neighborhood near the dock.
Her body was found in her home.
The victim, Su Yao,
aged 19.
The younger sister of a teahouse owner.
Lived in the West Market.
Her body was found in a warehouse at the dock.
The victim, Liang Chuyi,
aged 30.
The youngest daughter of Boatman Liang.
Lived in the East Market.
Her body was found in her home.
The victim, Luo Pei,
aged 20.
The daughter of a fabric shop owner.
Lived in the East Market.
Her body was found
in her home at the corner of the East Market.
The victim, Su Xiang,
aged 20.
The biological younger sister of a sachet shop owner.
Lived in the South Market.
Her body was found in a rice shop in the East Market.
The victim, Wang Chun,
aged 19.
Lived in the suburbs.
Her mother was seriously ill in bed.
Her body was found
in an alley next to a tailor shop in the East Market.
All the bodies were found in the East Market.
And their routes home went from quiet to noisy areas,
passing through various shops,
and heading towards the dock.
The suspect might live around the dock.
A fisherman, a boatman,
or a dock merchant.
Strong and powerful. Not only that,
he's six feet tall and very familiar with the routes between the city and the dock.
He should have been under 30 when he committed the crimes. A local man living alone.
Now he should be around 50.
Su Lang.
According to what Jueming said,
investigate everyone around 50 years old at the dock.
I know who the killer is.