( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
You just said
this matter is definitely suspicious.
Why don't you elaborate?
I'd like to hear your assessment.
I am still unclear about the details of this case.
I dare not jump to conclusions.
That's easy.
Come, follow me.
Why did you faint?
I...
I probably just
haven't eaten in a while.
I am exhausted.
I'll be fine after I eat something.
What about the charred corpse?
It has already been taken to the yamen's morgue.
To prevent collusion,
everyone has been put into small rooms.
Chief Su is arranging for them to be interrogated one by one.
Why was the corpse brought back again?
You are so funny.
Why are you so funny?
You're really afraid of corpses!
I really guessed right.
You're afraid of corpses.
I've been a coroner for so long,
and I've never seen anyone faint at the sight of a corpse.
Why are you so funny?
I heard Wang Mingzhu say
that for all matters in the world,
if they are difficult,
once they come to you,
you know the answer right away.
I am curious.
You can't look at corpses.
Then how do you investigate cases?
I can pretend to be the corpse.
This hand goes up, right.
Left hand goes up too.
A bit shorter, right.
Turn your waist slightly towards me.
Look in this direction.
Where?
Look over there. There.
Are you sure
the head was facing this direction?
Please don't doubt
a coroner's ability to restore a corpse's position.
Then that's strange.
When a person is burned by fire,
out of instinct for protection,
the head should turn inward,
not outward.
She might have been looking at something.
It is said that before the fire started,
people present said
she shouted toward the empty doorway.
Do you think
she saw a ghost?
If she really saw a ghost,
she should have looked at the doorway,
not outward.
Makes sense.
Then what was she looking at?
What did she shout?
Wanrou.
Wanrou is back.
Who is Wanrou?
Wanrou
is my twin sister.
When she was ten,
she jumped into the river and committed suicide.
Why?
Because she was born with a stutter
and extremely uncoordinated limbs.
Born in the Music and Dance Troupe.
Father was the master,
and mother was a dancer.
At that time, I could sing and dance.
So,
my parents always focused their attention on me since I was little,
and neglected Wanrou as a result.
She often felt inferior.
That's why
she couldn't think straight,
and did something foolish.
Nianyao's death
must be related to Wanrou.
Why?
A few days before Nianyao died,
she had seen Wanrou.
These are Wanrou's shoes.
She was wearing these exact shoes the day she disappeared.
Is it true?
Does it mean she crawled back out of the well?
Wanqing!
Why are you here?
I've been here the whole time.
If you are here,
who was dancing at the academy just now?
Who was that?
It's right inside.
Please believe me.
But there's no one here.
Nianyao,
did you see it wrong?
Let's go back.
I just
saw Wanqing
dancing the Shangyuan dance on this stage.
I couldn't be wrong.
Just now,
the costume you saw,
what color was it?
Blue.
In the past,
Wanrou's favorite clothes
were blue.
Stop talking. I'm scared. Let's go, Nianyao.
Since then,
we often heard Wanrou's singing.
She wouldn't sing words,
only hum the tune.
Just like this.
It's okay, sis.
It's a bit creepy.
Nianyao.
Nianyao, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Nianyao?
Nianyao!
Nianyao is
possessed.
The top courtesan can only be me.
I am the only top courtesan.
Whoever tries to take what's mine,
must die.
Nianyao.
It's her.
She really came back.
Since then, strange things kept happening,
and Nianyao became more and more abnormal.
Somebody come quick! Nianyao is dying!
Nianyao.
Nianyao. Nianyao.
Don't be like this, Nianyao.
What should we do?
Nianyao, are you okay?
Snap out of it!
I'll kill you all!
I will kill you!
I am the top courtesan!
I'll kill you all!
What should we do, Wanqing?
I am the top courtesan!
You all have to die!
Nianyao! You all have to die!
Nianyao.
Nianyao, I'm going to kill you all.
Nianyao!
Dongling!
Someone is trying to kill me, Dongling.
Someone is trying to kill me, Dongling. Don't be afraid.
I know about this too.
But as the master of the music house,
I cannot believe what they say.
We can't report this to the authorities,
so we can only comfort them,
telling them that
they heard it wrong
or saw it wrong.
You did the right thing.
I am her mother.
If my daughter could really come back,
that would be great.
Although my parents run the music house,
my job is very simple.
I just need to wait before the dancers go on stage,
help them with their makeup,
and change their clothes and accessories.
Before going on stage tonight,
Qi Nianyao's behavior
was indeed a bit strange.
Wanqing.
Can you tell your father
that I don't want to perform today?
Please? Nianyao, what's wrong?
Wanrou.
Wanrou will come back.
She will come back to kill me, Wanqing.
Nianyao,
don't scare everyone.
Are you just nervous?
I'm not.
Wan...
Wanrou, she will really come back.
She will come back and kill me.
Nianyao, don't scare me.
I'm not lying.
Wanrou will really come back.
Why don't you believe me?
Everyone heard what she said.
But I
didn't tell my parents.
I thought
Nianyao was just under too much pressure.
I didn't expect that going on stage
would actually harm her.
My dear ancestor,
it's late at night,
and there are so many complaints from the people against you!
Shh.
What complaints?
Tonight,
did you smash people's shops?
I was chasing a thief
and accidentally bumped into them.
How about this.
For the people who suffered losses,
I will compensate them three times the amount.
Aren't you a coroner?
Why are you doing the work of a constable, catching thieves?
I work as a coroner
to find clues from corpses
to better solve cases.
This doesn't conflict with catching thieves.
Besides,
everyone is responsible for catching thieves.
That's Moya and Moying, father and daughter.
It's excusable that you didn't catch them.
You...
But you can't always be like this.
Look at what the commoners wrote.
They are all complaints against you. You...
Why is the gold thread from the costume on him?
Bamboo stick.
Help me get a bamboo stick. Thanks. Okay, okay.
Gold powder.
Gold thread.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
It has nothing to do with me.
So you still remember I'm your father?
Your matchmaking with Mr. Xu
has been discussed for a long time.
You are going to meet in a month.
But you
are still here examining corpses.
This is totally unacceptable.
Go home right now
and learn music, chess, calligraphy, and painting.
As a girl,
you should act more gracefully.
Mr. Xu's father
is the Deputy Mayor of Jingzhao.
So what?
My father is the Deputy Mayor of Henan.
Isn't it a perfect match
in terms of social status?
Father, do you still want to solve the case?
I don't want my daughter to be a coroner.
What's wrong with being a coroner?
What's wrong with it?
Getting closer to the corpse means getting closer to the truth.
For all unsolved mysteries,
the corpse will provide the answers.
I just want to be a coroner.
And the best one at solving cases.
Fine, fine.
You want to be the best coroner.
Then tell me,
what cases have you solved lately?
We still have a bet.
Within three months,
if you can't become the best at solving cases,
you will dress up and get married.
Miss Li.
What happened again?
Lord Li, you're here.
Looking for me?
Yes, I need you for something.
Something to do? We are too busy.
We'll leave first. No.
Too many things to do. Let's go.
Next time my father comes to inspect,
remember to come in early and give me a signal
to help me get away.
Understood.
Please come in.
I missed you so much, sir.
What are you afraid of?
We are here to investigate a case,
not to seek pleasure.
Let's go.
Don't go weak in the knees. Let's go. Come on.
Please come in, you two.
If I bring you to this kind of place,
and Lord Li finds out,
I'm afraid I'll lose my job.
Don't be afraid. It's fine.
Have you been here before?
I never come here.
Are these pastries good?
Her osmanthus cakes are especially good.
Boss.
This is really boring.
I'm not having any fun at all.
Mr. Chen.
Why are you not having fun?
There's no curfew around the Ghost Festival.
You must stay a little longer anyway.
Chuntao.
Come here quickly.
Let me introduce some nice girls to you.
Hurry!
Give Master Chen a pot of good wine.
Enjoy your drink.
Have fun, Master Chen. Come on.
What would you like to drink today, Master?
I'll leave it to you.
Dance with more passion.
Smile!
Don't act like the guests owe you money.
Isn't this Constable Su?
What brings you here?
The wind of solving cases, of course.
It's not convenient for me
to come here without official business,
right?
Today,
I'm here to find someone.
Who are you looking for?
There are no suspicious people here.
Does Miss Wang Mingzhu live here?
Are there clues about Wang Kang's cause of death?
We are still investigating.
There are some details of the case we need to ask her in person.
Sure.
I'll have someone take you to her.
That's alright.
I'll take her to the backyard.
We can find her and ask ourselves.
Alright.
You go back to your work.
You seem quite familiar with my place.
Never been here.
My lady,
where is the backyard? This way, please.
This is their backyard.
They usually rehearse here,
start fires,
and cook here.
No men are allowed to come here.
It still feels fishy.
Why are you here?
I live here.
You live here?
You can live here?
Is there a problem?
Have you found the murderer who killed my brother?
Let's sit down and talk.
For now,
we don't have any news yet.
We came today mainly to ask you,
how was the relationship between Wang Kang and Wanqing?
Why did you two ask me the same question one after another?
You also suspect Nanrong Wanqing?
Today in the morgue,
while examining Wang Kang's body,
I found that
his clothes had gold threads from a Jiaofang costume entangled on them.
And there was gold powder under his nails.
I suspect
the last person he saw
was Nanrong Wanqing.
What about you?
What's your basis?
The deceased, Qi Nianyao, told me
she was killed by Wanqing.
You
can see ghosts?
Both the deceased Wang Kang and Qi Nianyao knew Wanqing.
I don't think this is a coincidence.
Let's hear what Miss Mingzhu has to say
about Wanqing.
To be honest,
I absolutely don't believe Wanqing would harm my brother.
They've known each other since childhood,
childhood sweethearts and deeply in love.
It's only because of my brother's low status
that he wasn't a match for the eldest daughter of Jiaofang.
Wanqing tried hard to persuade her parents.
They finally agreed.
The wedding was set for next spring.
Although she is a betrothed wife,
she has long become part of our family with my brother.
The two often interact in private.
I really can't figure out
what reason she would have to harm my brother.
In that case,
that Wang Kang had gold thread and gold powder on him
does make sense.
Constable Su.
Didn't you ask me to arrange someone to watch the Jiaofang
and keep an eye on Wanqing?
It turns out she saw a ghost too.
Saw a ghost?
What?
Do you believe there are really ghosts in this world?
In beautiful clothes,
tapping lightly,
the past is gone.
Sister, you sing
so well.
The doctor said
speaking with something in your mouth
can correct your pronunciation.
Can I
go on stage
with you?
You can't.
You can't even speak clearly.
How can we sing on stage together?
Okay.
Our Wanqing is really good.
She dances well, indeed.
Wanqing really
did me proud today.
Today, the Luoyang Magistrate kept praising Wanqing's singing.
Maybe she can go to the Court of Imperial Sacrifices in the future.
Court of Imperial Sacrifices?
It's too hard to get into the Court of Imperial Sacrifices.
If Wanqing could go to the Taile Bureau under it,
that would be great too.
Yes.
Alright, Wanqing, go change your clothes.
We will take you to a banquet.
Go now.
Who do you think this child Wanqing
takes after?
Takes after me.
Yes, takes after you.
Sister! Sister!
Nianyao, did you see Wanrou?
She said she was going to the river.
I don't know what she wants to do.
Wanqing! Wanqing!
Wanrou! Wanrou!
Where could they have run off to? Where do you think these two children could go?
Wanqing!
Wanqing! Wanqing!
Wanrou!
Wanqing! Wanrou!
Wanqing!
I found Wanqing!
Come.
Let me look at you.
Are you okay?
Qinger!
Where is Rouer?
S-Sister, play with me.
S-Sister,
p-play with me.
Sister, p-play with me.
S-Sister,
p-play with me.
Sister!
Sister, p-play with me.
Wanqing, Wanqing.
Are you okay?
Why is this guy here again?
Someone is helping you solve the case,
and you still get the credit.
What's wrong with that?
I think he has an ulterior motive.
Shut your mouth.
The bronze mirror can really reflect ghosts.