( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
The boat is back.
The boat.
Look.
Where is the head? Why is the head missing?
There is no head.
Master.
Uncle.
He...
Amitabha.
County Defender Zhang.
Everyone here
cannot retreat.
When Anlan Dam collapsed back then,
the flood swept away tens of thousands of folks.
We make sacrifices every year,
but something still happened.
Amitabha.
Catcher Pei,
this is bad.
Something happened in the temple.
Junior Brother Huaian's
head is gone.
Sinful. It matches.
Sinful.
It matches.
What matches?
A vengeful ghost is claiming lives.
Don't talk nonsense here.
Go.
My Lord, you don't know.
When Anlan Dam collapsed back then,
the flood destroyed the village,
and I was responsible for poling the boat to transport people.
During the trip, a young boy suddenly grabbed the edge of the boat,
begging to be saved.
That small boat couldn't hold one more person.
The people on the boat didn't dare to save him,
and the boy refused to let go.
They forcibly drowned the boy in the water.
Some time ago,
I had a dream.
In the dream, my house was flooded.
Old woman.
I beg you.
I didn't harm you.
Look for them.
It's them.
Who are they?
Perhaps it was out of a guilty conscience.
Afterwards, one became a monk.
One made sacrifices every year.
And another one
became a local official.
Since it's a dream,
it's not proof.
At first, I also thought it was a dream.
When I woke up, I asked my wife.
She said she was cooking porridge in the outer hall,
and there was no sound at all in the inner bedroom.
Look.
How to explain these scratch marks?
I'm not lying.
There is a cold aura on the scratch marks.
It must be caused by a vengeful soul.
Since all three murders started from nightmares,
then we should go to his house to catch the ghost.
Whether there is a ghost in his house,
I can tell by smelling.
You can smell ghosts?
Why can't I smell them?
Others can't smell them.
I can make it reveal itself by following the scent.
What a nose.
Interesting.
I want to see
how you catch ghosts.
If you are not capable,
don't blame me for punishing you.
This way, please.
Officer, what's wrong?
Are you Li's wife?
Your husband said he shouted loudly in his nightmare.
Did you hear it?
Help!
What are you doing?
Was it this loud last time?
How could no one hear?
You lied!
I didn't.
I clearly did.
If he was lying,
why would he tell the nightmare
and drag himself into a murder case?
In your dream,
did you find anything different in this room?
No.
Think again.
I had a string of prayer beads under my pillow.
But I couldn't find it in my dream.
Amitabha.
Old man.
There is no water mark on the furniture.
And the prayer beads were missing in the dream.
It seems that it's not a ghost's doing,
but someone's trick.
The key to this mystery
is hidden in some corner of Yangzhou City.
If there is an identical room in this world,
then all the unexplainable things
can be explained.
The two rooms can't be too far apart.
Otherwise, when his wife finished cooking porridge,
she would have noticed he was gone.
And it must be in a remote place.
So his shouting wouldn't disturb others.
It can be seen that
this place is rarely visited,
detached,
and uninhabited.
Not far from here,
there happens to be an abandoned tower.
How is this possible?
Exactly the same.
It really exists.
Then who is the murderer?
Isn't it easy to find the murderer?
Don't we have Li Laogao's testimony?
Let's reconstruct his dream.
Li Laogao,
I'll play you.
You play the water ghost.
Play the water ghost with you.
Old woman!
Buddha bless me.
It's not me.
It's them.
Who are they?
They are Monk Huaian,
Cao Dianniang, and County Defender Zhang.
I... I'm just a boatman.
It has nothing to do with me.
Really nothing to do with me.
You have only yourself to blame.
You held on tight to the edge of the boat,
and the boat almost flipped over.
If we let you on,
the boat would definitely have sunk.
None of us would have survived.
The boat wasn't full.
The boat was full!
There was really no room left.
It wasn't full!
Nonsense! There was absolutely no room on the boat!
There was room.
No, there wasn't.
There obviously was room!
Where was the room?
If there was room, why didn't you let him on?
There wasn't any.
Answer me, why didn't you let him on? Tell me!
If you got on, what about the other four?
Did you want them all to die? If there was room, why didn't you let him on?
Where was the room? Why didn't you let him on?
If you got on, four people would die.
There was also a chest on the boat.
A chest.
If they
threw that chest away,
would there be room?
Would he be able to get on the boat?
Wait a minute.
There wasn't an argument like this in the dream.
How did you know there was a chest on the boat?
Because when the crime occurred,
you were also there.
You witnessed them committing the crime with your own eyes.
But it was too dark for you to see their faces clearly.
Years later, you accidentally overheard Li Laogao muttering to himself,
"It's my fault."
You learned that he was the boatman from back then.
Knowing he wouldn't reveal a thing while awake,
you found an excuse to visit his house.
You secretly memorized the dimensions of his room,
then returned to the tower,
and built an exact replica of his room.
Then you drugged his wine,
climbed through his window after he passed out,
and carried him to the tower to put on this act.
After he blurted out the truth in panic,
he fainted from fright.
You then carried him back home.
When he woke up, he naturally thought it was just a nightmare.
At the dock,
when you walked up to me,
I noticed that your fingers
smelled of raw lacquer and sticky rice mortar.
And the wooden table in the tower had the exact same smell.
Do you have any proof?
If not,
this is just groundless speculation.
Ma Wei, as a constable,
though you had the convenience to commit the crimes,
conviction
still requires solid evidence.
After you learned the identities of the three from Li Laogao,
you decided to kill them.
You first confronted Huaian.
Plagued by guilt, he confessed everything.
After that, you killed him.
Then, you dove into the river
and waited for a chance to strike Cao Dianniang.
After it was done,
you took off your blood-stained clothes
and threw them into the river.
Then you returned to the government office,
falsely ordered the sedan bearers away,
and catching him off guard,
you killed the county official inside the sedan.
After that, you followed everyone to the dock.
Someone as meticulous as you
must have discarded all the murder weapons,
except for the wooden tally you used to dress up as a water ghost.
I'm afraid it's a relic from a close relative,
so you definitely couldn't bear to throw it away.
Guards.
Search him.
No need.
Boss.
I killed
those people.
Why did you do this?
Because
they killed my
only brother.
That boat was obviously not a small boat,
and there was a big box on board.
As long as the box was thrown into the water,
they could have saved him onto the boat.
But they couldn't bear to part with that box of valuables,
watching helplessly as my brother struggled in the water,
and eventually let him drown alive.
When I saw my brother again,
he had already been salvaged from the shore,
a headless corpse gnawed by wild beasts.
Only the wooden tally on his wrist
could identify him.
Who exactly are you?
I am Jueming,
living in Luoyang.
Father, who are you burning paper for?
For the tens of thousands of people in Dongshui Town, Yangzhou.
Back then,
the Anlan Embankment in Dongshui Town collapsed,
the flood destroyed the whole Dongshui Town,
and your mother passed away.
You have to be a good boy.
Chief Su.
I originally wanted to move my old mother's grave.
I didn't expect that when I asked someone to dig the grave today,
there was an extra skeleton inside.
The gravedigger mistakenly thought it was my family's,
so he moved it back.
My lord, please.
I don't know whose family it belongs to,
so I could only report it to the authorities.
Miss Li.
Coroner Li,
why are you here first?
I heard the report
and rushed here as soon as possible.
We too,
rushed here immediately after hearing the report.
You brought chicken legs from the yamen?
I've checked it, no problem.
Are you craving it, kid?
How dare you talk about your old man?
Coroner Li,
what are the details?
The skeleton is relatively short.
According to the measurement and estimation, it should be about four feet.
Judging from the growth cycle of children,
the height of this skeleton
is consistent with that of a ten-year-old child.
Looking at its slender bones
and light weight,
it should be around forty catties.
Checking its bone development characteristics,
its pelvis is relatively narrow,
so it is judged to be
the skeleton of a girl.
At the skull,
there are obvious signs of being hit hard.
There is also a fracture at the frontal bone.
According to this speculation,
the suspect should be holding a murder weapon,
standing behind the victim,
and slamming the back of her head.
The victim fell to the ground and hit a sharp object with her forehead at the same time.
Look at the condition of the neck bones again.
The suspect strangled the victim from behind,
causing the neck bones to fold inward.
Su Lang.
What's wrong, sister? What do you need?
If strangling face to face,
wouldn't the bones fold outward?
In this case,
would it face downward?
Got it.
Are you okay?
What about the specific time of death?
Based on the weathering of the bones
and color changes, we can tell
the time of death
was eight years ago.
Eight years.
The suspect chose to attack a ten-year-old girl
from behind.
You do it, Father.
He strangled her to death
before even turning her over.
This means
he was afraid of being recognized.
As such,
this was a crime
committed by an acquaintance.
We are acquaintances.
Miss Li.
If you call me that again,
I'll have my father punish you.
Coroner Li.
To deduce so many details
from just a simple corpse,
you are amazing.
Did you all hear that clearly?
Coroner Li has already analyzed the case
very clearly for everyone.
Go investigate right away.
Within a radius of a hundred miles,
find out whose ten-year-old child died eight years ago.
First, identify the deceased,
then through her identity,
investigate all her relatives.
Everyone must be screened.
Understood?
Thief!
Catch the thief!
Follow me.
Safety comes first, the case can wait.
All right, stop staring.
Hurry up and pack the bones,
and send them back to the yamen.
Yes.
This petty thief...
Every family is preparing to worship their ancestors for the New Year,
and even the King of Hell is on holiday and not accepting ghosts.
You sure know how to pick a day.
What are you staring at?
Chase him!
Father, let's split up!
Excuse me!
What are you staring at?
Okay.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
My cart!
Su Lang,
I'm coming to save you.
I'm sorry.
I was careless
and blocked your way to the afterlife.
I'll burn more paper money for you later
to express my apologies.
I'm sorry.
What's going on here?
Everyone.
Don't panic, everyone.
My brother went missing half a month ago.
Apart from the remaining bloodstains at home,
there are no other suspicious clues.
I suspect
that he has been murdered.
Jueming is my friend.
Seeing me worrying all day,
he came up with a plan.
He pretended to be a corpse and lay in a coffin,
hoping to find inspiration for solving the case while being transported.
Since he's been missing for half a month,
why didn't you report it to the authorities?
I did.
But there are simply no results.
Since there are no results,
you should wait at home.
You will be notified naturally when there's news.
What's the use of
you looking for a charlatan here?
Don't panic, miss.
Please recount the details of the case.
My brother, Wang Kang,
has always run the coffin shop at the corner of the street.
He makes a living by transporting corpses.
My name is Wang Mingzhu,
his biological sister.
I usually live at the Yichun Brothel,
and occasionally return home.
My brother has been missing for days,
and the authorities have no news from their investigation.
I am filled with worry and doubt.
The madam saw me looking devastated
and frowning all day,
so she dragged me to the backyard to find Jueming,
hoping he could help me find a solution.
This is my brother's coffin shop.
What my brother used to do every day
was transport these coffins with corpses to the suburbs.
Naturally, the relatives of the deceased
would wait by the road to receive them.
Then they would carry the corpses together
into the mountains for burial.
On the day he went missing,
someone still saw my brother.
At night,
he transported coffins back and forth.
Why are you so sure
that he has been murdered?
This...
This extra pool of blood,
I don't know where it came from.
Previously, my brother and I agreed
to offer sacrifices to our parents before the Ghost Festival.
But he has been missing.
He had never left the shop before.
This inevitably
makes me think too much.
The last time Wang Kang transported a coffin,
he was still seen by someone.
Can anyone testify?
Although I can't see,
my cane did indeed hit
the horse's leg that night.
The horse was startled, and the coffin fell to the ground.
I felt it,
and it was a coffin that fell to the ground.
I knew
I bumped into the coffin transport cart.
I hurriedly apologized repeatedly
and helped him carry the coffin onto the carriage.
My brother's daily route for transporting coffins
was always the same.
Near where the collision happened,
I picked up this piece of coffin wood.
It proves that Blind Zhang is telling the truth.
The route for transporting coffins,
do you know it?
This horse knows the way better than I do.
It can get there,
then it's easy.
Put me in the coffin,
and let it give me a ride.
What does Wang Kang's disappearance
have to do with this coffin transport route?
Blind Zhang.
After you bumped into the coffin carriage that night,
did you touch the corpse?
No, I didn't.
Did the other party complain to you?
No.
He didn't say a word.
He must have been very angry.
You didn't bump into me just now, did you?
This proves
the one lying in the coffin was a living person,
not a dead one.
You mean
the murderer was hiding in the coffin?
Any driver of a carriage
would try to avoid a blind person.
The suspect lay in the coffin,
tying the deceased to the front of the carriage,
giving pedestrians at night
the illusion that the deceased was still alive.
Blind Zhang overturned the carriage,
and happened to knock out the murderer inside.
Sorry, sorry.
Blind Zhang can't see,
he naturally thought
that inside the coffin
was a corpse.
This horse
is familiar with the transport route.
In my opinion,
the place it stops
from where the suspect hid the body
won't be too far.
Good boy.
I'll rely on you to solve the case.
Good boy,
finding this is all your credit.
Here's some grass for you.
Why is he acting so weird,
talking to a horse?
What's his background?
How come I haven't seen him before?
What kind of place is Yichun Brothel?
A place of pleasure.
The people there are either playboys or vagabonds.
How many good people can there be?
For this unsolved case that has baffled the authorities for days,
he actually deduced without any clues from the remains,
the suspect's modus operandi.
He is really something.
Why don't you believe it?
Got it. Right here.
Dug it out. Found it.
How could this happen?
How could this happen? How could this happen?
Next month,
you were supposed to marry Miss Wanqing.
Who is Wanqing?
Nanrong Wanqing,
the eldest daughter of Anning Music House.
Constable Su.
Coroner Li.
Chief Su told you to go to Anning Music House immediately.
Someone died there.
How could it be such a coincidence?
Our music house has been open for over a decade,
and such a thing has never happened before.
Oh my.
Coroner Li,
you're finally here.
Did you catch the thieves?
Look at the masks of these two thieves.
You can tell they are Mo Ya and Mo Ying.
Let's put that aside.
A body was found in the suburbs.
Before the investigation started,
we received news of an incident at the brothel.
How is the situation here?
I just sent the girl's body back to the government office.
I hadn't even warmed my seat
when I got a report
saying that Qi Nianyao, the top courtesan of the brothel,
is dead.
Where did she die?
Hurry!
Come on.
The dance tonight is going to be so beautiful.
Yes.
Good.
It's so beautiful.
It's wonderful.
I told you so.
Really good.
Well danced.
Bravo!
So pretty.
Encore!
Wanrou!
Wanrou is back!
Wanrou is back. She wants to kill me.
She's back.
What?
Wanrou is back.
She wants to kill me.
The deceased suffered extensive burns all over the body.
The skin and flesh are blackened and carbonized,
facial features are indistinguishable,
and nails have fallen off.
But facing one side.
The chest and abdomen are burst open, and deformed organs are visible.
In the oral cavity, nasal cavity, and throat,
there is a large amount of soot.
The cause of death was burning by fire
and inhalation of dense smoke while struggling.
Coroner Li.
Judging from the scene,
it should be that while she was dancing,
the many flames lit around her
ignited her skirt,
causing this disaster.
Is that really how she died?
This is completely impossible.
If clothing catches fire
and the flames grow to burn a person to death,
it takes time.
But everyone clearly said just now
that she was burned to death instantly.
Such a sudden and absolute end,
there must be something suspicious behind it.
Do you have the right to speak like this when the government is handling a case?
Alright.
Who are you?
I am Jueming.
I was just with Miss Wang Mingzhu
finding the bones of her brother, Wang Kang.
I came to Anning Brothel specifically
to inform his betrothed.
Mingzhu.
Is what he said true?
Is my fiancé, Wang Kang,
really dead?
Who killed him?
My daughter.
Alright.
Two murders occurred consecutively tonight,
causing great grief
to the relatives of two families.
As a government constable,
I express my sympathy.
I also promise you
that the government will thoroughly investigate this case
and give you an explanation.
Alright, alright.
Alright, Su Lang.
Yes.
These two are not involved in this case.
Please escort them out first.
Let's go.
Wait.
You just said
there must be something fishy about this matter.
Why don't you elaborate?
I'd like to hear your assessment.