( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Candied hawthorn! Fresh candied hawthorn!
Come and take a look!
Wanqing.
It really is you.
It's been a few years.
You haven't changed a bit.
Buying things?
Just picking out some stuff.
I'll get going first.
You girl, running away as soon as you see me.
Have you forgotten where we last met?
The pier. It was at the pier.
Don't you remember?
It was at the pier.
I... I have something urgent to attend to today.
I'll go back first.
Have a look! Take a look!
Did you report this missing person case?
Old Su.
Stop sleeping. We're on a case.
What is your relationship with the woman in the portrait?
She is my daughter.
Take a look, sir.
There is definitely something wrong with this girl.
I obviously don't know her,
but she answers when I call her.
Jueming.
My wife and I
originally had a daughter
named Jiang Siyan.
Daughter!
Siyan!
Where are you, daughter?
Daughter!
Siyan!
My Siyan!
My dear.
Look.
Is this Siyan's shoe?
My daughter went missing when she was ten.
We searched all the streets and alleys,
but only found a pair of her embroidered shoes
by the moat.
The authorities said she must have fallen into the river and been washed away.
I followed the moat
all the way to the lower reaches of the Tianhe River in the west of the city.
I actually found a girl lying on the bank.
When I saw her,
she was the same age as my daughter.
When she woke up, she couldn't remember anything.
I thought,
maybe this was heaven's will.
Seeing our pitiful state,
heaven granted us a daughter.
I brought her home
and still called her Jiang Siyan.
We raised her,
raising her for eight years.
But
she suddenly disappeared.
Her mother got so anxious
that she fell seriously ill,
and doesn't have much time left.
So, in my desperation,
I rushed over to report the case.
Why on earth do you want me to help you with this?
My deduction shouldn't be wrong.
Where exactly is the problem?
Brat, being disrespectful to me again, huh?
There are so many people on the street.
What are you waiting for?
You two,
please be our witnesses.
We're betting on who will treat us
by guessing the coin.
Yes, be a witness.
Watch closely, just this once.
Just this once.
No more cheating.
Watch closely.
Guess which hand it's in.
It's here.
No, I clearly saw it was in this hand.
Because when you weren't paying attention,
I secretly switched it.
How could you
do that?
I got it.
Wanrou and Wanqing switched more than once.
Why didn't I think of that?
Sister Chunyi, I figured it out.
Thank you for today.
Hold this for me. Bye.
Brat, where are you going now?
Where did you say you found the child?
Downstream of the Tian River in the west.
Tian River.
Isn't that where Wanrou jumped into the river?
When you found her,
did she stutter?
No, she didn't.
She was articulate
and could sing and dance.
Has no one come looking for this child all these years?
I was afraid someone would recognize her,
so I didn't let her go out.
I kept her locked at home.
You...
It's my fault.
What a waste of the child's talent.
Stop.
Let me in.
Stop. What are you doing?
What's going on?
I figured it out.
Let him go.
Let him in.
I figured it out.
The suspect is actually Wanqing.
Go on.
Back then, Wanqing went to find Wanrou.
Wanrou.
Wanrou, Wanrou.
Wanrou acted on impulse
and pushed Wanqing into the water.
She just wanted to embarrass her,
but ended up harming her.
She got scared,
put on Wanqing's clothes and went home.
She always thought it was because of her sister's status
that she was favored by the family.
Little did she know, the moment she put on her sister's red shoes,
she began to bear fear and guilt.
Wanqing.
What are you doing here?
Mother, I- I pushed my sister into the water.
Mother has already lost one daughter. Don't say it.
She can't lose another one.
So she started hiding the truth.
This also explains
why Wanrou, who came back disguised as Wanqing,
because of her stutter,
didn't speak for a whole year,
until she got rid of her stutter.
The drowning girl picked up by a family back then
was exactly Wanqing.
She suffered a head injury and lost her memory.
She went missing a while ago,
and that family reported it to the police.
Sulang, show it to him.
So, after Wanqing regained her memory,
she ruthlessly
killed Wanrou, who had taken her place,
and reclaimed her own identity?
I don't think so.
Wanqing must have thought of a way out.
She would definitely find a place to imprison Wanrou first,
and then kill her.
I might as well tell you,
we are currently looking for
the place where Wanqing imprisoned Wanrou.
Liao.
Bizhi.
Jiu.
I originally just wanted everyone to believe
that it was a ghost causing trouble.
Burdened by your guilty conscience,
you wrote a suicide note,
confessing that you pushed me into the water back then,
admitting that you impersonated Wanqing,
and apologizing with your death.
Unexpectedly, things changed yesterday,
forcing me to sing and dance,
trying my best to prove that I am the real me.
It's ridiculous.
Since you want to be me so much, sister,
in the end,
just die for me.
No.
Her plan has been disrupted by me.
She won't wait anymore.
Wanqing
will definitely force Wanrou to use her identity
to fake her death.
The location
must be where Wanrou pushed her into the water,
Tianhe in the west of the city.
The downstream of Tianhe in the west of the city.
Wang Kang,
Qi Nianyao,
Mother,
are they really all dead?
What do you think?
When I regained my memory
and found out you became Wanqing,
I started to hide
and observe all of your lives.
Hearing you say this,
we were very much in love.
Of course.
Why would you ask that?
Over the past few months,
after learning about your life,
I made a move on you,
didn't you always want to have me?
and then started to enjoy
this life that was supposed to be mine.
I didn't plan to kill him.
He found out I didn't have a burn on my back shoulder,
and that's when I learned your little secret.
So I made a similar one to yours.
Qi Nianyao, I never expected
her to come to me on her own.
Guan family's ball.
Your mother wants to replace you with Dongling as the top courtesan.
Did you know that?
I didn't.
If you don't help me,
I will tell everyone your dirty secret.
What dirty secret?
I saw it clearly when you
pushed Wanqing into the water.
You said
you would always help me be the leading lady.
Do you want to be the leading lady that much?
Easy.
As long as you play along with me,
I will make sure Dongling
won't dare to compete with you.
What about Mother?
I didn't know until yesterday
that she was also protecting you.
Why are you here?
I came to see you.
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Wanrou.
For so many years,
you have never been yourself.
Now you are eighteen.
You can go wherever you want
and do whatever you want.
I chose this hairpin for you.
Do you like it?
What do you mean?
You knew all along
that the one who came back was Wanrou.
How can you face the dead Wanqing?
I am Wanqing.
Sister.
What happened back then
was my fault.
This life is yours,
and I will give it back to you.
After I die,
I just hope you won't harm anyone else.
I've felt guilty my whole life.
I hope you won't keep making the same mistakes as me.
Don't come any closer!
Wanqing,
let us save them.
Don't make any more mistakes.
I understand how you feel.
It was indeed Wanrou's fault before.
But you can't punish everyone
for her mistakes.
What would Mr. Jiang, who has always cared for you, think?
Because of this,
Mrs. Jiang got very sick.
She doesn't have much time left.
Mr. Jiang,
he knelt at the gate of our office,
begging us to find his daughter.
After all these years,
they have already treated you as their own daughter.
If Mr. Jiang saw you like this,
he would hug you
and persuade you to turn back.
I let them down.
He won't come.
You are wrong.
They all love you.
For those who love you,
stop it.
Hurry up and save them.
Hurry.
The one I held at that moment,
though a murderer,
was also a poor soul swallowed by darkness.
We got them!
Come up quickly.
Eight years ago,
we lost our child.
Her mother went mad.
Siyan, if you are not good,
Mommy will be angry.
Good Siyan.
Good Siyan. The doctor suggested I raise the foundling
as Jiang Siyan.
This might help alleviate her mother's illness.
After thinking it over,
this might be the best choice.
I took her back,
forged a fake notice,
and lied that she was our lost daughter,
Jiang Siyan.
Child,
do you remember everything I told you?
What is your name?
Jiang Siyan. I'm 10 years old.
I got lost making sugar skewers.
Good child.
Come, Dad will take you to see Mom.
Siyan, it's getting cold.
Mom will make you a pretty floral dress.
Dear, look who's here.
Look who I brought back.
I found our daughter.
Siyan, come closer.
Let Mom get a good look at you.
No.
She is not my daughter.
Siyan, hurry, call her Mom.
Mom, I am Siyan.
Go away.
My Siyan
doesn't look like this.
It's not like this.
No.
Dear, look.
Isn't this our daughter Siyan?
Look how much she resembles her.
This is our daughter.
[Missing Person Notice]
Mom, you asked me to learn to make sugar skewers.
Come back early after you're done.
I also said I would bring you a skewer
to see if it's sweet.
Right.
[Missing Person Notice]
Come, hurry up and tell Mom.
What did you do the day it rained?
It rained that day.
I got lost
and lost my shoes.
Let Mom see.
Why aren't you wearing shoes?
Are you cold?
Where are your shoes?
Dear, I found her shoes.
Let Mom put them on you.
They are on.
Mom, is it sweet?
Sweet, very sweet.
Siyan.
My daughter.
Where did you run off to?
Mom couldn't find you anywhere.
Don't run off anymore.
You mustn't run away.
Don't run off.
Mr. Jiang.
Based on what you said,
the real Jiang Siyan was very likely murdered back then.
I happen to have the skeleton of a little girl here.
The pelvis is relatively narrow,
identifying it as a female child.
Based on the weathering
and color changes of the bones,
the time of death is estimated to be 8 years ago.
Do you want to identify it?
The style of these clothes.
It belongs to my daughter, Siyan.
I remember
she was wearing these clothes when she left.
This one isn't.
My daughter doesn't have this one.
Siyan doesn't have it.
Siyan,
who killed you?
Lord Li,
Lord Li, I beg you.
Tell me,
is this my daughter Siyan?
Who killed her?
You must catch the killer
and avenge my daughter.
I beg you.
Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Jiang, please get up. I beg you to catch the killer.
My daughter,
I'm taking you home.
Rest assured.
I will definitely catch the killer.
Don't rush.
I want some too.
There's enough for everyone.
Don't choke.
Drink slowly.
Thank you.
Thank you, ma'am.
Don't push. There's more.
I want another bowl.
Okay.
Here.
So delicious.
Who are you looking for?
You work with Constable Narisu.
I'm here for Jueming.
Did that brat get into trouble again?
No.
Not at all.
I just came to talk to him about a case.
You scared me.
Have a seat.
He'll be back in a while.
Alright.
Thank you. Drink up.
You haven't got any, have you?
Is this his room?
This mustard greens porridge is Jueming's favorite.
Do you want to try some?
Sure, thanks.
Here.
It's delicious.
Here, have a taste.
Thank you.
Drink slowly too.
Don't choke.
Mmm.
It's delicious.
No wonder they like it.
The osmanthus cake I make is also Jueming's favorite.
You can try it next time.
Has he lived here since he was a child?
I really feel for the boy Jueming.
When he was seven,
his mother was murdered in the pharmacy.
The case remains unsolved to this day.
Jueming became an orphan after that,
and had to work at such a young age.
I felt sorry for him,
so I let him stay in the backyard
to sweep the courtyard.
But Jueming is also a smart boy.
Once,
Miss Xianglan gave him some pastries she made.
Jueming.
Eat something.
Xianglan,
The wealthy Merchant Ma you usually entertain is not a merchant,
but a scholar.
How do you know?
He has a childish face,
and there are ink stains on the pads of his index and middle fingers.
He usually likes to show you his poetry collections.
His family must be strict,
valuing reputation,
and fearing criticism.
You just need to praise his poems,
and he will be happy.
He was actually right.
Xianglan received a lot of tips since then.
After this spread,
Jueming became the most popular person
in Yichun Brothel.
However, the tips the girls gave him,
he saved them every time.
I only found out today
that he wanted to buy back the old pharmacy.
The pharmacy?
Yeah.
Do you know where the pharmacy is?
Of course.
Is there any place in Luoyang that I don't know?
Oh, this house
has been lived in by several families.
You
are quite sentimental about your home.
You saved money for so long
just to redeem this house.
Give me the land deed.
What's the rush?
Did you bring enough money?
Enough.
It was this price a few years ago.
But now, it's more than that.
Didn't we agree?
I give you eight taels of silver,
and you give me the land deed?
Back then...
Back then, it was because no one wanted this house.
Look, so many years have passed.
I've put a lot of effort into it,
and finally someone moved in.
I informed you right after they moved out.
If it's inconvenient for you,
I'll just put the house on the market.
Wait.
How much do you want now?
Twenty taels.
Twenty taels?
This isn't a price increase.
This is extortion!
Why are you here?
This lady
looks like a wealthy one.
Good eye.
Show me the land deed.
If you don't show it to me,
how do I know this house is yours?
What are you doing?
Robbing the land deed!
Robbery! Robbery!
Don't come closer! Give it back to me.
Stop yelling!
This purse
is mine now.
Too much, right?
Enough, enough.
Then this house is yours.
Farewell.
Wait.
Don't you want your mother's pharmacy back?
You saw Sister Chunyi?
I...
Look, he has the house deed.
He can raise the price however he wants.
Besides, housing prices in Luoyang keep going up.
You definitely can't save money that fast.
You paid for it. It's yours.
Wait.
I haven't finished speaking.
Let's make a deal.
Come to the yamen and help me investigate cases
to pay off your debt.
I see that you
have a clear mind
and are suited for investigating cases.
You're full of talent.
As for your looks,
you're quite ordinary.
Perfect for our yamen.
I heard
the allowance for a constable in the yamen
is about ten taels a year.
How about this?
I'll help you solve cases.
Two taels per case.
Here is ten taels.
After five cases,
the house deed is mine.
Deal.
Hold onto this for now.
Come with me to the morgue.
The morgue?
I forgot.
You pass out at the sight of corpses.
I have a way.