( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Boss.
Please come in.
Mrs. Wang.
I came here today
to tell you a story.
This is what Cao Tai placed in the shrine.
It is also Jiang Siyan's relic.
Cao Tai was afraid of seeing ghosts,
perhaps because he killed Jiang Siyan.
But I never understood.
Cao Tai had no grudge against the Jiang family,
why did he kill Jiang Siyan?
Until Wang Wan told me
that this handkerchief was hers.
It was raining heavily that day.
She handed me the umbrella,
so I took off my cloak and put it on her.
On a rainy night eight years ago,
Jiang Siyan was wearing Wang Wan's clothes,
and both were girls of the same age.
In the blurred vision of the rainy night,
Cao Tai mistook Jiang Siyan for Wang Wan.
Cao Tai wanted to kill Wang Wan,
and it could only be because of you.
Cao Tai used to get medicine from you often.
Over time,
taking advantage of your husband and Wang Wan being out at the same time,
you two got together.
After you accidentally miscarried,
you believed it was Wang Wan harming you.
You intended to kill Wang Wan.
You tricked Cao Tai into believing the child was his,
wanting to take advantage of Dr. Wang going out to gather herbs
to have Cao Tai kill Wang Wan.
Old Wang went to gather herbs.
Wang Wan walks past here every day.
Tonight is the best time to strike.
If you are a man,
prove it to me.
Wait for my news.
The rain was too heavy,
I couldn't see clearly.
And I was very nervous at the time,
I didn't even dare to look at her.
It wasn't until I strangled her to death
that I realized I killed the wrong person.
What should I do?
You can't even kill the right person.
I can't sleep well every night now,
dreaming every night that she comes to question me.
We had no grudges against each other,
why did I kill her?
I want to surrender to the authorities.
I am going to surrender to the authorities.
Surrender?
What will you tell the authorities?
Why did you kill that girl?
Don't drag me into this.
You can't even kill the right person,
what else can you do?
I am going to surrender to the authorities.
You idiot!
Listen to me.
Find a grave
and hide her in someone else's grave.
Pretend this never happened,
understand?
What a pity.
Cao Tai ultimately chose not to surrender.
Feeling guilty,
he put Jiang Siyan's handkerchief in the shrine,
burning incense every day,
praying for Jiang Siyan to have good fortune in her next life.
The Jiang family lost their youngest daughter,
so they treated the foundling Wanqing as Jiang Siyan,
raising her for eight years.
Cao Tai hasn't had a good night's sleep in these eight years.
You also know that
seeing a ghost was the last straw that broke Cao Tai.
You know even better
that if things continued like this,
Cao Tai would definitely turn himself in.
So you played the ghost
to lure Cao Tai into committing suicide.
I am Jiang Siyan.
Aren't you a child?
I've grown up.
I am not happy down there at all.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I was wrong.
Don't you feel guilty?
Come down and keep me company.
That way,
you won't owe me anymore.
You must have boiled a lot of cough powder yesterday.
It contains schizonepeta, balloon flower, aster,
stemona, licorice, and dried tangerine peel.
Among them, the smell of schizonepeta is the strongest.
Even if you bathed and applied rouge and powder,
I can still smell it.
Are you saying
that I instigated Cao Tai to hang himself?
This is all your deduction.
What evidence do you have?
You want evidence?
I happen to have evidence.
This is Zhou's shoe shop's ledger from yesterday.
The shop assistant clearly told me
that you went to buy embroidered shoes with an umbrella yesterday.
Didn't you tell us yesterday
that you didn't go out after the rain?
Why did you buy those embroidered shoes?
Actually, I've been wondering,
if you cover half your face,
how do you make Cao Tai
believe that you are the grown-up Jiang Siyan?
It can only be the shoes.
You definitely bought a pair
of embroidered shoes exactly like Jiang Siyan's.
Am I right?
Cao Tai.
You dragged me down even in death.
So,
you want to confess right here?
But I must remind you,
if you falsely confess
and affect the investigation of the case,
according to the Tang Code, the punishment will be more severe.
According to your deduction,
he really killed someone.
I thought he never did it.
Where is the mound?
There was clearly a mound here.
I followed your instructions
and buried the wrong body here.
If you really killed Jiang Siyan,
why would Old Jiang report it to the authorities?
I heard a constable say with my own ears
that Old Jiang's daughter disappeared just a few days ago.
Open your eyes and look!
Look for yourself!
Old Jiang's only daughter.
Then who did I kill?
Eight years ago,
you didn't kill anyone at all.
You were just afraid I'd call you a coward,
so you came back and lied to me that you killed the wrong person.
I can't believe I trusted you for so many years!
No, it's impossible.
Believe me,
I really killed her.
Where are the bones?
Didn't you say you buried them in someone else's mound?
Where is the mound?
Let go!
Listen to me. Listen to me. Listen to me.
I really killed her and buried her here.
Could it be that she turned into a ghost
and came back to life?
So the body disappeared?
Get out of here!
You loser!
Loser!
I killed her
and buried her right here.
She must be
right
here!
I killed her.
It must be here.
What are you doing here?
Let's go report to the officials, okay?
I used to comfort you
because you killed someone,
and I was afraid you'd drag me down.
Now that you haven't,
what am I afraid of?
Go report it.
If you don't believe me,
I'll tell Dr. Wang
about our affair!
I believe you.
It's been so many years,
maybe you just forgot the place.
Go back first.
We'll figure this out
later.
After he left,
I wanted to kill him.
Since he's afraid of ghosts,
I'll pretend to be one.
Since you say he killed someone,
where are the bones?
There are no bones.
A few days ago, a family was moving a grave
and happened to dig up two skeletons.
One of them was Jiang Siyan's.
By mistake,
how could you find her bones?
In my opinion,
those who pretend to be evil will eventually be haunted by it.
It's time for a shift change, right?
Yeah,
let's go.
There must be the information I want here.
The archives hold all the files of the government office,
it's an important place.
Irrelevant people can't enter.
Keep a close eye on this place.
Yes.
It's done, Sister. Su Lang,
I've sorted out Jiang Siyan's belongings,
go give them to Uncle Jiang.
Okay.
Constable Su, I beg you,
please help me.
I have no other choice!
Alright, what's the use of begging me?
We're just constables,
I can't judge cases.
How the lord will judge tomorrow,
is up to him.
Officers,
Officers, I beg you.
My wife is about to die,
she just wants to see her daughter before she dies.
Please be lenient, officers,
let my wife fulfill this wish before she dies.
I beg you!
Get up first,
stand up and talk.
Uncle Jiang,
the law has no mercy.
And she is already waiting for the Ministry of Justice's sentence.
She is not your daughter, Jiang Siyan.
I know.
In these eight years,
we have long regarded her as our biological daughter.
I pinned all my love
on her.
The Wanqing you speak of
is my daughter.
Catcher Su.
Bring Wanqing out tomorrow.
We need to identify the crime scene.
Daughter,
Siyan,
Dad is here to see you.
My child.
Daughter.
Siyan.
Am I dreaming?
You are really my Siyan.
You are finally back.
Your daughter is back.
My child,
you are finally back.
Come, let me look at you.
Did you eat well out there?
Did anyone bully you?
N-no one bullied me.
Mom, don't worry.
I'm fine. Stop it.
My child.
Let me tell you.
Looking at it now,
Nanrong Xiang is the most miserable.
When I went to inform him of the case,
as soon as he heard
that Wanqing and Wanrou were both locked up,
he went crazy.
The dancers of the Jiaofang have been dismissed.
Now, he sits at the door every day,
drinking and singing to passers-by.
Nanrong Xiang and Ye Xian.
If he could have treated them equally
and taken good care of both sisters back then,
wouldn't this have been avoided?
After Wanqing was locked up,
she didn't even see her biological father,
yet she has such deep affection for Mother Jiang who raised her.
Relatives are often assumed to be connected by blood,
but deep companionship is the key.
For example.
Suppose you were accidentally switched when you were young
and lived in a family with no blood relation.
At this time, your biological father appears.
If it were you,
how would you choose?
Of course, I'd choose the father who raised me.
Catcher Su.
Am I your biological child?
You brat.
I picked you up in the garbage dump.
Picked me up?
Then tell me,
what was the situation when you picked me up?
What else was in the garbage dump? Don't go, wait for me.
Where are you going?
Wait for me.
Why are you walking so fast?
Now, deducting two taels,
you still owe me eight taels.
You are quite honest.
Of course.
I, Li Jinglan, never owe anyone a single cent.
In that case.
I want to help you investigate cases in the future.
Why don't you give me an identity
and let me be a Buliangren?
That way, when I go out in the future, my status will be perfectly justifiable.
You want to go to the archives to check the case files.
Actually,
I looked into your mother's autopsy records.
She had multiple struggle marks on her body.
Both her wrists and ankles were broken.
A sharp knife with a blue dragon and roaring tiger pattern was found next to the body.
She was a medical woman at the medicine shop.
I really don't know who
would have such a deep grudge against her.
You can't bear to see corpses.
That should be the reason.
This is my private matter.
If you really want to be a Bad Man,
I can help you.
Magistrate Chen.
Miss Li.
Why are you here?
You've solved several cases in a row.
You're the favorite in the yamen now.
You flatter me.
It's all thanks to Magistrate Chen's good guidance.
I strongly support you being a coroner.
As for your bet with Vice Magistrate Li,
I also bet you'll win.
Magistrate Chen, you have a good eye.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I just came specifically to bring you some dry brewed wine.
I can't take this.
Last time, because I drank your wine,
I got drunk and allowed you to be a coroner.
As a result, Vice Magistrate Li scolded me for three days straight.
I won't fall for it this time.
Yes, you can.
No, no.
No, take it away.
You can.
No.
This time it's not for me.
Not for you?
Who else could make you worry so much?
Jueming.
Jueming?
The assistant who helped me with the case, Jueming.
This person is extraordinarily capable.
He is definitely the talent our yamen needs.
You want him
to be a Bad Man?
No, no.
The list of Bad Men has long been set.
Father, you're here.
Miss Li.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
No, Miss Li.
Miss Li insists
that I test your martial arts.
Let's see if you can pass the Bad Man test.
Then don't blame me for being rough.
First round.
Jueming wins.
Good, beautiful!
Liu Zhuang wins.
Second round, Xiao Yi wins.
Final round.
It's because I taught him well.
I am his master.
You taught him well.
Jueming wins.
From today on,
you are a Bad Man.
Follow Constable Su
and wait for his orders at any time.
As for your new home,
Don't worry.
We'll help you clean up.
We.
Guys, clean it up properly.
Clean that side up too.
Hey, wipe that window frame again.
Throw away that broken flower pot in the corner.
You guys are so careless.
Gently.
Put this table in the wing room.
Be careful.
This table is very expensive.
Move it to the parlor.
From now on,
you stick close to me,
and we'll roam the martial world together.
We'll share our wine,
and solve cases together.
You're not allowed to sneak off halfway.
Honglian.
When the red flower is outside,
my father isn't home.
I brought you some delicious food. Let's go.
Here, try it. It's still hot.
Watch your sleeves.
Your father again.
So sweet.
If your father...
Zhen'er probably hasn't had this.
Let's bring some to her to try.
Who is Zhen'er?
Sister Qiuhua's youngest daughter.
She's very well-behaved and cute.
If you had told me earlier, I would have brought an extra portion.
It's fine.
I can't finish a whole bowl anyway.
Let's go and bring some to her.
Okay.
Is this the place?
Yes.
Sister Qiuhua's house.
Okay, let's go.
Be careful.
She will definitely like the porridge we brought her.
Open the door.
Sister Qiuhua!
Wait for me at the door.
This...
What's wrong?
She died in bed.
And her state of death is bizarre.
The deceased's face and lips are cyanotic.
Her eyes are bloodshot and swollen.
Her nails are bluish-purple.
Her hands, feet, and head
were bound by red ropes and suspended.
The ligature marks are quite obvious.
The rope marks are evenly distributed.
She died of asphyxiation by strangulation with the red rope.
There's a large incantation on her back.
It looks like it was drawn with cinnabar.
Looking at her condition,
she didn't struggle much before she died.
But we can also rule out suicide by hanging.
It's a homicide.
Livor mortis is quite pronounced.
Time of death was around the hour of Xu last night.
This stove
has been used to brew Shenqi decoction.
Someone in this house must have had kidney disease.
Besides the smell of herbs,
there's a strong scent of Chinese honey locust.
The deceased's lips are slightly curved upwards.
Why would she smile before dying?
Honglian.
Don't be too sad.
We will definitely get to the bottom of this
and get justice for Sister Qiuhua.
Stop crying.
When was the body found?
During the hours of the Snake.
The deceased is Qiuhua.
She was a washerwoman around the dock.
She made a living washing clothes for boatmen
and had a six-year-old daughter named Zhen'er.
Let's go in and take a look.
I'll go in and take a look.
It's still uncertain
why the suspect deliberately posed the body like this.
Was she strangled with a hemp rope?
The red hemp rope,
the posture of the body,
and the mysterious spell on her back,
they are exactly the same.
Same as what?
Exactly the same as a few unsolved cases from over a decade ago.
The victims were also all female.
The killer tied the victims' bodies
into various shapes with red hemp ropes.
But what is the same is that
on every victim's back,
there was a mysterious spell drawn in cinnabar.
Third watch.
All is well.
Whose house is this?
The door isn't closed properly.
Is anyone there?
Dead body!