( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Can bronze mirrors really show ghosts?
Do you believe
there are ghosts in this world?
I believe it,
because I can see ghosts.
So you can see them too.
But what I'm more curious about is,
why are ghosts looking for you?
The day Wanrou committed suicide,
I followed her
to the river,
watched her go into the water,
but I couldn't do anything.
If it weren't for me,
she wouldn't have killed herself.
Thinking about it this way,
if she comes back to take my life,
I can understand.
Wanqing and Wanrou were twins.
Wanqing is the older sister,
and Wanrou is the younger sister.
The older sister was good at singing and dancing from a young age,
and had a good voice.
She was deeply loved by people around her.
The younger sister, Wanrou,
had a stutter since childhood
and struggled to speak.
Naturally, she wasn't as loved as her sister.
Please, have a seat.
After Wanrou
jumped into the river,
Wanqing became withdrawn.
Wanqing, start.
Sing, sing!
Sing!
That day,
Wanqing just stood on the stage,
motionless.
We all tried to persuade her,
but it was useless.
Years later, she told me that
before Wanrou committed suicide,
she wanted to perform on stage with her,
but was rejected.
She felt
she was responsible for Wanrou's death.
So, she refused to go on stage.
For so many years,
she hasn't performed once.
Usually,
she takes care of the dancers' clothes and makeup.
But because of this,
she is very popular.
These dancers
love her very much.
Where did Wanrou jump into the river?
Tianhe, west of the city.
Slow down.
According to Constable Su's orders,
I was arranging for a night watch.
I saw Wanqing leave this room
and go to the makeup pavilion.
While patrolling,
I suddenly heard a scream
and rushed over immediately.
I found Wanqing choking herself in the room,
almost out of breath.
Who made this dish?
Do you know the rules?
Can you touch the crime scene?
Go.
He's asking you a question.
You haven't answered.
Her mother cooked it herself.
I've checked all the ingredients.
No problem.
I always feel
there's something wrong,
but I can't figure out why.
Every complex case
has traces to follow.
No clue means not enough evidence,
and not enough clues.
Chief Su,
where should we go next?
As for us,
next,
Dad, did you figure it out?
Let's go eat roast chicken.
I know a place that serves amazing roast chicken.
I guarantee you'll crave it after one bite.
Good idea. Chief Su,
can we focus a bit?
We are investigating a case.
I don't want to eat it.
It's your mother who does.
She keeps asking for it ever since she tried it.
I have to bring some back for her.
Besides,
investigating cases in the future
will depend on you young people.
As for me,
I'm just a greedy old man about to retire.
The best advice I can give you is
that you can solve cases better on a full stomach.
Remember what I always tell you.
Safety first.
Cases can wait.
Got it, Dad. We know.
Constable Su, you're early.
Thanks for your hard work.
Dongling, stop right there.
This performance was booked by the Guan family long ago,
to pray for his seriously ill grandson.
Master Guan is in Luoyang.
His family is rich and powerful.
Our small music house
cannot decline it no matter what.
Now,
you are the best dancer among us all.
You should be the lead dancer.
Nianyao just had an accident,
and now you are targeting me.
Before Nianyao's accident,
I already decided you'd be the lead dancer.
Everyone knows it.
Have you forgotten?
Everyone knows Wanrou is back.
Whoever is the lead dancer will suffer.
She killed Nianyao, and now she wants to harm me.
Nonsense.
Nianyao's death
was just an accident.
Then why don't you let Wanqing be the lead dancer?
She is the best among us,
isn't she?
Stop arguing.
Tomorrow,
I will dance.
Miss Mingzhu.
Sister Chunyi has to watch the shop today.
She specially told me,
since today is your brother's funeral,
to bring some money to help out.
Please take care of yourself.
My brother ran a coffin shop for a long time.
He made coffins for many people.
In the past, I thought these coffins
were prepared for others.
Unexpectedly today,
after my brother passed away, I realize
there's always a coffin
left for one's own kin.
Please restrain your grief,
Miss Wang.
Why are you here?
Aren't you here too?
Coroner Li.
The government notified me
to claim my brother's body for burial.
Is there any problem?
Today, I went to Changning Street,
and happened to see Wanqing picking up new clothes at the fabric shop.
Thank you, boss.
Please come again.
Isn't this Wanqing?
Long time no see.
When she came out of the fabric shop,
she happened to run into an acquaintance who said 'long time no see',
but she acted like she didn't know them,
and reacted slowly.
I learned from her acquaintance
that she is a doctor.
A while ago, Miss Wanqing had a burn on her shoulder.
She was treated by the doctor you introduced.
At that time,
Wang Kang accompanied her,
and they treated the wound together in the clinic.
My brother was usually careless.
That day, he spilled boiling water on Wanqing's shoulder,
causing a burn,
which left a scar afterwards.
If Wanqing's parents knew about this,
the marriage would be ruined.
So we kept it a secret before.
So she deliberately pretended not to know her.
So Coroner Li,
besides autopsies,
is also in charge of investigation.
Me?
Autopsies and investigations
are all for catching the killer as soon as possible,
so the deceased can rest in peace.
Who exactly killed my brother?
We are still investigating.
Currently, I also suspect Dongling.
Both her parents have committed crimes
and are now serving their sentences.
It can't be ruled out that she wants to be the top courtesan,
and became jealous of Qi Nianyao and Wanqing.
Her parents' mistakes
have nothing to do
with whether she makes mistakes.
My father said,
if parents commit crimes,
the chance of their children offending is very high.
Who is your father?
Anyway, we are still investigating.
We won't miss a single clue.
Yesterday,
I noticed Wanqing's mother's eyes were a bit strange.
She must be hiding something.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Let's go.
Go. Hurry.
We're late.
She's already dead.
What was her cause of death?
The deceased is clutching a blue hairpin tightly in her left hand.
Blood on the head,
purple face, dark lips.
No pulse.
Pupils slightly dilated.
I want to ask,
did the madam suffer from a heart condition before she died?
Yes. She needed to take medicine all year round.
Preliminary judgment: the deceased suddenly had a heart attack,
then became weak,
and fell from the high platform,
hitting the back of her head on the stone bench, causing death.
I want to see that hairpin.
Take the body away first.
Madam.
All right, don't get so worked up, Father.
Don't worry.
The authorities will definitely get to the bottom of this case.
Come, sit down first.
Sit down and tell me
what exactly happened today.
Around
the hour of Shen.
Madam
took the dancers to the stage
for rehearsal.
After everyone was ready,
Wanqing stood on the high platform,
but she hesitated to make a move.
Her mother knew something was wrong.
All right.
Let's stop practicing for now.
Everyone go eat and touch up your makeup
in preparation for tonight's performance.
The dancers rehearsed the moves once,
then returned to their rooms to eat and touch up,
waiting for the evening performance.
Unexpectedly at that time,
she suddenly heard Wanrou's voice.
Mother.
Wanrou.
She must have missed her so much
that it created such an obsession and hallucination.
Madam!
Rou!
By the time I reacted,
it was too late.
Then what is this hairpin about?
This hairpin
was originally given to my daughter by Madam.
But she seemed to see Wanrou on stage,
so she took it off.
As far as I know,
Wanqing has liked red since childhood.
When performing on stage, she wore red shoes.
Growing up, her boudoir was mainly decorated in red.
But Wanrou was exactly the opposite.
She liked blue.
If you say Madam Ye wanted to give this blue hairpin
to the non-existent Wanrou on the high platform,
it makes sense.
But for such an important performance today,
Wanqing, you
decided to change your red attire
and wear a blue dress.
So you are not Wanqing,
but Wanrou.
No, impossible. How could she be Wanrou?
How could that be?
Father, look at what nonsense he's talking about.
Wanrou has been dead for so long.
Wait a minute.
I think his question makes sense.
When all impossible options are eliminated,
this only reasonable answer,
no matter how absurd,
must be the truth.
No, it's impossible.
She is my daughter, Wanqing.
Parents can always notice slight changes in their children.
Walking into your room
and seeing that the dishes your mother made all have leeks,
I assume you love to eat them.
But when your mother cleaned the room, she found
that the leeks in every dish had been picked out,
which made her suspicious.
realizing you had changed.
And this suspicion
grew stronger
when she saw you again.
When you came to the Guan residence in a blue dress,
your mother knew it was Wanrou's favorite color.
She immediately suspected that the person in front of her might not be Wanqing.
When you stood on the stage
and everyone was practicing the dance,
you didn't move at all,
which made her even more certain.
After all, Wanrou couldn't dance,
so she couldn't replace Wanqing at all.
So, after everyone left,
she quietly went up the stage.
Mother,
why are you here?
I came to see you.
It's alright.
Let's go.
Wanrou.
Growing up,
you were neglected.
For so many years,
I didn't know where you were.
Now you can speak clearly,
and you have grown up.
Your father and I owe you so much.
Stop it.
It's not too late.
There is still time.
What's the point of saying this now?
Will it make you feel better?
When I was five,
everyone laughed at me for stuttering.
What were you doing?
When I first performed on stage at seven,
they laughed at my uncoordinated movements and being off-beat.
What were you doing?
When I was ten, I went to the river to kill myself in a fit of anger.
Where were you?
I...
Do you think you can get my forgiveness
just by saying you owe me too much?
You pushed your own mother down with your own hands.
You didn't die back then.
Perhaps some family adopted you.
The seeds of revenge took root
and sprouted in your heart over time.
So, you killed Wanqing,
took her identity,
and started your revenge plan.
Wang Kang accidentally burned Wanqing,
so he secretly asked a doctor to examine her and prescribe medicine.
Today in the market,
the doctor greeted you,
but you seemed not to know him at all.
It makes sense
if you are a different person.
So,
you killed Wang Kang because...
Who are you?
Because he found no scars on your shoulder.
You killed him to silence him.
What about Qi Nianyao?
Did Madam Ye plan to replace the top courtesan before she died?
It must be you.
That explains it.
You took advantage of Qi Nianyao's fear of losing her title as the top courtesan,
making her collude with you to stage a haunting.
Have you thought it through?
Do as I say.
Make everyone think Wanrou came back to fight for the title of the top courtesan.
Would Dongling still dare to take the position?
After things settle down,
my mother will realize
who the real top courtesan is.
Nianyao.
Nianyao, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Nianyao?
Nianyao, what's wrong with you?
Don't kill me!
You instructed her to claim she saw ghosts multiple times
and had her pretend to be possessed in her room,
all to set the stage for the fire during the final performance.
According to the plan,
you smeared flammable oil on her costume.
She would suddenly shout Wanrou's name during the performance
and then ignite the costume.
Wanrou is back!
And you would be standing by with a basin of water,
ready to put out the fire immediately. Wanrou is back!
However, on the night of the incident,
when she set herself on fire,
you walked away.
Because of this,
when Nianyao was dying,
she stared fixedly to the side.
After that,
you used the same trick
to fake your own murder,
which also reduced others' suspicion of you.
From the moment you took Wanqing's place,
your seemingly flawless plan
slowly began to unfold.
In your eyes,
you can't tolerate anyone else being the top courtesan.
The former Wanqing was one,
and so is Qi Nianyao now.
Nan Rongxiang.
So you are covering up for your daughter.
Covering up?
My wife just fell to her death from the high platform.
She is my only daughter.
How dare you still argue?
I'm not arguing.
She really is my...
After hearing your deduction,
I almost thought I had become Wanrou.
Unfortunately, I am not.
This dress
was ordered by my mother at the tailor shop,
and she chose the color too.
If you don't believe me,
you can ask the owner of the tailor shop.
Do you dare to take off your clothes to check for scars?
I guess
you might say
I deliberately burned myself.
But Wanrou was born with a stutter.
She was tone-deaf
and couldn't dance.
A stutter can be corrected,
but a sense of dance and rhythm are innate and cannot be changed.
Since Wanrou died,
I have never danced again.
Today,
to prove that I am Wanqing,
I will dance for all of you.
Wearing gorgeous clothes,
fingers tapping lightly,
the past is no more.
Foolishness and anger,
half covering the face,
endless affection is thick.
She really is Wanqing.
Her movements and dance are exactly the same as when she was a child. If there is no sorrow,
It is her.
burning longing surges.
Could it be that I was really wrong?
She really is Wanqing.
Sis, I told you Jueming was a fraud.
He gave an impassioned speech yesterday,
and guess what? He went in the completely wrong direction.
Freshly roasted chicken is here!
Who wants some?
Smells good, right?
Silly boy, according to your analysis,
we've been talking to ghosts these past two days.
I don't think Nanrong Xiang is a good guy either.
He clearly had something on his mind yesterday.
Miss, here's your favorite chicken leg.
I'm not hungry.
Oh, there are only two legs on a chicken.
One for you, and one for you.
Ah, people just get
irritable when they're hungry.
Once you're full, everything looks better.
Actually, I think that brat Jueming's
analysis made a lot of sense.
It's just that the conclusion
doesn't quite add up.
Then wasn't it all for nothing, Dad?
Is this going to become another cold case?
This chicken leg is really good.
Oh, this chicken leg...
Constable Su! Come over here.
Why does this person look so much like Wanqing?
But the name written here is Jiang Siyan.