( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Your little grandson has been found.
He is safe and sound.
So rest assured.
Don't bring him to see me.
I don't want him to see me like this.
I'm a monster.
Tell him
he doesn't have a grandfather.
Live a good life.
Zhen'er,
what did you wish for?
I hope Mother is happy in another place.
You are so sensible, Zhen'er.
If your mother knew,
she would be very happy for you.
From now on, you will live here.
I will come see you often.
Do you have any other wishes?
I want to see the Lu Family Acrobatics Troupe's performance again.
Mother took me to see it once before.
I will take you.
This is Su Yuerong
and Su Xiang's old sachet shop.
Nowadays,
it has become so dilapidated.
Who are you?
You must be Su Xiang's older sister.
About Su Xiang's death,
I am sorry.
I am truly sorry.
It is not your fault.
You don't need to take it to heart.
If you can solve the case in time,
it will comfort Su Xiang's soul in heaven.
Constable Qin.
Su Xiang.
If your spirits are watching from heaven,
I came today to tell you some good news.
Your case has been solved.
The one who solved this case
is the kid next to me.
Cheers.
Good wine.
Come on.
I also brought something very delicious.
Wait a minute.
From Xiangmanlou,
chicken flavor,
tofu filling,
right?
Really? He even smelled that.
Have a taste.
Try it.
Let me have one too. It really is!
Why is your sense of smell so sharp?
My mother taught me when I was a child.
How can that be taught?
When I was a kid,
in the pharmacy,
Mom would blindfold me with a black cloth,
put a pile of herbs in front of me,
and make me identify them by smell.
Gradually,
I could not only distinguish different herbs,
but also recognize different scents.
Is it this one?
You'll be punished if you get it wrong.
It doesn't hurt.
Did I say something I shouldn't have,
and make you sad?
It's fine.
My mother passed away 17 years ago.
Even her silhouette has become blurry.
I can't remember her.
Alright.
Recently,
we have solved major cases one after another.
Now that Jueming has joined us,
let's forget all the unhappy things
in the past.
Let's drink. Cheers.
Cheers.
Jueming.
Here, mustard green porridge.
Careful, it's hot.
And this.
Osmanthus cake.
You won't be able to eat it whenever you want in the future.
I'll accept them all.
Did you stay up late to make this?
You're not young anymore.
Take good care of your skin, you still have to get married.
Is that how you talk?
Are you really planning to move out?
I'm just going back to where I used to be.
Yichun Pavilion has always been my home.
How good you've been to me,
I won't forget.
Cheer up.
You brat.
You haven't even left yet and you're already acting like a stranger?
Come back and visit often.
Brother Jueming.
Thank you for finding the culprit who harmed my brother.
Be sure to come back often when you have time.
Okay.
Smells so good.
I'm leaving now. Take care of yourself.
Remember to come back and see us. Think about coming back. Yes, yes.
Bitch.
Slut.
You have to serve me today,
whether you want to or not.
Sister Chunyi.
It's nothing.
You go first.
Someone must have had too much to drink.
I'll go take a look.
Bullying customers because you're a big shop?
Damn it.
Slut.
Putting on airs and playing hard to get in front of your Grandpa Niu?
Your Grandpa Niu just got out.
What's the matter?
Isn't money enough for you?
Still won't serve me? Excuse me.
Sir.
Everyone comes here to have fun.
Why are you getting angry?
Don't be angry.
That one.
Zhao Xuanli.
She kicked me out of the private room.
Isn't that infuriating?
This Zhao Xuanli.
I'll punish her later.
Don't be angry.
Pour him a glass of water.
How about this.
I'll find you a prettier one,
the top courtesan.
Look at her, our top courtesan.
She's beautiful.
I want her.
I'm telling you,
you have to serve me today,
whether you want to or not.
Don't you know who Grandpa Niu is?
Why are you doing this?
We don't have much here,
but we have plenty of girls.
Look, you can choose whichever you like.
Don't be angry.
Today, it's my treat.
Consider it an apology.
Zhao Xuanli,
don't think you're anything special.
You're just a plaything for people's amusement.
I'm telling you.
You won't serve me? How could she not serve you?
I'll turn this Yichun Brothel upside down today.
Let's see how long you can hide.
Oh, look how angry you are.
I'll serve him.
Isn't she coming down now?
Today,
I will give up my body.
You... don't regret it.
Don't regret it.
What do I have to regret?
Wait for me.
Come, come.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Today, I'll give everyone another pot of wine.
Come, go back and continue.
Hurry back to dancing.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Come, continue.
Keep playing.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
I'm fine. I've seen a lot of people like this.
It's better to avoid trouble.
Don't worry.
Tell me if anything happens in the future.
Got it. Let's go.
Bitch.
Come here.
Let go of me.
No.
The deceased's name is Niu Dali.
He was just released from prison last month.
Last night, someone saw him at Yichun Pavilion.
After leaving Yichun Pavilion, he went home alone.
After that, he never came out of his house.
The person who reported the case is a tea servant from Yichun Pavilion.
He was also the first person
to discover Niu Dali's body at his house.
All right, I'm dressed.
Did you just say Niu Dali?
I think I saw it yesterday.
Don't think you're something special.
You're just a plaything for people's amusement.
I didn't expect that after you became a Buliangren,
your second case would be related to Yichun Brothel.
Give me your hand.
What is this?
Constable Su got this peace and success charm for us.
To bless us with a smooth investigation.
Wait a minute.
Don't forget to wear this.
That's very thoughtful.
How is it?
Perfect.
The deceased's eyes
are wide open.
The fatal wound is on the neck.
The wound is extremely deep,
causing massive blood loss.
The deceased's upper clothes are completely soaked.
The right hand is tightly gripping a long-handled razor.
By comparison,
the razor's blade matches the shape of the fatal wound.
Preliminary judgment suggests
the fatal wound was caused by this razor.
Livor mortis is prominent.
It's dark red.
Based on the rigor mortis,
the time of death should be between 7 and 9 a.m. today.
You were up early.
Did you see anyone suspicious?
No, I didn't see anyone suspicious.
When I passed by here this morning,
I noticed that he
went right in,
but ran off very quickly.
I took a look,
peeking through the crack of the door.
I found someone already dead inside.
What a heavy stench of blood.
And the smell of rouge.
The smell of rouge?
There's the smell of rice wine on his feet.
Where is the person who first found the body and reported it?
Constable Su.
Go over there.
Tell us again in detail how you found the body.
I... I've already said it many times.
I told you to say it again. Don't you understand?
Yes.
Last night, I found a purse at Yichunlou.
It was exactly the same as the one Niu Dali took out.
I thought he would come to get it early in the morning.
But he didn't come at dawn.
So I took the purse to his house.
Brother Dali!
Brother Dali.
Then how did you know this is Niu Dali's home?
He's been coming here often recently.
He often gets drunk and needs someone to help him home.
I've walked him home several times.
He gave me a little tip every time.
Chief Su.
Any other clues?
His next-door neighbors said
that last night,
they heard a loud argument.
But he loves to drink,
and makes a scene after drinking,
so they didn't take it seriously.
What time was that?
It should be the hour of You.
Around the hour of Mao today,
the night soil collectors started working.
They didn't see anyone suspicious around.
They said that after Fan Le came back,
he went straight into the room,
found the body,
and rushed out screaming.
The night soil collector was curious and peeked inside.
So,
the time he went in and out was very short.
He couldn't possibly have had time to commit the crime.
Looking at it this way,
it's highly likely he committed suicide.
People like him
deserve to die.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Keep your mouth shut.
Why would he commit suicide?
Why did he commit suicide?
I don't know.
Last night, after he left the room,
I never saw him again.
Miss Li.
Then from last night until now,
have you been anywhere else?
No,
I was in my room all the time.
The madam of Yichun Brothel can testify for me.
If you don't believe me,
you can ask her.
Xuanli,
why did Niu Dali insist on having you serve him?
As for this question,
he can answer it for me.
It's like this.
Three years ago, I received a report.
The informant said that at the Zhao residence in Lianhua Alley,
a man was dragging an unconscious woman into the house.
After hearing this, I rushed over.
Officer,
someone is raping a young woman.
Hurry.
Hurry, officer.
Don't move.
The man
was Niu Dali.
The woman.
Afterward,
Niu Dali was sentenced to three years for rape.
He was just released from prison last month.
At that time,
I was still an innocent girl
and hadn't been sold to Yichun Brothel yet.
That night,
I was alone at home.
I was defiled by a scoundrel,
which changed my destiny forever.
Xuanli.
So when Niu Dali went to Yichun Brothel for fun,
he saw you at first glance
and wanted you to serve him.
Niu Dali...
Is he really dead?
Dead.
Completely dead
and cold.
Look, here she comes.
Where do you think she went?
Who knows?
She's been gone all day.
I heard her client died yesterday.
Why were you gone so long?
I was worried sick.
Are you okay?
Don't worry, Madam.
Xuanli is fine.
Glad to hear it. Go on.
Did she kill him?
I didn't see her go out.
Who knows?
I think it most likely has something to do with her.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Too much free time, huh?
Hurry up and entertain the guests.
- If you don't have any, go find some.
- Yes.
Go, go.
Why are you here?
Look at this pretty face.
Hand over all your money.
I saw everything you did.
We've visited three liquor stalls.
Do you have any leads?
This morning,
I smelled rice wine on Niu Dali's shoes.
To make our customers lose their minds
and spend extravagantly,
Yichun Brothel only sells strong liquor,
not rice wine.
You mean on his way home,
- he bought wine?
- Yes.
Mellow rice wine,
fragrant for miles.
What about this stall?
Sir, have a pot of rice wine.
Good wine.
Boss.
Do you remember this man?
Did he come to buy wine yesterday?
I remember him.
He came here to buy wine last night.
Before leaving, he bumped into a traveler.
The wine he just bought spilled all over the floor.
The traveler apologized repeatedly.
He bought another pot of wine from me
and gave it to him as compensation.
Is there any wine left?
Boss, I'd like a pot of wine.
Coming right up.
The pot right in front
was just filled today.
Thank you, sir.
Take care, sir.
Niu Dali bought wine on his way home.
The coin purse was still on him.
The servant, Fan Le, said he went to Niu Dali's house to return the purse.
That's how he found the body.
He is lying.
How are the notes coming along?
Let me see.
The victim's name is Fan Le.
The proprietress of Yichun Brothel said
he didn't return to the servant's quarters last night.
He might have taken the chance to go home,
and was murdered here.
Let's go inside and take a look.
Did you see him yesterday?
I haven't seen anything recently.
Okay.
Then it's nothing.
Come.
There are stairs going up.
One, two, three.
Right side.
What happened?
Why is his cause of death exactly the same as Niu Dali's?
His back was against the window.
The wound on his neck is fatal.
His right hand was clenching a razor,
with blood on it.
Judging from the rigor mortis,
the time of death is less than eight hours.
He also reeks of alcohol.
Son,
don't you think
the MO of this case
is very similar to a previous one?
Right.
Isn't that how Zhao Xuanli's father died?
Niu Dali, Fan Le, and Zhao Xuanli's father all died like this.
All had fatal wounds on the neck,
sitting on the ground with their backs against the window.
Wait. Such a crucial clue,
why didn't you mention it at Niu Dali's crime scene?
I forgot.
I thought it was all a coincidence.
But now seeing how Fan Le died,
the MO should be the same.
At the time of the incident,
Zhao Xuanli's father was alone at home.
According to the time of death inferred by the coroner,
Zhao Xuanli has an alibi.
So she should have an alibi this time too.
These victims are all connected to her.
I really don't know how she did it.
It's sorcery.
Sorcery
can kill.