Pan is a regular of mine.
He came to borrow money yesterday.
Considering our friendship,
I lent it to him.
Then what was his reason for borrowing money?
Do you know what he does for a living?
He once said he was a cloth merchant.
But he really didn't mention the reason for borrowing.
But these days,
who doesn't have difficulties living away from home?
If he doesn't say, I won't ask.
He's a grave robber.
We found his body by the moat
at Hai hour last night.
Then he also stole my husband's remains.
According to his account before he died,
he indeed did it.
He found treasures in the tomb
and acquired a windfall because of it.
That's impossible.
I arranged my late husband's funeral myself.
There were no treasures in the coffin.
If he said so,
it must be a scam.
We also can't figure out
why he stole your husband's remains.
Then how did your husband die?
Died of alcoholism.
How was your relationship as a couple?
That's all in the past.
He was a merchant.
He cared for me deeply.
I thought I had found a good husband,
so I married him.
But after we got married,
he became an alcoholic and a gambler.
He wouldn't stop until he lost everything.
Over time,
the business also declined due to his absurd behavior.
And my emotional support was all placed on Acai.
It became the best companion in my life.
Do you like it?
Acai.
This is called a longevity tag.
Your name is engraved on it.
This way, you won't get lost anymore.
Let's go back.
People can't even get enough to eat,
and you're feeding milk to this beast.
Go make me a bowl of noodles.
What are you doing?
This must be worth a lot of money.
I'll pawn it.
I can definitely get my money back.
This belongs to Acai. Give it back to me.
Let go,
or I'll sell it too.
Acai.
I'm sorry.
This longevity pendant is not made of silver.
But he will never take it away again.
Where is the money?
Don't mention it.
I had bad luck today.
Played ten rounds. None of them came up big.
Go get me a basin of water to wash my feet and wash away the bad luck.
You always say you'll win it back.
But you end up losing everything.
You should really quit gambling.
I'll quit.
I'll look for a job tomorrow.
You say that every time.
I mean it this time.
Why does it smell like urine?
It might be Acai's pee.
I'll clean it up later.
Damn it. This dog has grown so big but still doesn't bark.
What's the point of keeping it?
I'm going to sell you today.
What are you doing?
If you dare touch Acai, I'll fight you to the death.
Fight me?
Ever since that dog came here,
my luck has been getting worse. I lose every bet.
I must sell it today no matter what.
Don't touch it.
Let go! Acai!
Wait, I have money.
I have money.
I have money. Let Acai go.
Let it go.
I have money.
Wow, Xia Chunyi.
You really paid a high price for this dog.
Acai!
Where is Acai? Where did you take it?
Stop pulling me. I sold it.
Sold it?
Where did you sell it?
The ghost market.
You bastard!
Don't go.
The dealers wouldn't take it,
so I threw it in the ruins.
I regretted it later and went looking for it.
The vendor told me it was too cold,
and it froze to death in no time.
What's wrong?
I just drank too much.
I don't remember what I did.
Besides, didn't I go back to look for it?
Don't be mad, honey.
I promise I won't drink anymore.
I won't gamble either, okay?
I will work hard
and earn good money.
Don't be mad.
I'll start working right now, look.
Give me back Acai!
Give me back Acai! Are you done?
Have you made enough of a scene? Do you still want to live together?
Acai!
When he treated you like that,
why didn't you report to the authorities?
What good would reporting it do for a woman like me?
They'd lock him up for a few days and let him out.
My life would only get harder.
Why don't you government officials do anything?
I was just born too late.
Otherwise, I would definitely arrest him.
Later, I searched for a whole day but couldn't find Acai.
Acai, where are you?
Excuse me, have you seen a little yellow dog about this big?
His name is Acai.
Never seen him.
Sir, have you seen a dog about this big?
Never seen him. Acai!
Go away. I haven't seen him. My dog is named Acai.
Maybe heaven was watching.
When I got home, I found that
he had suffered a sudden stroke from heavy drinking
and already passed away.
The neighbor called the officers and a doctor
to examine the body.
He was only buried after confirming he died of illness.
For the sake of our marriage,
I arranged his funeral.
But after all these years,
I've never visited his grave.
From the day he was buried,
our bond came to an end.
Sorry to bother you today.
If we find any other clues,
we will come back to ask.
I also didn't expect that Pan would meet with an accident.
I might be the last person he saw.
But I was at Yichun Pavilion all day yesterday.
You happened to be there too,
so you can testify for me.
Stop. Take two steps forward.
You missed your mark.
Before the guqin music starts,
you need to walk here in advance.
And light the candles at the same time.
Okay.
Let's do it again.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Sister, do you know?
The new magistrate was transferred from Chang'an.
They say he is extremely eccentric
and hard to get along with.
I'm starting to envy my dad.
He doesn't have to deal with such a difficult superior.
Just be content.
As long as the new official loves the people and is just,
he is a good official.
True.
Jueming.
Jueming!
You haven't said a word since you came back from Yichun Brothel.
No, you didn't say anything when you were there either.
Is something on your mind?
No.
Or did you figure something out?
Smells good.
Let's go in.
Let's go.
Sit down. I went back and sorted out the whole case.
This Pan Lang...
He robbed Xia Zhiming's tomb.
And then, right after that, he borrowed money from the proprietress.
Finally, he died by the moat.
Logically speaking, the proprietress is indeed a suspect.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm just analyzing all the possibilities of the case.
Just as the proprietress said.
We were all at Yichun Brothel that day.
She never left her room on the third floor,
so she didn't have time to commit the crime.
We can testify for her.
The boss lady usually gives food to homeless children.
She also adopted Jueming.
I really think she is a very, very kind person.
Besides, doesn't murder require a motive?
Yeah.
Losing a dog
wouldn't be a reason to kill her husband.
But I think
an alcoholic and abusive husband
is worse than a dog.
Right?
In my opinion,
we should hurry up and find the Gambling King,
then find out where the fool is,
and look for more clues about Mr. Pan.
Okay, let's go find the Gambling King after we eat.
Yeah.
You go find the Gambling King first.
I'll go to the county office to check the old files.
Let's split up then,
and meet up at the county office later.
Okay.
Who is it?
Hello. Who are you?
Well, ma'am,
I want to ask you something.
What do you want to ask?
This household,
Xia Zhiming and Xia Chunyi used to live here.
I want to ask, how was their relationship?
Well...
I'm their distant cousin.
I just want to ask about what happened back then.
I heard Xia Zhiming was up to his ears in gambling debt,
so he hid out in this old house.
He gambled, drank, and had every vice imaginable.
He treated his wife terribly,
constantly beating and humiliating her.
He usually didn't let Xia Chunyi go out,
so I don't know much about his wife.
Did the couple keep a dog?
Yes, they did.
Xia Zhiming used to complain about having to buy goat's milk for it every day.
He said he'd rather use the money to win back his losses.
Do you know how he died?
He drank too much and died of illness.
Officers.
Xia Zhiming drank excessively for years,
causing disrupted blood flow,
a sudden brain disease,
and his sudden death.
Do you know
who examined Xia Zhiming's body back then?
Zhao Yi'an.
I heard he died too.
But he has a cousin who is also a doctor.
He opened a pharmacy
called Baicao Pharmacy.
Got it.
I was never here today.
Why are you here?
Actually, when you came over,
I was following you the whole time.
You didn't notice me.
I was wondering if something's on your mind.
Not at all.
I've just never been to Chunyi's house before,
so I came to look around.
Let's go investigate the case.
Do you also suspect the landlady is the murderer?
I know the lady boss is your last remaining family.
You don't want her to make another mistake.
Actually, I was also wondering,
if the prime suspect in a case was my father,
what I would do.
I think I would do exactly what you did.
I wouldn't tell anyone,
investigate the case quietly by myself,
and silently pray for him,
hoping things wouldn't get worse.
I want to ask you.
If the landlady is really the killer,
would you cover for her?
I want to verify my hypothesis.
It's okay.
It really doesn't matter if you haven't decided.
You still have me,
and us.
We can search for the truth together.
Have you forgotten that our squad
shoulders everything together?
Where is Su Lang?
Did you agree?
Su Lang is with the King of Gamblers.
Alright, let's go check out Baicao Hall.
Let's go.
Zhao Yi'an was my cousin.
He passed away from a stroke years ago.
When he was alive, he also ran a pharmacy.
There weren't many coroners in his area.
So he also did some coroner work on the side.
After he passed away,
I brought over all the patient records
that he had collected.
So some patients who needed to see a doctor for medicine
could still come to me.
Father, I'm heading out.
I want to have soup tonight.
Okay.
The mountain roads are slippery.
Remember to be careful.
I know, Father.
I'm leaving.
That my daughter and I could reconcile,
I really must thank you two.
I wonder if there is anything else
I can help you with this time.
That Pan guy,
left you here as collateral before leaving.
A whole day has passed,
and he has no intention of paying to redeem you.
Don't blame me.
I can only follow the rules
and chop off both your arms first.
Don't be afraid.
My blade is very sharp.
My blade is faster.
Keep moving and behave yourself.
Hurry up.
Don't try to run. Go.
Tanghulu.
So Pan Lang lives here?
This house is abandoned.
My master brought me to stay here temporarily.
How long have you lived here with Pan Lang?
Good boy.
You are not stupid at all.
You lured me into a trap.
Put me down.
My master said
people who wear these clothes are bad.
Your master got it backwards. I catch bad guys.
Put me down. Hurry.
Pan Lang is dead.
Liar is a puppy.
Do you think this can trap me?
Don't let me catch you.
Tanghulu, one coin a stick.
Candied hawthorns! Come and take a look!
Little kid,
want a candied hawthorn?
Look, they are very sweet.
Pan is my master.
Do you have money?
No money?
You can't afford candied hawthorns without money.
Get lost, dirty beggar!
Get lost.
Candied hawthorns!
One coin per skewer!
Delicious candied hawthorns!
Jueming, you haven't been here for a long time.
I prepared a lot of delicious food for you.
Osmanthus cake, peony pastry.
The boss is upstairs.
Should I call her for you?
Mingzhu, no need.
I'll go find her myself.
You go back to your work.
What do you want to ask her?
I want you to carefully
watch the candlelight dance one more time.
Okay.
How is it, Jueming?
The dance is over.
Let's go find Su Lang.
Have you figured out the landlady's method?
When we went to her room this morning,
I smelled the ash of burnt cardboard.
I can tell you three need something from me.
Don't just stand there. Come in.
Then what did she burn?
Evidence that could prove her method.
Look at this.
How impressive.
The light and shadow principle of shadow play.
It's exactly the same as Sister Chunyi's modus operandi.
Yesterday, as we were about to leave,
Sister Chunyi deliberately kept us back to watch the candlelight dance.
During the performance of the candlelight dance,
we saw Sister Chunyi's silhouette behind the screen on the second floor.
In reality, it was just a piece of cardboard,
not Sister Chunyi herself.
The candlelight dance alternates between light and dark.
The proprietress knew exactly when it would be light and dark,
so she silently counted the beats in her head,
and went downstairs to the moat quickly in the dark.
Have you already tried it just now?
From the first time the lights went out until the end of the dance,
the timing is just right.
Well, you two actually have the mood to watch a play.
I caught you slacking off.
I've made a major discovery here.
I found Panlang's house.
Take me there.
This way.
Okay, okay.
This is where Panlang lives.
This kid isn't stupid at all.
After making me fall into the trap,
he slipped away.
These are all grave-robbing tools.
This is undoubtedly Panlang's house.
What exactly is the relationship between this fool and Panlang?
I asked around.
Panlang indeed picked up this fool in the ghost market,
and raised him for many years.
At first, he couldn't even speak.
Later, Panlang trained him to be a helper.
It is indeed as Little Mouse said.
Although he is foolish, he is honest and obedient.
So, when Panlang is robbing graves,
they cooperate with each other.
There are bones.
Come here.
Why didn't I notice it just now?
You are amazing, Miss.
These must be Xia Zhiming's bones.
Judging from the bone color and shoulder width,
the time of death and bone age match Xia Zhiming.
But why is there no skull?
Look, the gaps between the vertebrae
seem to be caused by external force.
It seems someone chopped it off with a shovel
and took the skull away.
Could there be a secret on the skull?
Come look.
How is it?
Jinglan, head back to the yamen first.
Carefully examine Panlang's head
to check for any external injuries.
Brother Su and I will go to Baicao Hall first to find Dr. Wang
and reopen his cousin's coffin for a re-examination.
Okay.
Brothers, dig faster
so we can go back early.
Envoy Jueming.
My cousin has been buried for so many years.
Why the sudden need to open his coffin for an autopsy?
There are still many doubts about this case.
Could there be another reason for my cousin's death?
It is still unclear.
We need to open the coffin for another autopsy.
However, without the cover of human skin,
the bones will reveal the truth.
If my cousin died an unnatural death,
please, Envoy Jueming, find the truth for him,
so he won't die in vain.
Of course.
Slow down.
Put it here first. Come.
Come help me hold this.
There is a silver needle on the side of the skull.
The silver needle entered through the left ear,
passed through the skull,
and protruded from the right side by about an inch.
This is the real cause of death.
This needle pierced the skull,
causing damage to key meridians.
Pan Lang lost control and fell into the water.
After his head hit the stones under the river,
he died.
Come, take the evidence back.
You guys bury the coffin.
Pan Lang robbed the tomb and dug up Xia Zhiming's remains.
He found a silver needle stuck in the skull,
and inferred the real cause of Xia Zhiming's death,
using this to blackmail Sister Chunyi for money.
Madam.
Let's go upstairs and talk.
Didn't I give you money this morning?
I was unlucky today and lost it all.
You are really greedy.
I'm telling you,
I won't give you any more money.
Then I'll go,
to report to the authorities,
and say there is a silver needle in your husband's skull.
His cause of death needs to be investigated again.
I'm off to report it to the authorities.
At 7 p.m.,
wait for me by the moat.
Bring the head.
Money for the evidence.
The pear is too sour.
Peaches are better.
Where is the stuff?
Where is the money?
What are you doing?
Acai is missing.
Why did you treat it like this?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm done! I'm reporting to the authorities right now.
Why would you report this to the authorities?
If you like them so much,
let's have one.
Then you won't be sad. Let go of me.
Let's have one.
Let go.
Stop right there.
Let's have another one.
Let go.
Help! Let go of me.
Help!
When Xia Zhiming died,
my cousin performed the autopsy.
Because the silver needle was too deep in the skull,
he didn't find any abnormalities.
Xia Chunyi was afraid of complications,
so she silenced him too.
He actually found a problem during the autopsy.
Officers,
Xia Zhiming died suddenly from a brain disease.
But greed is human nature.
After Zhao Yi'an learned the secret,
he actually tried to control her.
He blackmailed her repeatedly,
and showed up to humiliate her time and again.
A worthless thing.
If it's lost, it's lost.
If you want,
we can have another one.
If you want to keep the secret,
you have to stay with me always.
Do you still want to live together? Are you crazy?
Chunyi made one wrong step, leading to another.
She sank deeper into the swamp of mistakes,
and eventually murdered Zhao Yi'an.
Once your hands are stained with blood,
it's hard to wash them clean.
She completely stepped onto a path of no return.
To end this haunting nightmare,
Chunyi came to the city
and became the proprietress she is today.
What I just said is only my guess.
To find the real killer,
we have to visit Baicao Hall again.
I think Chunyi and Zhao Yi'an knew each other long ago.
After all, giving a false autopsy statement for a stranger
involves huge risks.
Dr. Wang.
Please,
find all the patient records your cousin collected
back then.
Okay.
Ma'am.
Look for girls downstairs.
I don't take clients here.
You really are forgetful, Ma'am.
I saw you kill Pan Lang.
I'm not blind.