( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
According to Coroner Li's examination,
the victims Niu Dali and Fan Le
both showed signs of poisoning.
It is highly likely they consumed water containing Datura flower
and fell into a coma after returning home.
Then, the killer went to the victims' homes
and helped them sit by the window.
The killer took a thin hemp rope
and tied a small knife to it
to make them one piece,
and looped the rope around the victims' necks.
They tied a stone to one end of the rope
to sink it into the well behind the scarecrow.
The other end was pulled straight
and tied to the iron nail on the wooden table.
A candle was placed next to the hemp rope,
its height taller than the rope.
Then the bloody razor was placed in the victims' hands.
Once everything was ready,
the killer could leave the crime scene in advance.
At first, the burning candle wouldn't reach the hemp rope.
When the candle burns out,
its height lowers.
The flame then reaches the hemp rope.
When the rope is burnt through,
the blade cuts the carotid artery.
Then the stones all fall into the well.
Is this how Niu Dali died too?
So,
the suspect could leave the night before,
and the victim wouldn't die until dawn.
In that case,
Jixiang would have the time to commit the crime.
I think Jixiang
knows best who you wanted to kill.
I...
This is what Jixiang asked the proprietress
to bring you today.
Inside, besides the treasure Fan Le extorted from you,
there is also the money Jixiang worked hard to save,
enough to buy your freedom.
But it is exactly this treasure
that is enough to prove
Jixiang is the real killer of Fan Le.
As for Niu Dali,
on his way home that day...
The person buying wine we met
must be Jixiang.
Are you blind?
I'm sorry.
I'll compensate you with a new jar.
Sir.
Here.
While handing the wine back to Niu Dali,
he tampered with it.
The wine Niu Dali received was poisoned.
Wearing a bamboo hat at night...
Niu Dali was poisoned because of this.
The wine shop owner
should also be able to recognize Jixiang.
And the datura flower is not easy to obtain.
I think
in Jixiang's house,
there are still unused petals.
Now,
do you want to talk?
Three years ago,
it was because he reported it in time
that Niu Dali was caught.
After I was sold into Yichun Pavilion,
He is also the one who visits me the most.
Regarding the curse,
I did mention it to him.
Because I am illiterate,
I needed him to help me write the name on the paper.
Do you really want him dead?
I haven't tried it yet.
As long as you want to.
If it works,
you must never tell anyone.
The spell is fake.
You should know it best.
From the very beginning,
you've used the lie of channeling spirits
to swindle money from people everywhere.
But only when you took the blame for my daughter,
you told the warmest
lie.
Mother.
You...
I admit it.
I have deceived many people.
Actually, I just wanted to earn more money
to redeem my daughter.
Xuanli,
I am sorry.
I have failed you.
Since you knew all along that Jixiang was the killer,
why didn't you tell me to arrest him?
Because I knew
Jixiang
would turn himself in for Zhao Xuanli.
Jixiang.
Why did you do so much for me?
Why did you kill for me?
Why are you so foolish?
Tell me.
Three years ago,
the one who knocked you out
was me.
Alright, alright.
Get out.
Go.
Officer, officer!
Someone raped a young girl.
For so many years,
I have been filled with guilt.
I only felt it was my own fault
that made you suffer such a misfortune.
For the past three years,
I've tried everything,
doing my best to make up for it.
When I saw you at Yichun Brothel
serving others,
my heart was bleeding.
In the process of getting along with you,
I realized you are
both kind and innocent.
I don't know when,
but I realized that
I have fallen deeply in love with you.
But how could I have the right to say it out loud?
All along,
I haven't had the courage to say sorry to you,
because I am the sinner who made you suffer.
My lord, this case is closed.
Jixiang is guilty of murder.
Zhao Xuanli's mother is suspected of fraud.
Zhao Xuanli is guilty of a heinous crime.
Considering her tragic background,
her sentence has been reduced.
I heard she has left Yichun Brothel
to become a nun in a temple.
These recent cases
were all solved by you.
I...
I only solved the case with the help of Miss Li.
If you answer like this,
my father naturally won't believe you.
He will definitely ask you again.
My daughter has been a coroner
for over a year.
Why didn't she solve cases before?
If he asks you this,
you must not answer immediately.
You need to think first,
and then make an inference.
What can I infer?
Just say...
This must be a process of accumulating experience.
In my opinion,
Li Jinglan is definitely a great coroner.
Sir, you must never underestimate a coroner's work.
It is the key to solving cases.
As soon as Li Jinglan arrives at the scene,
it's as if she can talk to the corpses.
All the clues on a body,
no matter how small,
can never escape her eyes.
Solving cases is good.
But for a girl,
dealing with corpses and blood all day long...
Being a coroner is a lowly job.
How will she get married in the future?
Did he really say that?
Yes.
Those were Lord Li's exact words.
He had his hands behind his back,
looked into the distance,
and let out a tragic howl.
Alas, how will she get married in the future?
Whether I can get married or not
is none of his business.
A coroner, what's wrong with that?
Why is being a coroner considered a lowly job?
It is not lowly.
Do murder cases need coroners?
Yes.
Through my autopsy,
can't I find out the time of death,
cause of death,
and the process of the crime?
Can't I also understand the killer's mindset,
and even reconstruct the crime scene?
Right?
Can't we use my diligent hands
to solve the case as soon as possible?
I
just want justice
to be served.
My lady, swords have no eyes.
I've already said all this.
I don't care about his attitude.
Anyway, I just want to be a coroner.
Since you've said all this,
I have one more thing to remind you of.
If you just judge by the behavior of the suspect and his family
and subjectively assume he is the killer from the start,
it's very easy to cause wrongful convictions.
Well put.
We can't hold such thoughts when solving cases.
The porridge is ready. Have a taste.
Come, try it.
You added so many lotus seeds.
These lotus seeds nourish the heart and calm the mind.
It also nourishes the kidneys.
Besides, its soft and glutinous texture
can make the sweetness of the red beans richer.
Lotus seeds can nourish the heart and calm the mind,
and nourish the kidneys.
Its soft and glutinous texture
can also make the sweetness of the red beans richer.
Here.
You cooked it. Thanks for your hard work.
Have a taste.
Thanks for your hard work. You have a taste first.
Where is your son?
Why haven't I seen him?
Why don't you feed him?
Right. Where has that brat been these two days?
I haven't seen him.
All right.
Where are you taking that?
Look how happy you are.
Did you think I made it for you?
We are going to Yichun Pavilion.
We got up early in the morning.
Do you need my help?
No need.
Go back and take care of your wife.
Remember to buy some flowers.
You made this?
Taste my cooking and see how it is.
Impressive.
Come, taste your brother Jueming's cooking.
Careful, it's hot.
Thank you, Chunniang.
Thank brother Jueming.
Thank me.
Thank you, brother.
After you moved out,
this room became empty.
I happened to be on the street
and saw these siblings begging there.
The sister had a high fever,
and the brother was bowing to people.
So I brought them back.
The boss lady is so kind-hearted.
She's only kind to children.
Brat.
Am I not good to all the girls in this house?
Fine.
Quick, take the porridge to them.
They are already eating.
Don't worry.
That's more like it.
Someone told me
that a person's palm lines dictate their destiny.
Do you believe in fate then?
If my fate is perfect, I will believe in it.
If it's bad,
why should I believe it?
But the family I was born into determined my fate.
Just like a shadow,
I can never shake it off.
Then I will
hide with you.
Away from the sunlight.
Let's hide our shadows together.
This jar of Xifeng wine
was buried more than ten years ago
by Constable Qin and me.
At that time, we agreed that
if we solved a major case,
we would dig it up
and drink to our hearts' content.
Today, we solved a major case,
so I brought it out.
Then we must have a good drink.
You kid, you really can solve any case.
There is no unsolvable case in this world,
only unseen clues and truths.
Time to eat.
Smells so good.
These dishes are great.
I have to say,
you really look
a bit like Constable Qin around the eyes.
But don't be proud,
you are still far behind him.
Constable Qin solved countless cases in his life.
We called him a divine detective.
To me, Constable Qin
was both a teacher and a friend.
Today,
by solving major cases one after another,
we can comfort his soul in heaven.
Constable Qin, I toast to you first.
I toast to Constable Qin too.
Constable Qin wasn't a heavy drinker,
these two bowls are enough for him.
It's obvious you're reluctant to part with this wine.
This wine is indeed precious.
I've saved it for ten years.
Today we solved a major case,
let's have a good drink together.
Here, son.
Thank you, Dad. Miss.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Constable Qin,
how did he die?
That day,
the Qin family suddenly caught fire,
and five people in his family were burned to death.
His father Qin Boyan,
his wife Su Yuerong,
his son Qin Nian,
and their daughter Qin Wan'er.
What caused the fire?
Was it investigated?
Yes, it was.
It was investigated very carefully.
It was just an ordinary accidental fire,
and the case was closed in a few days.
But when I was learning to be a coroner,
my teacher's teacher
was old Mr. Qin Boyan.
I guess I received the old master's true teachings.
He had a book back then
called Records of Corpse Examination.
It recorded a lot of things about autopsies,
a lot of real content and key points.
Too many.
It's just a pity it was lost.
I can never see it again.
Do you really want to read it?
I have it here.
Stop joking.
It's right there.
Come, let's drink.
Where is it?
Over here.
The one in the middle of the first row.
You really have it!
Would I lie to you?
Why do you have it?
I used to hang around the ghost market in my early years.
They had everything there.
So whenever I saw something I liked,
I would buy a couple of copies to read.
In that case,
you must have more strange tales and weird records.
Can I have a look too?
I actually have quite a few.
Go ahead.
All right.
I won't be polite then.
Come on, let's drink.
Let me have a look too.
Let's see what's good here.
'Family Rules of the Leng Family'.
What is this?
'Legend of the Strange Swordsmen'.
I've read this one.
'Collection of Beishan Tower'.
I've read this too.
You definitely wouldn't put the good stuff out in the open.
Let me see.
What good stuff is hidden in here?
Miss.
Hmm?
Come take a look.
Here is a couplet with elegant handwriting.
Let's go see.
Did you write this couplet?
I haven't seen this couplet before.
The paper is already yellowing.
It should be quite old.
If this couplet was found in the secret compartment,
it means it has been in this desk all along.
This desk is old.
Oh, Miss.
You can't call it an old desk.
I found this at the market.
It is an antique piece of furniture.
You all know antique furniture
is very valuable, yeah.
Look at this wood grain,
and this color.
It's good stuff.
But we said earlier
that since Jueming is moving to a new home,
we should get him a new set of furniture.
I know, Miss.
But I asked the carpenter.
It takes at least ten days to make a set of tables.
There's not enough time.
Besides, for these secondhand finds,
using antique furniture shows more taste.
Right?
Yes.
I really like this table.
The older it is, the more character it has.
It has texture and taste.
Let's take a look.
This first line looks quite good.
The second line seems
a bit frivolous.
Flippant.
Would any of you like to complete it?
Match it with a couplet.
Give it a try.
I have one.
Green willows swaying in the wind,
weak branches and thin leaves,
dancing wildly in the spring.
How is it?
My literary talent is not bad, right, Dad?
I really didn't expect this.
Do you like it?
It's for you.
Okay, I'll take it.
Since Brother Su composed it,
I will definitely treasure it.
Alright,
then keep it safe.
Brother.
Brother, come up here!
Brother, come look!
Coming!
Brother.
What is it, brother? This...
Who wrote the second line of this couplet?
No one has been in your room.
Didn't you write it yourself?
Could it be that
someone is helping me in secret?
You treasure whatever he writes, don't you?
Let me do one.
Go ahead then.
Clouds hide the ancient temple.
Distant bells echo among the deep pines.
As expected of the young lady. This is great.
She is elegant and virtuous.
And has brilliant literary talent.
The mood and the poetry
match perfectly.
Then look at you.
What is this rubbish? What's wrong with me?
It's completely unpresentable.
You have no literary talent at all.
How could this...
I do not know which worthy sage
added this second line to my scroll.
Who matched this line,
and why give guidance so quietly?
How strange.
That's not right.
No, no.
After we put it in just now,
the four of us haven't touched this table!
Right, no one touched it.
This... this is haunted! Haunted!
Haunted?
How interesting.
Could this table have a spirit
that can automatically generate essays?
Interesting.
Let me write a few words.
Put the one you just put in
again to see.
Should we
take
another look?
It should be about time.
Let's take a look.
Come.
Why is it a blank piece of paper?
Am I seeing things?
There's nothing on it.
There really are words.
I am a poor scholar.
My name is Sun Wenhuai.
I live south of the Luo River. It's appearing! It's appearing!
The third house to the east.
I found your couplet brilliant.
I pondered hard for a matching line but failed.
So I ask who you are.
Why do these words look like they were just written?
Is this drawer really haunted?
There's an address here.
Let's go take a look.
If this person really exists,
I'd like to meet him.
That's right. You should go take a look. Go.
Who is it?
I am Jueming, a Buliangren.
Excuse me, is this Sun Wenhuai's house?
Sun Wenhuai? Hmm.
He... didn't he die a long time ago?