Back then, when the masons were cutting into the mountain,
they discovered an ancient tomb during the blast.
Judging from the style of the ancient tomb,
it must be a grand tomb of a noble.
There were countless burial objects inside.
That Deputy Magistrate Cao insisted on going by himself.
And then?
Yeah.
At that time,
the main burial chamber was wide open.
It was full of gold and silver treasures buried with the dead.
It was absolutely dazzling.
At that moment, a shaman arrived.
She said they absolutely couldn't enter the tomb.
If anyone entered, they would surely face divine retribution.
But Cao Shaoyin refused to listen
and insisted on entering the tomb.
The shaman tried to stop him,
which made Cao Shaoyin fly into a rage.
He even sent many soldiers
to forcibly drag the shaman out of the tomb.
Cao Shaoyin led his men into the tomb.
After opening the coffin, strange things happened one after another,
and people kept dying.
Who among you here
entered the tomb with Cao Shaoyin?
I... I also went down into the tomb.
Me too.
So many people.
Yeah.
How strange.
Why did those few happen to be the ones who died?
That day, they were the first to dig to the tomb door,
and reported the matter to me.
Their actions must have angered the tomb owner,
causing them to suffer this misfortune.
He is Cao Shaoyin's younger brother.
We can't afford to offend him.
Alright, let me introduce him.
This is Military Advisor Cao.
He is Cao Shaoyin's younger brother
and also the chief supervisor for our quarrying operation.
Cao Fang.
Next to die from the curse was the Deputy Governor Cao.
According to his wife,
at noon every day,
the Deputy Governor would take a short nap after his meal.
When Cao Fang came to see him,
his wife went into the bedroom to wake him up.
But he had a dead look on his face,
and hung upside down.
Their deaths were all too strange.
Maybe it really was a curse.
Our opening the tomb must have angered the owner.
We shouldn't have dug it up.
I heard that in this kind of ancient tomb,
there are guardians at the entrance.
Those who break into the formation
will be punished by Heaven.
In that case,
we might as well try
going down the tomb to break the formation.
Going down the tomb?
This is my amulet.
I've never had an accident in so many years.
I'm giving it to you.
It will keep you safe.
Don't worry.
Let me put it on you.
Are we really going down the tomb?
Constable Qin, you can't pat people on the shoulder here.
It could be fatal.
What?
Do you really believe in curses that kill?
Otherwise, what?
Could someone have murdered them?
So far,
the first to die was the foreman
because he owed his subordinates wages
and had a dispute with them.
The ones who died later were all workers.
The last one was Junior Governor Cao.
He was advanced in years
and had no children,
but recently his young wife brought good news.
He was going to be a father in his old age.
He originally wanted to hold a banquet to celebrate,
but unexpectedly,
the happy event turned into a funeral.
The condition of their bodies currently appears to be consistent.
So we can now conclude
that the suspect is the same person.
But there's no connection between them at all.
Why would the suspect kill them?
Let's hurry back to the government office.
I think we need to sort out the clues again.
Right, we can't stay here long.
Alright.
Stop picking it up. Leave it.
This place isn't clean.
Ask Madam for another one. Okay?
Hurry up.
This incense bead was made by Mrs. Qin herself.
Although so many years have passed
and the fragrance is gone,
I still remember its size and color.
So, the grave robbers told the ghost market merchant
that they went through a lot of trouble to bring it out of the tomb
just to sell it for a good price.
And the tomb they robbed
is the princess's tomb you went to back then.
Yes.
Back then, all the burial objects in the tomb
were collected by the government
and sent to the Court of the Imperial Garrison in the capital for safekeeping.
Therefore, the tomb must be completely empty now.
Then how was the case solved back then?
And who was the suspect?
Why did he kill those people?
The trick the killer used is called
hiding a leaf in the forest.
What does that mean?
If you want to hide a leaf,
the best place
is in the forest.
If you want to cover up a murder motive,
the best way
is to kill more people.
At first, I didn't understand either,
why the suspect killed several people in a row
when the victims seemed entirely unrelated.
Actually, the suspect wanted to hide a leaf in the forest.
The real purpose was to kill Cao Shaoyin.
The rest of the murders
were just to cover up this real purpose.
And the only one who could do this
is you.
Cao Shaoyin is my own brother.
Why would I want to harm him?
Cao Shaoyin originally had no children,
so all his property would have been inherited by you.
But he had a son in his old age
and changed his mind under his wife's instigation.
You wanted to kill them after you found out.
Just when the ancient tomb was dug up while building the mountain road,
you came up with an idea.
You bribed the shaman
to spread rumors about the ancient tomb's curse,
while using the curse to kill them one by one
to minimize suspicion against you.
Nonsense.
Their strange deaths are... are what?
They were poisoned to death, weren't they?
Bo.
This is a colorless, odorless, and water-soluble Miao poison.
The poisoned person twitches all over and bends backward.
It's a rare and exotic poison.
I believe
there should still be some of this Miao poison in your mansion.
To prove you're not the killer,
we just need to search your mansion.
Before we reached his bedroom,
Army Supervisor Cao drew his sword and killed himself.
Later, we found Miao poison under his bed.
After Vice Governor Cao died,
Miss,
your father was promoted from Recording Supervisor
to the position of Vice Governor.
Elder Su,
may I have a look at this incense bead?
Sure.
It's been so long.
The smell must be gone by now.
Dad, I really didn't expect
that you were involved in so many strange cases when you were young.
You
always underestimate your dad.
Let me tell you, the cases I participated in back in the day
were countless.
The riverside cruise ship murder case,
the Luoyang golden Buddha theft case,
and the thousand-year-old painting theft case,
were all solved by me and Constable Qin.
As long as you are interested,
I will slowly tell you about them in the future.
Okay.
I just remembered
I still have soup stewing at home.
Then go quickly.
Hurry up and go.
That's not right.
I came today to ask you about the theft involving the Guan family's youngest daughter.
How did it turn into a tomb-raiding case?
Ah, I'm so cold.
I'm going inside to put on a jacket. Can I wear yours?
Okay, go ahead.
It's freezing.
About that case, I...
I recently learned a new dish,
beef stew. I'm going to study it.
No,
we have enough to eat.
I need to use the restroom.
Su Lang, where are you running off to now?
These kids.
Another poor man's tomb.
Master.
Why didn't you let me crawl through the tunnel this time?
We only dig tunnels for you to crawl through in big tombs.
Poor men's tombs are buried shallow,
and easy to dig.
But there's not much money in it.
Not even a gold tooth.
Xiaobao, hurry and bring the bag.
Hurry up.
Come on, hurry.
Master!
There's treasure!
This is a huge treasure!
Keep up.
Oh no, someone's coming!
Xiaobao, go home first.
I'll distract them!
Run!
Don't move.
Bad guy.
Let me go.
He's a fool.
I'm not a fool.
Let go.
Don't bite. Don't bite.
Let go of me.
It's me. It's me, sister.
We lost them.
The routes in this area,
they are more familiar with.
I should have called more people.
But I was afraid of alerting them.
In this tomb,
why are there no bones?
It must have been stolen.
Stealing bones.
What's the use of that?
Come here.
Xia Zhiming.
Wife, Xia Chunyi.
This is the grave of the landlady's late husband.
The landlady?
This place is so desolate and overgrown with weeds.
No one has visited this grave for a long time.
Ever since the day I met her,
I have never heard her mention her husband.
I only knew that her marriage was unhappy.
She ran away from home and stayed in Yichun Brothel.
Later on.
She became the landlady.
So you first met her in Yichun Brothel?
Yes.
Don't go! Don't go!
You little brat.
Believe it or not, I'll beat you to death.
You stole something! You're a thief!
Did I steal from you?
You stole the oil seller's money.
I saw it.
Forget it. Let the child go.
Child, I won't.
He is the thief.
See if I don't beat you to death today! I... I...
Stop!
I...
You're a grown man bullying a child here.
Aren't you ashamed?
Who are you?
None of your business.
Get lost.
You are causing trouble in front of my shop.
Believe it or not, I'll report to the authorities.
Yes, report to the authorities.
We must report to the authorities.
Come.
Why did he hit you?
He stole the old man's money.
The old man sells oil.
The money he works hard to earn every day,
once it passes through his hands,
will be stained with oil.
While ordinary people's money won't have oil on it.
Makes sense.
If you really didn't steal the old man's money,
do you dare to take out all your copper coins
and soak them in water?
We'll know if there are oil stains once tested.
Yes, take them out and test them.
Test them. Test them.
Take them out and test them.
Fine, test them.
We should have stopped him just now.
Eat slowly.
What's your name, and how old are you?
Jueming, 12 years old.
Where are your parents?
They are both gone.
Then where do you live?
My mother mortgaged the house.
The pawnbroker took it away.
I took my luggage and lived in a temple.
I look for work everywhere.
What can you do?
Wash dishes, cook, wash and dry clothes.
I can do it all.
I can also gather herbs.
My mother used to be a pharmacist.
Why don't you stay here and do chores for me?
But I just took over this place.
I can't pay you much.
But I can provide you with food and a place to live.
Are you willing?
I am.
Thank you, boss.
Don't call me boss, call me Sister Chunyi.
Sister Chunyi.
Eat.
The girls at Yichun Brothel
are mostly homeless.
She kindly took them in.
Such a loyal and affectionate person,
yet she never mentions her late husband.
She must have her difficulties.
The boss must have set up this tomb herself.
Now that her late husband's tomb has been robbed,
I must tell her.
As for those two thieves,
we must bring them to justice.
Pastries. Sweet and fragrant pastries.
- I'll take one.
- Alright, two coins.
Two coins.
Alright.
Take care.
What do you want?
This one? Two coins.
Two coins. Two coins.
Where is the money?
Go away, you idiot.
Seriously.
Don't ruin my business. Get lost.
Watch your mouth.
Are you...
I didn't know the child was yours.
Please forgive my offense.
- Wrap it up.
- Alright.
Here, young master, take it.
This one. And this one too.
- Wrap it up.
- OK.
What a snob.
- Take care.
- Let's go, Xiaobao.
OK.
Xiaobao.
You know, just reaching out your hand is useless.
You also have to say, Pan Lang is my master.
Then they will give you food.
Pan Lang is my master.
That's right. Eat.
Is it good?
Master, you eat too.
I won't eat. You eat, Xiaobao.
I have money now.
I can take you to a restaurant for roast chicken.
When you get to the restaurant, just yell, Pan Lang is my master.
Who said my Xiaobao is silly?
My Xiaobao is not silly at all.
Let's go play a few games first.
Make some more money, okay?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Panlang is my master.
Mr. Zhou, it's been a while.
Boss.
Have you forgotten all about me?
How could I?
Quick, we have good seats inside. Right this way.
Please.
Okay.
Right this way, sir.
Chunyi.
You brat.
Finally remembered to visit me today.
I've been too busy lately,
but I dream of you often.
Such a smooth talker.
You always know what to say.
Miss Li, Constable Su, please come in. This way.
Right this way.
Bring out all of Jueming's favorite dishes.
Bring extra portions. Sure thing.
Just a moment.
Let's go.
How have you been lately?
I'm doing well,
just a bit tired.
This new belt is nice.
Boss Zhou got some new fabrics,
so I made some clothes for the girls.
There were some scraps left over, and I didn't want to waste them,
so I made a belt.
Chunyi, was your late husband's name Xia Zhiming?
Yes.
Why do you ask?
Here's the thing.
Last night, we found his coffin in the eastern suburbs cemetery had been robbed.
Were there any valuable burial objects inside?
Burial objects?
No.
Our family was poor back then,
so there weren't any burial objects.
That's strange.
When we found the coffin, it was completely empty.
Even the bones were stolen.
Even the bones are gone?
Were there any valuable items worn on the bones?
Definitely not.
Then in the dead of night,
what use would a grave robber have for a pile of bones?
Could he be a necrophiliac?
Don't talk nonsense.
Just guessing.
A guess.
Don't worry, Chunyi.
We will definitely bring these grave robbers to justice.
It's fine.
There's nothing valuable in the coffin.
It doesn't matter if it's lost.
I've forgotten about this person long ago.
Come have some snacks.
This is osmanthus cake made by Sister Chunyi herself.
Try our signature dish.
Place your bets! Big! Big! Big!
Hurry up! Quick!
Bet! Place your bets!
Small! Small!
Again.
Place your bets.
Bet big or small.
I don't believe it won't be big.
All in on big! Big! Big!
Reveal!
Continue.
Place your bets.
Bet big or small.
I'll bet small this time.
Little goldfish.
Don't you have a mother either?
You said your mother is in the water.
I'll send you to find your mother.
Come back often.
Welcome to Yichun Pavilion. Come back often.
Cheers.
Chunyi, the bill.
Madam.
Come back often.
Coming.
I'll go say hello.
Oh.
Pan, you really come here morning and night.
I've been missing the boss lady day and night.
A day apart feels like three years.
Let's go upstairs and talk.
You guys go ahead and eat.
Come.
Mingzhu.
What's wrong?
Who exactly is this person
that the boss lady would personally entertain him?
I'm not exactly sure either.
I just know he's a cloth merchant.
He used to come by occasionally for a drink.
Mingzhu.
Please get me another portion of this pastry.
Coming right up!
Is the osmanthus cake good?
It is.
Let's save one for Brother Sulang later.
Yeah.
Hold out your hand.
Sister Chunyi said we can't just take money from others.
We can't take this.
Right.
Chunyi is right.
We really shouldn't just take things from others.
But this
isn't given for no reason.
I know you've had a hard life since you were little.
This
is a reward I prepared for your bravery.
Take it.
In the future, if you face difficulties
or need help,
you can protect yourselves better.
Thank you.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Ma'am, don't forget.
I'll be waiting for you.
Don't worry.
Come, take your time.
Take care.
Take care. Mr. Li, take care.
Sister Chunyi.
Jueming.
As for that grave robber,
we'll let you know as soon as we have news.
We'll be going now. Let's go.
Don't go.
There's a Candlelight Dance tonight.
You've seen it, but these two haven't.
What is the Candlelight Dance?
You'll find out in a bit.
How is it?
It's really nice.
Where did this dance come from? I've never seen it.
Sister Chunyi created this dance herself.
It uses candles as a guide, lighting or extinguishing them
to create an atmosphere of alternating light and dark.
The audience
can see the dancers constantly shuttling between light and dark.
Interesting, right?
It's really nice.
In ancient times, there was the magnificent Nishang Yuyi Dance,
and the elegant Jinghong Dance.
I've seen the passionate Huxuan Dance,
but I never imagined the magical Candlelight Dance.
It's truly fantastic.
I'm glad you like it.
I really enjoyed drinking today.
It was great.
Let's do it again next time.
Okay.
What's that?
Why is there a pair of shoes?
What's in the water?
It's a person.
It really is a person.
Okay.
Pan, who was just here, died by the moat.
What?
Thank you all for coming tonight.
Be careful. There is a step here.
How did you two find the body?
My lord.
Zhang and I were drinking in a tavern.
On our way back, we found someone in the water.
There is a small amount of silt in the corpse's mouth and nasal cavity.
The silt is attached to the inside of the nasal cavity and between the lips and teeth.
There is a small amount of fluid in the mouth.
It was likely inhaled while struggling after falling into the water.
Su Lang, come help me.
Turn the body over.
There is a distinct wound on the back of the head.
The wound is irregular in shape.
There are abrasions around it.
The surrounding hair is matted with blood.
It is suspected to be the fatal wound.
Blood is also oozing from the ear canal.
Let's check the rest of the body.
There are abrasions on the hands.
They were likely caused by scraping against underwater rocks
and other debris after falling into the water.
Rigor mortis is present,
initially showing in the jaw and neck.
The livor mortis is light red.
Time of death is less than two hours ago.
I remember when the proprietress saw Pan off,
we were also getting ready to leave.
She pulled us to watch the candlelight dance.
That was about two hours ago.
For a body recovered from the water,
there are four possible causes of death.
The first is natural drowning.
The second is being forced underwater and drowning.
The third is being thrown into the water after death.
The fourth is falling into the water after a fatal injury.
Generally, for natural drowning victims,
there is a lot of mud in the nose and mouth,
and dirt under the fingernails.
This is caused by struggling and grabbing.
So we can rule out the first possibility.
This is a homicide.
If the body was dumped after death,
the chest appears relatively flat.
When pressed, there's no obvious fluctuation of fluid.
But his whole body
is edematous.
Thus, he fell into the water while still breathing
and struggled for a while before he died.
At this hour,
the suspect had to keep the victim pressed in the water.
Wasn't he afraid of being seen?
Is it possible that he was drowned elsewhere
and then his body was dumped here?
If he was forced into the water to suffocate,
there would be petechiae in the victim's eyes.
But he doesn't have any,
and there are no choke marks on his neck.
There are no signs of pressure either.
And no scratch marks on the hands.
That leaves only one last possibility.
The victim suffered a fatal injury
and then fell into the water and died.
The suspect first invited Pan to the river,
then caught him off guard and hit his head with a rock,
causing him to fall into the water and die.
Be careful.
The soles are dry.
It seems before he fell into the water,
his shoes had already come off naturally.
The smell of the mud on the soles
perfectly matches the mud from the mountain graveyard.
Stepping on a yellow talisman.
What is this?
Edict.
This is a method used by grave robbers
to ward off evil when exploring yin tombs.
It seems he is the grave robber we are looking for.
He's dead just like that?
Little Mouse knows him.
Let's go ask him.
Come here. Why are you standing so far? Come take a look.
Get closer.
Yes, that's him.
He sold a lot of things at my place.
How did he get murdered?
What about the kid he usually brings along?
Do you know where he is now?
Do you know who killed him?
I don't know.
You don't know anything.
I don't know why you are here.
I found a bag of money this morning.
Is it yours?
Yes, yes, it's mine.
Yes, it's mine.
I even saw him this morning.
Go on.
He was gambling at Yabao Wang's place.
He was extremely generous with his money.
I told you to bet big.
Haozi, Haozi.
Haozi.
Don't go, Haozi.
Come back, Haozi.
Haozi, why are you running?
Give me some money.
Money.
I haven't made a single sale today.
How much did you lose?
Where did you get the money?
Just don't ask.
I can definitely pay you back.
No wonder you're so generous today.
Where did you strike it rich?
Let me tell you.
I went grave robbing again yesterday.
I cracked open a large coffin.
There were some truly valuable items inside.
Give me some today.
I promise to pay you back with interest.
I don't have any money.
But I know the Gambling King.
I can take you to get some credit.
Don't forget what you promised.
Let's go.
I haven't made a sale.
I know the Gambling King.
Okay.
Did he really say that?
Of course.
I swear I didn't get a single word wrong.
So you lent it to him?
I didn't, but...
I introduced him to the Gambling King for credit.
But he lost again.
This Gambling King
took the fool as a hostage
and ordered him to go get the money.
Xiaobao.
Xiaobao, go with this man later.
Master lost money.
I need to go find some money.
You stay here as collateral for now.
Understand?
Is that kid the hostage?
Yes.
I don't think Pan Lang would use money to redeem a fool.
Sir, you don't know this.
This fool is very important to Pan Lang.
Forming a team for tomb raiding is crucial.
Usually, it's either brothers
or a father and son.
One holds the rope outside,
while the other digs the hole.
If the hole is small,
Pan Lang lets the fool go in.
If the tomb is complicated,
Pan Lang goes down himself.
He knows this fool is not greedy and values loyalty.
He won't just pull the treasure up
and let go of the safety rope.
Where is the Betting King?
I really don't know.
I've told you everything I know.
Didn't I tell you?
Don't bother me these days if it's nothing. Don't you understand?
Chunyi.