( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Sir, when did Lingyin Academy close?
That was a long time ago.
About five years ago,
it closed down due to poor management.
Miss, if you want to learn arts,
I suggest you find another place.
It's completely abandoned.
There's nothing to investigate here.
Are you officials investigating a case?
If you need any help from me,
just let me know.
The third house to the east used to belong to the Sun family,
but now it's the Liu family.
Do you know anything about them?
The Liu family.
Their ancestors were in the hand-weaving business.
They moved here many years ago.
As for what's inside their house,
I have no idea.
Indeed.
It's completely empty.
There's nothing left.
Brother, I'm afraid your mysterious friend isn't coming.
Then who on earth matched my couplet?
And how did they
silently put it in this hidden compartment?
I think it's either a prank,
or you're just teasing me for fun.
I'm really not lying to you.
The writing on this paper isn't mine.
You know that at least, right?
Besides, if I could match it so well,
I wouldn't have been so worried a few days ago.
Then who wrote this?
Well...
Let's go take another look.
Yeah.
Brother,
words have appeared on this paper again.
I saw your letter.
Based on what is written,
its owner is the Liu family, not you.
I also went to the nearby music academy,
only to hear that Lingyin Academy
was destroyed five years ago.
Therefore, the time and place you mentioned are both wrong.
Could this desk reply on its own?
It's not the desk that can reply,
but the previous owner of this desk.
Previous owner?
He said the addresses of the house and the academy are correct.
He is also curious about how he could receive a reply,
because he only put the rice paper in the hidden compartment.
After a while,
handwriting appeared on the paper.
It's exactly the same as our encounter.
He also said he just finished attending the Lotus Pond Poetry Gathering.
This couplet is from the gathering.
However, he couldn't match it at the gathering,
so he copied it down
and pondered over it after returning home.
He said
he attended the Lotus Pond Poetry Gathering?
Exactly.
This is truly bizarre.
Because the poetry gathering is crowded and noisy every year,
I'm afraid of any problems occurring,
so I send patrols to ensure safety.
If I remember correctly,
the theme of the annual gathering is its name.
This year's gathering is called Willow Moon.
Last year's gathering was called Reed.
And the Lotus Pond Poetry Gathering was over ten years ago.
That's strange.
Since this person has been to the gathering,
how could he remember the name wrong?
December 22nd, the 11th year of Kaiyuan.
What era are you from?
So,
the era Sun Wenhuai lived in
is actually 17 years ago.
It means
the secret compartment of this desk
can send letters back to 17 years ago.
We have been exchanging letters with someone from 17 years ago.
How could this be?
This is too absurd.
He claims he is in the 28th year of Kaiyuan,
which is exactly 17 years later.
Then how is he communicating with us?
Through this desk?
Brother,
where did you buy this desk?
From a pawnshop.
The owner said
this desk is quite old.
No one had asked about it for a long time,
so he sold it to me at a very low price.
If he really lives 17 years later,
how can he prove it?
I don't know.
How could there be a problem with this desk?
If you truly live 17 years later,
how can you prove
what you say is true?
He asks how we can prove it.
That's easy.
Just tell him who our emperor is
and what the era name is.
It seems to be the same 17 years ago.
Then tell him who our Deputy Governor is.
The Deputy Governor back then was Cao Fang,
not your father yet.
Then how can I prove that the Deputy Governor seventeen years later is Li Ze?
He's in a time seventeen years ago.
He has no way to verify it at all.
Yes.
What should we do?
I remember now.
He said the time he is in is December 22nd, right?
Yes, exactly.
I remember it very clearly.
December 23rd
is the day the results of the Lotus Pond Poetry Gathering in Luoyang City are announced.
The top poet that year
was named Zhou Ran.
I remember it clearly.
He was so excited and happy
that he stepped on a big melon peel,
fell flat on his back,
and made a huge fool of himself.
Where did that melon peel come from?
It must be from those old ladies who threw it away after eating.
So I think with the huge crowd back then,
many people should remember this incident.
Zhou Ran.
Brother,
if the results are truly released tomorrow,
why don't we go take a look?
We'll know the truth immediately.
Alright.
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Zhou Ran.
My name is Zhou Ran.
I passed.
I, I passed.
I am Zhou Ran.
I, I am the top scholar.
I am the top scholar.
The top poet slipped on a melon peel and fell.
I passed. I passed.
Thank you, everyone.
I passed.
I am the top poet. I am the top poet.
I am the top poet.
I passed.
I now completely believe
you are from 17 years in the future.
I am thrilled
and eager to ask you.
Seventeen years later,
will I become a scholar?
Will my brother, Sun Wuwei,
become a Great General?
Sun Wuwei.
Why does this name sound so familiar?
I just can't recall it right now.
Doesn't the flatbread vendor in the south of the city
also go by the name Sun Wuwei?
Right, right, right. That vendor is named Sun Wuwei.
It seems if we find Sun Wuwei first,
we might uncover the truth of this matter.
It's my brother's handwriting.
This indeed happened back then.
So,
you were the one talking to my brother all that time.
After all these years,
you actually received each other's letters.
Then where is Sun Wenhuai now?
My brother
passed away long ago.
Does that mean
we've been talking to a dead person these past few days?
Right.
When did he die?
It's been 17 years.
I'm a bit confused.
What exactly is going on?
That night,
I was practicing martial arts downstairs.
Suddenly, I heard my brother yelling upstairs.
I rushed there and found out
that the couplet my brother had been racking his brains over
had a better second line.
At first, we looked around for the person who matched the couplet,
but later we learned
that this person actually lived 17 years later.
He predicted that the winner of the poetry contest would fall in public tomorrow
to prove his words.
My brother and I happily went back inside to write a reply.
Just as we received his letter,
the authorities came to make an arrest.
My brother
was immediately taken away by the constables.
He wrote a letter in prison
and asked me
to make sure to put it in the secret compartment of the desk.
Over here.
Take a close look at this desk.
Is it the one your brother used back then?
This is exactly the desk my brother used to practice writing.
This is the character 'Wu' I carved back then.
Did you really carve it?
Judging by the change in wood color and the wear,
it was indeed carved a long time ago.
Could this desk really travel through time
and let us contact people from 17 years ago?
When we open the drawer,
put a letter inside and close it,
the other side receives our message.
When I was little, my brother received letters this way too.
In that case,
the mechanism works the same on both sides.
What are you writing?
I need to tell my brother
that he's been framed.
The constables are coming to arrest him.
He must leave home immediately
and run as far as possible.
Your brother was framed?
What crime is he accused of?
Murder.
Brother, when will the letter arrive?
It should be here by now.
Open it and see.
It's here.
I have been framed.
The constables are coming soon.
Flee immediately.
Brother.
Does this look like my handwriting?
Are you Sun Wenhuai?
Officers.
That is me.
Take him away.
Move.
Brother!
What are you doing?
Officers!
Brother!
What wrong have I done?
You must have made a mistake.
There is no mistake.
Come to the yamen with us.
Move. Little brother!
Brother!
Don't interfere with official business.
You...
Why are you arresting my brother?
Brother!
What exactly happened?
Thinking back to the day my brother was arrested,
I finally understand.
The last letter we saw was written by me.
It was me telling him to run away.
But neither of us realized it at the time.
We just felt the handwriting looked familiar.
Then the constables entered the room
and took my brother away.
Are you saying Sun Wenhuai, while in prison,
wrote a letter,
and asked you to put it in the secret compartment?
What was the content of the letter?
I never read it.
I was so anxious at the time
that I hurried home to put it in the secret compartment.
We didn't receive this letter.
I remember
it was sent during Xushi that night.
Maybe the timing doesn't match.
What time is it now?
It is Wushi now.
What time was Sun Wenhuai arrested?
Also Wushi.
You mean
at Wushi on this day 17 years ago,
Sun Wenhuai was arrested?
And you were entrusted to put the letter in the secret compartment.
So,
we have to wait until the time of Xu to get a reply,
and then we'll know what's in the letter.
It is still too early for the time of Xu.
You might as well go back first.
Let's go back to the yamen to check the files,
and then see
if there are any records of Sun Wenhuai's murder case.
We will come back after checking the files.
I remember
that summer,
the weather was exceptionally hot.
When the new clerk was sorting out the files,
he accidentally knocked over the candlestick.
All the case files from April to June of that year
were completely burned.
The case of
Sun Wenhuai you want to check
happens to be burned too.
Why such a coincidence?
Nearly thirty
case files were completely destroyed.
It couldn't be helped.
Why must you all insist on investigating such an old case?
Since the materials no longer exist,
there is no need for us to continue the investigation.
We will take our leave now.
I really couldn't help.
I am ashamed.
It really is a letter at the time of Xu.
Open it and see what it says.
This...
Why is it a letter written in blood?
Meeting with this sudden disaster,
I was misunderstood by Constable Su Yu'an.
I truly did not cause Miss Liu's death.
The authorities have always been just.
I believe they will get to the bottom of this case.
If you read this letter,
please let me know if this case has been cleared.
I eagerly await your reply.
How many constables in the government office are named Su Yu'an?
I really don't know.
He is Sun Wenhuai.
It seems you've remembered something.
The Miss Liu he mentioned
should be Liu Shiqin.
She and I were neighbors since childhood.
Childhood friends.
Though we live far apart now,
our friendship remains as before,
just like real siblings.
When others listen to my playing,
they are full of energy.
When you listen to my playing,
you get drowsy.
No, no.
It's just that your playing
makes me feel so peaceful,
and cures my insomnia perfectly.
I was just an ordinary constable back then,
responsible for patrolling the streets.
Brother Su.
That night, Liu Shiqin asked me for help.
That man is following me.
She said she was being followed by a man,
and felt he had malicious intent, making her afraid.
So I reprimanded the man privately,
warning him not to do it again.
That day, this man went to find Liu Shiqin again.
Liu Shiqin.
To avoid his harassment,
she accidentally fell from a high place
and broke her ribs.
But this person insisted it was unintentional.
Why didn't you knock?
Alright.
Let him hear it too.
But based on my deduction,
he intentionally harassed Liu Shiqin.
So I informed the magistrate
that he did it on purpose.
The case then entered the liability period.
The so-called liability period means that
if the victim's injuries worsen within a certain time
or even lead to death,
the perpetrator will bear
all the criminal penalties.
Since Liu Shiqin broke her ribs,
the liability period is 50 days.
On the twentieth day, Shiqin,
Liu Shiqin succumbed to her injuries
and died in her bed at home.
Shiqin!
Since it was within the probationary period,
How could this happen?
the man was convicted of murder.
I only remember that man's face,
but I don't know his name.
I didn't know he had a brother named Sun Wuwei.
So you are the one who framed my brother.
He didn't mean to break Liu Shiqin's ribs,
but you insisted it was deliberate.
My brother's death
has everything to do with you.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
Let me go!
Don't move!
Su Lang!
Let him go.
Sun Wuwei.
A fight won't bring your brother back,
nor will it help us find the truth.
If we were in Constable Su's shoes at the time,
he did nothing wrong.
If your older brother was truly wronged,
we should sit down,
calm down,
unravel the clues,
and investigate the cause.
Constable Su.
Who did Liu Shiqin's autopsy back then?
Were there any suspicious points?
I later brought Liu Shiqin's body back to the yamen.
It was personally examined by the coroner Qin Boyan.
The coroner's report was very clear.
She fell from a height 20 days ago,
which broke two ribs.
Her liver ruptured and she bled to death.
There were no new injuries in the past 20 days.
So the cause of her death
was just the injury from 20 days ago.
Then what about the coroner's report?
Did you forget?
Today we went to the archives.
Registrar Fang said
the fire had burned the files.
That's the most suspicious part.
Why were only the files from April to June of that year burned?
I know you find it suspicious,
but there's no way for us to continue investigating.
This case is very old,
and both the suspect and the victim
have already passed away.
The files are gone too.
Unless
we can question Sun Wenhuai from back then.
I put the letter from my brother into the secret compartment.
Since there was no response,
I never opened it again.
To pay for my brother's lawsuit,
I sold all the furniture in the house
to the secondhand shop.
But in the end, we still lost the lawsuit.
Filled with grief and indignation, I made a scene at the government office.
I was exiled to Lingnan,
and only returned to Luoyang half a year ago.
Now,
I make a living by making sesame flatbreads.
So even if we write a letter to ask about the case,
you from 17 years ago wouldn't be able to read it.
Wouldn't be able to read it.
Do we have any other options?
If Qin Boyan was really the one who did the autopsy back then,
he must have kept a draft.
When I bought the Corpse Observation Record in the ghost market,
the broker there told me
that Qin Boyan had a habit when doing autopsies.
After every autopsy,
he would keep a draft.
Because he well knew the hardships of coroners,
and also to make it convenient for people to learn and reference.
After the fire at the Qin family,
a lot of things were indeed lost.
Did those things end up in the ghost market?
Valuable things naturally have their own ways of circulating.
You actually have such a treasure?
The deceased Liu Shiqin.
The ribs on the lower left of her chest were broken.
The broken ends pierced her liver,
causing unstoppable bleeding,
leading to severe injury and death.
The marks of the broken bone do not look like an old injury.
It seems someone inflicted further harm on the old injury.
Therefore, the cause of death is suspicious.
It is not solely due to the fall from the stairs 20 days ago.
There might be a hidden truth.
Then this autopsy report is enough to prove
that my brother is not the real culprit who caused Liu Shiqin's death.
Is the information in this autopsy report true, Constable Su?
The autopsy report states it clearly.
Why is what you said different?
Or are you lying?
This is not right.
I didn't lie.
It was written clearly on the autopsy report back then.
Otherwise,
the government office wouldn't have sentenced Sun Wenhuai to death for murder.
Do you think the whole government office would lie along with me?
Right.
How can we prove that this is definitely Qin Boyan's handwriting?
It could also be forged.
Qin Boyan did so many autopsies for the government office.
As long as we find the autopsy reports in the files
and compare them,
the truth will be clear at a glance.
And I believe
the one in the master advisor's hand must be fake,
so it couldn't be kept.
This perfectly explains
why the files that were burned
happened to be from April to June of that year.
That means this master advisor was forging it.
He has a problem.
Arrest him.
The master advisor died many years ago.
How did he die?
He died of a stroke at home.
It seems the lead is broken again.
If Liu Shiqin was murdered while recovering from her injuries,
and the autopsy report was forged
to frame Sun Wenhuai, who was in his probation period,
then we just need to figure out
who benefits most from her death.
That's right.
After Liu Shiqin's death,
her father became seriously ill.
He passed away in less than a year.
All of her father's property
was passed to his adopted daughter, Liu Qing.
And Liu Qing's husband, Chen You,
is the current county magistrate.
To find out the truth,
we need to visit Baicao Pharmacy again.
That wicked woman is finally in prison.
I never expected her to harm Wang Wan.
Now, I'll just pretend I never married her.
However, Wang Wan has moved back in.
My daughter.
In the past, because of that wicked woman,
I rarely communicated with my daughter.
Now that we spend more time together,
I realize
how sensible she is.
Dr. Wang.
The world is full of hardships.
Family ties are unbreakable.
It is truly a blessing.
I came today
to ask you about something.
It's about Liu Shiqin's father, Liu Jingzhao.
As far as I know,
Liu Jingzhao often came here for medicine before he died.
Is this true?
Yes, it is true.
What disease did he have?
Diabetes.
When he came to me for medicine,
he was already terminally ill. The medicine is ready.
Taking medicine was just to maintain his condition. Thank you.
At that time,
I prescribed him snakegourd root, dwarf lilyturf, and Rehmannia.
These herbs can relieve the discomfort to some extent,
but they cannot cure it completely.
Do you remember when he came for the consultation?
It's been a long time.
I can't quite remember.
Was Liu Shiqin still alive at that time?
When Liu Shiqin was recovering at home,
he was already blind
and had lost his sense of taste.
Why is that?
This is because when the wasting-thirst disease becomes severe,
the toxins in the body erode the meridians.
That means
while Liu Shiqin was recovering,
her father was already terminally ill.
Exactly.
Enjoy your tea, everyone.
I need to get back to work.
Okay, thank you.
Please.
Let's go.
Constable Su.
Liu Shiqin and Liu Qing,
how is their relationship?
They are not as close as normal biological sisters.
But since they live under the same roof after all,
they get along fine.
Where was Liu Qing before she was adopted?
I think it was Jingkong Temple.
Then why did he adopt Liu Qing?
Well, I'm not too sure about that.
Did Mr. Liu leave a will?
I think so.
I see.
Su Lang.
Hurry up and investigate if this happened.
After the investigation, let's go to the government office.
No, let's meet back at the mansion.
Okay.
Such an old case,
why are they reinvestigating it?
It doesn't make sense.
Moreover,
there's nothing related to this case happening now.
I heard the last man say
he's going to Jingkong Temple.
The Buliangren they just met,
where does Jueming live?
Go, go, go.
Is Sun Wenhuai not dead?
Impossible.
He clearly died.
Guo Cheng, come here.
Come here.
Look.
Prefect Chen.
Sun Wenhuai was beheaded.
We were all watching at the execution ground.
It's impossible he's not dead.
According to what they said,
it was through this table
that they made contact with each other.
You mean
this table connects the past and the present
and intertwines them?
Better to believe it
than not.
Then I'll burn this table.
Let's see how you contact each other then.
Sun Wenhuai,
you don't give me peace even in death.