( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
It has been confirmed
that the skeleton found by the villagers a few days ago
belongs to Mr. Jiang's daughter, who went missing eight years ago.
Moreover, Mr. Jiang
has also identified the remains.
This way.
Okay.
We have reached the skeleton.
Go a bit further.
Look.
I forgot you can't see.
But I noticed something strange.
There are pieces of red cloth on her upper body.
But Mr. Jiang told me
that his daughter didn't own a red dress.
Could it have been left by the culprit?
The young lady wanted to keep this boy,
bought him a house,
and had him repay the debt by solving cases.
He gets two taels of silver for every case he solves.
But she forgot
that Jueming can't stand the sight of corpses at all.
Then deduct one tael of silver from his pay.
His martial arts aren't as good as mine either.
Indeed.
My son is so amazing.
Let's deduct another tael of silver.
I think it's still a girl.
Let me untie you first.
Hey.
Don't look this way.
Wait a moment.
Usually, only corpses come here.
Very few living people do.
Um, let me find it.
This one.
Here, look.
And this is the statement.
Mr. Jiang's statement.
Yes.
From a single skeleton,
you can vividly describe the victim's murder.
That's truly rare.
As a woman,
why would you choose to deal with corpses?
You don't have to tell me if you don't want to.
I grew up without a mother,
and my father was rarely home.
I watched the small animals I raised slowly die,
so I got used to dead bodies.
Later, I started studying them.
I studied why they died
and why they got sick.
Then, I secretly watched my father judge cases,
and read a lot of coroners' documents.
I found that the dead are more honest than the living.
Corpses don't lie.
They just lie there quietly.
As long as you are careful enough,
you can definitely find the stories they carry.
What you say makes some sense.
Others work as coroners for a living.
You do it out of true passion.
And it saves me a lot of trouble.
As the daughter of the Deputy Prefect,
what trouble could you possibly have?
Of course I have a lot of trouble.
This is the son of Zhao Qi, the Vice Minister of Revenue,
Young Master Zhao.
This is my daughter, Li Jinglan.
You two are of a similar age.
You must have a lot to talk about.
Young Master Zhao, please have a seat.
Have a seat.
I heard from Lord Li that you also like reading.
I wonder if it's "The Analects" or "The Five Classics"?
Neither.
I like reading the Huangdi Neijing
and Tanglu Shilu.
It talks about
various structures of the human body
and the tragic states of different deceased.
From the perspective of a corpse,
first of all,
it is very interesting.
You must know how to embroider.
Embroidery?
It's a bit tedious.
However, I am good at suturing corpses.
It's okay. Never mind.
My daughter is just getting carried away.
Mr. Zhao, please don't mind her.
May I ask why you always deal with corpses?
Because I am a coroner.
To me,
corpses can talk.
Whether it's a headless corpse
or various dismembered body parts,
I can touch them with both hands
and carefully examine them.
I suddenly remembered.
My father has an appointment.
I have other things to do.
Goodbye.
Take care, Mr. Zhao.
Mr. Zhao!
My daughter,
if you keep fooling around like this,
who will dare to marry you?
I'm just telling the truth.
Without blind dates
and the etiquette of a lady,
you will find that getting along with corpses
is much more peaceful.
How did you know I am the daughter of the Deputy Magistrate?
You can walk safely in front
and let Constable Su walk behind you.
You are no ordinary coroner.
In this Luoyang City,
although the magistrate is respected,
the people who can make his constables obey them completely
are very few.
The magistrate only has one son,
who is still a child.
The wealthy merchants in the city
are rich,
but they can only maneuver in business matters.
Although there are high officials and nobles,
they serve their own masters
and are not closely related to the affairs of the yamen.
Taking everything into account,
your surname is Li,
you must be the only daughter of Deputy Magistrate Li Ze,
Li Jinglan.
This guy really has some skills.
I think he just got lucky.
I read Lord Jiang's confession.
Jiang Siyan left the candy shop that day
and headed home.
If we walk her route home,
we should be able to find some clues.
This case happened eight years ago.
What clues could there be?
Jiang Siyan took this road home that day.
There are so many people on this street.
The crime couldn't have been committed here.
Come, take a look!
Candied hawthorns! Fresh candied hawthorns! Take a look!
Delicious wontons!
Fresh out of the pot! It smells great!
Official trinkets!
Come and take a look!
Candied hawthorns!
My silk is the best!
Wait.
That day,
Mr. Jiang found the little girl's embroidered shoe right here.
There are very few pedestrians here.
And Jiang Siyan might have come home at night.
If it was night,
and if it was raining,
it would be easier to commit the crime.
Who knows which shop sells this yellow paper?
You don't think
the killer came to burn this in person, do you?
After committing their first murder, many suspects,
even if they aren't caught,
at certain times,
will restlessly return to the scene.
They either watch silently,
or
burn some yellow paper,
praying not to be haunted by vengeful spirits.
Honestly,
what he said makes some sense.
I've also heard that
if a person dies an unjust death,
and their grievances are not redressed,
they won't be willing to reincarnate.
Their soul
will repeatedly wander around the place they were murdered.
You saying this yellow paper was burned by the killer
is quite possible.
These are all businesses here,
with no residences.
Really, coming here to burn paper is very suspicious.
If this yellow paper was really burned by the suspect,
then this is our only hope.
This talisman looks like it was drawn by Daoist Priest Chen,
right?
Look.
Was this bought from you?
This was indeed bought from me.
I even drew the disaster-averting talisman on it myself.
Do you remember who bought it?
During the Ghost Festival, there are too many people buying this kind of paper.
But not many ask for this disaster-averting talisman.
Then recently,
who bought a lot of it?
Let me think.
Let me remind you.
Has anyone recently said
they felt like they did something guilty
and couldn't sleep?
Guilty?
I remember now.
There's a man named Cao Tai.
He said he did something wrong
and couldn't sleep well at night.
He said he always felt like his house was haunted at night,
and specifically asked me to do a ritual at his house.
I know I was wrong.
He said he did something wrong
and was haunted by vengeful spirits.
Didn't you ask him what he did wrong?
You know, I'm just a talisman seller.
Every day,
those who come to pray for blessings or confess
are everywhere.
I can't ask everything.
I wouldn't have time to ask them all.
Besides,
who hasn't done something they feel guilty about?
Put simply,
don't you have any secrets?
This Cao Tai...
Let's go. Take us to his house.
This is Cao Tai's house.
Cao Tai!
What is this stuff?
Did you do this?
Cao Tai told me to do it.
I'm just trying to make a living here.
Cao Tai.
Hurry, come here.
Come.
Here.
Hurry and let him down.
How did he die?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
How did he die?
I'll go check.
Put him down.
There are no obvious signs of a struggle on the body.
The strangulation mark on the neck is clear and obvious.
Aside from the strangulation mark,
there are no obvious injuries on the rest of the body.
Judging from the stiffness of the knuckles
and the ambient temperature,
the victim probably died last night during the You hour.
Are there any other items near him?
There's only a wooden ladder.
It must have been used for the hanging.
Do not move any items.
Move this away first.
Alright,
you guys, come
carry the body away first.
Hurry.
Can I go now?
When did he buy the talisman from you?
Yesterday, around the Shen hour.
This has nothing to do with me.
I just sell talismans.
You can't go yet.
You'll come back to the yamen with us later for questioning.
Stay right here.
Alright, next,
let's have our master step up.
The rope's structure is intact.
The angle and position are normal.
It looks like a typical hanging.
Combined with the autopsy results,
it is indeed a suicide by hanging.
The body has been moved away.
If he can really find something out,
I'll be damned.
What are you doing?
Imitating the victim's actions before death.
You're doing this again?
Doing what again?
When I first met him,
he was in a coffin imitating a corpse.
Imitating a corpse?
It seems he forgot to tell us
when to let him down.
Is he... is he dying?
No.
If he really can't take it, he'll tell us.
Right.
He probably can't take it anymore.
Hurry, let him down.
Can't take it?
Danger!
Hurry!
It's been a long time since I made such an error in judgment.
Drink some water.
Kid, were you really suffocating?
That ladder,
has it been moved?
No.
It hasn't been moved.
If that's the case,
there must have been another person in this room.
Normally, when a person hangs themselves,
they step on a chair. After the chair falls,
their legs dangle and struggle.
The body will instinctively try desperately to save itself.
At this point, if they were given a solid object,
they absolutely wouldn't die.
Unless...
Unless someone grabbed him tightly,
preventing him from stepping on the ladder.
What is this?
Bring it here quickly.
Are there any women in Cao's family?
I... I really don't know.
You are useless.
This Cao Tai,
is he some kind of pervert?
This blindfold isn't bad, right?
I made it.
The young lady is indeed beautiful and intelligent. A true lady from a noble family.
Smelling the corpse blindfolded.
There's a strong smell of rouge on his legs,
mixed with a herbal scent.
There are no herbs kept in his house.
The suspect
is very likely a woman,
and has something to do with herbs.
Could it be that the suspect has a sick patient at home?
Judging from this smell,
it's more like someone who deals with medicinal materials all year round.
Only they would have such a strong herbal smell on them.
Perhaps
it's related to a pharmacy.
Captain Su,
immediately search all the pharmacies Cao Tai visited when he was alive,
starting from when he was born.
I'll get to it right away.
I've checked.
Among the dozens of pharmacies in Luoyang,
this is the only one with a female shopkeeper
and associated with Cao Tai at the same time.
And this place is only a mile away from Cao Tai's house.
Right here.
So it's this one.
Look at the paper umbrellas.
Come and take a look.
This pharmacy belongs to my husband.
Unfortunately, today,
he went up the mountain to gather herbs,
and hasn't returned yet.
Didn't it rain heavily yesterday?
So I closed the shop early
and never left the house.
So you were home alone last night?
Captain Su, you might as well speak frankly.
Last night, Cao Tai died in his home.
Don't be nervous.
In order to solve the case,
we are questioning everyone he knew one by one.
He died?
How did he die?
Could it really be that his life was claimed by a ghost?
Mrs. Wang, what do you mean by that?
Did Cao Tai say something to you?
Come, sit down, tell us slowly.
Cao Tai often came here to get medicine.
We got familiar with each other over time.
Yesterday afternoon, he came to see me.
You're here.
What medicine do you need today?
What's wrong?
I want some medicine to calm the nerves.
What happened?
I did something wrong.
A ghost is trying to take my life.
Please,
save me.
Okay.
Save me.
I asked him what was wrong,
but he wouldn't tell me.
In the end,
he left in a daze by himself,
and even forgot to take his medicine.
Constable Su, this is the medicine Cao Tai prescribed.
Now, he can't take it anymore.
Su Lang.
Where is my father?
He went to gather herbs
and will be back tomorrow.
Then please give him a message when he returns.
Tell him I came looking for him.
Never mind, don't look for him.
I'll tell him myself.
Okay.
Who is this little girl?
My husband's child with his ex-wife.
I want to ask,
did Mrs. Wang
meet anyone in the shop yesterday?
Well,
no.
Did the proprietress of Baicao Hall go out yesterday?
It rained at 5 PM yesterday.
I went back early.
I didn't see anything.
Excuse me, did you see the proprietress of this shop go out yesterday?
Thank you, sir. I don't know.
Did Mrs. Wang go out yesterday?
I don't know.
I don't know. I didn't pay attention. Okay, thank you. Okay.
Brother, did Mrs. Wang go out yesterday?
I don't know.
I found out something.
At 1 PM yesterday,
Cao Tai did come to see Mrs. Wang,
and they stayed together for about an hour.
After that, Cao Tai probably went to see Taoist Chen.
What about 5 PM yesterday?
It was raining heavily.
People all stayed indoors.
There was no one on the street.
So no one noticed if she went out.
That woman we just met,
bring her to the government office.
We should be able to get something from her.
How many days have you been starving?
I only came because you said I could eat my fill.
I mean, eat slowly.
What do you want to ask?
I'll answer while eating.
You don't seem to like your father's new wife.
Would you like her if you were me?
I'm not afraid to let you know.
This Baicao Hall was built by my birth parents,
step by step, from a street stall to a small shop.
She, on the other hand, seduced my father with her wiles
and got a high position.
It seems your father isn't a good person either.
That's right.
So now, I don't have much contact with them.
If my mother hadn't told me to fulfill my filial piety,
I definitely wouldn't have any contact with them.
Then you used to live with your father.
Why did you move in with your mother later?
Because she thinks
I'm the reason she can never have a child in this life.
At that time, she was pregnant
and was in charge of decocting medicine at home.
What happened?
Madam.
Madam,
wait a moment.
I'll go get your medicine.
Don't be afraid.
Our child will be fine.
After this fall, she will never be able to have children.
Tell me, is this retribution?
Was she careless herself,
or did you push her down?
My father asked me the same thing back then.
What do you think?
I asked Lord Jiang.
Lord Jiang said this handkerchief is not theirs.
Jiang Siyan doesn't know them either.
There is no bad blood between their two families.
Jiang Siyan doesn't know Cao Tai either.
There is no grudge between their two families.
This handkerchief
is mine.
It's yours?
I want it. Give it to me.
So sweet.
So delicious.
Your handkerchief is so pretty.
It's for you.
Thank you.
Your home is far.
Take the umbrella.
No need.
My family might come to pick me up later.
Didn't your father go to gather herbs?
Your father's new wife definitely won't come to pick you up.
Just take it.
Don't be polite.
Thank you.
Come.
Put this coat on.
No need.
It's cold outside. Don't catch a cold.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm leaving now.
Goodbye.
It rained heavily that day.
She handed me the umbrella.
So I took off my coat and put it on her.
When she left, she clearly took this handkerchief with her.
But now, why would it appear in the shrine?
Right.
Where are you going?
Cao Tai.
To Cao Tai's house.
Wait for me.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
You two slow down.
Let her pack the chicken to go.
Slow down, girl.
Don't choke.
It's all yours. No one is fighting with you for it.
Like this.
You go out now.
I am Cao Tai, you are the female ghost.
You go out and come in again.
Okay.
I know the murderer's modus operandi.