( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Don't you think an ordinary person like that
is a better match for her?
Let's go home.
Shiori.
Were you...
invited by Rena?
Yes. Sorry for keeping it from you.
I knew it.
Did she say something to you?
No, Rena just invited me
out of professional kindness.
I see.
There were a lot of people.
You must be tired.
Yeah...
Everyone was so different
from anyone I've ever known.
Let's go home and rest early.
Okay.
Shiori didn't tell me
she was called to the event.
There's no way
Shiori would go back to Keiichi.
That much, I already know.
[Episode 6]
Come to think of it, you were with Keiichi.
We ran into each other by chance.
He said he came
because it might be a sales opportunity.
I see.
That's a relief.
Huh?
Well,
I was a little worried
that he might be harassing you again.
He's not, but...
Huh?
He asked me to introduce him to Rena.
I'm sorry.
No...
You shouldn't apologize.
I'm the one who should be sorry
for asking something strange.
It's fine.
I have a meeting this morning,
so I'll head out first.
Okay.
Well, I'm off.
Have a good day.
Ms. Hanai.
Could you tell us about
the Seko Group's future prospects?
Hello, this is Shiori.
Oh, Nijihashi.
Thank you for your support as always.
Yes.
Oh, Ms. Hanai!
Thank you for coming all this way.
Not at all.
Look at this.
It's turning out nicely, isn't it?
You're amazing, Nijihashi.
Such meticulous work.
Since the clothing part is being handled
by the major companies,
we'll focus on the details and do our best
to reproduce every fine point
of the designs we've received.
Right, we're counting on you.
Likewise.
To be honest, when I heard
that the Seko Group had acquired us,
I was worried about what would happen.
Huh?
I mean, there are cheaper, faster, and
bigger companies you can order from, right?
So I thought a small company like ours
might get cut right away.
No way. That would never happen!
It's reassuring
to have you in charge, Ms. Hanai.
And now you've been entrusted
with such a big project.
I haven't done anything special.
You're always attentive to the little things,
and your instructions are spot on.
I'm just doing what's expected.
No,
people who can follow through on
what's expected are surprisingly rare.
Is that so?
It is.
Because someone like you
is properly watching over us,
we small folks can do our best with pride.
Thank you, truly.
Thank you too.
I'm so happy.
Please continue to support us in the future.
Likewise.
Hello?
Hello. Are you free right now?
I'm free. Did you need something?
I met with Factory Manager Nijihashi earlier,
and the novelty items are on schedule.
I see. Thank you.
It's thanks to your hard work.
No, not at all.
Thank you.
I was so happy,
I wanted to tell you right away.
That's why I called.
Shiori.
Are you going home now?
Yes, that was my plan.
Then, if you're up for it,
how about eating out tonight?
I want to treat you
because you worked so hard.
Huh?
I'd love to, thank you!
I'll head over right away, so wait nearby.
Okay.
Thank you for waiting.
Mr. Seko, thank you for coming again.
Thank you too.
He booked the whole place?
Reservations are impossibly hard
to get here.
- Aren't they?
- This is Shiori.
She's going to be my wife.
Nice to meet you. I'm Shiori Hanai.
Come in.
What non-alcoholic options
do you have today?
Oh, how about Alain Milliat?
Is that okay?
Um, yes.
Then we'll have that, please.
Certainly.
This way, please.
Thank you for waiting.
Langouste Dugléré
with Shadow Queen potato croustillant.
What kind of dish is this?
Looks delicious.
Shiori, go ahead and try it.
Okay.
Thanks for the meal.
It's delicious.
That's great.
I chose things you can eat while pregnant,
but let me know if you don't like them.
Okay.
If it were Rena instead of me...
She'd be used to places like this,
completely at ease,
and she'd be worthy of you...
Shiori?
I'm sorry!
Miss, please sit.
I'll bring a new one right away.
I'm sorry, I was just trying to pick it up.
Don't worry about that.
Your body is precious right now.
You shouldn't move suddenly.
Shiori?
You look pale.
Sorry. I'm fine.
- Really?
- It's nothing!
I'm sorry.
This is my own personal problem.
Then let me help.
That was delicious. Thank you.
Yeah. Let's come again.
Okay.
Sorry, can I take this?
Yes, go ahead.
Good work today.
Sorry, I'll call you back later.
They pulled out?
Why?
I understand.
No use thinking about it here.
I'll go talk to them in person.
Shiori, I'm sorry.
I have to go to a client's now.
Um, pulling out?
It's fine.
You don't need to worry, Shiori.
Okay.
Sorry I can't go home with you.
No, don't worry. Go ahead.
I see...
I realized that I'm not worthy
of Takahito, I guess...
Why would you say that?
Well, when I went
to greet Takahito's father...
Yeah.
He said I'm not a suitable match
for Takahito.
Huh?
And that he has a fiancée.
So I can't...
Oh, Takahito did tell me
she's just a childhood friend,
and that it was an arranged marriage, but...
I see. That's rough.
Yeah.
After that, I met her.
What?
Her name is Rena,
the daughter of Asakaze Bussan.
And she said she's a better wife for him
than an ordinary person like me.
Whoa, so the villainess finally appears?
Villainess? Don't say that.
What's she like?
She's very intelligent.
She really is a good match for Takahito.
And she's from the right kind of family.
Even that restaurant just now...
I bet Rena would've been...
Shiori! You're being too negative!
Did Takahito choose that Rena person?
No, right?
Takahito chose you, right?
Yeah.
You just need to get
through this work crisis.
Takahito must be having a hard time too,
so you have to support him.
You don't have time
to be depressed like this.
You're right.
- I suppose.
- Yeah.
You have the strength and kindness
to support someone.
You're always helping me out too.
Have confidence!
Thank you, Yuna.
No problem.
I'll support Takahito.
Yeah, I have to.
When he comes home,
I'll talk to him about what I can do.
That's a good idea.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Anytime!
- Shall we drink?
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
Welcome back.
I'm home.
- You waited for me?
- Yes.
Um,
what happened?
It's late tonight,
so I'll tell you and everyone else
at work tomorrow.
Is there anything I can do?
For me, just having you by my side is enough.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Okay.
All the factories we ordered from
are pulling out?
What are we going to do now?
I negotiated.
But honestly,
there was no hope.
What do you mean?
They insisted they pulled out
because of a factory defect.
But,
it's hard to imagine a defect serious enough
to shut down a factory of that scale.
And what's more,
both companies gave the same reason.
Probably there's another real reason.
Since they're hiding the truth,
I decided pushing wouldn't work.
No way...
There's nowhere else
that can take on an order of that size.
Even if we look overseas,
we won't have time for a quality check.
We won't make the deadline.
I'll apologize to the customers
who placed orders...
for the delay in shipping.
We have to restart...
from scratch.
From scratch?
We're starting all over again?
We advertised so heavily.
No matter the reason,
it doesn't matter to the customers.
All they care about is that
we don't have a product to deliver.
I've wasted everyone's efforts.
I sincerely apologize.
Um...
Isn't there anything we can do?
I will inform you...
at a later time.
There's no one more frustrated than you,
the one who started the project.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Rena?
What is this?
Don't make such a scary face.
I came with a good proposal.
Good proposal?
Looks like the project has hit a snag.
You're awfully well-informed.
The industry is small. Word gets around.
Now, I have a suggestion.
Shall I help you?
What do you mean?
As you know, our company
has lots of manufacturing factories.
We can easily meet
the quantities you want to produce.
We can even meet the original delivery date.
What do you think, Ms. Hanai?
I think it's a generous offer.
Honestly, I can't stand
seeing Takahito like this.
Were you so blind with happiness
that you ignored your own company?
Got any other options?
But knowing you,
I bet you were bowing to everyone,
saying you'd restart from scratch.
Are you really going to hurt
your dejected employees
and even Shiori,
the one you care about that much?
Face reality, Takahito.
Think about what you can do
and who you can rely on.
Takahito,
maybe it would be best
to accept Rena's help here.
That would save everyone.
But on one condition.
You have to marry me.
Now, it's that golden boy's turn
to be miserable.
Don't get in my way.
I'm afraid I simply can't do that.
Have I always been blind to your feelings?
I'm exhausted from being with you, Takahito.
I can't live without you
and this child anymore.