(Day 1)
Mmm.
- Kasuga Yuma-san, 28 years old.
- This is good.
- Is it good?
- Mmm-hmm.
Hasegawa Itsuki-san, 27 years old.
The two live together in an
apartment in the suburbs of Tokyo.
What is it?
You have some sauce on your mouth.
No, not there.
That's a cute bandage.
Huh?
Oh, it's not that.
It's just the only one we had left at home.
As a same-sex couple,
they registered for the
"Partnership Oath System" last year.
There were two main reasons.
The first was emotional.
We want to be together forever,
so we wanted something tangible
to prove our relationship.
The other reason was a matter of rights.
For a same-sex couple like us,
if one of us were to suddenly
collapse and be taken to the hospital,
the other wouldn't be able to sign
the consent form for emergency surgery.
This kind of inequality...
The Partnership Oath System alone
can't completely solve it.
Because the system is just a
local government ordinance,
it doesn't have the same
force as a national law.
Unlike a married man and woman,
we can't receive inheritance rights
or get personal income tax deductions.
If we want to have those rights,
we need to achieve
true "marriage equality."
And for marriage equality
to become a reality,
it's necessary for society to
see that same-sex couples exist.
That's also why
we used this system.
We wanted to prove
that if the system exists,
there will be people
who need it and will use it.
After the two were featured
on a news program last year,
they became a hot topic on social media.
(Aired June 30, 2025)
In 2015,
the partnership system was first introduced
in Japan in Shibuya and Setagaya Wards.
It has now expanded to
local governments nationwide,
with nearly 10,000 couples registered.
Now, a decade after its introduction,
how does the public view this system?
How are you feeling right now?
Yes, I'm very happy.
Because from now on,
I can confidently say
that we're a couple.
To be honest,
I really did feel like we
weren't "recognized by society."
We're just like any other ordinary couple
you'd see anywhere,
but the people around
us didn't see it that way.
Do you feel the same way?
No.
I've never really cared
about being recognized or not.
But if this guy is happy,
then I'm happy too.
At the time, this interaction between them
led to them being called
the "viral couple" online,
drawing widespread attention.
This time,
our program will be closely
following the couple for 100 days.
"100 Days with Him and Me"
We've been dating for
about a year and a half.
We started living together
around the same time.
Oh, I'll get it.
- I'll put this here then.
- Mmm.
Back then, I got kicked out
of the place I was living in.
I didn't have any money,
And I was forced to quit my job.
Once you come out as gay,
you really run into all
sorts of situations at work.
Itsuki-san used to work as a chef in a bar,
but it seems he had trouble finding
a workplace that was understanding.
He's currently unemployed.
But it's been great living together.
He waits for me to come home
with a delicious meal ready.
He's completely won me
over through my stomach.
(Day 2)
After graduating from college, Yuma-san
joined an advertising agency as a planner,
where he's been very successful.
- Morning.
So they're really following you around.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to be interviewed too, right?
Yes, we'd appreciate it.
I'm going to talk so much trash about you.
Go ahead, but they
probably can't air that part.
So cocky.
When he first joined WAVES,
I was the one who trained him.
(Kubota Shinya, Strategic Planner, WAVES Inc.)
He has great taste and his logic is very clear.
He's also great with people,
which is important for a planner.
- It's in Otemachi.
- Otemachi?
This is the first I'm hearing of it.
There's a lot I've learned from him, too.
Like what, for example?
For example... let me see.
Once, I was in charge of an ad proposal
for a real estate agency.
In a scenario about helping
someone find a home,
I came up with several ideas.
One of them included a gay male couple.
But Kasuga seemed
hesitant about that proposal.
It turns out that this agency
had recently been slammed on social media
for refusing to rent to a same-sex couple.
I didn't know about that at the time.
And I wasn't really aware of
the reality that gay people could be
refused housing by an agency.
If we had gone ahead
with that proposal as it was,
it might have caused a huge backlash
for being so out of touch with reality.
To me, Kasuga Yuma
is a planner worthy of respect.
Right now, Yuma-san's team
is working hard to win a proposal
for a major cosmetics company.
Yuma-san's college LGBT
group, "Colorless and Transparent,"
was holding a lecture event,
and our crew went along to cover it.
(Day 21)
By the way,
Kasuga-san, how long has
it been since you were here?
It's probably been five or six years.
- I haven't been back since I graduated.
- I see.
So you haven't been
back once since graduating.
And Hasegawa-san, have you ever
been here with Kasuga-san before?
No.
Oh, so this is your first time?
For Itsuki-kun...
Yeah, this should be his first time.
This used to be a dojo.
Oh, it was a dojo?
If you lived in this building,
you could definitely oversleep
and still make it to class on time.
Totally.
Ever since Yuma-san fell for a male
classmate the summer he was 14,
(Lecture: Learn More About the LGBTQ Community)
he had kept those feelings hidden deep inside.
And this place was where that Yuma-san
first found a place where
he could be himself.
I even met my first boyfriend
through this group.
Then, with the encouragement
of my friends in the group,
on my 20th birthday,
I came out to my parents.
(Katagiri Asuna, Representative of Marginal
Women) A woman who can't marry a man is unhappy.
I feel like that kind of
curse still exists today.
When I was little, I
actually hated Girls' Day.
Especially the Emperor and Empress dolls.
They really repulsed me.
I felt like the idea of "this is your
happiness" was being forced on me.
The group "Marginal Women," which specifically
supports female sexual minorities,
is represented by Katagiri Asuna-san.
As an openly lesbian activist,
she was also Yuma's
upperclassman in the college group.
Yuma was the only gay guy in the group
I could really talk to.
"The only one" is an exaggeration.
Weren't we debating all the time back then?
That's pretty much all I
remember of you, Katagiri-san.
What was it called again?
Topics like "heteronormativity."
Oh, this guy, in high school,
was apparently so popular with the girls
that it bothered him.
I wasn't that popular.
Excuse me, what does
"heteronormativity" mean?
Oh.
In heterosexual relationships, it's usually
the man who approaches the woman, right?
In most cases, both gay men and lesbians,
live as if they're straight
before coming out.
So they end up being pursued
by people they're not interested in.
How should I put it...
that sense of frustration?
Many of the gay male members couldn't
immediately understand that feeling.
Differences like that
aren't always easy to understand.
Right.
Connecting different groups
is what LGBT is all about.
But that point has become blurred now.
That's why I wanted to create a
group that values those differences,
and why I founded "Marginal Women."
When Kasuga-san came out back then,
what were your thoughts?
Well...
But, how to say it... Coming out
is a very heavy, momentous
thing in your own mind.
But for some people,
they can accept it so naturally.
So,
how should I put it...
knowing that I was someone who made
him feel like "maybe I can be accepted,"
that made me really happy at the time.
Yuma.
Look at that.
You guys are pretty popular.
No, we're not.
Here they come.
I told them I don't really
have an autograph.
Just write your name.
Um, I really look up to you both.
Ever since you came out, Kasuga-san,
the atmosphere on social
media has really changed a lot.
There's even fan art of you guys online.
Whoa! No way!
Wow, so cool.
Thank you.
- Can I ask a question?
- Huh?
Um... what do you like about each other?
What I like about him?
Uh, well...
What is it?
Hmm...
- His face.
- Ah, not surprising.
- I totally get it.
- Right?
For me, it's his face too, I guess.
No, wait, maybe his smile?
Though he rarely ever smiles.
Huh?
Itsuki-san, who is said to rarely smile.
We asked people who know
him about their impressions.
(Kitani Toru, owner of the
bar where Itsuki used to work)
Well, if I had to describe
him in one phrase...
I'd say the most fitting would be,
"He's a very straightforward kid."
Right from his interview...
He's really direct about everything.
Like how he'd changed part-time jobs
many times in a short period.
And also the fact that he's gay.
What was the reason
you decided to hire him?
I had him cook something
for me, and it was delicious.
So I hired him.
He can really get along with anyone.
Through his personality and cooking skills,
we started getting more customers.
(Day 42)
So cute.
Mori Naomi.
She's the one who initiated
this documentary project.
She was originally
scheduled to direct it herself,
but she was on maternity leave
during filming and couldn't participate.
But you know...
It's easy for us to stand on the sidelines
and irresponsibly say how cute he is.
Such a fragile little life.
It must be so hard to raise him well.
That's true. It's easy to say "so cute"
when it's not your responsibility.
Or thoughtless things
like "I'm so jealous."
You just mentioned you were jealous.
Kasuga-san, do you want children yourself?
Hmm, children...
Yes, I do.
But for people like us,
it's very difficult.
There are many same-sex
couples raising children abroad.
Yes, but this is Japan, after all.
What about you, Hasegawa-san?
No, me?
Hmm?
I've never really thought about it.
I don't really understand
what "family" is supposed to be.
According to Itsuki-san himself,
he's had a very strained relationship
with his family since he was a child.
As soon as he graduated from junior high,
Itsuki-san came to Tokyo.
He's been living on his
own and working ever since.
So, Yuma-san invited Itsuki-san
to go back to his hometown with him.
(Day 49)
Itsuki-san is finally going
to meet Yuma-san's family.
(Commercial break)
We'll be right back after a short break.
On this day, midway through filming,
Yuma-san, on the anniversary
of his grandfather's death,
returned to his family
home in Shizuoka Prefecture.
This was the first time he
introduced Itsuki-san to his parents.
I'm home.
Welcome back. Come on in.
Welcome, Itsuki-kun.
It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too.
Please, come in.
Are you filming right now?
- Yes.
- Please, come in.
It's pretty cold here, isn't it?
Yes, it really is.
Here.
Oh, so this is what it looks like.
- A partnership oath certificate.
- I can't see it very well.
See? The names are written side by side.
Oh.
This was the first time we'd
heard of this partnership system.
We were a little surprised at first,
but I guess this is just
one of the ways things are now.
I heard that Kasuga-san once told you,
"I'm sorry, I've been lying."
Ah, yes.
It was on his 20th birthday.
He told us, "I'm sorry, I've been lying."
So I told him, "We're the ones who are sorry
for making you feel like you had to lie."
Whether Yuma is the way he is,
or whether he never said anything about it,
I wanted Yuma to know
that it was never his fault.
He seems like a very honest kid.
He seems very dependable.
And didn't he say he's a good cook?
- He might be even more dependable than Yuma.
- Really?
How should I put this?
Well...
It's like... we're his other parents.
We already think of
Itsuki-kun as another son.
So I hope he can think of
this place as his home too.
What are you making?
Oden.
Oden?
I haven't had that in ages.
Until what age did you use this room?
This room? I went to college in Tokyo
after graduating high school.
So, until I was about 18.
Oh, so it's really been a while, huh?
Yeah.
It's been a long time.
But was this room always this small?
Well, it's your childhood room.
So it's bound to feel different.
I always thought it felt bigger.
A poetry contest?
Huh?
Oh...
It's the kind of thing they
made us write in class.
My teacher submitted it without telling me.
The Minister of Education, Culture,
Sports, Science and Technology Award.
Isn't that amazing?
Itsuki-san, if you don't mind,
could you hold it up to the camera?
No, there's nothing to film.
Back then, the principal even read it
out loud during the morning assembly.
It was so embarrassing.
Huh? How did it go?
I don't know. I've long since forgotten.
So, Kasuga-san, you were actually pretty
good at subjects like Japanese, then?
Yeah.
If I had to say,
- I guess I was better at Japanese.
- I see.
Is it this one?
No, no, no, no.
Not that one, not that
one. Seriously, not that one.
You've got the wrong one. Seriously, no.
It contains a poem Yuma-san wrote in class
when he was in the sixth grade.
(Since When)
I asked the night sky,
"Since when has the moon"
"been the moon?"
The night sky answered me,
"Since a long, long time ago."
I asked the summer field,
"Since when have the sunflowers"
"been sunflowers?"
The summer field answered me,
"Since a long, long time ago."
I asked my mom,
"Since when have I"
"been 'me'?"
My mom answered me,
"Surely, surely, it's from now on."
It seems I'm still a long way
from truly becoming myself.
After dinner, his father
suggested setting off fireworks.
- Did you find them?
- I found them.
See? We set off fireworks
all year round at our house.
Today is the anniversary
of my father's death.
Back when he was taking
my mother home after a date,
he wanted to spend a
little more time with her.
So he suggested they
set off some fireworks.
And it was the middle of winter, you know?
He made an excuse, saying they
had leftover fireworks from the summer.
That's when he proposed, right?
So in our family, we can set
off fireworks in any season.
If you were to teach these two the secret to a
long and happy relationship, what would it be?
What do you think?
Let's see... Thinking more about the
other person than yourself, maybe?
Yeah, it's about
consideration and acceptance.
If my parents were still alive,
I wonder what they would've
said if they'd met Itsuki-kun.
I think they would have
accepted him without any fuss.
I really wish they could have met him
while they were still alive.
Hey, should we show Grandpa and Grandma?
Huh?
Show them what?
Like this. Tell them, "We're together now."
See? Just like this.
Perhaps this is how two people
gradually become "a couple."
(Day 62)
Two weeks later, they received a notice.
Yuma-san's proposal was selected in a competitive
bid for a major cosmetics company's ad campaign.
(Komori Megumi, Brand Marketing, Sophia Cosmetics)
The moment I saw it, I felt this design was different.
The message this piece conveys is that
"makeup isn't for others, it's for yourself."
That message, through its vibrant colors,
is expressed so vividly.
If, through this commercial,
we can contribute to building a more
diverse and inclusive society,
it would be a great honor
for our company as well.
(Day 85)
On Itsuki-san's birthday,
the two went to Enoshima.
So why did you want to
come to Enoshima last year?
Oh, that was Itsuki-kun's idea.
We were planning a birthday trip,
and he said he wanted to come to Enoshima.
A society full of diversity.
What does that really look like?
Perhaps it's a world
where these two can live as themselves,
walking forward side by side.
That was Plan A.
Hmm...
What do you think?
I think it's well-organized.
Alright, next up is Plan B.
Okay.
(Day 100)
We are truly sorry.
I, Kasuga Yuma, and Hasegawa Itsuki...
when filming for this
documentary began...
were, in fact, no longer a couple.
"The Boy and I Who Will Break Up in 100 Days"
(He and I agreed to be filmed for 100 days.)
100 days?
(Next episode)
Their natural selves.
Hmph... "Natural selves," huh?
(We pretended to be the "perfect couple.")
Cute bandage.
It's all I had.