Here in Zhenyuan County,
you dare lay hands on the Imperial Uncle?
Ning Chen.
The Imperial Uncle defied Da Xuan's laws,
preyed upon the common people,
and his crimes warrant death.
Come with me to the capital for trial.
Insolence!
How dare you!
This is the Imperial Uncle!
Imperial Inspectorate business!
All bystanders, get out of the way!
Anyone who disobeys
dies.
Arrogant fool!
Golden Guard Pan,
does your Inspectorate have any rules left?
Calm your anger, Imperial Uncle.
Ning Chen,
the Imperial Uncle is royal kin.
Even if he is guilty,
His Majesty must decide his fate.
Lower your blade.
Even the emperor is equal under the law.
The blade in my hand
answers only to the law,
not to royal kin.
You—
Golden Guard Pan,
you've seen it all, haven't you?
The people around here are in rags,
unable to fill their bellies,
even the tree bark has been stripped clean.
And what are you doing?
Feasting on meat, women, and fine wine.
Don't you feel the slightest unease or guilt?
Since when do you get to lecture me?
The law demands it.
Everyone present here today,
every single one of you,
will return to the capital for trial.
You included.
What a mighty official you are!
Golden Guard Pan,
this man has run wild in my estate
and tried to harm royal kin.
His crime warrants beheading.
Ning Chen,
I'll say it one last time:
lower your blade.
Before you give me orders,
shouldn't you reflect on your own deeds?
Are you worthy of the uniform you wear?
This uniform of mine
wasn't earned by coasting on seniority.
Fine.
Then let's see
whether you can protect him today.
You brought this on yourself.
Golden Guard Pan, impressive skills indeed.
Is this how you wield your blade?
Imperial Uncle, are you all right?
Get lost!
Guards!
Drag this traitor away
and publicly chop him up for the dogs!
Let's see who'll dare,
ever again in Zhenyuan County,
to cross the Imperial Uncle.
Hold on.
Calm your anger, Imperial Uncle.
Ning Chen is His Majesty's Silver Guard.
Even if he's guilty,
His Majesty must judge him.
Rest assured, Imperial Uncle.
What has happened today
will never leak out.
Remember what you just said.
Let go of me!
Let go!
The day is still young.
I'll treat you to quite a show.
Lian'er!
Ning Chen!
Since you know
that Zhenyuan County is my turf,
how dare you leave them right there?
Do you know how many spies
I have in Zhenyuan County?
The moment you walked away,
my men dragged them right back.
You say I abduct innocent women,
that I treat lives like dirt.
Well, let me tell you,
you're absolutely right.
And what are you going to do about it?
Ning Chen!
You beast!
Boy,
can't take it anymore?
Today the Imperial Uncle will teach you
what royalty really means.
This whole realm belongs to my family.
I am the law! I am heaven itself!
You beast!
Lian'er!
Let go!
You beast!
Let me go!
Ning Chen! Ning Chen!
Imperial Uncle!
Father!
I... I...
What is going on here?
Chief!
He deserved it!
A righteous kill!
This is a disaster!
Take Ning Chen away.
I'll walk on my own.
You!
Guard him well.
He deserved it!
A righteous kill!
Our righteous lord!
I'm a Silver Guard of the Imperial Inspectorate.
I take the sovereign's pay,
and bear the sovereign's burdens.
I'm not worth kneeling for.
All of you, rise.
No, look at you.
At least eat a few bites.
It's been days. Come on.
If you keep this up,
before we even get back to the capital,
your body will give out first.
Golden Guard Pan sent word to the capital.
Brothers from other prefectures
will come to handle the aftermath.
Don't mention him to me.
Ning.
You've truly misunderstood the chief.
Misunderstood?
He took bribes from the Imperial Uncle.
How did I misunderstand him?
The chief did that
to placate the officials of Zhenyuan County.
The dirty silver has all been catalogued
and sent to the capital.
That dirty silver
will be the evidence to convict them later.
Then why stop me from arresting him?
Why?
Be...
Because you were too impulsive.
Ning Chen.
The Imperial Inspectorate came here
to purge all of Chongzhou's officialdom.
How could you arrest him without evidence?
Fine.
Even if you used force,
and dragged him back to the capital,
and accused him of reckless murder,
of abducting common women,
where's the evidence?
How could you convict him without proof?
What's more,
the chief stopped you to protect you.
That single strike of yours,
sure, you vented your anger,
but didn't you throw your own life away?
You fool!
When the emperor rages,
millions of corpses fall.
A commoner's rage spills blood three feet.
Even with only a commoner's courage,
I have no regrets.
If I had to do it again,
I'd still slaughter that beast.
Wasted my breath.
By the way,
how are Old Li and A-Lian?
Golden Guard Pan sent them home.
You should worry about yourself instead.
Well, he did one decent thing.
Ning.
Be honest with me.
Is it that you don't trust the chief?
And don't trust us two brothers either?
That Pan, I definitely don't trust.
As for you two,
you'd better not get tangled up with me,
to avoid being dragged down.
It really was our fault.
We didn't watch over you.
If you'd stayed with us the whole time,
none of this would have happened.
We shouldn't have brought you to Zhenyuan County.
By the mandate of Heaven,
Silver Guard Ning Chen of the Imperial Inspectorate,
defied the law in gross insubordination,
slaying the Imperial Uncle by the blade.
For such reckless audacity,
he is stripped of his Silver Guard rank,
escorted back to the capital,
strictly tried and sentenced,
and executed according to the law.
Lord Ning! Lord Ning! Lord Ning!
Stop the cart!
Lord Ning!
Lord Ning has been wronged!
Yes!
We beg you officials to see the truth!
Lord Ning doesn't deserve to die!
He's a good man!
Please spare Lord Ning!
Lord Ning has been wronged!
The Imperial Uncle was pure evil!
That's right!
Get up.
All of you, please get up.
We beg you, my lord!
Please spare Lord Ning, my lord!
Please spare Lord Ning!
My lord!
We just want to see Lord Ning off.
Please show some leniency, my lord.
Yes, please!
Lord Ning.
On behalf of the people of Zhenyuan County,
this old man thanks you.
Lord Ning.
Thank you, Lord Ning.
My lord.
Take these to eat on the road.
My lord, Lord Ning.
We don't have much at home.
Please take this, my lord.
My lord, please take it.
Big brother.
Mama said you're a good man.
You must take this.
Lord Ning.
Take this water to drink on the road.
It's just a small token.
Lord Ning.
Please take this.
Have a bit to eat on the way.
My lord! My lord!
Take care, my lord.
Take care!
Overseeing the officials,
rooting out the corrupt,
this is simply what we ought to do.
I am a prisoner of the imperial court.
I must return to the capital for trial.
They wouldn't dare do anything to me.
Hurry on home now.
You must take care, my lord!
All of you, head home.
My lord! My lord!
Take care, my lord!
Take care, Lord Ning!
Let's go.
Move out!
Lord Ning, my lord, take care!
Thank you, Lord Ning!
My lord, take care!
Lord Ning!
Lord Ning, you must take care!
Hewn from deep mountains by countless blows,
it endures the raging flames with ease.
Though shattered to dust, it stands unafraid,
to leave its purity in this world.
If justice is absent from this world,
I will wield my blade to slay the wolves.
Lord Ning! My lord!
Take care, Lord Ning!