( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Wuhui.
I won't let anything happen to you.
It's His Majesty's dragon energy.
Sister.
My sister is helping me.
This is my illusion.
No one can overpower me.
Get in!
Steal the beams and pillars.
Activate!
Lin Mo.
How did you get in here?
Strange.
Why is it fake?
This is my world.
Everything is under my control.
So confident?
Then why are you impersonating someone else?
Or could it be
that you're just extremely insecure?
Liu Ruyan.
Long time no see.
Lin.
Since we parted at the Lin Residence,
I have missed you dearly.
Don't talk nonsense.
I barely know you.
You lecher.
How do you have a history with everyone?
We were engaged before.
But the engagement was broken off.
Lin.
Help me deal with her.
And I will stay with you forever.
We can be a happy couple.
How about it?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
I'm just disgusted by her.
You.
Long time no see.
You've really got some skills now.
Wait.
Your Majesty.
I wish to slay demons and eliminate evil.
I pray
to borrow the Shanhe Sword.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Lin Mo.
How can a mere mortal like you
gain the approval of the Imperial Weapon?
What gives you the right?
You...
Why can you also use the Shanhe Sword?
Joint marital property.
Su Wuhui.
Fighting side by side with the one you love,
are you happy?
Remember.
If you like something,
you have to take it by force.
I win after all.
Lin Mo.
The beloved.
No way.
Did a piece of frozen wood like you fall for me?
Does your sister know about this?
I...
I was kidding.
How could a fairy fancy a mortal?
That great demon bewitched people's minds.
I have practiced the Supreme Path of Forgetting Emotion since childhood.
It was just my first time interacting with the opposite sex,
so my mind was disturbed.
It's inevitable that my Dao heart would be interfered with.
Don't use this as an excuse to make a fuss.
Right.
Su Tianjiao has outstanding talent.
This little thing
is just a small episode on the path of cultivation,
not worth mentioning.
The Supreme Path of Forgetting Emotion
is not actually being ruthless and heartless,
but a manifestation of deep affection and righteousness.
One who forgets emotion
does not abandon emotion,
but sublimates it
to reach a state of selflessness.
As the ancient saying goes, 'Desirelessness leads to strength.'
Therefore,
forgetting emotion means removing the self to see the true nature.
With a clear mirror in the heart,
one can reflect the various aspects of the human world.
So,
forgetting emotion
is actually forgetting personal love
and retaining universal love for the human world.
Kid,
you fooled her into making a breakthrough.
Damn.
I was just PUAing her.
Thank you.
Wuhui.
Sister.
I asked you to call me sister before,
but you always called me Your Majesty.
Why did you change your tune now?
Before,
I was ignorant
and threw tantrums.
Are you...
You broke through.
A blessing in disguise.
You were stuck in a bottleneck before
and couldn't grasp the essence.
I didn't expect
that facing death in the illusion
would actually make you break through.
It was Lin Mo
who helped me break through my bottleneck.
I didn't expect
you to be somewhat useful.
What are you talking about?
I'm the pillar of our family.
Here.
Here they go again.
Benefactor,
holding your sister-in-law's hand
while flirting with Her Majesty...
You are truly
a role model for us all.
I was unconscious for a long time.
My hands are a bit numb.
I'm sorry.
Sister,
I'll go look for
the passage to the next level.
I'm going to the restroom.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
Remember to return my pouch!
I didn't mean to!
Don't run!
Don't hit me!
Zhiwei.
Brother Li.
This is for you.
Qiaoyun
asked me to say sorry to you.
Brother Li,
why don't you come with me?
Daqian will be very turbulent in the future.
My benefactor saved my life.
I have to stay to protect him.
Brother Li,
take care of yourself.
I'll take my leave now.
Master, you're back.
Where is Madam?
My Lord,
you didn't come back last night.
Madam was worried.
Her condition has worsened.
What did the doctor say?
The same thing as before.
She just needs to rest.
Master!
Madam fainted again.
Please go see her quickly!
Doctor.
Chancellor Lin.
I'll be frank.
As for the poisonous herb of the Demon Clan,
our Human Clan's medicine
can hardly cure it.
I know.
Doctor,
go get some rest first.
Okay.
Chancellor Lin,
please take care of yourself.
You may all leave now.
I need to have a word with the master.
Madam.
You should rest more.
I've been holding some things inside for too long.
If I don't say them now,
I'm afraid I won't have another chance.
Moonlight dances in the shadows,
candlelight flickers red,
sleeves flutter in the dance,
walking alone in the jade pavilion.
The world calls me a beauty that could topple cities.
But who knows my heart
holds a myriad of sorrows?
Okay.
Emperor Ruyan,
you truly live up to your reputation.
Indeed.
Liu Ruyan can be evil,
calculating,
sinister, ruthless, hypocritical, and selfish,
but she has never been ugly.
I will take that as a compliment from Your Majesty.
Lin Mo,
how did you win the Emperor's favor?
I'm very curious.
The Emperor
has better taste than you.
Are you bringing up the past with your ex?
Tell me.
What are the rules
and tests for this round?
The rule is
to lure the emperor here.
And then
kill me?
Even if I had ten times the courage,
I wouldn't dare
assassinate the emperor.
However,
this position of Master of Baihua Pavilion,
I am indeed tired of it.
Now,
I want to take the throne of the Daqian Emperor.
I wonder if Your Majesty
would yield the throne to me.
You have a death wish.
You may be a master in Daqian.
But this Baihua Pavilion is my domain.
Your cultivation is useless here.
Isn't this the spirit dog
our ancestor gave to the late emperor?
You should call me great-uncle.
You're at death's door,
and you're still trying to take advantage.
My husband.
Listen to me this time.
Let's stop the treatment.
My wife.
I told you.
Don't interfere in my affairs.
Just rest and recover.
In the past, if you went east,
I never went west.
But this time,
please listen to me, my husband.
My wife.
My husband.
Before I die,
I want to see you become that passionate man full of knowledge,
with lofty ambitions,
dedicated to saving the country again.
My wife.
I'm useless.
My husband.
Be yourself again.
Okay.
Take me to the pond.
I want to see the lotus flowers.
Let's go.
We'll go see the lotus flowers.
If you want the throne,
come take it yourself.