( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
This is the blueprint for the steam engine.
No.
Do I look like a steam engine to you?
Right now, Daqian can't even smelt steel.
Let's finish the loom first.
Your Majesty.
Bad news!
Chancellor Lin Youtang is coming with the officials.
Your Majesty bypassed the Ministry of Justice's investigation,
deliberation,
and conviction,
and privately executed Duke Xue and his family.
Having done such a thing that harms the harmony of heaven,
Your Majesty,
how will you explain this to the people?
As the Emperor of Daqian,
Your Majesty should set an example,
and according to our laws,
hand over Lin Mo, the culprit of the poisoned salt case,
to the Ministry of Justice.
To the Ministry of Justice.
What must come
will come sooner or later.
Please think of the state, Your Majesty.
Do not let the late Emperor down.
Is this the most powerful official in Nanqian?
He is so persuasive.
Lin Youtang has run the government for years.
He is indeed extremely powerful.
He was cultivated by those prominent families
specifically to keep me in check.
This hurdle,
we must overcome it.
Guards!
Carry the body over there
for all the key ministers to see.
Yes.
Everyone,
take a look.
This...
Xue Qian colluded with Beijing,
transformed into a demon,
deceived the Grand Empress Dowager,
and attempted to defile me.
I killed him with the Shanhe Sword.
Investigations reveal
that the Xue family secretly fueled the fire
and pulled the strings.
This...
this is absolutely unconscionable
and deserves universal condemnation!
The Xue family
deserved to be destroyed!
They deserved it!
Next,
is the reckoning for the Lin family's poisoned salt case
and the demon infestation in Luoxian Town.
Men,
seize the Minister of Revenue, Li Xian!
Your Majesty,
do not listen to this person's slander!
My dear Minister Li,
the Lin family is gone.
They won't be able to send you money anymore.
And also,
the new concubine in your estate is my person.
Everything you say during your nightly pleasures,
I know it all.
Luckily, I've read the book,
so I know who among you is human and who is a ghost.
Chancellor Lin.
A court official colluding with Beijing,
taking bribes to pervert the law,
and murdering the loyal.
What should the punishment be?
Your Majesty,
this is a matter of great importance.
Please provide conclusive evidence.
Otherwise,
the court is bound to be in panic.
His concubine's confession
and the treasonous letters
are already in the Dali Court.
Your Majesty,
a concubine
can be coerced
or induced to confess.
These treasonous letters
can also be forged.
You!
Lin Youtang,
how dare you!
I wouldn't dare.
I am merely doing my duty.
Doing your duty, huh?
Fine.
Lord Li Xian,
let me ask you,
did you collude with Bei Jing?
And harming the people of Daqian.
Tell the truth.
I have a clear conscience.
[Activate]
Your Majesty.
I plead guilty.
I did
secretly contact the Beijing spies.
It was my insatiable greed
that harmed the loyal.
I was momentarily possessed.
The evidence from the Dali Temple is all true,
and the concubine's confession is also true.
I beg Your Majesty to punish me.
Chancellor Lin,
do you have anything else to say?
I failed to judge people well.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
Lin Youtang is highly influential.
It's not good to fall out with him.
Let's appease him first.
People always make mistakes in judgment.
I don't blame you, Chancellor Lin.
Then everyone,
is there anything else?
Your Majesty.
Although this demon scourge is within our borders,
the matter of Beijing
concerns our foreign policy.
I ask Your Majesty
to act cautiously.
I will take my leave.
Guards,
take Minister Li to the imperial prison.
Order the Dali Court, Ministry of Justice, and Censorate
to conduct a joint trial.
Yes.
Go.
Dowager Consort,
the Empress
has successfully returned from Luoxian Town.
The demon trouble in Luoxian Town
has been resolved.
What a lucky escape.
Mother,
my dear sister
has been acting quite unusual lately.
First, she killed the demonized great-grandmother with a single sword strike.
Now she returns victorious from Luoxian Town.
She is now recognized by the Shanhe Sword.
Things are different now.
Your Highness,
there is actually another reason.
Let's hear it.
The reason the Empress is so successful
is because someone named Lin Mo is helping her.
Lin Mo?
His surname is Lin.
That's right.
He is the eldest legitimate son of the Lin family.
Half a year ago,
they failed in their family's internal struggle
and became death row prisoners.
But the strange thing is,
a few days ago,
the Huaiyang County prison where he was held
suddenly suffered a demon invasion.
He actually slew the demons all by himself.
And he saved the Governor of Huaiyang,
Feng Yong.
Therefore,
His Highness took a liking to him,
so they went to Luoxian Town together.
His family is also in Luoxian Town.
Such a coincidence?
Tell me about it.
Now there are no more monsters in Luoxian Town.
And the Lin family
was wiped out too.
All of the Lin family's salt production
has now been handed over to the royal court by Lin Mo.
This involves some personal grudges.
It seems our empress
is going to start restoring the court's order.
Mother.
We can clip her wings first.
Do you have a plan, my son?
If the empress controls the salt industry,
the salt merchants in the capital will definitely be furious.
They won't be able to sit still.
It seems you
are making progress, my son.
You even know how to use one enemy against another.
Actually,
sometimes I really envy the ancients.
Such a big house,
even if I didn't eat or drink,
I wouldn't be able to afford it with a lifetime of work.
The place where I live,
you couldn't afford it in eight lifetimes.
You are quite good at time-traveling, alright?
Master Lin.
Xiaoying.
It's my first time living in such a big house.
I need to clean it up thoroughly.
Xiaoying.
You can stay here.
But I have a question to ask you.
You must answer honestly.
Are you Han Xiaoying or Mo Xiaolan?
Master, you can tell.
You took over Han Xiaoying's body.
No.
Absolutely not.
Han Xiaoying is indeed dead.
Even her soul is gone.
But her body is intact.
And she still has a trace of true spirit.
So I merged with her.
Merged?
Isn't that body snatching?
No, Master.
That's different.
Kid.
It's really not body snatching.
Body snatching is swallowing a living soul.
This is fundamentally different from body snatching.
Alright.
I believe you.
Xiaoying.
So,
Han Xiaoying's memories,
did you inherit all of them?
Actually, I am both Mo Xiaolan
and Han Xiaoying now.
Maybe
there is a bit more of Han Xiaoying.
You can stay here
as a guest.
Before Han Qingyun has his own place,
you can all stay here.
As for a maid,
I don't need one.
I have hands and feet.
I can take care of myself.
Unlike some people
who have 800 people to serve them.
I think some people are just jealous.
Master.
I'll go find a room to put my things.
Okay.
I was scared to death just now.
I almost summoned the Shanhe Sword.
Don't be afraid.
If there's real danger,
I still have my trump card.
Tonight,
how about
staying here?
What did you say?
Bye-bye.
What are you doing?
I haven't secured my throne yet.
So many eyes are watching me in the palace.
I can't be reckless now.
Besides,
I have to attend the morning court tomorrow.
Many memorials are waiting for me to read.
Morning court?
Su Ning, your day has come.
Experience the feeling of being dominated by 996.
Say that again.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I was wrong.
My bad.
Right.
You're attending the morning court tomorrow.
You'll need this.
This is...
Digging out the heart to absorb vital energy.
Demons have indeed infiltrated Fengming City.
In this capital city,
something big is going to happen.
Mr. Ye,
enjoy your drink.
Three warriors,
don't just drink.
Getting a few girls to keep you company,
wouldn't it be more fun?
No need.
We are here today to accompany our eldest brother.
He just wants to see his lover.
Sir,
I didn't expect
you to be such a romantic.
I wonder which girl
is so lucky.
It's one of your courtesans,
Miss Qiaoyun.
So that's who it is.
With Qiaoyun's looks,
she isn't even considered average
around here.
How about
I find you someone
younger and prettier?
No, no, no.
My brother
only has eyes for Miss Qiaoyun.
Please let her know we're here.
Unfortunately,
Qiaoyun has been booked by someone else.
Please come back next time.
Next time, I...
Impossible!
Qiaoyun only performs, she doesn't sell her body.
Brother.
Forget it.
Sir,
as long as the price is right,
our girls will sell anything.
Nonsense!
Qiaoyun isn't that kind of person.
When I was with Qiaoyun before,
we just drank, listened to music, wrote poetry,
and talked about romance.
We never did anything inappropriate.
What, Brother?
Writing poetry and talking about romance?
Aren't you illiterate, Brother?
Brother.
Is it possible that
she only performs for you without selling her body?
Sir,
calm down.
I'll go find her for you.
Right away.
The mortal world weaves a cocoon.
Yaoniang.
Half a life of absurdity ground into sand.
Lust is but the trace of snow on an empty mountain.
Wealth is like a passing mirage.
Great poem!
Great!
Bravo!
Good. Good poem.
Good poem.
Really good.
You have great literary talent, sir.
You are handsome,
free-spirited,
and highly talented.
But you still have to pay the brothel fee.
You're being tacky, my lady.
I have long since achieved enlightenment.
The flesh is but a leaking wine skin.
And the seven emotions are but stale wine.
Fill it up.
So you just don't have money, right?
Beat him up!
Not the face!
Finally, I can study it properly.
Cheat.
How do I use this thing?
Hint:
Rule-type item.
Parchment Title Deed.
This item
has the function to modify the rules of an area.
As long as you are in the area,
and write in the deed
the name of the area
and the name of the owner,
you can redefine the rules of the area.
The owner can also ignore the rules,
without any restrictions.
Duration:
One hour.
Cooldown:
Twenty-four hours.
What a good thing.
Note:
If the location already belongs to the parchment owner,
there is no time limit.
It takes effect as long as the owner is in the area.
Wow,
this is so awesome!
Let's see if it works.
Who should I test it on?
Han Xiaoying.
No, no, no.
She doesn't know what's going on right now.
It's better to keep my distance.
I'll just test it on the servants.
Whoever slacks off
and is lazy
during the day
will work twice as hard at night.
You, go mop the floor.
Okay.
You, go chop the wood.
Got it.
You, go prune the branches.
Sure thing.
I'll go clean the latrine.
What kind of new gadget did you get this time?
It's amazing.
It can actually set rules for an area
and alter cause and effect.
Old man, don't be interested in everything.
Go back to sleep early.
It's me.
Master.
Your face is all bruised.
What happened?
This is
the price of my enlightenment.
It's the price of detoxification, right?
You
little brat.
It's all your fault.
Tell me,
why are you here?
I was in Luoxian Town.
I almost turned the Lin Residence upside down,
but still couldn't find the Sha Demon Ancestor.
I suspect
he is right here with Lin Mo.
Disciple.
Are you really going to go against your eldest brother?
You didn't want to fight with him before.
Coming here to catch some little demons was harmless.
But the Sha Demon Ancestor,
he is determined to get.
Master.
The tragedy in Luoxian Town,
you saw it, didn't you?
Although they are not the people of Beijing,
they are still ordinary people.
If he were to become the emperor,
what would become of this world?
What becomes of the world
has nothing to do with me.
You are my disciple.
I can't let anything happen to you.
Come back with me.
Master.
This time,
please grant my request.
Fine.
A girl of age cannot be kept at home.
Your Ten Thousand Demon Banner
has absorbed too much evil energy lately,
and the demonic aura is leaking.
Su Wuhui from the Tianji Pavilion
is tracking your demonic aura.
Deal with it as soon as possible.
Be careful.
I'm leaving.