( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Ruo.
(Spirit Tablet of the Late Qi Feng)
I'm back.
Ruo.
(Du Ruo, the Wang family's new bride)
I'm back.
Qi Feng.
Ruo.
I'm back.
(Qi Feng, Former Young Master of Hengshun Salt Bureau)
You promised you'd come back
and marry me.
Qi Feng.
Ruo.
Over there.
Du Ruo.
I saw Lady Du.
Come back up.
- Come back up.
- I saw Lady Du.
Come back up.
Ruo.
Why are you down there?
Come back up.
Come back.
Come back, Ruo.
Come back up.
(Father Du, Du Ruo's father)
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 2=
Invite the spirit child.
(Qi Feng)
Let go.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Ruo.
Stop struggling.
(Wang Xian, Young Master of Hengshun Salt Bureau)
You're going to hurt yourself.
Ruo.
Let go of me!
Let go.
Everything was fine before.
How did it end up like this?
Feng,
you've been gone for two years.
From now on,
Xian will take care of Ruo for you.
You can rest in peace now.
Please don't worry, Uncle.
This master is well known
throughout the region.
He will surely cure Ruo.
Whether she recovers or not,
I, Wang Xian,
will still marry Ruo.
Ruo.
It's been two years.
Qi Feng has been gone
for two years.
Are you still unable to let him go?
You should move on.
Ruo.
Let go of me.
Her obsession runs too deep.
An evil spirit has possessed her.
(Qi Feng)
He was burned to death!
- What nonsense are you talking about?
- He was burned to death!
Wasn't he supposed to have drowned?
He was burned to death!
Hurry and get off the boat.
Boatman,
I've never seen anyone
do business like this.
The boat hasn't even stopped properly,
and you're already rushing us off.
Ever since the water ghost
appeared in Ruanjiang,
I never wanted
to come to this side of the river.
You people kept insisting,
so I finally brought you across.
I still need to head back
before dawn.
Two hundred wen.
Not a coin less.
Two hundred wen?
Old man,
you're charging two hundred wen
just to cross the river?
One round trip
and you'd make enough to buy a pig.
That's robbery.
Look at this river.
There's not a soul around.
Back in the old days,
Ruanjiang was never like this.
Listen,
I can't just take
your money for nothing.
I have
protective talismans here.
Everyone,
take one.
It could save your life.
One each.
Buyan,
pay him.
Ruanjiang County
is one of Tang's richest counties.
It is a major center
for salt production.
How did things end up like this?
Another death.
Go home now.
Run!
The water ghost is out killing again.
The people of Ruanjiang County
depend on these waters
for their livelihood.
Now everyone is terrified.
The foundation of Ruanjiang County
will begin to crumble.
Let's go.
To the Bureau.
That's enough.
The water ghost has appeared again.
Wherever Master goes,
strange cases seem to follow.
What can I say?
Magistrate Cao.
(Ruanjiang County Bureau)
The water ghost incident
has caused a huge uproar.
Many workers
are refusing to board ships now.
How are we supposed
to keep our business running?
Master Wang,
it's not just you who is anxious.
I am far more troubled
(Cao Mingzhi, Magistrate of Ruanjiang County)
than anyone.
But my manpower is limited.
There is...
Don't forget,
(Wang Dingrong, Master of Hengshun Salt Bureau)
Hengshun Salt House
is one of the county's
biggest taxpayers.
Even your salary,
Magistrate Cao,
is partly paid for
by Hengshun Salt Bureau.
Yes.
I know all that.
But solving cases
takes time.
Please give me a few more days.
You?
A mere county magistrate like you
means nothing to the Wang family.
Hengshun Salt Bureau
has supplied salt to the army for years.
We also have connections
within the Ministry of War.
You'd better think of another solution.
I'll give you a few more days.
But if you still fail,
you'll answer for it.
Hm.
Master Wang,
why are you kneeling before me?
I cannot accept such courtesy.
You...
Who are you?
Imperial Commissioner of Jiangnan,
Di Renjie.
I am Cao Mingzhi,
Magistrate of Ruanjiang County.
Greetings, Official Di.
I was blind and ignorant.
I...
I offended you, Official Di.
When trouble befalls the people,
it is the local officials
who bear the greatest burden.
Please rise, Magistrate Cao.
Thank you, Official Di.
Magistrate Cao.
For the people of Ruanjiang,
he has worked tirelessly.
He has kept the waterways safe,
which is why
Ruanjiang's river transport
still thrives today.
Isn't that right,
Master Wang?
Master Wang,
why are you still kneeling?
Please, rise.
My salary
is partly paid by you as well.
I am only a civil official.
If you were to report me
to the Ministry of War,
I would not
stand a chance against them.
I...
I wouldn't dare.
When it comes to sarcasm,
no one compares to my Master.
Your Excellencies,
with the water ghost causing such panic,
business has become
impossible to carry on.
I spoke out of turn.
Please forgive me.
When did
the first water ghost case occur?
Half a month ago.
The deceased was a local
boat tracker from Ruanjiang,
Sun Qi.
(Half a month ago)
Is it fixed yet?
Hurry up.
I need to get back.
Almost done.
Stop rushing me.
It'll be ready soon.
Sun Qi.
Li.
What now?
Did you see that?
Over there just now.
It looked like...
Like something was there.
Something?
You're imagining things again.
I'm leaving first.
I'm not waiting for you.
Sun Qi.
A water ghost!
By the time
Sun Qi's body was found,
it had already started decomposing.
So it was buried.
After that,
there was this man.
Jia Gui.
A carpenter at the docks.
He also
drowned.
And
with Liu Shun today,
that makes three deaths.
The skin is pale.
The face is swollen.
The mouth and nasal cavity
are filled with foam and mud.
These are all signs of drowning.
We need to dissect the body
and examine the lungs.
This Liu Shun
worked as a dock laborer.
Everyone knew
what a strong swimmer he was.
If he didn't have arms and legs,
people would've mistaken him
for some kind of river creature.
Yet even so,
he still drowned.
Were there any other witnesses?
Official Di,
these days,
no one
dares go near the river anymore.
Could it have been an accident?
Even skilled martial artists
can be injured by their own weapons.
No one can say for sure
what happens underwater.
He may have been tangled in weeds
or simply exhausted.
Both are possible.
I do not wish to believe
there are ghosts
in this world either.
But rumors throughout the town say
this water ghost
is connected to Hengshun Salt Bureau.
That Master Wang just now...
No.
The former master
of Hengshun Salt Bureau
The Qi family.
Slow down.
You two,
(Wenhua Splendid Embroidery)
bring that one over too.
Hurry up.
Careful with that.
Master.
Where is the Young Master?
He went to Yihua House two days ago.
He's probably still there.
The wedding is tomorrow,
and he's still fooling around like this.
Should I go bring him back?
Du, forgive me for not welcoming
you sooner.
Come.
Please, come inside.
Wang,
I came today
to call off the marriage for Ruo.
Call off...
Du,
why?
Ruo
is not blessed enough
to marry into the Wang family.
(Spirit Tablet of the Late Qi Feng)
I heard from Uncle
that you've been feeling better lately.
I came to keep you company.
You're drunk.
You should go back.
I am drunk.
My future wife
is far more beautiful
than those girls
at Yihua House.
Let go of me!
Ruo.
Qi Feng is dead.
Not even his bones remain!
Even if he is dead,
he is still the only husband I,
Du Ruo, will ever have.
Stop!
Father.
You disgraceful fool.
That unfilial son
lost all sense after drinking.
Ruo is sensible and understanding.
Please do not
stoop to his level.
Stoop to his level?
If I hadn't shown up in time that day,
have you thought about
what might have happened?
Ruo has never been able
to let go of Qi Feng's death.
Lately, her illness has been
flaring up lately.
As for the marriage,
let us end the matter here.
Tomorrow,
I will return every item
from your betrothal gifts.
Steward.
I...
I'm here.
Bring Xian back at once.
Give him a proper whipping
and make him apologize to Du and Ruo.
Yes, sir.
There is no need.
Du,
Qi Feng has been gone for two years.
I understand
that both you and Ruo
value love and loyalty deeply.
But Ruo
still has a long life ahead of her.
In the future,
she will need someone to rely on.
Besides,
Xian and Ruo
grew up together.
Wang!
Ruo still has me.
You need not concern yourself.
Farewell.
Du...
The water ghost
has been causing trouble lately.
You should be careful as well.
Du.
That disgraceful fool.
This time,
the whole county
is going to laugh at the Wang family.
I'll go bring
the Young Master back right away.
With his temper,
he's bound to cause trouble.
Once he returns,
he'll understand soon enough.
Yes.
Stop working.
Take them all down.
Qi Changshun, master of the Qi family,
his wife Su Ye,
and the Young Master Qi Feng,
were escorting a shipment together.
They had planned
to enjoy the journey along the way.
But unfortunately,
all three perished in the river.
Official Di.
The river transport orders.
Indeed.
These transport orders
must state
the cargo,
the date,
the ship owner,
the place of departure,
and the destination.
But on these three...
(River Transport Orders)
The cargo is listed as the three deceased,
and the ship owner is listed as Qi.
Magistrate Cao,
what do you make of this?
These transport orders
were found near the place
where the victims drowned.
People in town all say
these are death summons
from the wronged souls of the Qi family.
The townsfolk all believe
the water ghost
is the vengeful spirit of the Qi family?
Please take a look, Official Di.
The dates written on these orders
are the very same as the day
the Qi family ship sank two years ago.
If this really
is a water ghost seeking vengeance,
then there must be injustice behind it.
In that case,
let us find out
where that grievance began.
Qi,
if you lack anything on the other side,
(Spirit Tablet of the Late Qi Changshun)
please appear in my dreams and let me know.
After all, Hengshun Salt Bureau
was your life's work.
Surely you wouldn't want
to see it destroyed.
If you truly are the water ghost,
(Spirit Tablet of the Late Qi Changshun)
then please let this all end.
Wang Dingrong.
A water ghost.
(Preview of Next Episode)
Ruo!
Don't come over!
Qi Feng!
There is soot
in the victim's mouth and nose.
The skin is badly charred.
There are localized burns and blisters.
Parts of the skin
have shriveled and peeled away.
All signs point to death by burning.
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪