( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Xiao.
Come.
Master,
stop blocking my way.
I am heading back to Beijing right now.
Go do your thing.
I know you're planning something big in Beijing.
But
how can you do it without helpers?
I
have brought you two helpers.
You two,
say hello to my disciple.
Um,
why do you two listen to him?
Your Highness is going back to deal with the Eldest Prince, right?
Yes.
I can help you.
Count me in.
You all hold a grudge against him?
The Demon Clan had no intention of interfering in human conflicts.
But he
has gone too far.
You just need to help me deal with his minions.
Leave the rest to me.
Are we
a little short on manpower?
Don't worry.
The Empress has already sent two helpers.
All right, let's set off.
It will take a few days.
I can get a good sleep in the carriage.
You won't be able to sleep.
We will arrive
at the Eastern Palace in an instant.
Your Ladyship!
Your Ladyship, bad news!
The Imperial Guard camp is under curfew.
The east gate leading to the camp
has been sealed off.
Who is so bold
to seal off the Imperial Guard camp?
It's the Prime Minister.
He ordered the Imperial Guards
to seal off the camp.
Lin Youtang,
how dare he?
The Prime Minister has Her Majesty's verbal edict.
What should we do, Mother?
Sister already knows our plan.
She will definitely kill us.
What should we do, Mother?
Are we going to die?
Useless thing.
How did I usually teach you?
Have you forgotten everything?
You taught me
to stay calm
and steady as a mountain.
Remember this from now on, my son.
I can't always protect you.
You must be strong yourself.
All of you, step down.
This matter
has nothing to do with you,
and won't implicate you.
Tell the Empress
to come see me herself.
Now,
I finally don't have to die.
Your Majesty.
Dowager Consort Hua
has committed suicide.
Understood.
After her son finishes the funeral,
demote him to a commoner
and exile him to the border.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
Is this news accurate?
If it is wrong,
we will be
doomed.
With such cowardice,
how can you help me ascend the throne?
Father's breakthrough failed.
Now,
he barely has half his life left.
I must succeed to the throne
before Chu Xiaoer returns to seize it.
Your Highness,
these two women
are the daughter of the Grand Secretary
and the granddaughter of the Duke of State.
If you do this...
Now all of Nanqian's plots have failed.
Once Father passes away,
power will surely fall into the hands of those two.
If I don't take these two women,
how can I get the support of the Prime Minister and the Duke?
As long as what's done cannot be undone,
they will have to support me even if they don't want to.
In that case,
I will say no more.
Please leave us.
My two ladies,
I
will be very gentle.
You...
Brother,
you are so impressive.
Do the Prime Minister and the Duke
know you kidnapped their daughters?
Chu Xiao'er,
why are you here?
why...
You spend very little time with Father,
yet you always win his favor.
As for me,
no matter what I do,
in the eyes of the world,
I will never be as good as you.
You deserve to die. You deserve to die!
Do you know, Chu Xiao'er,
if you hadn't caused a tragedy in Luoxian Town,
if you hadn't sent assassins from miles away to kill me,
maybe
I really wouldn't compete with you for anything.
But now...
What a sin.
My disciple,
now,
what do you want to do?
Father needs to rest.
In the future, I ask Master and you two seniors
for your continued support.
We
will swear loyalty to the death.
You...
What are you going to do?
Brother,
don't you like sisters?
Then I will satisfy you.
I'll let you play
to your heart's content this time.
This is the ghost marriage curse.
Luoxian Town.
As expected, you were the one behind it.
Chu Xiao'er,
I won't let you off even as a ghost.
If you become a ghost,
you can still come after me.
I'll be waiting.
Uncle,
you plotted all this with the First Prince of Beijing
just to force me to abdicate.
Is it worth it?
Not worth it.
Now that the spiritual energy of this continent is exhausted,
we cultivators cannot ascend.
We can only wait to die here.
But the appearance of this Demon Domain...
It gave us a glimmer of hope again.
Human cultivators
can break through bottlenecks by transforming into demons
and reach the Great Dao.
So you are the final boss.
How cliché.
Imperial Uncle.
Being neither human nor ghost
is not the righteous path.
You two.
Your mission
has been completed.
This sword
is safer in my hands.
Between you two,
one has the power of laws that transcends this world,
and the other has the dragon aura that protects the nation.
As long as I absorb you husband and wife,
I can break through the laws of this world
and achieve transcendence.
Then who should I choose first?
Kid.
His body suits me very well.
Find a way to control him!
What?
How is this possible?
Sha Mozu,
weren't you sealed by the Empress?
How is that possible?
Evading your detection
took quite some effort.
Your body is hale and hearty.
I will gladly take it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
That night,
three girls were fighting in your bed.
You took the opportunity to touch Su Wuhui's hand
and pinched Han Xiaoying's butt.
And then you...
you also...
Okay, okay.
Okay.
I believe you.
Now,
I've really entered his body.
Notification.
All missions in this world have been completed.
Countdown to
return to the original world.
I think I'm leaving.
Leave?
Where are you going?
What about me?
I don't know.
We didn't even have time to...
Where did they go?
Where are you?
Lin Mo.
You jerk.
I thought you would never wake up.
I thought you were in a car accident.
No.
I just sprained my ankle.
But you,
walked so fast without looking.
Why are you so careless?
I...
Honey, I was wrong.
We will never fight again.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault too.
I shouldn't have dumped all my emotions on you.
Let's
remarry.
What remarrying?
We didn't even get divorced in the first place.
Did you forget
about the 30-day cooling-off period?
That's great.
Look at you, silly.
What's wrong?
It hurts.
Does it hurt?
I have to go to the company.
There's a document I need to sign.
Look at your condition.
How can you go?
Ask them to deliver it here.
It's fine.
I'll just take a taxi there.
You should eat something.
Wait for me here.
Be good.
Wait a minute.
One more hug.
I'm leaving now.
Wait for me to come back.
Stealthy Substitution,
activate.