( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Xiaoying.
How could this happen?
Village Head.
What did you do?
That day when you went to pick herbs,
Lin Fan took advantage of your absence
to sneak into your house
and attempted to assault her.
Unable to fight him off,
she chose to take her own life.
By the time I found her,
she was already on the verge
of death.
What did you say?
Her eyes were full of unwillingness to die.
I couldn't bear to see
you two separated by death forever.
I also had to clean up the mess for the Lin family.
So I turned her.
Then I wiped her memory of that day.
Are there any others in town
that you turned?
Yes.
How could this happen?
Lin Fan is dead.
We can live a good life now.
Xiaoying.
Brother,
I'm leaving.
From now on,
take good care of yourself.
It's a pity
I won't live to see the day I get a sister-in-law.
No.
Xiaoying.
I haven't taken you to the capital
or found you a good husband yet.
You can't just leave like this.
I haven't even become an uncle yet.
You can't go.
Brother,
I'm so tired.
I can finally
get a good night's sleep.
Xiaoying.
Since the matter here is settled,
it's time for me to let go.
Fellow villagers,
I'm sorry.
I can no longer maintain
your loved ones' forms.
I won't kill you today.
Leave Daqian,
and never come back.
Otherwise,
no matter where you go,
I will kill you.
Why did you let him go?
My spiritual power is depleted.
I wouldn't have stood a chance in a fight,
so I could only scare him away.
My daughter,
I'm sorry.
I can't stay with you anymore.
Father, what's wrong?
I'm long gone.
My daughter,
take care of yourself.
No!
Is this my Daqian?
I used to be a real joke.
My own people are being bullied like this,
and I did nothing.
Su Ningxue,
you really are a bastard.
It's not too late.
There's still time for everything.
What a tragedy on earth.
Brother,
this is your doing.
How could Father pass the throne
to someone like you?
Don't let her body be exposed to the sun.
Let's go back first.
Greetings,
Governor.
This is our lady.
Greetings, my lady.
Feng Yong,
you're right on time.
Your-
My lady,
for some reason, Luoxian Town
has been blocked by an energy since yesterday.
We couldn't get in.
The local garrison in Huaiyang Commandery
refused to follow my orders.
Talking until I was blue in the face didn't help.
I could only mobilize the troops from the county office,
which is why we just arrived.
You are the commandery governor.
How do you not have the authority to mobilize troops?
To answer you, Miss.
Mobilizing troops requires an order from the Ministry of War,
or a handwritten letter from you
stamped with the Daqian Shanhe Seal.
Governor.
Mr. Lin.
I understand.
Feng Yong.
I am here.
Go raid the Lin residence.
Take the living away in custody.
Bury the dead immediately.
Confiscate all of the Lin family's properties for the imperial court.
Exempt Luoxian Town from taxes for three years.
No taxes shall be collected from any merchants either.
For families
who lost someone because of the Lin family,
give them compensation.
After you finish these,
tomorrow,
send someone to escort us back to the capital.
Yes.
I will follow your orders.
Old man,
I'd like a pot of tea and a bowl of noodles.
Alright.
Just a moment, little girl.
Here,
your noodles.
Enjoy.
Young lady,
are you hiding from enemies?
Why so careful?
I have no choice, old man.
A girl traveling alone
must be extra careful.
Young lady,
my tea and noodles here,
you can consume without worry.
They are
very clean.
Countless wandering martial artists
as well as officials and escorts
have passed by here.
But someone as careful as you,
it's my first time seeing.
Old man,
you're being modest.
The wandering martial artists, officials, and escorts you've killed
must be countless.
You must be joking.
I don't have such great abilities.
Come on, Master.
I know it's you,
stop pretending.
Tell me,
how did you figure it out?
Who uses such good tea at a roadside stall,
and boils noodles with sunflower seed oil broth?
Is this a branch of Guixiang Restaurant?
Not bad,
you've made progress.
But such a rookie mistake
doesn't seem like something you would make.
Wrong.
How could I make a mistake?
I used the tea aroma and sunflower oil
to cover up the smell of the muscle-relaxing powder.
Impossible.
I checked everything.
Yes,
there's no problem with the food and water.
Did you check the chopsticks?
Master.
You,
you're too insidious.
My good apprentice.
Nanqian is plagued by demons now.
As a princess
and my beloved apprentice,
how can you put yourself in danger?
Just get some sleep.
We'll be home when you wake up.
Come here.
You little brat.
How dare you poison your master!
But you forgot,
I am a
poison cultivator.
Your name sounds so fresh and refined,
Gu Qingfeng.
So elegant,
so celestial.
Yet you're a poison cultivator.
Cut the crap.
Are you coming down yourself,
or should I come up?
I...
What's going on?
What poison did you use?
An aphrodisiac.
It's not poison.
But if you use your internal energy,
the drug will take effect faster.
You little brat!
Get down here!
Master,
your wife shouldn't be too far away, right?
Go find her for the antidote.
Until we meet again.
You...
Come back!
I'm doomed.
His Majesty will deduct my wages again.
Come here.
Um,
do you know the nearest
Jiaofangsi or
brothel?
You know.
You know what I mean.
The most famous Jiaofangsi around here
is Baihua Pavilion in Fengming City.
Lord Gu,
aren't you going to ask your wife to cure your poison?
The girls there are not cheap.
What are you talking about?
This is a work injury.
Of course, it should be covered by public funds.
Yes.
Han Qingyun,
what are your plans now?
Plans?
Leave here
and then see.
Why not come back to the capital with me?
To the capital?
To pay respects to that damn emperor?
Watch your words,
or don't blame me for being rude.
You seem to hate the emperor very much.
I don't just hate the emperor.
I hate all the injustice in this world,
the people who cause injustice,
including you
and your Lin family.
Lin Mo
helped your Luoxian Town
solve the demon disaster.
You even hate him?
Isn't he the legitimate son of the Lin family?
Isn't it because of him
and his brother's infighting
that the people of Luoxian Town suffered this disaster?
Lin Mo,
you didn't kill the people of Luoxian Town,
but they all died because of you.
Brother Han,
I don't want to make excuses,
but I also hope
you don't fall into the abyss of hatred
and be unable to extricate yourself.
So what?
Now I just want to kill all the demons in Beijing
and overthrow the damn emperor of Daqian.
If it weren't for her inaction,
would the residents of Luoxian Town be like this?
Would my sister
be like this?
Oh no.
He's starting to turn evil.
This is bad.
If this goes on,
he will kill you sooner or later.
Eliminate the danger in advance.
Are you serious?
Are we going to kill an innocent person in advance
because of the future?
Don't forget,
we are the villains in this book.
If you can't subdue him,
you can't let him grow strong.
Don't be a saint,
we need to survive too.
Han Qingyun.
What will it take
for you to stop hating the Empress and Lin Mo?
Unless my sister comes back to life.
Can you do that?
As long as your sister is resurrected,
you can let go of your hatred, right?
Okay.
My demon core has a wood attribute.
It can bring the dead back to life.
Xiaolan.
Young Master.
I don't have much time left.
Let me help you one last time.
Your sister still has a trace of true spirit left in her.
With my demon core,
she can be resurrected.
But she will become a demon from now on,
no longer human.
You must teach her how to survive among humans.
Han Qingyun.
What my young master owed you,
I have repaid.
In the future.
You must protect my young master.
What's wrong with me?
These are clearly not my memories.
Why am I so sad?
Sister.
Sister!
Brother.
Sister.
Are you going back to the capital with us?
I promised Mo Xiaolan
to protect you from now on.
I don't need your protection.
Brother Lin.
You don't have a maid, do you?
I'll be your maid and take care of you.
That sounds good.
A maid is unnecessary.
You have hands and feet.
You have hands and feet too.
You probably have countless servants serving you.
You want someone to serve you, right?
My pal...
My mansion has plenty of candidates.
When we get back to the capital,
I'll pick two for you.
You can keep those old ladies for yourself.
Lin Mo!
Brother Lin.
You told me last night
that the Empress is actually a good ruler,
who just has too many involuntary constraints.
How can you prove it?
Well,
you'll have to verify it yourself.
If you really want to rid the world of injustice,
I have an opportunity for you.
I wonder if you'd be willing.
And by the way,
you can also verify what I said.
What do you mean?
Take this.
Go to the Dali Court in three days,
and someone will give you an assignment.
The Dali Court investigates all officials,
and observes the conditions of the people.
There,
you can find the answers you want.
I will go back and reorganize before heading to the capital.
See you at the Dali Temple in Fengming City.
Location: Luoxian Town.
Monster: Shamo Ancestor,
Corpse Puppet, Yin Fiend, Wood Monster.
Task:
Clear the monster threat and recruit the Child of Destiny.
Task completed.
Settlement reward:
Strength, agility, and spirit
are greatly increased.
The rewards are quite rich.
Cheat system, you're finally reliable.
I can kill a martial arts master with one punch now.
Rule-type items,
I'll check them when I get back.
Oh, right.
Xiaoying,
why don't you ride in our carriage?
Lin Mo.
Do you want to die?
Brother.
Brother, come to the capital early.
I'm leaving first.
Xiaoying,
don't cause trouble for them.
I know.
I sent someone to Fengming City
to get a new Lin Residence for you.
You can live there from now on.
It's also close to the palace.
Let's not call it Lin Residence.
It's annoying.
Let's call it Mo Residence.
Agreed.
From now on,
I will be the chief maid of the Mo Residence.
Boy,
can't you see that since this girl came back to life,
she's become more clingy to you?
Maybe she's thanking my maid for helping her revive.
Do you believe that yourself?
Mr. Lin,
wait for me!
We'll go hang out with you in the capital.
We've wandered half our lives.
Finally, we have met a wise master.
Please let us follow you.
Brothers,
if you two want to go to Baihua Pavilion in the capital,
just go.
Why make up such excuses?
You damn scum!
First brother,
second brother,
why are you hitting me?
Shouldn't we?