(Warm Reminder)
(All characters, backgrounds,
and details are fictional.)
(The special actions and scenes
are dramatized for the show.)
(All photos, audio, and video used)
(have been authorized,
including AI-generated content.)
(Safety precautions were taken
during filming. Please do not imitate.)
(Minors should watch
with parental guidance.)
(Game Start)
(The Truth 1 - Where the dream began)
Apartment No. 11.
We're here.
(The Truth 2 - Chasing passion)
The Truth 2.
(The Truth 3 - A new journey begins)
The Truth 3.
(The Truth 3 Team-Building Arc)
We're here!
(When are they filming Season 4?
I'm so bored lately.)
(The Truth 4)
(Meeting year after year,
still as passionate as ever)
(Changsha. March 24, 2026)
(Wake up and eat.
Getting ready before livestream)
Here?
(Meeting again)
Hello.
Alright.
So handsome.
It's been a year.
Bro!
I missed you so much.
My bro.
This feels so familiar.
Surrounded by handsome men.
I can't even see anymore.
Look at me.
(Camera-ready as always)
Not bad.
What's this? Who brought this?
Zhang Linghe.
He recently got into photography.
Seriously?
(From ancient to modern photography)
(Backstage right now)
Oh my gosh.
(Accidentally entered giant kingdom)
(Struggling)
Please enjoy your meal.
Okay, thank you.
Sorry.
Thanks.
No, wait.
This doesn't feel very professional.
Why do these two waiters have
such completely different hairstyles?
One's so fresh-looking,
while the other is so...
(Refined)
So
not refined.
(Not refined)
Always gotta change things up a little.
(Even the hair was carefully styled
just to get your attention)
Then how about this?
You test the food for poison first.
Sound good?
Try it.
Hey bro,
what do you think?
I'm not a waiter.
Hey bro, come try some.
(Exposed himself instantly)
(It's too hard to pretend)
It's Ding!
Ding, you came without saying a word.
(Ding Chengxin from Teens in Times)
(Content sourced online)
(Ding Chengxin. Singer Mode)
I wasn't waiting for Peirong.
(Ding Chengxin. Actor Mode)
I was staying for you.
(Ding Chengxin. Dancer Mode)
(Ding Chengxin. Chaos Mode)
Let me see if I look handsome.
Northeast China is my hometown.
(Ding Chengxin. Sports Mode)
Let's welcome...
Welcome.
Welcome Ding Chengxin.
So happy.
Hello, everyone.
(Unlocking Ding Chengxin. Truth Mode)
All departments ready.
Livestream starts now.
Alright.
Let's welcome...
Welcome!
Welcome Ding Chengxin!
(This lineup is insane)
Hello everyone.
We're back again!
Honestly, bro.
I heard you're actually
pretty cowardly.
(Hahaha)
(Cutting to scared Ding)
(Content sourced online)
Sorry.
Really?
(To everyone watching)
Guys,
prepare to have your minds blown.
(Minds blown)
(Can't wait for brave Ding)
(When does it air?)
What the hell?
Zhang Linghe.
(Ding Chengxin)
So this is The Truth?
(This is kinda scary)
What the hell?
(Resources loading...)
Anybody there?
Why is it so dark?
(Too scared to open his eyes)
Can you move?
Don't move yet.
This is terrifying.
I don't even dare open my eyes.
Weren't we livestreaming just now?
Yeah.
How did we end up here?
(Still keeping his eyes shut)
After the malfunction,
we ended up here.
What do you mean?
Where even are we?
(Where are they now?)
I can see something
in front of me, guys.
There's something there?
I think so.
(For plot purposes only. Do not imitate.
Filmed safely.)
(Shocked)
(Excited)
(Ahh!)
(Mind officially blown)
(Weak. Tiny. Helpless.)
(Someone save him)
(Press [F] to comfort Ding)
It's okay.
(Double protection activated)
Don't be scared.
(For plot purposes only. Do not imitate.
Filmed safely.)
(The surroundings fall silent)
What was that?
(The future is pitch black
and freezing cold)
Starting this intense already?
This is so annoying.
It's okay.
If they go crazy, we'll go crazier.
(Little battle cry)
You're such a coward.
Such a coward.
Baby, it's been so long already.
(Seeking emotional support)
You've started losing it.
(Achievement unlocked: Human Backpack)
Guys!
(Clings onto people when scared)
Prepare to have your minds blown.
(Minds officially blown)
What is going on?
(Analyzing the situation)
Did anyone see clearly what that was?
Nope. I never opened my eyes.
(Still tightly shut)
A ghost lady.
(Saw everything)
It was a ghost lady.
This is a cage.
We've been locked inside.
Looks like
one of those MMA octagon cages.
Welcome to
a large-scale, open-world,
real-life social deduction game,
Push the Door.
(Real-life social deduction game.)
(Push the Door)
(Prologue. Players Logging In)
(Don't be scared)
(Full protection mode)
That scared the hell out of me.
(Player login in progress)
Players,
please follow the rules.
The world of Push the Door
is filled with danger.
Survival is mandatory.
(Players logged in)
So we have to survive?
Survive?
Which means we could actually...
Die?
Die.
Dead. Eliminated.
Does that mean we have to...
Avoid being eliminated?
Maybe we'll have
to compete for survival.
Possibly.
So this is every man for himself?
Not necessarily.
Why are you so murderous this time,
Zhang Linghe?
Why do you
always start off acting against us?
(First place)
I'm taking first place this time.
Okay.
(Softest voice, fiercest threat)
I'm taking first place this time.
Okay.
Alright.
We'll see.
Alright then, Zhang Linghe.
I'm looking forward to it.
Sure.
(Remember this flag)
Players,
please complete the beginner trial.
Beginner Trial Stage One
is to test your observation
and deduction skills.
(Stage One, Escape the Iron Cage)
Unlock all ten locks
(Observation & deduction)
and escape the cage.
Each lock has a character on it.
(Every lock contains a riddle)
(Observation: Four stars)
The character corresponds to
the one over there.
(The answer)
This wire can stretch.
(Keys can extend freely)
See?
Pull it over to unlock it.
Right.
(The keys are here)
There are more keys than locks.
Yeah.
(Liu Yuning)
(Jin Jing)
(Zhou Keyu)
(Ding Chengxin)
(Zhang Linghe)
Let's solve the first lock first.
Okay.
I'll read it.
(Who is the greatest detective
in the world?)
(Is it Ning, Season 3's MVP?)
(Is it Jin, the detective?)
(Or Linghe, the deduction genius?)
(Or Keyu, the star of Push City?)
(Or our all-round player Ding?)
I'd suggest we try
Jin Jing's name first.
(Self-recommendation)
No need to waste time.
Zhou Keyu.
He won last season.
(Makes sense)
Try it.
Come on.
Go ahead. Unlock it.
(Still holding onto hope)
Not me.
(Refuses to believe it. Keeps trying)
You're trying way too seriously.
If it's wrong once, that's enough.
Why keep trying?
(What if it works?)
(Continuing to find the answer)
(Third Brother Zhang Fei)
Who is the world's best detective?
(Liu Yuning. Ginkgo.
Zhang Linghe. Sunflower)
Who is the world...
Could it be Cousin?
(Pumpkin)
Pepper chicken?
I'll slaughter pigs to support you?
Some are placed too high.
I can't reach them.
(Fun fact: Zhou Keyu is 188cm)
(I'll do it.)
(Taking the high ground)
(Surveying the keys above)
Right, mainly check what's up there.
Makeup remover.
And then?
That's water.
Your strength is here.
What's this?
A chick.
A chick means...
666.
(Your strength is here.)
I don't know. My figure is graceful.
You are my everything.
I'm not talented.
Who?
(Who?)
Who's the best detective?
Who?
(Suspicious)
Are we all "fools"?
Let's try it.
(Trusting instinct)
Come on.
Here.
Careful.
(Who is the world's best detective?)
Who?
Who is it?
Amazing.
This is so interesting.
Second question.
(There are three types of rulers.
Straight ruler, triangle ruler, and...?)
You're heartless and shameless.
Find something related
to rulers.
(Physical prince takes over climbing)
(Up you go.)
I'll check the upper ones.
(Dividing tasks)
I'll check the lower ones.
(Warm reminder)
Be careful up there.
I'm fine.
(Watch your head.)
(Careful.)
Careful.
Watch your hand.
If you get hit...
(Worrying hard for this family)
(Check keys, move around,
solve and unlock)
(Everyone has their role)
(Baby. Thump, thump.)
(I love you very much.)
Any ruler there?
There's "much".
(What "much?")
I love you very much.
(I love you very much.)
(Sudden cheesy pickup line)
It works.
(Reasonable enough)
Here you go.
This is it.
This is the one.
(Assembly-line teamwork)
(Straight ruler, triangle ruler,
and...?)
(I love you very much.)
It opened!
Good.
Third question.
(One chicken + one chicken)
Who's the best detective?
One chicken plus one chicken.
(One chicken + one chicken.)
Could it be two chickens?
(Thought process: direct)
This is math.
(What if it really is that direct?)
Chick?
What? Two chickens give birth
to one chick?
(Chicken hatches chicken)
Maybe that's what it means.
Try it.
But shouldn't chickens
lay an egg first?
Which came first?
The chicken or the egg?
(World-famous question)
No.
(Chick)
Not "chick".
Who's the loudest here?
Me.
(Ah!)
Try Jin Jing.
(One chicken + one chicken
= screaming chicken)
(Is it that abstract?)
Do we really go that far?
Let's try Jin Jing, okay?
Will it open?
No.
(Jin Jing)
I know.
I'll pull all the upper ones down.
(Makeup remover)
Then we can see them more easily, right?
Right.
(Miss you so much. Sika deer.
Zhang Fei)
Otherwise you'd keep climbing
up and down.
Yeah, just hold them all in your hands.
(Makeup remover. They know each other.
I don't know. My figure is graceful.)
(You are my everything.
I usually appear in the afternoon.)
(Strawberry cake.
I'm not very talented.)
(All upper-level answers gathered)
(Push the Door has its own Spider-Man)
Chicken chicken...
Double chicken?
Your "strength" is here.
Double-click 666!
666.
(Double chicken/click 666)
You're amazing.
666.
It's here.
Where?
You're incredible.
Double-click 666.
Gift received.
666.
Right. Come.
Finally, someone tapped 666.
It really is.
(Double chicken/click 666)
An elite homophone joke.
Mind blown.
(Mind blown again)
Okay, from now on,
all answers are homophone jokes.
Got it.
(Thought process received: homophones)
It's homophones.
Next.
You ignored me all day,
so I became a chicken.
All homophones.
I Became a chicken.
Homophone joke.
Ignored me all day,
so I became a chicken.
(Sentenced by love
to lifelong loneliness.)
This works.
(Homophone genius)
What is "God's" mount called?
Pepper chicken?
(Following the homophone logic)
Is it pepper chicken?
Try it.
(Pepper chicken)
Not pepper chicken.
God's mount isn't "divine ride"?
It's "divine" indeed,
but the word isn't there.
Then let's try something abstract.
I don't know.
Anyway, my figure is graceful.
(Oh, maybe. Makes sense.)
My figure is graceful.
How would I know what God's mount is?
(Abstract solving mode activated)
But my figure is graceful.
Nonsense-style.
That kind.
(What is "God's" mount called?)
(I don't know. My figure is graceful.)
Still no.
Nope.
Is it Cousin?
(Going deeper into abstraction)
Could try this.
"God's" mount...
is it Cousin?
God's mount...
(What is "God's" mount called?)
Nope.
(Is it Cousin?)
Try me.
Try Zhang Linghe. Use this one.
Why Zhang Linghe?
Because he's a "cow"?
(What is "God's" mount called?)
(Zhang Linghe)
What about strawberry cake?
(Why though?)
We're really out of ideas, huh?
I think it's possible.
Because
(What's the logic?)
a lot of cakes
have birthday stars
on top, right?
(Kinda makes sense)
Try it.
I'll try.
Strawberry cake...
Isn't that way too ridiculous?
(Is it really strawberry cake?)
(What is "God's" mount called?)
It won't even fit in.
(Strawberry cake)
I seriously want to try them
one by one now.
(Xin's strategy: brute force)
I haven't tried pepper chicken, right?
Try it.
(We've got time to test them all)
(What is "God's" mount called?)
(Pepper chicken)
Not pepper chicken.
God's mount is a chick?
(Chick)
Doesn't even fit.
Big foodie girl.
(Big foodie girl)
Not this either.
God's mount...
Zhang Fei?
It opened?
Nope.
(Zhang Fei)
No.
What about "dang dang dang"?
What even is "dang dang dang"?
God's mount. Dang dang dang dang.
(Cheerful)
Dang dang dang dang.
You think this is Doraemon or something?
God's mount...
(Stretches out round hand)
Dang dang dang.
(What is "God's" mount called?)
This doesn't even go in.
(Dang dang dang)
What is God's mount called?
(Direct logic)
Who's the best detective?
Who?
It really is "who".
I got it!
What?
It should be a sound.
Like...
(Guessing the keyword)
Dang dang dang, meow meow meow.
What sound it makes or something.
It's called "baby".
(Try "baby" once)
"Baby" could work.
Try "baby".
(What is "God's" mount called?)
(Baby)
It really is "baby".
It's really "baby".
Pokemon.
(Pokemon = magical baby)
(Back to homophone jokes again)
Homophone jokes.
Pokemon.
(So good!)
That's right.
Okay.
Pokemon.
This one's the hardest today.
Then what's this one?
(What do you want from me?)
Want...
I raise you to kill what?
Kill pigs.
I kill pigs to raise you.
(Raise you to kill pigs)
I raise pigs to kill you.
Raise pigs to kill you.
What?
I kill pigs to raise you.
I raise pigs to kill you?
(I'm splitting apart here)
Because "want" sounds like "slaughter"?
Right.
(What do you want? Want = slaughter)
What do you slaughter for?
I kill pigs.
I slaughter pigs to support you.
Right.
Nope.
(Victims of homophone jokes alliance)
What do you want from me?
Want...
Want you to stop bathing.
Want you...
Want you old, want you smelly.
Want you stinking all over.
(This guy watches too many dramas)
Want me talking harshly.
I raise pigs to kill you.
(Doesn't sound great)
Wait.
There's a line like that in my drama.
What do you want?
There's that line in my drama.
Zhang Linghe.
(Zhang Linghe)
Your name is here.
From your drama?
Could it actually be you?
It's my name.
Zhang Linghe.
(A sudden realization)
It's me!
(What do you want from me?)
(Zhang Linghe)
That's your line.
(A catchphrase)
Why did the logic
suddenly start making sense again?
It's probably
everyone's catchphrase or work.
Each person
should have one matching question.
(Everyone has their own question?)
Let's check the remaining ones.
(Remaining unsolved questions)
(Never fail. Ptooey ptooey ptooey.)
Possibly.
(East City's one and only Zu.)
Could really be one each.
(Never fail. Ptooey ptooey ptooey.)
I have a song with that line.
(Liu Yuning)
I saw that clip.
Right.
Never fail. Ptooey ptooey ptooey.
Never fail. Ptooey.
Jin Jing's representative work is...
(Jin Jing)
Round oily head pig.
That's my iconic line.
(Start from the homophone)
Round.
(See The Truth 3 prologue)
Oil.
(Oil)
Round oily head picks oily pig.
Don't call me bro, call me baby.
Ding Chengxin.
(Don't call me bro, call me baby)
Why though?
That's from your livestream clip.
(Temporary memory loss)
Right.
I really did say that.
Don't call me bro, call me what?
Call me baby.
(Don't call me bro, call me baby.
Teens in Times Ding Chengxin)
(Three locks opened in a row)
Almost done, guys.
We're amazing.
(Only one lock left)
We solved all this in just ten minutes.
(Victory in sight)
(What painful realization)
What's that sound?
(The soul of music awakens)
♪You are my everything♪
♪You got me drunk♪
♪You made me♪
♪Heartbroken♪
♪Sentenced by love
to lifelong loneliness♪
♪Won't let go♪
(Duet mode)
(Final question)
East City's one and only Zu.
It's me. Zhou Keyu.
(Who's calling for East City Zu?)
What even is this?
Because Daniel Wu himself said it.
(That's just how cool he is)
(Daniel Wu:
Nice drawing, East City Zu)
What is this?
(Officially certified East City Zu)
He said I'm East City's
one and only Daniel Wu.
Okay, suddenly it'll become pitch black.
Then everyone rushes in and...
(Group huddle activated)
Bro.
What are you two doing?
Keyu, I missed you so much.
Long time no see.
(I'm joining too)I've been missing you.
Last one. You go.
All geared up.
(Can't hold it together anymore)
East City's only Zu.
Come on.
Zu.
I'm tied up already, bro.
Hurry up.
Zu.
Stop running, Zu.
Bro, get over here.
Come here.
(East City's one and only Zu.
Zhou Keyu)
(All ten locks unlocked)
Beginner Trial Stage One complete.
(Beginner Trial Stage One Complete)
(Stairs unlocked)
Please proceed upstairs
for the next two trials.
(Teleporting to upper level)
That was basically just
pure sound attack.
It was insanely loud.
Let's go.
And that was only Stage One.
Come here. Hurry over here.
(Clinging to each other for survival)
You two seriously overreact.
Looks like...
Looks like this season,
the two of us...
(Gripping tightly)
I'm scared too.
Didn't you notice?
The power keeps cutting out.
What if a murder's happening right now?
Don't say stuff like that.
(Can't handle hearing that)
What are we supposed to do now?
(Dungeon One)
(Dungeon Two)
(Dungeon Three)
(Dungeon Four)
(Game Dungeon Loading Terminal)
Look at this first.
Push the Door.
Join us.
Here, you'll find the best gaming buddies.
The most immersive experience.
Players will be transported
to Beginner Trial Stage One
during the first group dinner.
Stage One is a highly open-ended,
exploration-based open world.
There is no fear here.
No restraints.
Friendliness rating: Maximum.
No fear.
No restraints.
We're literally full of restraints.
And fear.
Yeah.
Definitely fear.
So that wasn't Stage One?
No, that definitely was Stage One.
That was Stage One too,
but it feels like
someone modified it or something.
After players reach the third floor,
they'll enter the remaining two trials.
There is no pressure here.
No tests.
Relaxation level: Maximum.
Great.
So this is the third floor, right?
(Then we're safe.)
This is the second floor.
Second floor.
Third floor's over there.
(Heading to the third floor
to continue clearing stages)
The strongest person...
No, wait.
Hold on.
What do you mean?
You go last.
I go last?
(What does that mean?)
You two need to protect me and Ning.
(Me?)
Only relaxation, right?
Let's see how "relaxing" it really is.
(Not relaxed at all)
My legs are sore.
What? You want me to carry you?
You actually understood that?
(Elite awareness)
It's over. Our cannon's gone.
Otherwise this door would've already
(Missing Bai Cannon as always)
been smashed open.
The...
The door's already open.
Looks like we've arrived.
Beginner Trial.
The second stage starts now.
(Stage Two: Rise as One.)
This round
tests your strength
and teamwork.
Right here.
Come on.
Five players must complete
a total of 100 pull-ups.
(Next stage unlocked upon completion.)
Each person has to do at least ten.
I can't do pull-ups at all.
(Being honest.)
I'm doomed. Haven't trained in a year.
Same here. It's been a while.
Look at him.
Says it's been a while…
(But he looks ready to show off.)
(Professional equipment in use.
Do not imitate.)
What's happening?
It's electrified.
(Here comes the electrotherapy again.)
(Professional equipment in use.
Do not imitate.)
(Haha!)
(Huh?)
That's way too chill.
(Redefining what "chill" means.)
Come on, Jin Jing, give it a try.
(Being kind.)
No way.
You go ahead.
Try it.
Ning, you're not doing the pull-ups.
Just touch it.
Nope,
I'm good.
(Being kind.)
I'm scared of getting shocked.
Ding, just feel it.
I'm good.
Go.
Try it.
I'm too scared to touch that.
Nah, you're already fully charged.
(Grins.)
Wait,
do we really have to do
100 pull-ups for this stage?
I don't think we can pull this off.
It's 100 total between the five of us.
Even if you can do 20 or 30,
the rest of us probably can't.
(Tough challenge.
Each person has to do at least ten.)
No.
We can support each other.
For example, I'll carry her
on my back
and do squats.
Yeah.
(Is there a more proper way to do this?)
Isn't that the point?
That works.
Don't you stream fitness
every day?
That's just
roleplay.
(Kidding.)
Is it just
about draining all its power?
So I'm the one draining it,
and you...
That's right.
Hey...
Hurry up and drain it.
We're friends, right?
Why do we always pick on him?
He's the youngest.
(The forever youngest)
What month were you born?
February.
I'm older than you.
So Keyu's the youngest.
Bullying the youngest.
(Too much pressure on the youngest.)
This swinging ring setup
is really tough.
It's basically a gymnastics move.
It won't stop swinging.
Let him try.
(Good?)
(Keep going.)
Five.
(You can do it.)
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
(Keep it going.)
(Five.)
(Six.)
(Seven.)
(Live counting.)
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Good.
(Completely drained.)
(Ning, Jin, He, Ding, Ke. Total.)
It's doable.
(Test run complete.)
Give it a try.
Come on.
Come on, Ding.
(Go by age.)
It's definitely going to shock us.
We're way too nervous
right now.
Electrotherapy actually helps us relax.
Exactly.
(That makes sense.)
I just can't touch it.
It's okay.
Ding, listen.
I'm touching you.
I've got you.
So if you get shocked,
I get shocked too.
So what?
So we're in this together.
(You're not alone.)
I'm with you.
Yeah.
Hold the soft part.
Grab his ankle.
It conducts, right?
Yeah.
You ever seen "Guardians of the Galaxy"?
Yeah, we'll share the power.
Let's do it together.
We're in this together.
No.
No need for that.
(You can do it.)
(Courage loading...)
(Quick test.)
(Professional equipment in use.
Do not imitate.)
(I'm with you.)
(It's okay.)
I'm starting.
Come on.
(Stop scaring yourself.)
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Alright, ten's good.
That's enough.
(I can keep going.)
(No stopping me now.)
(Hidden powerhouse.)
12.
13.
(Surprising strength.)
(Pull-up machine.)
14. 15.
(Reality check.)
Come on.
12. 13.
14. 15. 16.
Alright, enough.
That's enough.
Alright.
17.
Okay.
(Ning, Jin, He, Ding, Ke. Total.)
Ding got 17.
We're screwed.
None of us are escaping this.
Come on.
Come on, Ding.
Ning.
(Returning the favor.)
(Everyone's watching you.)
I'm starting to freak out.
I'm lost.
Try it.
I'm scared of getting shocked.
No, I'm really scared of this.
It's fine. Just give it a try.
(Reassuring.)
It only
shocks you when both hands are on it.
(All feints, no contact)
The shock doesn't last long.
(Extra reassurance.)
Just do it.
The power should weaken over time.
It's fine. Just hold it.
No worries.
(Boosting Ning's courage.)
(I'm not scared.)
(I am scared.)
I'm sweating.
Maybe I'll go first.
Okay.
(Need a moment.)
(Covering Ning.)
It's fine.
No worries.
(Fair reassurance for everyone.)
Anticipated pain
is the most frightening.
It's okay.
Is the current
strong?
Not really.
It's subtle.
(It's subtle?)
No way, I'm sweating.
Water conducts electricity.
(Such a reassuring expert.)
But I'm really scared.
He's screaming again.
(Ah!)
(Let's scream together.)
Feels like bungee jumping.
(Boosting courage.)
(Back on his feet.)
(I can do this.)
Okay.
His scream
sounds like he's been stabbed.
You just...
Like this.
He's like this.
It feels like Crocodile Dentist.
That shock feeling.
(It's totally fine.)
Like
putting your hand on a lie detector.
(Sounds okay.)
Okay.
Alright, relax and go ahead.
No need for perfect form.
Good.
Support him.
Give him some push.
Okay.
Let go.
(Random shock triggered.)
(Voice: Let go.)
Let go.
(Hands: Nope.)
(Not a single hand lets go.)
(Holding him up.)
Wanna come down?
(Can I get down?)
12.
(Holding on.)
13.
He took the shock.
Okay.
(Shock incoming again.)
Come down.
That's enough.
You're holding him up so much
he can't even let go.
(Ning, Jin, He, Ding, Ke. Total.)
He can't let go.
The sounds he's making up there…
Friends are a blessing and a burden.
Poor guy.
We're just helping.
Honestly,
holding it tight
actually helps.
(Hard to believe.)
(Trying to reassure.)
It doesn't hurt that much.
Not really.
It's subtle.
It's doable.
(That's not what they said at all.)
My heart's about to explode.
(I'll go first.)
You know what,
just standing here actually feels...
Yeah.
Have you ever
done Thermage before?
I do it all the time. Every day.
(Starts rambling.)
Three times a week.
Three times a week?
Thermage, three times a week.
It's fine.
(It's fine.)
I need to carry my baby.
Do ten.
Come on.
Support her.
One.
This feels familiar.
Surrounded by handsome guys.
Five. Six.
Good.
Seven. Eight.
Nine.
(Free trial's over.)
Okay, that's it.
Put her down.
(Upgrade successful.)
I'll do 20.
Let's go for 100.
11.
More?
12.
Okay.
Okay, that's enough. Come down now.
Come down.
That's the limit.
That's not Jin's limit.
It's ours.
21.
17.
68.
(Ning, Jin, He, Ding, Ke. Total.)
32 to go.
(32 left.)
I just got over my fear of the dark,
and now it's shocks.
Come on, Ning.
It's fine.
Just hold it tight.
I can do at least 15 more.
Go ahead. Do fifteen.
Give Ning a second.
(The VIP today.)
(It's fine.)
Hold it tight.
Just hold it tight.
Yeah, just hold it tight.
Really.
Three, two, one. Go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
11.
12.
13.
(Desensitized.)
Enough.
21.
22.
Okay, enough.
Is that good?
Yeah,
enough.
(Workout KPI maxed.)
Save ten for Ning.
(Ning, Jin, He, Ding, Ke. Total.)
Ning, there's no escape.
Yeah.
Alright.
Ning, I got it.
When you hold it tight,
(All-in reassurance.)
you barely feel anything.
I don't believe it.
It's true.
You're sweating from the shock.
No, I'm just sweating from the workout.
Honestly, just hold it tight.
(Don't worry, Ning.)
Just hold it tight.
Yeah.
It's okay.
It's quick.
We've got you.
Life's just one hurdle after another.
(No way out.)
Jeez...
It's fine.
You can do it.
I can't.
Come on.
Don't hold it like that.
That'll...
Just hold it.
Hold it tight.
Yeah.
It's okay, right?
Good.
Come on.
(Now's the time.)
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
(Supporting.)
Keep going.
Seven.
Eight.
It keeps shocking me.
Nine.
Ten.
Come down.
Help him.
(Ning, Jin, He, Ding, Ke. Total.)
Okay?
Any shock left?
Ning, can you hold the mic steady
at your concert?
My face feels tighter.
Right?
(Beginner Trial Stage Two Cleared)
Stage Two
cleared.
Stage Three has started.
The purpose of this trial
is to test your endurance
and reasoning skills.
(Stage Three may be electrified)
Among these 50 buttons,
(Endurance and Reasoning Skills)
15 are unpowered,
(Mission Rules)
and 35 are live.
We need to identify
the 15 unpowered buttons
and submit
the correct numbers in one try.
If you start randomly guessing,
I've got plenty
of ways to mess with you.
Just wait and see.
Who is that?
Who are you?
Who even are you?
Here's how to find
the unpowered buttons.
(Method to Find Unpowered Buttons)
One player holds the electrified rod.
Pick any two numbers.
If either button is live,
the player gets shocked.
If both buttons are unpowered,
the player won't get shocked.
(Fibonacci sequence, perfect squares)
(50 buttons,
15 unpowered, probability theory)
We...
(Got an idea?)
Let's do hand-in-hand-out
to see who goes first.
I'll do it.
You go.
I'll go.
Fine.
Wait, hold on.
(Totally not panicking)
Let's think this through.
How are we supposed to play this?
We can't just brute-force it.
This is basically a math problem.
Let's test one and two first.
If we get shocked,
then try one and three.
Eventually, we'll find a pair
with no electricity.
But what if button one is always live?
How about this?
Let's test them
in a pattern.
This column
against that column.
(Test Strategy)
We pair
(Pair outer rows and move inward.)
opposite numbers
and work inward one by one.
If we don't
find any matches,
then we eliminate that row
and start testing within the next one.
Okay.
Maybe there's some kind of symmetry,
and we'll hit
two unpowered ones together.
Right.
So, one and ten. Two and nine.
That works.
Zhou.
You guys casually
volunteered someone to go up there.
Zhou, you go first.
You go first.
We feel bad about it,
but we're too scared.
(Boldly cowardly)
You're in the best shape.
You know?
Exactly.
Alright, let's do this.
One and ten.
I think we'll hit
two unpowered ones on the first try.
(Ouch)
(1 and 10 failed)
It's live.
Two and nine.
(2 and 9 failed)
Three and eight.
(3 and 8 failed)
Four and seven.
(4 and 7 failed)
There's more.
(Four straight failures)
(Looking nervous)
I'm too scared to call them out now.
You do it.
(Every failed attempt
means getting shocked)
My turn.
It's okay.
I can take it.
Really,
I'm fine.
Still hanging in there.
(Big brother mode activated)
What if all 50 are live?
(There's no way
we're that unlucky, right?)
(They were that unlucky)
Still live.
Again.
No way there isn't
a single unpowered pair.
There is.
There is. I...
(Completely out of ideas)
(All 25 attempts failed)
Let me try.
(Cheerful)
Let's eliminate the last row.
Match the second-to-last row
with the first row moving inward.
(Starting Plan B)
Okay, let's do one and nine.
Right.
One and nine.
(Will the smiling boy)
(finally get lucky?)
(1 and 9 failed)
Two and eight.
(2 and 8 failed)
Three and seven.
(3 and 7 succeeded)
(First successful match)
(Big breakthrough)
Nice.
We got it.
(Beginner's luck at max level)
Three and seven are both safe.
We can use three to test the others.
This just got easier.
Let's test the second row first.
(The first row fails more often)
Forget the first row for now.
(1 & 10, 2 & 9, 3 & 8, 4 & 7,
5 & 6, 1 & 9, 2 & 8 all failed)
Okay. Let's go.
Three and eleven.
(3 and 11 succeeded)
(Luck is finally turning around)
Three and twelve.
(Keeping the streak going)
(3 and 12 failed)
Three and thirteen.
(3 and 13 succeeded)
Nice.
Three and fourteen.
(3 and 14 failed)
Three and fifteen.
(3 and 15 failed)
Nope.
Alright, switch players.
I'll do it.
Okay, hold on tight.
(Using all strength)
Three and sixteen.
(3 and 16 failed)
Three and seventeen.
(3 and 17 succeeded)
Okay, that's five.
We've got five now.
Do you see a pattern?
Three, seven, eleven, thirteen,
seventeen.
Fifteen wasn't one. Seventeen was.
Three, seven, eleven, thirteen...
Fifteen wasn't one.
Seventeen was.
Are these prime numbers?
(A prime number is a natural number)
(greater than 1 that can only)
(be divided by 1 and itself.)
(The unpowered buttons
are all prime numbers.)
Twenty-three.
Seventeen and nineteen.
(17 and 19 succeeded)
That's it.
Nice.
How many do we have now?
Then we just list
all the prime numbers.
Done.
Okay.
Three, seven, eleven, thirteen,
seventeen, nineteen,
twenty-three,
twenty-nine,
thirty-one,
thirty-seven,
forty-one,
forty-three,
forty-seven...
Forty-seven...
How many is that?
Did we count five?
We didn't.
Then add two.
Right.
That should be all of them, right?
We're done, right?
(The 15 selected numbers)
(Will they clear the stage?)
(Beginner Trial Stage Three Cleared)
Beginner Trial Stage Three complete.
Players,
please proceed to the game lobby.
Take the elevator down.
A whole crowd
isn't gonna jump out, right?
Good question.
If a crowd comes out,
we'll kick them right back in.
(Don't worry)
Alright.
Let's go.
(Long legs ready)
(Scared)
They didn't even give us a chance.
(No one there)
Then suddenly the windows
will be full of people.
(You'll say anything)
No way.
That would be insane.
There are people right behind you.
(Actually believes it)
No. The elevator wouldn't go that far.
Right now, we're basically scared
of everything.
(Game Lobby)
Game lobby.
Welcome, players.
Liu Yuning.
(Player: Liu Yuning. All-rounder leader.
Top-tier strategist.)
Jin Jing.
(Player: Jin Jing.
Social butterfly. Master empath.)
Zhang Linghe.
(Player: Zhang Linghe. Hardcore STEM
problem solver. Logic expert.)
Ding Chengxin.
(Player: Ding Chengxin. To be unlocked.)
Zhou Keyu.
(Player: Zhou Keyu. Fearless wildcard
with unexpected charm.)
(Game Lobby)
Congratulations on clearing
the beginner trial
and entering the game lobby.
Next,
you'll enter
dungeon world as players
and begin your role-playing adventure.
This version of the game
(Dungeons 1, 2, 3, and 4)
contains four dungeons.
Each dungeon world will feature
different limited-time players.
(Dungeon World)
Inside every dungeon,
(Starlight Cafe)
players will unlock new roles,
experience different lives,
and meet NPCs.
(NPCs)
(Game Rules: Suspects and Detectives)
Players are split into detectives
and suspects. Among the suspects,
there may be a real killer.
The killer's goal
is to hide their identity
and avoid getting caught.
Only the real killer can lie.
Familiar rules.
But they mentioned one key detail.
They said, "Among the suspects,
there may be a real killer".
That means,
just like Season 1,
an NPC could be the killer.
Possible.
(Attention
The killer may not be one of you.)
Please pay close attention.
(Called it)
(Game Rules: Suspects, NPCs, Killer)
After the case ends,
the voting phase begins.
If the killer is identified,
(Correct vote: True killer)
players who
voted correctly receive a Golden Key.
(Killer, Player)
If the killer
receives fewer votes
than another suspect,
then the killer player
gets the Golden Key instead.
Why are you laughing?
Your smile today is kinda creepy.
I'm getting a Golden Key today.
(Determined to win)
Nobody's stopping me.
(Game Rules: Suspects, NPCs, Killer)
After each dungeon,
players return to the game lobby
for Golden Key tallying.
(Player)
Attention.
Golden Keys
aren't just symbols of victory.
They can also
be exchanged for Skill Cards.
(Skill Cards)
I love Skill Cards.
They're super useful.
(Time Extension Card,
Restore Card, Lights Out Card)
First-time players entering a dungeon
(Soothing Card, Copy Card, Rewind Card)
receive one free Skill Card.
Please choose your Skill Card
and set a trigger gesture.
The Time Extension Card can
extend certain timed segments.
Like that time we failed to pull you up,
(See The Truth Season 3,
Episode 2 (Part 1))
I activated a skill,
and the door stopped.
We were literally seconds away.
Skill Card Two.
(Restore Card)
Restore...
Restore a clue.
Restore the clue
to replay how the crime happened.
At that point, you might as well
just ask the killer directly.
I want to restore it.
Restore the crime scene.
Then the killer walks in like,
(First this, then that)
"Here's how I did it".
(Straight to the ending)
(Lights Out Card)
Skill Card Three.
Turn off the lights once.
What kind of useless card is that?
That sounds like a killer's card.
(Copy Card:
Copy any player's Skill Card)
Copy Card.
That one's strong.
(Unstoppable)
This one's the best.
This is good.
It's like the Star Absorption Technique.
It copies.
It doesn't steal.
(Very precise wording)
Exactly.
(Soothing Card: Calm an NPC's emotions)
Soothing Card.
Like if you run
into a terrifying scene
or an NPC loses it,
you calm them down.
Yeah. You told me to stay calm.
Perfect for you guys.
(Interested)
Can we buy?
I wanna bulk order these.
(I want a lot of it)
(Rewind Card:
Makes an NPC repeat their last line)
Like if we missed something,
we can hear it again.
That means NPCs
will play a huge role this season.
Definitely.
(Skill Cards)
Everyone can pick one card.
Here's the real question.
Are we choosing
these cards
as teammates,
or as opponents?
The show just started filming,
so for now, we're teammates.
Sound good?
Then I'm taking the Copy Card first.
(Wait, that's allowed?)
You're taking Copy Card?
You?
(Strikes a pose)
Do you want the Copy Card?
Doesn't seem that impressive.
Then I'll take Soothing Card,
and you take Copy Card.
It's fine.
(You take Copy Card)
Alright then, I'll take Copy Card.
(Gladly)
Like this.
(Set Skill Card trigger gesture)
No matter what card I use,
I'm doing this.
Six Meridians Sword.
(Copy Card:
Copy any player's Skill Card)
Okay, I'm using the Soothing Card.
(Soothing Card: Calm an NPC's emotions)
Do you guys wanna pick first?
(Being polite)
Ning.
Extend the time.
I'll use the Time Extension Card.
(Time Extension Card:
Extend timed segments)
Okay.
Honestly,
I don't think Rewind is that useful.
(Ning chose Time Extension Card)
Maybe it is.
(Jin chose Soothing Card)
If NPCs really matter
(Ding chose Copy Card)
that much this season,
there's probably gonna
be tons of information.
Then let's skip Lights Out.
That card feels too physical.
Skip it.
I'll take Rewind then.
(He chose Rewind Card)
Rewind Card.
(Ke chose Restore Card)
Then I'll take Restore Card.
Okay.
I want to use Rewind Card.
(Rewind Card:
Makes an NPC repeat their last line)
Okay.
Nice.
I want to use the Restore Card.
This one.
(Restore Card: Restore one clue)
Imagine during a case,
I say, "Let's restore the scene",
and someone says,
"I don't want to use my card".
That instantly makes them suspicious.
Exactly.
If we reach a critical clue
during the review...
No need.
I already figured it out earlier.
(Suspicion level instantly maxed out)
No need. Using it would just waste it.
Alright.
Skill Card selection complete.
Loading first dungeon...
Limited-time player, Wang Yuwen.
Match successful.
(Wang Yuwen)
(Limited-time Dungeon One Player)
Seriously?
Welcome.
It's Wang Yuwen.
Players, please enter transit portal.
Welcome aboard
the Tongcheng Travel Time Tunnel.
Entering dungeon world.
I'm your guide,
Fei Ermeng
from Tongcheng Travel.
Please collect
your exclusive dungeon pass.
Change outfits.
Transform.
Prepare to depart.
Investigate with confidence.
I'll be with you the whole way.
Let's depart together.
(Player: Teens in Times, Ding Chengxin)
(Role received: An Xiaoding)
(Player: Liu Yuning)
(Role received: An Xiaoning)
(Player: Jin Jing)
(Role received: Jin Xiangyu)
(Player: Zhang Linghe)
(Role received: He Jiahuan)
(Player: Zhou Keyu)
(Role received: An Ke)
(Player: Wang Yuwen)
(Role received: An Xiaowen)
(Dungeon One loading...)
(Official launching May 27)
Welcome to the World Beyond the Door.
Charge ahead!
(Liu Yuning, Jin Jing, Zhang Linghe,)
Meet the elite gaming squad.
(Teens in Times- Ding Chengxin,)
(Zhou Keyu, Wang Yuwen online)
(Limited-time player Sun Qian online)
Due to version updates,
X gameplay mode has been suspended.
Here,
you can fully immerse yourself
(True High Freedom)
in a highly free open world.
(Exploration)
Go places you've never been.
(Entering unknown areas.)
It's this room.
(Unlocking "Uncertain Events")
Wait.
(Explore scenes. Unlock new areas)
(Search for clues.)
Search corners no one pays attention to.
(Collect clues and reconstruct the case)
There's a corpse!
Use the Lights On Card.
(Skill Card)
Use a skill card.
(Source, one free card for first login.)
Don't force yourself.
It's okay.
(Time Extension Card, extra stage time.)
I have a Time Extension Card.
(Lights Out Card, lights off once.)
Lights out, close your eyes.
(Soothing Card, Calm NPC emotions.)
Soothing Card.
(With 10+ clues, some incorrect)
(options are cut.)
Elimination Card.
Ding, use Restore Card.
Then restore this mirror.
Can it restore that?
(Restore Card, restore one clue)
Okay.
I can't believe that actually worked.
Seriously?
Wait,
guys.
(Stamina Points)
Collect stamina points.
(Stamina drops randomly in dungeons.)
Without stamina,
(Use stamina to get food supplies.)
you literally can't eat.
I want food.
I'm elder than you.
Give it to the youngest.
Still thinking about food right now?
You're still thinking about eating now?
I didn't even bring my meal card.
You guys are unbelievable.
Beg me.
Please, Ding.
What the hell?
Take it.
Next episode, I'm taking that.
(Side Quest)
Help them out.
(Triggered by players or NPCs.)
Earn their trust.
(Side quests raise trust or rewards.)
Only then can we proceed.
(Players may accept or refuse.)
There are too many files.
(Accept File Sorting Quest? Yes / No)
Think of a solution, please.
(Accept Groom Rehearsal Quest? Yes / No)
Just a rehearsal groom stand-in.
(Accept Puppet Guard Quest? Yes / No)
Must protect it.
(Accept Hit Single Act Quest? Yes / No)
I'm Li Fei.
I have no spine.
Unaffected by gain
(Side Quest Complete)
or loss.
(Court Session)
Talk properly with people.
(Detectives may start court hearings.)
(Interrogate a suspect for 10 minutes)
No disadvantage.
(Advance the deduction process.)
What are you all doing?
We're investigating a case.
But that has nothing to do with me.
I don't know what you mean.
Then the word 'steal' doesn't fit.
Why did they do all this?
Wasn't it because of how you hurt
them when they were young?
You're linking
those two things together?
Of course. Can they really be separated?
This is trauma caused by my family.
Then tell us.
Who exactly is that child's father?
What?
Drag him out.
Guards!
(Main Quest)
But all of that is just setup.
(Progress the case to uncover truth.)
Main quest is the priority.
Find the real culprit.
Find the key evidence.
You criminal!
I'm locking in the culprit.
Locked in.
It's you, right?
You're no good.
I'm a good person.
Then it's you.
What does that have to do with me?
Also,
remember to stay alert.
The culprit may not be your teammate.
Make sure you watch the NPCs too.
He has to die.
He deserves to die.
Kill him.
He got what he deserved.
If there's no evidence,
I don't think that question fits.
Alright, here's the door.
Come and push it.
I'm player Zhang Linghe.
I'm player Jin Jing.
I'm player Liu Yuning.
I'm player Ding Chengxin.
I'm player Zhou Keyu.
(Player Oath)
From this day on,
as I enter "Push the Door",
I solemnly swear,
I will follow the rules in the game,
keep all secrets,
and hold the rules deep in my heart.
I won't go AFK or let the team down.
I'll stay engaged from start to finish.
I won't abandon anyone or give up.
My teammates always come first.
I'll analyze every door with care,
and do my best to stay alive.