( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Visitors are guests.
Have a seat.
Prepare the wine.
No, thanks.
I'll pass on the wine.
Sir.
You come to my brothel,
but don't drink.
Mainly because I have no money.
I can't afford it.
Remember,
every word these monsters say
is to make you
fall into their traps of rules and taboos.
Then how do we break it?
Either use the rules to beat her,
or before she triggers the rules,
finish her off.
Withdraw.
Done.
Go up to the second floor.
That's all I know.
Your Song family
is not innocent.
You just didn't get a share of the spoils.
I know.
That's why the Song family is gone.
I only hope Your Majesty
can eliminate the villains.
I'm not dealing with them for you,
but for Daqian.
It doesn't matter.
As long as you can kill them all.
By the way,
Miss Qiaoyun,
these two books,
can I take them with me?
Take them with you?
Isn't this an illusion?
This is not an illusion.
This is an independent space she set up.
She probably stripped her ancestral home
from Daqian,
and put it in this space.
You have a good eye, sir.
You even saw through this.
Only in my space
is it not easy to be detected.
Alright.
The conversation is over.
How do we get out?
Relax your mind,
and don't resist.
You...
What happened to you?
It doesn't matter anymore.
My mission is complete.
Qiaoyun.
Li.
Your heart...
It's fine.
It was all my choice.
I don't regret it.
It's just that
not being able to stay away from troubles
and spend my life with you
is my biggest regret.
Qiaoyun!
There must be a way.
Benefactor.
Your Majesty.
I beg you.
Please save her.
Save her.
I beg you.
Please save her.
She didn't want to be transformed into a hair demon,
so she chose this ending.
Respect her decision.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
I really envy you and His Majesty.
Li.
Help me give this
to Zhiwei.
Tell her
to leave here immediately.
And do what she wants.
Qiaoyun.
I will avenge you.
I'll kill all those sons of bitches.
Our enemies are not in Baihua Pavilion.
Li.
This is my last request.
Alright.
Leave the rest
to us.
Thank you.
It was her decision.
You don't need to blame yourself.
Maybe for her,
this is also a kind of relief.
Thank you, benefactor.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Let's go.
I won't take your demon core.
Likewise,
I won't pay you the balance this time.
Thank you.
Do you still want to continue with us?
Second Brother, Third Brother,
you follow Master Lin
and make sure to protect him well.
Brother.
Benefactor Lin,
I am sorry,
I...
It's fine.
I grant you a few days off.
Go attend to your business.
Hurry if you want to give her the demon core.
Once the time passes,
its power will start to dissipate.
Okay.
Just now,
when you deliberately approached Song Qiaoyun,
what were you trying to see?
She has two plum blossoms on her arm.
Yao Niang has three.
This should be a ranking system.
I guess
the master of Baihua Tower
only has one.
This Qiaoyun
has a higher rank than Yao Niang.
The weird thing is,
she didn't accept the transformation,
yet she still has such a high rank.
I suppose
she offered enough in exchange.
Your Highness Xiao'er is here to steal business again.
Lin Mo,
you steal my opportunities every time.
You have the nerve to say that?
This is Daqian.
Who's stealing from whom?
Have you paid your tariffs?
You!
Master.
Wancai,
you broke through the illusion!
That's great!
As expected of you.
By the way, Master,
something went wrong with Su Wuhui.
She is still in the illusion.
Go.
Let's go over there.
Over there.
This is what she should look like.
You can't even beat a fake like me.
How are you going to protect the Empress,
Chief of the Tianji Pavilion?
It's not that I can't beat you.
I just can't beat the Shanhe Sword.
Don't always use the Shanhe Sword
to cover up your weakness.
Your Dao heart is not firm.
You've been trapped in your own obsession for a long time.
Did you think
I couldn't tell?
Nonsense.
Just a mere inner demon,
do you think you know me that well?
You originally practiced the Supreme Dao of Forgetting Emotions.
Unfortunately,
you developed feelings,
and your cultivation stagnated,
right?
A cold girl's heart,
focused only on cultivation since childhood.
Oblivious to worldly desires.
Despite her outstanding talent.
But unfortunately, one day,
she had physical contact with a man.
It was like
morning dew on a dead branch,
or a spark to dry tinder,
igniting her long-frozen desires.
Am I right?
Slow down.
I can't ride a horse.
I'm scared!
Shut up.
Stop messing with my Dao heart.
You can barely stand,
yet you still want to fight.
What exactly are you running from?
That unconventional man
opened your heart.
But he is the Empress's man.
You can only watch from afar.
Right?
You are unwilling to accept it,
but there's nothing you can do.
Right?
Stop fighting.
You collapsed it.
It's not my fault.
Lecher.
Shut up.
She looks a bit hopeless.
Don't jinx it.
He is right.
If we don't think of a way,
she will sink in this illusion forever.
Master, no.
The demonic aura
has connected with her heart.
If we forcefully break it,
she will also die.
It seems that
only by going into the illusion
can we help her.
Do you have any good way
to enter her illusion?
I can think of a way,
but I need some
medium that can trick the barrier.
I can,
but
I need a medium that can trick the detection.
Here you go.
Zhiwei gave this,
a lock of her hair.
Hold her hand,
hold your breath,
and relax your mind.
Old man,
you wouldn't take the chance to frame me, would you?
Then forget it.
I don't care.
No, no, no.
You are well-respected.
You definitely wouldn't.
Stop resisting.
If one never feels love,
how can one forget it?
To forget love,
one must first experience it.
All my life, I purified my mind and limited my desires.
I disciplined myself,
refused to experience the world,
and suppressed all emotions.
It turns out
I took the wrong path.
Without experiencing the mortal world
and feeling emotions,
how can one forget them?
You finally don't look like a piece of wood.
Very good.
Yes,
just like that.
Become a demon, Su Wuhui.
Become a part of me.
Oh no.
He is showing signs of becoming a demon.
Lord L-Liu.
Maybe it hasn't come to this yet.
Stop resisting.
You have become a demon.
Joining us
is your only way out.
To feel love,
to forget love.
With or without love.
Lin Mo.
What exactly is my love?
What exactly am I?
Right.
Don't hesitate.
No madness, no survival.
You
are mine now.
Chief of Tianji Pavilion,
Su Wuhui.