( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Chiaki Hosho?
Would it be okay
if I borrowed Ms. Minase for a bit?
I'd like to ask her to be the replacement
for an actress who bailed.
I've always loved you.
A movie starring Mr. Hosho?
Apparently, Mr. Hosho recommended you
after seeing your acting.
No matter how close you get to him,
don't make any mistakes
with Mr. Hosho, alright?
God, she's such an eyesore.
I wish she'd just disappear from my sight.
You seem pretty happy too, Chiaki.
Did you find your true love?
The girl I'm working on
is harder to reel in than usual.
Oh, hey, let's make a bet.
If you can't get her in three months,
give me that watch.
Can't you stop doing that already?
When you finally find
someone you actually love,
it'll only cause you trouble.
I love seeing
how girls from a happy household look
when they make that look of despair.
Ready? Action!
- Cut!
- Okay!
- Thanks for your hard work.
- Thank you.
I'll head out first.
Thanks for your hard work.
Oh no.
Today's the dance lesson for the new song.
I have to go if I can, even a little bit,
so I don't cause trouble for everyone.
Are they on break?
Your performance today was really good.
Do your best with your dance practice.
The salon you recommended
was amazing, Rina.
- Right?
- Good work today. Sorry for...
Really? It's super pretty, isn't it?
Hey there...
What do I do? It's gone!
Huh? What's wrong?
Anna, what's wrong?
The necklace is gone.
The one you're always wearing?
Yeah, the one with the diamond in the heart.
It's so precious to me.
My dad gave it to me.
Did you drop it somewhere?
No, I always keep it in my bag.
And...
I had it before we went on break.
Hey, you were in here alone earlier, right?
Could be her.
I mean, she's broke.
Wait, please...
Are you accusing me of stealing it?
I kept my mouth shut all this time...
but this isn't the first time
that I've lost something.
Huh?
I thought it'd hurt our group dynamics,
so I kept quiet until now.
Hey, Ama, please, don't hide it!
If you tell me honestly, I'll forgive you.
You're mistaken.
If you doubt me, then look in my bag.
What's going on?
Mr. Suzui! Listen to this.
The truth is, Anna's necklace went missing.
Cut, cut!
- Cut!
- Ms. Minase, your position!
- Huh?
- Get closer to Hachimura.
Ama, a little more this way. Over here.
Thank you very much.
Focus, focus!
- I'm sorry!
- Let's do one more time.
I'm sorry.
Oh, don't worry. It's fine.
Really, don't worry about it.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay, it's okay.
There you are.
Chiaki.
Huh?
You seem down.
No, I'm fine.
Something's definitely wrong.
If you want, I'll listen.
Really, it's nothing.
I want to help you, Ama.
You should rely on me more.
Actually, lately,
I'm not getting along with my group.
I see... So that's what happened...
That must have been hard.
I can tell you wouldn't do that,
even though we haven't
known each other for long.
It's okay.
I'm on your side.
Chiaki.
Oh, right.
Let's go get a meal together sometime,
just the two of us.
Huh?
You've just started acting,
so I'm sure it's tough.
You need a break once in a while.
Thank you.
But...
I feel like I shouldn't rely on you
any more than this.
Huh?
Just having you listen to me like this
has already made me feel so much lighter.
To have a senior like you, Chiaki...
I'm really lucky.
Ms. Minase, you're up.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Good work.
Hey, Chiaki.
Yeah?
Your mom was outside earlier.
When I said you weren't here, she left.
Yeah.
Thanks.
[Mom]
Okay, let's take a break.
Anna, let's go get some food.
Yeah, let's go.
Oh.
Don't forget to bring your bag.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
I'm hungry.
Hey, what do you want to eat?
I'm craving ice cream.
Let's get some.
I can tell you wouldn't do that,
even though we haven't
known each other for long.
I'm on your side.
It's okay.
I have someone who really understands me.
Good work today.
Oh! Ama. Good work today.
Mr. Hachimura, thanks.
Oh, this scene...
I'm a bit nervous about it too.
Wanna read together?
- Yes, please.
- Right?
- This is the scene, right?
- Yeah.
Okay, let's start from
- the stage directions here.
- Okay.
Thank you so much.
- No, no, thank you.
- You helped so much.
But you know, with today's scene,
I'm glad we talked it through.
I had fun, thanks to you.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Then I'm glad.
- Good work, Ama.
Chiaki.
Oh, Mr. Hosho,
thanks for your hard work.
Good work.
Well, Ama, see you later.
- Yes, I'll see you next time.
- Thank you.
- See you.
- Good work!
Are you two close?
Mr. Hachimura and I share a lot of scenes,
so he's been very kind.
I see.
Is something wrong?
I was just thinking...
that I want to be the closest to you.
Huh?
I'll take you home.
I drove here today.
No matter how close you get to him,
don't make any mistakes with Mr. Hosho,
alright?
How could I ever, with a star like that?
But I don't want to impose.
I want to.
We haven't talked much today.
Well, if you insist.
Okay.
Oh, you're good at cooking?
I wouldn't say good,
but budget cooking is kind of my hobby.
I want to try it.
Your budget cooking.
Oh, it's nothing I could serve to someone.
It doesn't matter.
I'm fine with anything you cook, Ama.
If you'd like, why don't you stay for dinner?
Are you sure?
Of course!
You've been so helpful to me.
But... Chiaki, you might be surprised
when you see my place.
Surprised?
This really isn't a place
people would invite you to, huh?
Oh, no, that's not true at all.
He's so cool!
Let's pretend to transform!
Transform! Transform!
Hey, don't bother Chiaki!
No, it's okay. Don't mind me.
Sorry.
Transform, transform,
transform, transform...
Belt, fwoosh!
Fwoosh!
Your senior is a nice person.
Yeah.
Special Kicky! Kicky!
He's a really good person.
I beat you! Yay!
Thanks for the meal.
A Minase family special,
curry that's more like a soup.
Wait, I'm sorry.
This is way too ordinary, isn't it?
Sis's curry is really good!
I always ask for seconds!
- Right?
- That's true.
Really?
Thanks for the meal.
It's good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Sei, it's all over your mouth.
Sei, look this way.
There, let's clean that face up.
- So gross!
- Hey!
You always have curry
all over your face too, Nagi!
Is something wrong?
No.
It's been so long since I had home cooking.
Hey, sis is also good at "Jaga"!
"Jaga"?
That's what we call
our meat and potato stew.
But there's no meat in it.
Oh, so that's why it's "Jaga".
(*Jaga means "potato")
I'd like to try that "Jaga" sometime.
Yes, of course.
Yay! We get to eat Sis's "Jaga" next time!
Yay! I want to eat it soon! Yay!
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
I'm so glad you liked it.
No, really.
I think I get why
you're the way you are now, Ama.
That's definitely not a compliment, is it?
No.
For me, it's the highest compliment.
Is it?
Yeah.
Hello?
So?
Did you get that girl?
Don't rush me.
We still have time, right?
Don't tell me you're actually struggling?
Shut up.
Today's a long day.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
Thanks for yesterday.
No, thank you.
Huh, what's this, what's this?
Hey, are you two getting close?
No, no, that's not it, not at all.
How could someone like me
ever have a thing with Chiaki?
No way!
Oh, then, Ama.
How about me?
I mean, in this movie, we're playing lovers.
Jeez, don't tease me, Mr. Hachimura.
No, I'm not teasing you.
Hey, don't laugh!
No.
Ama is mine.
Huh?
Chiaki, please don't tease me either!
I feel like Chiaki and I have gotten closer.
What am I thinking?
Thanks for your hard work.
I'll see you again tomorrow.
Good work today.
You're ignoring my calls. The nerve.
Chiaki?
I've told you repeatedly.
Don't come to my workplace.
Whatever. Just hand over the cash.
Come on, hurry up!
I need to get someone.
Can't you even listen to your mother?
Huh?
Chiaki's mom?
What's with that look?
You're looking more and more like that man.
You make me so mad.
I wish I'd never given birth to you.
You useless thing!
What? Who are you?
What do you think you're doing?
None of your business. Move over.
I can't just stand by while you hurt Chiaki.
I see, I see.
You're being fooled, you know?
This guy isn't worth protecting.
He's a worthless guy with a pretty face.
You're his mother. How could you say that?
Chiaki is not worthless!
He's kind, and caring.
He saw something in someone like me.
He's a very important person to me!
You hear that?
You're still a good actor, aren't you?
By the way,
I recorded our conversation just now.
What?
- Give me that!
- It's no use.
I already sent it to another device.
Don't ever do anything like this
to Chiaki again.
Thank goodness.
The recording was a lie I made up just now.
Chiaki, are you okay?
Chiaki?
Are you okay?
I'll go get someone.
Please.
Don't move.
Stay with me.
Whenever I hear her voice, I can't move.
It's all because of you
that my life is a mess!
It's pathetic.
There's nothing pathetic about that.
I'll protect you, Chiaki.
Disappear, disappear, disappear!
You're such an eyesore!
Ama.
I've always wanted to apologize to you, Ama.
You're cuter than anyone, Ama.
But it's okay.
I'll stay by your side, Ama.