( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Grafting,
activate.
Go.
I wonder how my lady is doing.
Your lady is graceful and elegant,
and extraordinary.
Heaven will surely protect her.
If there's no news from Lin Mo before noon,
I will mobilize the Demon-Slaying Army of the garrison camp
and attack directly.
May I ask
whose daughter your lady is?
You'd better
not ask.
Boring.
Look.
That guy at the back of the line looks suspicious.
It's the pharmacy owner.
Oh no.
Let's hurry back to the pharmacy.
Open the door.
Brother.
Third Brother.
Brother Han.
It's me, Feng Buji.
Brother.
Third Brother.
Wait.
Brother Han.
Who dares to impersonate my second brother?
Leave immediately.
Otherwise,
don't blame my sword for being ruthless.
Brother, you left your sword at the Lin Mansion.
I think so.
Wait.
Brother.
To be safe,
tell us something only you and Brother know,
and no one else does.
Right.
Third Brother is always thoughtful.
Yes.
Tell us a secret only we two know.
Every time you go to Baihua Pavilion to drink tea,
I write couplets for you
so you can meet Miss Qiaoyun.
Even though you spend the night there every night,
her maid told me
you only dare to sleep on the floor,
and don't even dare touch the bed.
Also,
they say you talk a big game
but have no real skills.
Also.
Say another word,
and our brotherhood is over.
Brother.
You are still a virgin?
So every time you took my money to Baihua Pavilion,
you were just keeping it innocent?
You sly fox.
You planned this to dig into my past, didn't you?
I'll beat you up.
Stop fooling around.
Hurry and check on the pharmacy owner.
He might already be dead.
Wait.
What time is it now?
When does the pharmacy open?
Is this guy scared silly?
Don't be impulsive, heroine.
This is a substitute straw man from Tianji Pavilion.
As expected,
this pharmacy owner
is not as simple as he looks.
He kidnapped Han Xiaoying.
It's definitely not just to marry her.
This pharmacy owner
is from the imperial court.
He can't be from the imperial court.
Nor is he from Tianji Pavilion.
Tianji Pavilion's consumable magical artifacts
are all recorded.
How can you be so sure?
Because
we are from the imperial court.
You...
You guys...
Why are you kneeling?
My lord,
is it still in time for me to report them?
Master,
wake up.
Mo Xiaolan,
weren't you taken away by the bridal procession?
Master,
are you still drunk?
I am your maid.
What bridal procession?
But as for your marriage,
if you don't do something, it's going to fall through.
My marriage?
Yes.
The young lady of the Liu family
has brought people to our door to call off the engagement.
This is the room of my original body.
It feels both familiar and strange.
I must find Su Ningxue quickly.
Xiaolan,
if the Liu family's daughter wants to call off the engagement,
should I stop her?
Master,
what nonsense are you talking about?
The Liu family is a prominent family in the capital.
This marriage is too important to you.
You absolutely cannot miss it.
Okay.
Let's go
and take a look.
Let's go.
Here comes the boss.
Then let's talk.
Mr. Lin,
I have a son and a daughter.
Now,
my eldest son has passed the imperial exams
and entered officialdom.
So my family business
can only be inherited by my daughter,
Ruyan.
Therefore,
her decision
is my decision.
Lin Mo.
My brother has now entered the Ministry of Personnel.
And our Liu family's
business in the capital is also booming.
Although your Lin family controls the salt industry of Daqian,
you have no backing in officialdom after all.
It will be taken back by the court sooner or later.
Do you think
you are still worthy of me?
Is there something seriously wrong with this woman's head?
Emperor Ruyan
truly lives up to her name.
Then, Miss Liu,
what you mean is
this marriage contract
should be annulled?
I'll see how you suffer later.
Grafting,
activate.
Miss Ruyan.
My brother is deeply in love with you.
The jewelry and betrothal gifts he gave you
are enough to make an ordinary person extremely wealthy.
How can you be so heartless
and let down my brother's affection?
Say no more.
As for those worldly possessions he sent,
I will return them all.
As for the person I don't love...
Giving me more betrothal gifts
is useless.
This is too...
Then why did you accept them in the first place?
Master Liu,
does your daughter's word
count?
Of course it counts.
Okay.
I agree.
This is the letter of divorce.
Our engagement is hereby canceled.
Please return all the gold and silver
betrothal gifts I gave you over the years
in full.
From now on,
our two families owe
each other nothing.
Damn!
Where am I?
Am I still in China?
Ladies,
today is a joyous day.
Cheer up.
Madam.
I am already married.
My husband is still alive.
I shouldn't marry again.
Please have mercy, Madam.
So noisy.
Come.
Eat.
I've fed them all.
Open your mouth.
Eat.
Let's go.
We'll wait outside.
You...
Lin Mo,
do you know what you are saying?
I will give you one more chance.
What are they expecting?
For me to beg her like a lapdog?
They must be crazy.
Can't you understand human speech?
Fine.
I will tell you one more time.
You are divorced.
Lin Mo.
You are just a heartless scumbag.
Remember this.
Return all the gold, silver, and betrothal gifts I've given you over the years
in full.
Not a single penny less.
Otherwise, you, Liu Ruyan,
are just someone greedy for wealth,
selling your looks,
shameless,
and a morally bankrupt cheap tramp.
You...
You were not like this before.
How impudent!
Lin Ding,
is this how the Lin family's
eldest legitimate son treats his guests?
How could it come to this?
Brother,
how could you insult Miss Ruyan
with such words?
Our Lin family
is a family of scholars.
This goes against our family's tradition.
Brother,
you should apologize to Miss Liu...
Who told you to leave the kids' table?
When adults are talking,
is it your place to interrupt?
Fortunes rise and fall.
Never look down on a poor youth.
Young Master.
Young Master, apologize to Miss Liu quickly.
This marriage can still be saved.
Otherwise, it will be too late for regrets.
Just as I thought.
It's not a vine.
How dare you!
Lin Mo,
what are you doing?
Why?
I have deep feelings for you.
Shh.
If she were the real Mo Xiaolan,
she would be eager for me to break the engagement.
You left too many flaws.
Done.
Next level.
Lin Mo,
the position of the family head
should have been passed to you.
But I know
your ambitions don't lie here.
And you are infatuated with the Liu family's eldest daughter.
How about leaving the Lin family's business
for your younger brother to manage?
Whose obsession is this exactly?
Is it this so-called father's,
or that so-called younger brother's?
Trying to set a trap for me again.
Is this your idea,
or Second Mother's?
Does it matter whose idea it is?
It's all for the good of the Lin family.
I've canceled the engagement.
Our family has nothing to do with the Liu family anymore.
Also,
I just want to focus on my career now.
The burden of being the family head
is rightfully mine.
Pharmacy manager,
why are you here?
You.
Am I going to die?
I haven't even finished paying off my mortgage yet.
I'm fine.
I forgot I'm the emperor.
With dragon aura protecting me, no evil can harm me.
No wonder Imperial Uncle said only I could solve the demon threat.
It is a pity for these women.
I will make those demons pay with their blood.
Folks of Luoxian Town!
Come out, everyone.
I have something to say.
People of Luoxian Town!
Follow me!
It has begun.
Folks of Luoxian Town!
The village head has already started gathering the people.
Let's go take a look.
Everyone.
We live here in Luoxian Town.
We don't seek wealth or power.
All we want is to live and work in peace.
But the Lin family is inhumane.
They collude with demons
and harm the people of our town.
What the Lin family takes away
are our daughters and sons,
our parents and wives.
They are so heartless.
As the town chief,
I can't stand it anymore.
Why don't you give your brother a chance?
He's been trying very hard.
Life doesn't offer that many chances.
Once you fail,
the price is the destruction of the Lin family.
Come.
Here.
Sign my name.
How dare you!
Lin Mo,
what are you trying to do?
Say one more word of nonsense,
or get up from that seat,
and I'll throw you into the well immediately,
just like you did to my mother.
How could this be?
You are extremely talented,
but you've been cowardly since childhood.
You didn't know how to say no,
and never rebelled.
In everything,
you yielded to Lin Fan.
Why are you so tough now?
What?
I didn't grow up as you expected,
so you're not happy?
Sign here.
Let's have a smooth handover first.
As for the rest of the score,
we'll settle it slowly.
You...
Butler!
The pharmacy manager.
I don't know why you insisted on coming back.
But if you want to achieve your goal,
except me,
nobody can help you.
Why do I feel like a villain?
Father, Mother.
Lord Governor,
over here.
A new storyline has been triggered.