It's you.
Why wouldn't it be me?
Aren't you the Red-Faced Guardian
who blesses the people?
You shouldn't be taking lives.
The vile
deserve to die.
It's no reason
to stain your hands with filthy blood.
I am avenging my friend.
It matters not.
Zhuang Luobai!
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 10=
Search everywhere!
Find Zhuang Luobai and bring him back!
Go! Hurry!
Oh, Luobai...
Where could he have gone?
Troupe Master.
Have you forgotten?
Tonight is the Winter Festival.
I am the one performing.
Zhuang Luobai made your troupe
the finest in Raozhou.
I, Ming Yu, can do the exact same.
You...
He wasted his time raising a
heartless wretch like you.
Zhuang Luobai.
The Winter Festival is
over a month away.
My heart is no longer in the dance.
From now on,
let Ming Yu take my place.
The people of this city
only want to see you, Zhuang Luobai.
No one else will do.
But Ming Yu is more gifted than I am.
He lacks for nothing,
save for his timid nature.
He lacks the courage
to stand up for himself.
Over the next month,
I will train him rigorously myself.
I won't disappoint you, Troupe Master.
Luobai,
please stand up.
As for the Winter Festival,
we can discuss it further.
Troupe Master,
this Nuo opera has lasted a millennium.
You recognized my talent.
I must pass this kindness down.
If you do not agree,
I will not rise.
If Zhuang Luobai
hadn't begged on his knees,
someone with your meager skills
could never have taken his place.
For the past month,
he has been desperate to prove to me
that you are capable.
Again!
(Yet you keep making mistakes.)
Where is your strength?
Where is your passion?
Where is the emotion?
Again!
(He was anxious that)
(I would change my mind,)
(so he begged me
to give you another chance.)
(If you don't practice hard,)
(you'll embarrass yourself on stage.)
(If you perform
the God-Welcoming Dance this way,)
(how can you be the lead dancer
for the Winter Festival?)
(He hoped your new talent would shine,)
(outshining his past glory.)
(He wasted his time raising)
(an ungrateful wretch like you.)
You refuse to give me any recognition,
but the Troupe Master values me.
So he's replacing you with me
for the Winter Festival.
Troupe Master!
Bad news!
Master Zhuang is a murder suspect!
The Bureau is hunting him!
(Wangnian County Bureau)
Please see the truth, sir.
My master is not the killer.
Please see the truth, sir!
Zhuang Luobai didn't kill anyone.
Commissioner Di.
My master is not the killer.
I falsely accused him.
I can prove it.
On the night Gu Pan'er was murdered,
Master didn't step out of his room
for a single moment.
Because that night,
a tall woman
entered his room.
They remained inside all night.
(I thought Master
only cared about the Nuo opera)
(and about us, his disciples.)
I resented him for it.
Sir.
That day backstage,
I purposely misled you.
I exaggerated his strange behavior.
He has indeed been acting weird.
That disrupts your investigation
and turns him into a suspect.
I was wrong.
The Bureau is searching for your master.
You should join the search.
Report to me
the moment you find anything.
It is indeed the tassel
from the silver hairpin.
Why was it found inside Mrs. Gu's body?
In the face of her daughter's death,
this was the only way
she could preserve the truth.
Let's go.
We need to see Hou Guangming.
Vice Director Hou,
regarding the deaths
of your wife, Pan'er, and her parents,
I have already unraveled the truth.
Would you care to hear it?
I have been
humbly praying for you
to solve the case, sir.
Very well.
Let's begin with Pan'er's mother.
Pan'er...
I failed you.
I have
failed to protect you.
You accursed woman.
What are you staring at me for?
Why haven't you cooked dinner?
She's already dead!
Why are you keeping
her things? It's bad luck!
Pan'er was your daughter.
Your own flesh and blood!
Hmph.
She's dead and gone.
I...
What do you expect me to do about it?
If it can be traded for silver,
isn't that a good thing?
You're going to gamble again!
It's Pan'er's belongings!
- Give it to me!
- Let go!
As a mother,
I couldn't even protect my own child.
I am going to the Bureau
to report you all!
You accursed woman!
You worthless piece of trash.
If you dare
take a single step out of this room,
I'll rip you apart!
You couldn't even give me a son,
you useless wife.
If you had an ounce of beauty left,
I would have sold you off
for cash a long time ago.
Give it to me!
Give it here!
Stop right there, you miserable woman!
Inside Mrs. Gu's stomach,
we discovered this tassel
from the silver hairpin.
By doing this,
she must have
known the truth about Pan'er's death.
But as a mere woman,
she was powerless
against a desperate gambler.
This was her only way to fight back.
Master,
why didn't the killer
dispose of the weapon
or make it disappear forever?
How did Gu Qi get it?
There is only one explanation.
Gu Qi had long
been consumed by gambling,
and had run up massive debts.
Once he discovered
that this silver hairpin
was the weapon used in the murder,
he used it to extort money
for his gambling habits.
Di is right.
A few days ago,
Gu Qi did indeed
pay off a substantial gambling debt.
Are you implying that
my father-in-law killed his wife?
No.
Gu Qi only wanted leverage.
Only the killer
wants to take a life.
Stop right there!
Get back here!
Who are...
Who are you?
Hey!
Take this to pay off your gambling debts.
It was Zhuang Luobai.
How could he be so ruthless?
Not so fast.
Traces of a hallucinogen were found
inside Gu Qi's stomach.
Mind-altering powder.
Exactly.
A massive dose.
And it must have been
slipped into the liquor he drank.
The killer knew he was a gambler,
and that he had a guilty conscience.
To put an end to his endless extortion,
once his false testimony
was no longer of any use,
a mind-altering powder
drew out his inner demons,
causing Gu Qi to scare himself to death.
Finally,
the deaths of Gu Qi and his wife
were blamed
on the curse
of the Red-Faced Guardian.
False testimony?
I may be simple-minded,
but even I can tell
that you are suspecting me, sir.
I never suspect
anyone without reason.
The footprints at the scene
where Pan'er's body was found...
The foot length is 27.33 cm.
It does not match yours.
At first,
I believed the killer was left-handed.
He is left-handed.
It also does not match you.
But then, Qinglan made a new discovery.
During the autopsy, I found
that Pan'er herself was left-handed.
That was when I came to a realization.
I realized
how Pan'er died.
I don't care
who you are running away with.
Remember that
I bought and paid for you.
Please let me go.
I beg you.
I will return your money.
What are you doing?
Playing the unyielding martyr?
Stab yourself then!
Go on, stab!
Even in death,
you belong to me.
That was when
he appeared.
My daughter!
You...
You'll pay for her death!
So what if you're rich?
Does having money
give you the right to...
To think such a vile beast
existed under my jurisdiction.
Gu Qi watched
his own flesh and blood get murdered,
yet for the sake of money,
he helped cover up the crimes.
He is even worse.
Vice Director Hou,
is my deduction correct?
Sir,
this is nothing
but mere speculation on your part.
Do you have any evidence?
If not,
then please,
do not simply
abuse your authority to intimidate me.
Wearing shoes that do not fit,
aren't you afraid of taking a fall?
(Preview of Next Episode)
You desired nothing more than
to become the Red-Faced Guardian.
Today, your wish is granted.
Take it off.
You will find your true self
and become who you are meant to be.
The Guardian has come for me.
The Guardian has come for me!
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪