=Dungeon Unlocking=
Time leaves its mark.
Glass shines like a mirror.
Back in the 1980s,
a blazing furnace sparked a dream.
An Songqiu, founder
(An Glass Factory)
of An Glass Factory,
set out to bring premium local glass
to the world.
Three generations working side by side
built Tui City's glass empire
into the giant it is today.
Recently,
Chairman An Yi announced
that on March 24,
a magazine shoot
would take place at his home,
and the family heir
would finally be revealed.
I will
officially announce
the next chairperson
of the An family.
The candidates:
(Detective)
An Xiaoning,
An Ke,
Jin Xiangyu,
He Jiahuan,
An Xiaoding,
and An Xiaowen
arrived right on time.
An Er,
we're starting the shoot.
He fell asleep?
Unexpectedly,
An Er, one of the heirs,
died during the magazine shoot.
The calm facade shattered,
while the truth
stayed buried underneath.
Who's the invisible hand
behind the murder?
(An Songqiu)
Beneath the family power struggle,
the truth slowly begins to surface.
World Beyond the Door, Dungeon 1
is now unlocking.
=Case 1: My Family Is a Total Mess=
(Login successful.)
(An Xiaoding, An Xiaoning, Jin Xiangyu,
An Xiaowen, He Jiahuan, An Ke)
(Players loaded.)
(An Xiaoning, the detective.
Personal Stamina Points)
(Name: An Xiaoning
Age: 43)
(Identity: An family's eldest son
Occupation: Antique trade mogul)
(Skill Card
Time Extension Card)
(Ning: sharp-tongued)
Read what you wrote.
I can't get it out.
March 15, 2016.
That's when it all came out.
Just sweet talk.
Talk therapy.
Okay.
Talk therapy?
What makes you think you can boss
this family around?
Because of what you did,
we had to use
(confidential).
You knew the whole time.
Why stay quiet?
You're just a pawn.
He's her type.
He's just using you
for favors.
So yesterday it was "baby,"
and today it's "murderer"?
You love glass.
She loves you.
Could it be that when it kicks in,
(confidential).
Actually,
(Ning: sharp observer)
I think
(confidential) is in the room,
not on us.
I agree.
It might've been set up
to predict where Uncle Er
would be standing.
No one's been upstairs
since the death,
right?
(Confidential)
Did he really explain it
in that much detail?
Do you know why we came to you?
How could you possibly know
(confidential)?
You didn't just plan to kill him.
You acted on it.
Because your phone contains
(confidential).
Since he was right in front of us,
it had
to be done quietly
so nobody noticed
anything was wrong.
Yeah.
I‘ve got a question.
If they're both
telling the truth,
something doesn't add up.
(Can Detective Ning
spot the contradiction?)
(An Ke, the detective.
Personal Stamina Points)
(Name: An Ke
Age: 44)
(Identity: An family's fifth uncle
Occupation: Glass artist)
(Skill Card
Restoration Card)
Ning.
(Ke: model uncle)
Uncle Ke.
(Respectful)
How are things?
(Uncle Ke's usual concern)
Not bad.
I've made these rings for you two.
May you stay together
forever.
Perfect pair.
(Butterfly)
Butterfly.
So now you understand
what my gift means,
Ding?
Yes.
I fly a helicopter to work.
Oh, you're so charming.
No wonder you're so tall.
The iPad's upstairs.
Who wants to go get it?
I will.
(Diligent Uncle Ke)
Something's under this.
Where?
(Kneels down.)
(Kneels down again.)
Come on, move this board.
Yes, sir.
(Uncle Ke goes wherever he's needed.)
(Ke: everything under control)
Nothing in this world is absolute.
Absolute.
Why are you so sure
about that?
He's acting suspicious.
He keeps staring at him.
What are you trying
to take?
(Up to something?)
First, ask him about the necklace.
Start with his timeline,
then figure out his motive.
On March 24, between 9 and 10 a.m.,
where were you and what were you doing?
Be specific.
Think carefully before you answer.
(Confidential)
While he was dancing downstairs,
someone over here was...
(What exactly did
Detective Ke discover?)
(Jin Xiangyu
Personal Stamina Points)
(Profile
Name: Jin Xiangyu Age: 46)
(Identity: Wife of An Yi
Occupation: Group CFO)
(Skill Card
Soothing Card)
(Gentle care, all for her son)
Son.
(Always supporting her son)
Amazing!
My son can actually prove
that he's innocent.
Why?
Because he already destroyed this.
There was no reason
for him to kill An Er afterward.
(A mother's child is always treasured)
Exactly!
Son,
well said.
What you said makes sense.
My good boy.
How dare you question
your Uncle Ke like that?
I'll ask instead.
Where was it custom-made?
(No one bullies my son)
Butler, how are you handling Aunt Pai?
She seduced my son.
Your business.
(There's nothing Mom doesn't know)
What exactly happened?
You knew all along, son.
You've been protecting Mom
this whole time.
Who was here just now?
(Mutual love)
Son,
time to watch the show.
A once-in-a-century drama.
That document was shredded too badly.
The shredder.
Our card.
(Clever trick, activate anytime)
Instant Restore Card.
I think
this was planned by
(confidential).
Because
of
(confidential),
he wanted to murder An Er.
And he knew this family
inside and out.
He knew every one of us
had some motive
to kill An Er.
Cunning
is the perfect word for you.
Truly cunning.
You've already locked onto a suspect.
Because you just said
it shouldn't have been only me
logging in.
So once you logged in,
you confronted the killer directly.
That conversation
gave me a shocking new clue.
(What exactly did Jin Xiangyu know?)
(He Jiahuan
Personal Stamina Points)
(Profile
Name: He Jiahuan Age: 24)
(Identity: Son-in-law of the An family
Occupation: Glass production line chief)
(Skill Card
Rewind Card)
(Defiant and full of tension)
We're a loving couple. What about you?
(Going hard)
And you?
Viper woman.
You're already in this state.
(Someone stop them?)
You don't even have competition rights.
We're not going to die anyway.
(My fate is mine to decide)
What can you do?
Actually, it's very simple.
Because I am someone who is very...
(Think carefully before you speak)
If you put it that way,
then I'll have to choose my wife.
(Locked in)
I won't let you take her first.
You're all just used to this.
Here comes the young miss,
everyone step aside.
(CEO vibe: one-handed steering wheel)
(Unrestrained, handsome, relaxed)
Hurry up and come organize this for me.
(confidential)
Although you didn't let An Er
get hold of this document,
and he didn't know...
(Solid reasoning, steady control)
But you knew An Er was investigating.
It's possible he was originally
in that position,
but while turning things
over and over...
(confidential)
He even gave this to me himself.
Even if there’s a secret,
why are you saying I killed An Er?
What does An Er
even have to do with this?
He's always been very wary of me.
So between the two of them,
I'd be more inclined to think
(confidential)
the more innocent one.
He only learned about this recently,
so you started having killing
intent toward An Er?
Look at me.
Don't avoid my eyes.
(What did He Jiahuan see through?)
(An Xiaoding
Personal Stamina Points)
(Profile
Name: An Xiaoding Age: 23)
(Identity: Second son of the An family
Occupation: Glass ambassador)
(Skill Card
Copy Card)
Xiaoding, come here.
You walk in front.
Xiaoding，
you're brave.
Let him be a bit brave.
It's fine inside.
It's definitely fine.
I'm fine.
(Emoji spam machine, sweetness overload)
(Wasn't it supposed to be smooth
if you just stay calm?)
Slowly.
(Emotional support committee member,
feeling uneasy)
(Top-tier reaction speed)
(Oh~ GIF)
(Gossip detected)
(Roast mode)
This man's attitude.
What?
(When the gossip turns out to be about yourself)
No,
Mom!
Stop.
(Just quietly walking away like this)
(Is this even right?)
(eyes wide)
(pupil earthquake)
I'm hooked.
(Good drama falling from the sky)
Wait.
I really want to see this.
(I'm definitely taking
a bite of this gossip)
Can I find
a higher-level clue?
(No clue is too small to miss,
calm and thorough as always)
Is there something hidden in here?
What about under the table?
(Search every corner
without missing anything)
(Hey bro,
squeeze in and search together)
You go over there.
(Not only good at finding clues,
but also...)
How many years have you been doing this?
With my experience in this position,
I think both of them
(confidential)
You must choose one.
I don't know whose words
are true or false between them,
so I become defensive.
(Can An Xiaoding
uncover the real culprit?)
(Profile
Name: An Xiaowen Age: 25)
(Identity: An family eldest daughter
Occupation: Glass division head)
(Skill Card
Lights Out Card)
(Sharp-tongued but soft-hearted heiress)
It can't be him.
He's simple and kind.
(Heart over head)
Don't worry, darling.
I can explain everything.
I believe you.
Honey.
What is it?
We still have An Wen.
I can't let my wife
fall under anyone else's control.
So that's how it is, that's touching.
Dad.
What?
How could I ever harm my own family?
(Outsider)
You're the only outsider here.
(Caught you)
(Arrogant)
Why are you singing to him?
I've never heard
a voice so beautiful before.
Whose phone is this?
There's a computer here.
(An Xiaowen's intuition mode activated)
These plants look suspicious.
And these mirrors too.
Definitely.
Why are there so many
mirrors in this room?
They're all used to...
Maybe I did something,
but since no one died,
it's not my fault.
We need exact timing down to the second
to figure it out
(confidential)
who is it.
I found something wrong.
(confidential)
Everything you said is a lie.
Because from the very beginning,
it was...
(confidential)
So what exactly are you...
Because this thing...
(confidential)
So what I still don't understand
is one thing.
(What exactly did An Xiaowen discover?)
(Dungeon Bonus Station now
open for a limited time)
(Dungeon Bonus Station Rules)
(Limited-time challenge quests
refresh regularly)
(Clear the challenge to unlock
surprise rewards)
(Come refresh your Buff collection!)
(This round:
everyone on duty wins rewards)
Welcome to the Dungeon Bonus Station.
(Grab until you're sick of grabbing)
Today's challenge is:
Grab until you're sick of grabbing.
Players must use chopsticks
to move glass marbles from the plate
into the bottle.
Players must rapidly answer questions
from the production team.
Move twelve marbles
within the time limit,
and the challenge is cleared.
This actually looks pretty hard.
So it's basically rapid-fire Q&A?
I have to answer while doing this?
That's right.
This is tough.
I might not even get one in.
(Bro demonstrates first)
Ready? Go.
Challenge start!
(2-minute countdown begins)
(Current marble count: 0)
(Slip)
Any themes
you want to try this season?
(Score!)
(Current marble count: 1)
Republican-era theme.
(Bye-bye)
Say something to player Xin.
Give me that.
Hope he has fun playing.
You go first.
(Thanks, bro)
Among your past appearances
in Push the Door,
which styling theme was your favorite?
Which one?
That one.
(Current marble count: 2)
The red outfit set.
(Ning's choice)
(Steady)
Where do you think your courage
(Current marble count: 3)
ranks this season
in Push the Door?
Top three, I think.
(Current marble count: 4)
Definitely top three.
Top three includes me.
Keyu.
Linghe.
Who is second-to-last?
(Current marble count: 5)
I think
(Starting to get into the groove)
Xiaoding is more timid than Jin Jing.
(Current marble count: 6)
(Screaming siblings)
When concert streamers
flew into your mouth,
what was your inner reaction?
I just felt sorry for the audience.
They paid for tickets,
and I ended up singing like that.
(Flashback to the concert scene)
But I couldn't just swallow it.
I just felt really embarrassed.
Besides hip shaking dances,
what other dance styles
do you want to try?
(Current marble count: 7)
(Internet fully documented)
more large-scale choreography.
(Current marble count: 8)
Not just the basic kind.
The more rhythmic, groove-based style.
(Current marble count: 9)
I want to add high-difficulty moves.
(Current marble count: 10)
(Let's wait and see)
(Current marble count: 11)
Pick a song that represents
your mood right now.
(Current marble count: 12)
Pick a song for my current mood?
(Current marble count: 13)
(Busy)
(Current marble count: 14)
How do I feel right now?
I'm feeling...
(Current marble count: 15)
(Current marble count: 16)
I'm feeling busy.
(Current marble count: 17)I'm very busy.
(Human jukebox)Super busy.
Extremely busy.
(Current marble count: 18)
What do you most want to say to Daimi?
(Challenge complete)I miss Daimi a lot.
I just miss it.
Yeah.
I've been away too long.
Yesterday I watched some puppy videos,
and it made me miss it even more.
(Woof woof woof)
(I miss you too)
Congratulations, challenge cleared!
(Liu Yuning, 18 marbles
Challenge Success)
Alright.
Okay.
Start!
(Start 2-minute countdown)
In the latest season,
(Current marble count: 0)
what new character do you want to unlock?
(Let's switch it up)
What new character?
An ugly character.
For me, that would be a challenge.
(You're good at exploiting loopholes)
(Current marble count: 1)
(Current marble count: 2)
Set a personal goal
for this season.
(Current marble count: 3)
My personal goal is
(Smooth shot in)
I want to become
(Current marble count: 7)
the top Golden Key holder.
(She can even score two at once)
Rate your sense of humor.
I'd give myself a 5.
(Current marble count: 12)
Why?
I'm a little funny
and half funny.
On a scale of 0 to 10, it's a 5.
(Current marble count: -)
What would you say to your past self?
Past self,
are you cheating?
(Strike first)
(Challenging your past self)
Which moment from previous episodes
(Found another loophole)
scared you the most?
The scariest part was...
I actually forgot
my past episodes.
It scared me so much I lost my memory.
From the detective team,
who would you choose
to film a dance challenge with?
It's definitely Bai Ge.
Because he refuses to film them.
Back then,
Keyu and I managed
to get him to film one.
We felt so accomplished.
We turned his dance clips
into memes.
(Helpless.gif)
We still send them to him often.
Very well.
What style of vlog would you most like
to try shooting?
I've been meaning to try
a full English one
because I've been learning the language.
(Applying what she's learned)
(Challenge over)
Okay.
Success.
I finished them long ago.
(Jin Jing, multiple marbles
Challenge Success)
Alright.
Three, two, one.
Start.
(2-minute countdown begins)
How do you feel when fans
call you handsome?
(Current marble count: 0)
(He chases, it flees)
(Got it back)
(Current marble count: 1)
You're right.
(Man, you're too handsome)
(Current marble count: 2)
What is the most satisfying photo
you've taken recently?
Today.
The group picture.
If there is a time travel theme,
which era would you like to go back to?
I think
I won't want to travel back.
(Current marble count: 3)
I want to stay in the modern world.
(Current marble count: 4)
How do you usually take selfies?
Forward shot.
How are you alike
to a capybara?
What is alike...
(Current marble count: 5)
is the persimmon on its head.
Which agent have you
been using in games recently?
Reyna.
(Current marble count: 6)
Is there anything in particular
you'd like to try
in the new season?
(Current marble count: 7)
Domineering boss.
Then find out!
(Current marble count: 8)
What superpower do you want?
Superpower?
Turning things into gold.
(Very bold)
What's your recent hobby?
Photography.
Do you like dark romance
or wholesome love?
(Current marble count: 10)
I like wholesome love.
(Wholesome love)
If you were to send a comment
to the show,
what would you send?
(Current marble count: 11)
Send a comment to the show.
The Truth (Season 4) is amazing.
(Type "Season 4 is amazing"
on the screen)
Which part of your body
do you think is the most attractive?
(Current marble count: 11, counting)
(He's gotten 12 marbles)
Nose.
It's full.
Success.
(Zhang Linghe,12 marbles
Challenge Success)
Three, two, one.
Start.
(2-minute countdown begins)
(Current marble count: 0)
How does it feel to be here
(Deft-touch Xin)
for the first time?
(Three marbles in one go)
I feel very nervous and excited,
(Current marble count: 3)
and a little scared.
(Smooth)
Do you prefer solo quests or team quests
(Current marble count: 4)
in an escape room?
Team quests of course.
For someone
so brave like me.
I'll wow you all.
(Steady)
What type of plot setting
(Current marble count: 6)
do you want to try this season?
Mmm. Assassin.
Use three words to predict
(So smooth)
how you'll do.
(Current marble count: 9)
Interesting.
(Interesting)
Disheveled.
(Disheveled, Current marble count: 11)
Slight highlights.
(Slight highlights)
Can you say The Truth
in Sichuan dialect?
(Current marble count: 12)
(Right hand going crazy)
The Truth.
(Current marble count: 13)
If you were to send a comment
to the show,
what would you send?
(Calm and steady)
(Current marble count: 15)
Oh My God.
It's so dark.
(Speaks his mind)
(Current marble count: 17)
Okay.
(Ding Chengxin, 17 marbles
Challenge Success)
They're in.
(So easy)
It's so easy.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Bring it on.
(Current marble count: 0)
(2-minute countdown begins)
What do you want
to challenge yourself with this time?
What I want to challenge myself with
is to have better reasoning skills.
(Bad start)
(I pick and pick, and give up)
How do you like your hot chicken noodle?
I like
the normal spicy ones.
What role do you want
(Helpless)
to challenge but have not done so yet?
(Trying hard)
I want to challenge
the assassin.
(Great minds think alike)
(Not very skilled)
With Season 4's comeback,
what role are you prepared to play?
Well.
I'll be whatever I can be.
(All-star Ace)
Are you excited for new cases
(Finally got it)
in the new season?
(Aim for the bottle)
(Failed again)
For the new season,
(Out of ideas)
I hope it'll have
(Panicking)
new and exciting cases
that are unheard of.
If you entered an escape room
(Someone please save me)
and could bring one life-saving item,
what would it be?
If I entered an escape room
and had to bring one life-saving item,
(Working hard)
I'd bring a flashlight.
What aspect of yourself
(Guys, someone help me)
do you think will improve the most this season?
I hope I can improve a lot
in mini-games.
(Missed again)
What genre of music
(Life's stumbling marble for Uncle Wu)
have you been listening to most lately?
Lately...
(Brain working at full speed)
(Actually thinking about game strategy)
Genre I've listened to most lately is...
(Inspiration strikes)
Pop music.
What short-video niche
would you most want to break into?
(Got it under control)
(Current marble count: 1)
For short videos, I think I'd
probably be a gaming streamer.
(The gaming king is here)
(Current marble count:
2, consecutive scores)
Is there anything
you've kept doing since childhood?
(Current marble count: 3)
A habit I've kept since childhood...
(Current marble count: 4)
probably moving my scalp.
(Current marble count: 5)
What do you like being called most?
(Scoring nonstop)
What do I like people calling me most?
(Current marble count: 6)
I like being called...
(Current marble count: 7)
Xiao Zhou, Keyu... all are fine.
What step takes you the longest
before going out?
Washing my hair.
(Current marble count: 8)
Do you rewatch your own work often?
No.
What would you like to say
(Current marble count: 9)
to yourself from last year?
(Challenge over)
Not bad.
Nine.
(Zhou Keyu: 9 marbles, challenge failed)
Didn't figure out the trick at first.
Please begin your challenge.
(Two-minute countdown begins)
(Current marble count: 0)
Use three words to predict
(Too "Wen" for words)
your performance on the show today.
(Current marble count: 2)xxx
(Current marble count: 2)
Smart
Average
Stupid
(Covering all bases,
always hits at least one)
(Current marble count: 3)
What role you are in the group?
What role do you think
you are in the group?
The vibe-maker, I guess.
(Vibe generator)
(Current marble count: 4)
Who do you think you have the best chemistry with in the team?
Either Jin Jing or Ning Ge
(Counting)
If you could send a bullet comment to “Detective Club 4”
what would you say?
(Hahahahahahaha x100)
One hundred “ha”s
So fast
(Quick)
(Plus one accuracy)
Guess your courage ranking in the group
(Current marble count: 6)
Slightly braver than Xiao Ding
(Current marble count: 7)
Did you prepare anything before filming this season?
(Current marble count: 8)
Actually, not really
(Girls who smile a lot can't have bad luck)
Because I didn't know
(Current marble count: 9. Wen wants a fully immersive experience)
What's today's story?
So there's nothing
No chance of memorizing the answers in advance
(On a roll. Current marble count: 10)
(Current marble count: 11)
(Current marble count: 12)
Okay
(Liu Yuning, Jin Jing, Zhang Linghe, Ding Chengxin, Wang Yuwen: Pass; Zhou Keyu: Fail)
(Choose-one-of-three reward, now distributing, recommend: yummy snack)
(Recommend: useful gadget)
(Recommend: satisfying squish toy)
(Recommend: yummy snack)
Voting for yummy snack. No burning "green" allowed.
This is fruit, right?
Snacks
And then cyber flight
These are some props, right?
Voting for squish toy
(Recommend: satisfying squish toy)
My bounce-back is so stress-relieving
My happiness is totally random
Mint candy, I'd say
(Liu Yuning chooses: Full-of-Energy Mint Candy)
Yeah
So I can stay totally sharp at all times
And reason things out with a clear head
(As a detective, always stay on top of your game)
I kind of want to eat this jerky
But also want to squeeze it
(Torn)
Should I just go with the jerky?
Skip the squeezing for now
But nobody's probably picking the squish toy
Go with the squish toy then
Someone's definitely picking the food
My bounce-back is so stress-relieving
(Jin Jing chooses: My Bounce-Back Is So Stress-Relieving)
I'll pick this one
I actually wanted to pick the tangerine peel candy
But, how do I put it
I already have tangerine peel candy at home
(Xie Zheng "logs in")
So I'll pick a
Crispy snappy one
Little meat jerky
(Bluetooth connected)
Eat the jerky, then?
(Zhang Linghe chooses: Crispy Snappy Little Meat Jerky)
I want that lollipop
Feels good
(Ding Chengxin chooses: You're Truly Amazing)
Get a little boost of energy
I want this one - I'm a freeloader
Because I figure
(Wang Yuwen chooses: I'm a Freeloader)
They each grabbed something different
As long as I'm the freeloader
All of it can be mine
(Clever girl)
That's actually pretty clever
This one
Unfortunately, you've failed the challenge
(The only one who failed)
What's the penalty for failing?
You won't be able to claim a reward
Okay
(Players who fail cannot choose a small reward)
That's not so bad
(Better luck next time)
(Channeling frustration into appetite)
(Liu Yuning - Crispy Snappy Little Meat Jerky)
(Jin Jing - Full-of-Energy Mint Candy)
(Zhang Linghe - My Bounce-Back Is So Stress-Relieving)
(Ding Chengxin - You're Truly Amazing)
(Wang Yuwen - I'm a Freeloader)
(Zhou Keyu - You'll Get It Next Time)
Limited-time players entering the dungeon world for the first time
(Secretly pleased)
will receive a skill card
(Got it)
A little bonus
Right
Okay
(Limited-time players entering the dungeon world for the first time will receive a skill card)
Eighty lives
What you've received is a Lights Out card
(Wang Yuwen receives one Lights Out card)
(What does this mean?)
You can use it during the investigation
or before the voting phase
And when you use it, you can also
create your own
signature gesture for it
Lights out
Okay
(What kind of gesture should I do?)
So I'll take out this card
And say that
(Lights Out Card)
Okay - I'm now going to use my skill card
Right
Night falls - close your eyes
How's that?
And then everyone closes their eyes
And the lights go out
Night falls - close your eyes
And then it goes dark
Sound good?
Yeah, that works
Okay
Hope you solve the case today
(Skill card summary)
(Ding Chengxin - Copy Card; Liu Yuning - Extra Time Card; Jin Jing - Comfort Card)
(Wang Yuwen - Lights Out Card; Zhang Linghe - Rewind Card; Zhou Keyu - Restore Card)
(All rewards have been distributed to players)
What's this?
Beef jerky
(Sharing +1)
Crispy beef
(Sharing +3)
(Sharing +4)
(Sharing +5)
(Delicious)
(Crispy)
(Savory)
(Full of flavor)
This is actually pretty good
Alright everyone,
let's start the investigation!
Unlock every layer, let courage ignite
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪