My lord Left Chancellor
I trailed them the whole way
To the forest edge of Zhenyuan County
They split into two groups
Golden Guard Pan took the main road
The other three slipped into the forest
I laid an ambush in the woods
And shot Ning Chen dead
Where is the body?
The...
The body...
I did indeed shoot Ning Chen dead
He plunged from a sheer cliff into the river
There is no way he survived
I...
"No way he survived"?
Is this how I taught you to do things?
I want to see the man if he's alive,
and his corpse if he's dead.
Now go, find him at once!
Yes, my lord
Forgive me, my lord Left Chancellor
Young master, you're awake.
You were in the water for a long time.
My daughter Lian'er carried you back.
Your fever wouldn't break.
You've been unconscious.
Lian'er.
Bring some water.
Have some water first.
I'll do it myself.
Don't drink too much.
You've been out for a day and a night.
I'll go brew some medicine for you.
You rest for a while.
Much obliged.
Old Man Li.
You owe the Imperial Uncle four months' rent.
Debts must be repaid. That's only natural.
If you can't produce the money today,
we'll take your daughter as payment.
Steward Zhang, please.
Please show some mercy.
Just a few more days.
I'll definitely pay the rent.
I beg you, I beg you.
Spare my daughter.
The Imperial Uncle has taken a liking to her.
You should be delighted.
The Imperial Uncle has said,
once your daughter is his,
all your debts will be wiped clean.
No, please...
Men, take this girl away!
Don't keep the Imperial Uncle waiting.
Guards!
You can't! You can't!
You can't!
You blind old fool!
How dare you defy the Imperial Uncle!
You old wretch!
Father!
Who is it?
Who dares strike me?
The Imperial Inspectorate.
Good, you recognize it.
Don't believe me?
Here, take the badge.
Verify it yourself.
Greetings, my lord.
Damn it.
How did someone from the Imperial Inspectorate
suddenly turn up here?
In broad daylight,
attempting to abduct a commoner's daughter.
Who gave you such gall?
My lord.
I serve the Imperial Uncle.
He is the elder brother of the current Empress.
You dare strike me?
That's defying the Imperial Uncle himself.
The Empress's brother...
Could the corruption in Zhenyuan County
and the suffering of the people
be tied to the Imperial Uncle?
Now you know to be afraid?
As they say, imperial power doesn't reach the countryside.
In this Zhenyuan County,
the Imperial Uncle is heaven itself.
Heaven, my ass!
Forget a lowly thug like you.
Even if the Imperial Uncle himself came today,
I'd still beat him all the same.
My lord, spare me! My lord!
Stop, stop hitting him!
Any more and you'll kill him!
If he dies here,
the Imperial Uncle may not touch you,
but he'll never spare
the two of us, father and daughter.
For the sake of these two today,
I'll spare your worthless life.
Take me to the Imperial Uncle at once.
I'd like to see
who in this dynasty
truly is heaven.
My lord.
I have something important to tell you.
Old man, what are you doing?
Get up at once.
No, no, no.
My lord.
Though my eyes grow dim,
my judgment of character remains sharp.
My lord.
You are full of righteous fervor,
upright and kind.
For the people of Zhenyuan County,
I have a most important item
to entrust to you.
What is this?
My lord
There is something you might not know.
The former clerk of Zhenyuan County
was my dear friend for many years
He still had a conscience.
He gathered evidence of corruption
from the prefect down to the magistrates
across all of Chongzhou,
and recorded it in this very ledger.
Zhenyuan County is no longer a place fit for men
The Imperial Uncle, the Empress's brother,
has made this place his treasure trove.
Elder Li speaks the truth
Zhenyuan County has long become a living hell
The Imperial Uncle, drunk on royal favor
preys upon the common folk
Hu Qiang and his ilk abuse their power
committing every manner of evil
The officials collude as one
Their tyranny is fiercer than tigers
The people have no clothes to cover themselves
and no food to fill their bellies.
Tree bark and grass roots are their daily fare
Such misery
is beyond anything ever heard of
Aren't these men from the Imperial Uncle's manor?
How were they beaten so badly?
And, and bound up like this?
This man doesn't dress like an ordinary official.
Could he have come to save us?
Really?
Imperial Uncle
Please
Golden Guard Pan
Come
Let us share another cup, you and I
Thank you, Imperial Uncle
Come, gentlemen
Please
Golden Guard Pan
Our town is a poor and remote backwater.
Such a small place
We have nothing worthy to offer you
Forgive our poor hospitality
I beg your pardon
Lord Ai, you are too kind
Imperial Uncle
You worthless wretch!
How many times have I told you?
Only maidens of marriageable age
These rotten, ugly creatures
have no business prancing about here!
Imperial Uncle
Calm your wrath
Please, calm down
If your ears serve no purpose
I shall rip them off and feed them to the dogs
Do you hear me?
I will bear it in mind.
Get out, get out!
Yes, my lord
Golden Guard Pan.
If you fancy her,
she is yours.
Thank you, Imperial Uncle.
Allow me to pour your wine.
Good.
Come, come, come.
Let us raise a toast.
To these distinguished lords from the capital.
My lords, let us drink together.
I thought the Imperial Inspectorate's
Golden Guards were truly incorruptible.
Who would have thought
they accept both money and women.
Drink your fill.
Once you've had your fun, get lost.
No one shall disturb
my reign as the king of Zhenyuan County.
Let me feed you, my lord.
I can manage. I can manage.
Come now, my lord.
That won't do.
Ning Chen.
What is he doing here?
Who goes there?
Such audacity!
To barge into the Imperial Uncle's estate!
Ning Chen, you...
Golden Guard Pan.
Is this man your subordinate?
Ning Chen.
The Imperial Uncle is here. Mind your manners.
What do you think you are doing?
Well, isn't this grand.
Outside, the people are in rags
and starving.
Yet here you are, building high stages
and indulging in boundless extravagance.
You're nothing but beasts in human skin.
Ning Chen!
My good lord,
do calm yourself.
What on earth has made you so furious?
Who are you?
I am
the magistrate of Zhenyuan County,
Ai Wenguang.
You...
Even as a man of the Imperial Inspectorate,
you can't just beat an imperial official as you please.
So you know you're an imperial official?
As the magistrate of Zhenyuan County,
while your people starve to death,
you indulge in luxury here.
You beast, worse than swine!
Ning Chen!
Stop this!
I am the Imperial Uncle,
elder brother of the reigning Empress.
This is my estate.
In broad daylight,
you dare commit violence here?
Such audacity!
Shut your mouth!
As the Imperial Uncle,
you ought to uphold the laws of Daxuan,
preserve the dignity of the royal house,
and cherish the people as your own children.
But what have you done, you corrupt dog?
You...
You let these thugs seize women by force,
treating human life like dirt.
You haven't done a single decent thing!
So, Imperial Uncle,
do you acknowledge your crimes?
This is outrageous!
Even His Majesty has never rebuked me so.
You, a mere Silver Guard,
dare to spew such impudent words?
Even if what you say is true, so what?
Here in Zhenyuan County,
do you dare lay a hand on the Imperial Uncle?