( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Boy,
don't take it too far.
Be careful that these people might hold grudges against you.
Stop bluffing me.
Isn't this pretty impressive?
I am not bluffing.
Rule-based items
must also follow the cycle of cause and effect.
Working day and night like this,
tirelessly,
is obviously unreasonable.
When they wake up the next day,
the Heavenly Dao will automatically fix this anomaly.
In their memories,
you will be the culprit who forced them to work.
It works like this?
This is the conservation of energy.
Conservation of energy.
That's a very apt summary.
Alright.
How about this.
Everyone,
go back and rest tonight.
Work again tomorrow during the day.
Cancel the above rules first.
Make sure the security is in place first.
All magic and divine probing are forbidden here.
Any demonic spells are useless against me.
Oh, right.
Make those people stop hating me.
Like this.
The master of this place is quite charming,
likable,
and loved by all.
This is good.
Who is it?
Why are you here?
I miss you.
Didn't you have something to do tonight?
Nothing is
more important than you, Lin.
A moment of spring night
is worth a thousand gold.
It's late at night.
Don't flirt with me.
This
works too fast, doesn't it?
Lin,
let me undress you.
You have too many flaws.
If Su Ningxue could be like you,
providing full emotional value
and speaking in a sweet voice,
how great would that be.
Lin,
what are you saying?
I don't understand.
Still playing dumb, huh?
Chu Xiao'er.
What's up with you?
No cultivation base or divine powers,
yet you always see through others' tricks.
And you.
When imitating others,
you can't just copy their looks.
Where is Sha Mozu?
Hand him over.
I won't bother you anymore.
Sha Mozu?
Why do you want that thing?
I am not a thing.
Give it to me.
You can't handle that thing.
If you take care of this girl,
I will owe you a favor.
Young Master.
Are you asleep, Young Master?
The demonic aura disappeared here.
Could it be...
His Majesty is quite fond of this lecher.
Let's go in and take a look.
Qiaoyun,
how could you be so cruel?
why won't you see me?
Bro, you drank so much.
The two of us can't even carry you.
Leave me alone.
Just let me die.
Qiaoyun,
the money to buy your freedom
was almost ready.
How could you just leave with someone else?
Bro,
stop howling.
If you keep howling, the whole capital will know
that you got cuckolded by a girl from Baihua Pavilion,
and the least popular one at that.
You two bastards
are still mocking me.
There is a female thief.
Master.
Are you asleep, Master?
Xiaoying.
It's so late.
What's the matter?
I saw the candle lit in your room,
so I cooked you a bowl of porridge.
Han Xiaoying?
Isn't she dead?
What's going on?
The protagonist's halo shines on my sister.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Come in.
Move over.
No, Xiaoying.
Master.
I saw the candle lit in your room,
so I cooked you a bowl of porridge.
Get up and have some porridge.
Okay.
Master,
what's wrong?
I've been quite tired lately.
I don't want to move.
What are you doing?
Then,
let me feed you, Master.
Master.
Let me feed you then.
Glad no one is here.
Otherwise, it would be embarrassing.
What's going on here?
I can't use my magic.
In Luoxian Town,
what kind of opportunity did Lin Mo get?
This is the place.
She just used a Speed Talisman.
Isn't this our benefactor's house?
Mr. Lin's house.
Then just now,
that female thief showed great skills.
I'm afraid Mr. Lin is in danger.
We can't just sit and do nothing.
Right.
I've already lost Qiaoyun.
I can't lose my benefactor too.
Should we knock on the door then?
No.
If we alert her,
I'm worried the thief might do something reckless.
Let's sneak in quietly.
Zhuzi,
it's up to you.
Wait a moment.
Go.
Alright.
I'll do it myself.
Go back and get some rest early.
Master.
I used to feed you.
So.
You are Mo Xiaolan now.
No, no.
Actually,
I have merged the memories of two people.
Before meeting you,
Mo Xiaolan also had a bitter life.
It was when she died of illness
that I merged spirits with her.
And then I entered the Lin residence.
This is schizophrenia.
What is schizophrenia?
It's not a split.
It's a merger.
Don't overthink it.
Wood demons are just like this.
Being influenced by the memories and emotions of the previous host
is a side effect of their abilities.
I only said a couple of words.
It's okay.
Whether you are Han Xiaoying or Mo Xiaolan,
you must live well.
You don't have to keep following me.
I'm not the old Lin Mo anymore.
I don't mind, Master.
Send her away quickly.
You.
Xiaoying,
it's getting late.
Go back and rest early.
Young Master,
I used to sleep with you when you were little.
How about today...
No, no, no.
I'm a grownup now.
I can sleep by myself.
Lin Mo,
are you in there?
Open the door.
Oh my,
it's Su Wuhui.
Why is she here?
Lin Mo,
I know you're not asleep.
Open the door now.
No.
If she finds out
I'm shirtless with you,
and if Su Ningxue knows about it,
she will tear me apart.
Hurry up and find a place to hide.
I'll just hide behind you.
That won't work.
Chu Xiao'er,
long time no see.
Han Xiaolan.
No,
Mo Xiaoying.
Brothers,
I feel something is wrong.
I also feel
something is wrong.
We can't use our magic powers here.
Why are you shaking your head?
There's something wrong with the three of us.
What's wrong with us?
Why are we sneaking around like thieves?
Aren't we here to save someone?
How dare you, Chu Xiao'er.
You still have the nerve to pester our young master.
We'll settle all our old and new scores today.
Since we've been reborn into a new life,
let's not bring up the past.
Wuhui.
You came to see me so late.
What is the matter?
Shh.
I called you for a long time.
Why didn't you open the door?
What are you talking about?
It's so late.
You came to my mansion alone
and knocked on my door.
I haven't even asked what you want.
Does your master know you're doing this?
In Fengming City,
some people were killed by monsters who sucked their blood and dug out their hearts.
I tracked down a few traces of demonic aura.
The trail disappeared right at your mansion,
so I came in to investigate.
Right under the capital,
there are still monsters trying to harm people?
Monster plagues are rampant in the Daqian Dynasty now.
It's not surprising that they've spread to the capital,
so we can't afford to be careless.
Very good.
As expected of the head of Tianji Pavilion.
However,
I don't have any monsters here,
so you can go back.
Otherwise, a lone man and woman here
won't sound good if word gets out.
An upright person is not afraid of a crooked shadow.
I don't feel guilty,
so why should you?
Do I?
I don't think so.
Why must you
eat congee shirtless?
There's no rule in Daqian's laws
that says I can't eat congee shirtless, right?
Then why are you covering the bed?
What's inside?
Do I?
No.
Don't come over.
Don't.
No.
Don't get on someone else's bed.
What's in the blanket?
Commander Su, we meet again.
Hello, Sister Wuhui.
How dare you, Lin Mo.
My sister likes you so much.
But you dare to meet women secretly in the middle of the night,
and two at a time.
If I said
one of them came to me for something
and the other came for porridge,
would you believe it?
Wait.
What's wrong now?
What if we alert the enemy,
and it's not what we think,
wouldn't that be awkward?
Right.
What if that woman
is not a female thief,
but has that kind of relationship with him.
If we swagger in like this,
wouldn't we ruin their good time?
Makes sense.
Keep it down.
You lecher.
If my sister finds out,
let's see how she deals with you.
Anyway, whether you believe it or not,
it's not what you think.
Chu Xiao'er.
As a Demon Refiner from Beijing,
what is your scheme in coming to our Daqian?
And you.
You are no longer Mo Xiaolan now.
Don't just casually
move into a man's mansion.
Lady,
does what I do here have anything to do with you?
Have you caught the monster harming people in the capital?
You...
Sister Wuhui.
Getting into my young master's bed
and pulling off his blanket,
isn't it inappropriate?
What?
Did your young lady agree
to share my young master with you?
A fallen princess and monster refiner of Beijing,
and an unwanted newborn wood demon maid.
To think you two are actually huddling together for warmth.
This capital
is getting harder and harder to understand.
You guys chat.
I'm leaving.
Lin Mo,
come back.
Give that to me.
This has nothing to do with me anymore.
Don't even think about it.
Young Master, don't go.
She's bullying me.
Let him go.
Keep your hands to yourself.
No magic allowed.
I'm not afraid of a fistfight.