( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Village Head.
I know some of you
are skilled fighters.
You came to Luoxian Town
just to seek peace.
Those who know how to use a sword,
grab your swords and follow me inside.
Today,
those who are afraid to die can stand guard outside.
We must rescue our wives and children.
Village Head,
you stay outside.
If we don't make it out...
You must find a way
to get everyone out of Luoxian Town.
How can you charge to the front
while I, the village head, hide in the back?
I'm going with you this time.
Let's go.
Han Qingyun,
you and your sister wait outside.
Sister,
wait for me outside.
Brother.
Be careful.
So the abducted brides
are all here.
Wife.
Lin Mo,
get out of here quickly.
Mother.
Shh.
Do you want to die?
If you wake up the evil spirits here,
we'll all die.
Keep quiet.
Lin Fan,
what tricks are you playing now?
Brother.
This is the final trial.
Let's settle everything
right here.
Lin Fan.
You said if I brought Han Xiaoying here,
you would return my wife to me.
You lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
As long as you can
find your wife,
you can take her away.
Go ahead and choose.
So what are we
competing in this time?
Find your destined woman.
If you choose right,
you'll be safe.
If you choose wrong,
you'll die.
Are you kidding me?
I'm afraid these women
are all controlled by you.
I
have no obligation to tell you that much.
You.
Don't lift it.
Don't just lift the veil.
Lifting the wrong one will get you killed.
Wife.
This is the bracelet I bought for you.
I found you, Wife.
Wife.
Husband.
You.
You shouldn't have come here.
Wife,
I've already lost our child.
I can't lose you too.
Let's go home together.
Husband.
Look,
am I
beautiful now?
Beautiful.
My wife
is breathtakingly beautiful.
Wife.
Husband,
can you
stay by my side forever?
We'll be together forever.
I'm sorry, Husband,
I
just couldn't hold back anymore.
This is fine.
Fine.
Husband.
I
will join you soon.
Since the Lin family invited you all,
you are our guests.
The banquet is ready.
Please take your seats.
Cut the nonsense.
Where are our families?
Right.
Where is my wife?
Hand them over.
You all want your wives back.
I understand.
After the banquet,
I will let you see them.
You thieving witch.
Stop playing tricks.
We wouldn't dare eat your feast.
Release them right now,
and we might leave your corpse intact.
The wine is not poisoned.
It's safe to drink.
No demonic power infused either.
It's perfectly fine.
The food is not poisoned either.
Just a normal feast.
What trick is this woman playing?
Could it be
a last meal before execution?
Shut up!
Okay.
What a touching love story.
Brother,
it's your turn.
What kind of talisman is this? It actually works on humans.
I can't move or speak.
This is your last revelry.
After tonight,
the Lin family in Luoxian Town
will cease to exist.
Su Ning.
If you are turned into a Yin Fiend,
I will make this entire world
be buried with you.
Then I will follow you.
We will be buried together
as husband and wife.
But if you're okay,
please give me a hint.
Lin Mo,
I'm here!
On your right!
You walked past me!
This talisman isn't demonic magic,
otherwise my dragon aura could suppress it.
This must be something from Beijing,
used against Daqian.
Lin Mo, I'm here!
On your left!
You missed me again!
What's wrong, brother?
Can't find the girl you like?
You fool.
You're dazzled, aren't you?
You better hurry.
When time's up,
you'll be eliminated.
Your rules have a loophole.
What did you say?
Not lifting the veil
doesn't mean
I can't touch other places, right?
This fool.
He always finds a loophole.
The height is wrong.
The shoulders are too wide.
No.
She's not even as thin as I am.
Lin Mo, you bastard.
Have you touched enough?
This.
It's this feeling.
Nailed it.
Watch out.
You bastard,
how long are you going to pick?
I'm here now, aren't I?
Am I that thin?
They're all plumper than me.
Silly,
I was able to find you
because you have body temperature.
That talisman just now
made me unable to move
and speak.
It's okay.
It's good that
you're fine.
How is this possible?
Why didn't you turn into an evil spirit?
You...
You are...
You are the destined woman.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
However,
I am indeed here to deal with your Lin family.
I passed.
Your turn,
brother.
I don't know what tricks you're playing.
But I know
you're stalling.
So I won't let you succeed.
Since you all want your wives back so badly,
I'll grant your wish.
Someone,
bring the bride in.
This...
This is...
Everyone, stay back!
Come back!
Wife,
this is my wife!
My wife,
are you okay?
I was so worried about you.
Hus...
Husband.
Run...
Run!
They are no longer your family.
They have been transformed into Yin Fiends.
This is Beijing's dark magic.
Everyone must be careful.
How can this be?
My wife...
Please don't hurt my wife!
Wan'er,
my daughter!
We just saved you once.
Don't be so stubborn.
If you keep this up, don't blame us for being ruthless.
They are no longer your daughters.
They are no longer your family.
Everyone, calm down.
Brides,
take off your veils
and recognize your families.
If you really care about your female relatives,
help them pass on early.
Being neither human nor ghost,
they are in more pain.
Those who can't bear to do it,
step back.
The rest of you,
follow me!
Attack!
Second Brother, Third Brother,
attack!
Ring the bell.
How long are we ringing it this time?
This firework is huge.
We have to ring it a bit longer.
I don't know what custom this is.
Ringing the bell every day.
This pill
can simulate the Yin Sha aura,
so I won't trigger their attacks.
That's normal.
After all,
since we were kids,
you couldn't win without cheating.
Still stubborn at death's door.
Not bad.
It really works.
Although mine is a fake,
as long as the real one isn't here,
I can still command them.
Damn,
this isn't just cheating anymore.
This is literally having a substitute.
Listen to my orders.
Spare the women.
Tear the men
to pieces.