( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I was wrong!
I was wrong! Don't take me!
Don't take me! I was wrong!
Master Wang.
Master Wang!
Why are you panicking?
A wealthy merchant like you
keeps no lamps in your courtyard.
You made me fall into the pond.
My clothes are soaked.
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 3=
Just now,
you said you were wrong.
What exactly did you do wrong?
Well...
To answer you, Official Di,
Qi Changshun
treated me like his own brother.
Two years ago,
the court urgently needed salt.
I should have escorted the shipment,
but unfortunately,
I broke my leg.
Who knew
the ship would sink?
If I had boarded that day,
I would have been the one to die.
Qi
died in my place.
I have been ashamed
and unable to find peace ever since.
It was all my fault.
Qi built Hengshun Salt Bureau
from nothing.
So
after I took over
Hengshun Salt Bureau,
I never changed its name.
I only wished
to comfort Qi's soul
in the afterlife.
Everyone in town is saying
the water ghost
is the vengeful spirit of the Qi family.
What do you think?
Was there an injustice?
If there truly was,
then Qi must still blame me.
If he comes to take my life,
I am willing to go down there
and keep Qi company.
Where were the Qi father and son buried?
Buried...
Buried at...
And you call him your brother?
You even forgot where he was buried.
Perhaps Master Wang
has been busy with salt affairs
and has not visited for some time.
That is why
he cannot recall it.
I am ashamed.
I truly...
I truly have been too busy
to spare the time.
(Ruanjiang County Bureau)
Who comes to file a grievance?
I am Du Ruo.
I seek justice for my husband.
Du Ruo?
Aren't you the new bride
of Wang Xian, Young Master
of Hengshun Salt Bureau?
I am Du Ruo.
I seek justice for my husband, Qi Feng.
What?
Didn't
Qi Feng die
when the ship sank two years ago?
I thought
we had been parted forever too.
But Heaven showed mercy
and let us meet again.
What injustice did he suffer?
He was burned to death.
When?
Two hours ago.
Where?
Tell me everything.
Two days ago,
we agreed to meet tonight at Buxianxian.
- But when I arrived,
- Let's go.
I saw two people setting fire
to Buxianxian.
Qi Feng.
Qi Feng!
Ruo!
Go!
Qi Feng!
Ruo!
Don't come closer!
Qi Feng!
Did you see
what those two looked like?
Even in death, I could never forget.
There is soot
in the victim's mouth and nose.
The skin is badly charred.
There are localized burns and blisters.
Parts of the skin
have shriveled and peeled away.
All signs point to death by burning.
Just as Du Ruo said,
the deceased was indeed male.
The body measured six chi in length.
Official Di,
there is
something strange about this fire.
Official Di, these are letters
personally written by Qi Feng.
Please have a look.
Ruo.
(If this letter reaches you...)
(After surviving the disaster at sea,)
(I thought our fate had come to an end.)
(By fortune, I survived.)
Ruo.
If this letter reaches you...
once the troubles
of this world are settled,
we will enjoy the beauty
of life together again.
Qi Feng
appeared half a month ago?
Yes.
If he was still alive,
why did he wait two years
before showing himself?
He said...
There was something suspicious
about the sinking
of the Qi family's ship.
Before uncovering the truth,
I could not reveal myself.
We only resumed contact
through letters half a month ago.
(Ruo. Meet me at Buxianxian
two nights from now. It is urgent.)
Buxianxian.
Urgent.
What did Qi Feng discover?
Before he could say anything,
he...
Qi Feng
is the water ghost?
No.
No, he is not.
(River Transport Order)
The water ghost claims lives.
The transport order bears the name Qi.
Qi Feng appeared half a month ago.
That matches exactly
with the time of death
of the first victim
in the water ghost case.
It must be Qi Feng.
That is only speculation.
The handwriting above
was not written by the same person.
(River Transport Order. Qi Feng)
If Qi Feng wished to hide his identity,
forging different handwriting
would have been easy.
Lin is right.
Without proof,
we cannot make reckless conclusions.
Du Ruo
has truly suffered greatly.
Tomorrow was supposed
to be her wedding day,
yet such a tragedy happened instead.
Ruo.
The dead cannot return to life.
If you want to cry,
then cry.
Do not keep it all buried inside.
Seeing you like this
only pains me even more.
I will leave you alone now.
Qi Feng is the water ghost.
Ruo,
when did you find out?
When he killed the second man.
Qi Feng was an exceptional swimmer.
He survived the sinking.
After returning to Ruanjiang,
he uncovered the truth
behind what happened.
He wanted revenge
for Uncle Qi and Aunt Qi,
and for all the innocent souls
who died unjustly back then.
Ruo!
Father.
Qi Feng is the water ghost.
Ruo.
You have suffered so much.
Father,
I have already lost
the man I loved most.
I want you to stay with me forever.
I cannot lose you too.
I cannot.
Father will stay with you forever.
Forever.
Master Wang.
No...
No sign of him.
How about Yihua House?
They said he left two days ago.
Keep searching.
Keep searching!
Master,
report it to the authorities.
With the water ghost...
Shut up!
It cannot be the water ghost.
Absolutely not!
I have seen plenty of corpses,
but this is my first time
seeing someone burned to death.
This is...
Strange.
Why do both victims
have this kind of fiber on them?
What fiber?
Official Di,
look.
This is...
Hemp rope.
(They were stuffed into)
(fishing nets woven from hemp rope,)
(and weighed down before being drowned.)
(This is the true face
of the water ghost.)
Official Di.
You must help me, Official Di.
My son is missing.
Missing?
That Yihua House...
What I mean is,
the Young Master often stays out
all night.
So when he hadn't shown up
these past few days,
I did not think much of it.
But
today is his wedding day.
There is no way he would not show up.
Wasn't the marriage already called off?
Perhaps he could not accept it
and went somewhere else to drink.
Reporting to Official Di,
we have searched everywhere.
When and where
was Wang Xian last seen?
Two days ago.
The Young Master said
he was going to Yi...
Going to Yihua House
to see Cui Lan.
No, wait.
Official Di,
the last person
my son
should have seen was Du Ruo.
Missing?
Two days ago,
did you see Wang Xian?
No.
I am here.
You need not worry about anything.
That night,
what exactly happened?
Please seek justice for me, Official Di.
What makes him better than me?
Qi Feng was kindhearted,
upright,
and honorable in all he did.
His love for me
was beyond question.
And what about you?
Cruel and calculating,
yet cowardly to the core.
You wanted to marry me
for no reason other than to prove
that you were better than him,
to satisfy that pathetic
and laughable pride of yours.
How could you
ever compare to him?
What is this?
Give it to me.
Bring it here!
Give it to me!
Give me the letter!
Let go!
Give it to me!
(Ruo. Meet me at Buxianxian
two nights from now. It is urgent.)
(Qi Feng)
Qi Feng?
Impossible.
It's been two years.
I thought your illness
was only an excuse
to avoid marrying me.
I never imagined
Qi Feng was actually still alive.
You two truly disgust me.
You were willing to risk
your entire Du family for his sake?
Buxianxian?
What?
Were you planning
to elope before our wedding?
Did you tell Qi Feng
about what happened between us
at Buxianxian?
No wonder the shaman said
he wasn't drowned to death.
He was burned alive.
If drowning could not kill him,
then I would burn him to death.
The two people who killed Qi Feng
worked for Wang Xian?
Yes.
Why did you not say so last night?
Wang Xian
used my father's life
to force me to marry him.
Then he burned Qi Feng alive.
There is nothing he would not do.
I...
Qi Feng is the water ghost?
Yes.
Qi Feng is the water ghost.
Then if he is already dead,
why did you continue hiding
the truth for him?
Qi Feng
is the water ghost?
No.
No, he is not.
Qi Feng disguised himself
as the water ghost to kill.
He was already guilty
in the eyes of the law.
I feared the Bureau
would no longer
value his life,
so I lied.
Official Di,
Wang Xian must have fled out of fear.
Please seek justice
for Qi Feng, Official Di.
I do not think Wang Xian is missing.
Qi Feng's body
must have been discovered,
and Wang Dingrong hid him away.
Whether it is true or not,
our priority
is to find him.
Since Wang Dingrong has made his move,
we shall respond in kind.
Whether he is truly missing
or merely staging an act of self pity,
one wrong step in this move
could cost him everything.
If Qi Feng truly was the water ghost,
then Sun Qi and the other two
must have been connected
to the sinking of the Qi family's ship.
Di!
Two years ago,
on the ship that sank
with the Qi family,
Sun Qi handled the transport orders,
Liu Shun was one of the dock laborers,
and Jia Gui handled ship repairs.
In the half month
after the ship sank,
Sun Qi bought a house,
Liu Shun got married,
and Jia Gui
opened his own carpentry shop.
You even managed to find all that out.
No one handles this kind of work
better than Duan.
Naturally.
The sinking of the ship
must be connected to Wang Dingrong.
But it has already been two years.
The evidence is probably gone by now.
The most urgent matter
is Qi Feng's death.
Tell Magistrate Cao
to find the arsonists
as soon as possible.
Duan.
Hm?
The docks are crowded
and full of gossip.
Go investigate.
Understood.
My mother said
there's a water ghost in the river.
She told me not to come near it.
If she finds out,
she'll beat me senseless.
We'll spear two fish
and head right back.
What are you afraid of?
It's not like you've never seen
my fishing skills before.
I never miss.
It won't take long.
Look.
Whose clothes fell into the river?
(Preview of Next Episode)
Young...
Young Master.
Go.
Light it.
You do it.
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪