( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
You're so cute.
I'd do anything...
if it's for you, Ama.
So always stay by my side, okay?
OST title
♫  ♫
[Luna Nest]
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you very much!
- Minase!
- Yes?
You messed up the choreography again.
- Again?
- How many times is that now?
I'm so sorry!
You're all gonna stay to practice
for tomorrow.
What?
Come on, get to it.
- I can't believe this.
- I'm sorry.
- Can't believe she screwed it up.
Hey, aren't you thirsty?
Yeah, 'cause a certain someone
made us stay late.
Shall I go buy everyone drinks?
Ama, that's so thoughtful of you!
Thank you!
Excuse me. We're filming right now.
Would you mind waiting a bit?
I'm so sorry.
Excuse me, we have one person waiting.
One person's waiting.
I don't want to break up!
Wow, a lovers' quarrel.
I need to go.
Wait, Chiaki! Please...
Don't touch me!
This is the worst...
Sorry, I'll pay for it.
Oh, but I don't have my wallet.
My workplace is nearby.
Can you come with me?
I-It's fine.
After all, I can't just follow a stranger.
You're Chiaki Hosho?
Good, you know who I am.
If you're going this way,
could you be heading
to that rehearsal studio?
Yes...
Does that mean
we're in the same line of work?
I'm just starting out,
but I'm technically an idol.
Is that person from earlier
going to be okay?
Oh...
I'm in a bit of trouble.
She's like a stalker.
A stalker?
But I guess it's kind of part of the job.
That's rough.
Actually, come with me.
This time for real. Ready? Action!
Thank you. Okay.
- Prep for the next scene.
- Got it.
Here.
I don't need this much!
But this is the only bill I have.
It's 2,138 yen.
I can't accept more than that!
You're interesting.
I contacted the actress and her manager,
but I can't reach them!
Huh, what do we do? Try calling.
- Okay!
- Is something wrong?
Mr. Hosho, it seems Ms. Hibiki took off.
Is that so...
Took off?
[Anna Saotome]
What's taking so long?
Everyone's worried about you.
I'm so sorry.
I actually spilled the drinks on my way back,
and I have to go buy them again.
My apologies, my name is Chiaki Hosho.
Could I please speak with her manager?
Huh, seriously? Chiaki Hosho?
- Seriously?
- Huh?
Hey, Mr. Suzui!
It's... It's Chiaki Hosho.
Yes?
Would it be okay
if I borrowed Ms. Minase for a bit?
I'd like to ask her to be the replacement
for an actress who bailed.
Huh?
What do I do?
Even if it's just this one line.
[I love you. I've always loved you.]
Sorry for asking so suddenly.
Well, I don't think I can do it after all.
I've never done any acting before.
You're an idol, right?
Yes.
It could be a chance
to expand your work, you know?
That's true.
As a not-so-successful idol like me,
I rarely get the chance to be on a drama set.
Alright! This is my one and only big stage!
Here you go. We're about to start.
Don't be so nervous.
We can redo it, so it's okay.
Okay!
Alright, we're starting!
Take one. Ready? Action!
Just leave me alone.
I can't let the pressure get to me.
My character is a girl
who harbors feelings
for the young man played by Mr. Hosho.
It's a quick scene,
but to her, it's an important one
where she gets over a crush she's had.
That's right.
If I think back to that moment...
Ama.
I love you.
I've always loved you.
Cut! Okay!
Good, I didn't cause any trouble.
Hello, I'm Suzui, her manager.
Thank you for working with Minase today.
Thank you.
We'll get going now,
so you can focus on the shoot.
I'm home!
Welcome back, Sis!
Welcome home!
What were you doing?
Today, I was out shopping.
Welcome home.
Mom, go back to sleep.
You had a fever again this morning.
Sorry again.
It's okay. I'll get dinner ready now.
Thanks.
I'll help make dinner too.
[50% off]
- Me too!
- Really?
What are you making?
- A bookmark.
- I see.
It was only one line, but it was fun.
I hope I get to do acting work again someday.
What? A movie starring Hosho?
It's the production team from that drama.
A youth drama set in a music college.
You'll be a student.
Apparently, Mr. Hosho recommended you
after seeing your acting.
It's a dream come true,
but why would Mr. Hosho...
By the way, the pay is...
A month's worth of groceries?
I'll do it! Please let me do it!
Alright.
[Our Ensemble]
Minase.
- Yes?
- Listen, okay?
No matter how close you get to him,
don't make any mistakes with Mr. Hosho,
alright?
A mistake?
He's from a major agency. We're a tiny one.
If something happens,
you'd be the one to suffer for it.
Oh, there's no way.
That'd never happen.
How could I ever, with a star like that?
Yeah, I suppose not.
[Our Ensemble]
[Ama Minase]
Here's Ama Minase, playing Kanon.
Thank you.
- We're counting on you.
- Thank you.
You're amazing.
That... That's not true.
Cut! Cut! You blinked!
Sorry, sorry.
I really love when you play, Tatsumi.
- Cut!
- Cut! You flipped your line!
- One more time.
- I'm so sorry!
- It's okay.
- So sorry.
Ready? Action!
I'm not at my best lately.
What's wrong?
My fingers...
They can't keep up with my feelings.
Don't be so whiny.
You don't have to put it like that.
You guys wouldn't understand how I feel.
Wait!
- Cut!
- Hey!
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Why did you fall? Get the first aid kit.
- Can you get up?
- I'm sorry.
[Our Ensemble]
[Ama Minase]
Good work on the first day.
Good work today.
Sorry for causing so much trouble.
I was like that at first too.
Even for a minor role,
I'd do take after take.
The set felt tense,
and we'd run over schedule.
You went through that too, Mr. Hosho?
Of course I did.
You know, I think you have
talent for acting, Ms. Minase.
Huh?
I mean it.
I could tell just from acting
in that one scene with you.
You were so immersed in your character,
I couldn't tell it was your first time.
Hearing that from you...
I'll take them to heart
and give it my all until the very end!
So dramatic.
Oh, right.
Can I call you by your first name?
There's also a staff member named Ms. Minase,
so it might get confusing.
Oh, I see.
- My name is...
- Ama.
It's a cute name.
You can call me "Chiaki", if you want.
Huh?
Try it.
Chiaki?
Yeah.
Oh, right, about your next scene...
Listen, okay?
No matter how close you get to him,
don't make any mistakes
with Mr. Hosho, alright?
Oh, no, you see...
Chiaki.
This is Shiki Motomiya,
a member of my old idol group.
He has a cameo in this movie.
Hello.
Nice to meet you, I'm Ama Minase.
Oh, I should get going soon.
Yeah, see you.
See you.
Is that girl your new interest, Chiaki?
Yeah.
Getting bothered by that weird woman
was worth it.
Can't you stop doing that already?
You're a good guy, Shiki, unlike me.
That's not what I meant.
When you finally find
someone you actually love,
it'll only cause you trouble.
It's fine.
I'll never get serious about anyone
until the day I die.
Thanks for today.
Here, this is for the taxi.
Thank you very much!
And...
Oh, I'll make sure you get some work too.
I'll hold you to it.
Die.
Die! You're so disgusting, you fat ass!
If you weren't a producer,
I wouldn't even bother with you!
[Chiaki Hosho Cast in Lead Role!]
[Latest On-Set Photos for "Our Ensemble"]
[Congratulations on the start of filming!]
Why does that third-rate idol,
who can't even sing or dance,
get to be in Chiaki Hosho's movie?
God, she's such an eyesore.
I wish she'd just disappear from my sight.
I just got a great idea!
[Minase]
I look forward to...
Sis, act for us!
- What?
- I wanna see!
- You wanna see?
- Yup.
Okay, which line should I do?
I don't have many lines.
How about this one?
This one? The heroine's line, huh?
The heroine's line, huh?
Alright.
My heart still echoes with your song,
with feelings of love.
- That was great!
- Really?
Maybe I'll do one more scene then.
Yay!
My drama is number one in ratings
this season.
By a landslide.
Yeah, so I hear.
That producer who looked down on me
when I was starting out
got ranked "most disappointing".
It feels so damn good.
You seem pretty happy too, Chiaki.
Did you find your true love?
No way.
The girl I'm working on
is harder to reel in than usual.
Huh, that's rare.
It's usually so easy, I get bored.
This is actually more fun.
So? What's she like? Cute?
Her face is cute, I guess.
She's plain and kind of serious.
Let's play a harmony, you and I.
Wow, amazing! So good!
But...
I love seeing how girls
from a happy household would look
when they make that look of despair.
Oh, man. You're the absolute worst.
But that's classic Chiaki.
Shiki told me to stop, though.
Well, he's a goody-two-shoes.
Oh, hey, let's make a bet.
Whether you can get that girl or not.
If you can't get her in three months,
give me that watch.
Well... sure.
Oh? What's this?
Not confident?
Don't be stupid.
That's the spirit.
Oh, Chiaki, Kai! You came!
We sure did.
Let's sit!
- What are you feeling?
- How about tequila?
Tequila to start? Both of you?
- Tequila.
- Both of us.
Tequila? Well, if we have to!
Hey, that's fast...
You should rely on me more.
What am I thinking?
The necklace is gone.
Are you accusing me of stealing it?
How about me? We're playing lovers.
No. Ama is mine.
If you'd like,
why don't you stay for dinner?