( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Father.
What did you do to Father?
Oh, my son.
Just now, your brother
did something to your father,
and made him like this.
If something happens to your father,
how will the two of us
survive from now on?
Lin Mo.
For the position of family head,
you even had the heart
to murder your own father.
Act.
Keep acting.
You might as well be the main characters.
Come on.
Let me see what other backing you have.
I am their backing.
It's you.
We meet again.
How dare you!
Lin Mo,
don't try to get close to me.
I am asking you,
as the mastermind behind the poisoned salt case,
do you confess or not?
And,
to seize the position of the head of the family,
you intended to kill your father.
Do you confess or not?
That's right, My Lord.
He...
He is simply
heartless.
My Lord,
please seek justice for us
and severely punish this scoundrel.
Apothecary owner,
do you think these kinds of people
can help you achieve your goal?
Let's see how you break this deadlock.
Alright.
Then watch closely.
You stay isolated all day.
Take a good look at what kind of monster
your Governor really is.
Steal the Beams and Pillars,
activate!
What did you do to His Lordship?
The Governor was replaced by a monster.
He was locked in Huaiyang County's prison,
and I have rescued him.
Your information
is too outdated.
Lin Mo,
what sorcery did you use?
Useless trash.
You can't even grab the chance when it's given to you.
First you killed my mother,
then poisoned my father,
and framed me for the poisoned salt case.
Nice plan,
but the execution is too sloppy.
Why?
Why hasn't your state of mind shattered yet?
Why can you always turn danger into safety?
Lin Mo.
How am I not as good as you?
Die.
Why do you,
Lin Mo,
have so much strength?
Fellows,
pick up your weapons.
Follow me,
destroy the Lin Mansion,
and save our relatives.
Village head.
The people of the Lin Mansion know sorcery.
We neither have martial arts,
nor know magic.
Yeah.
Isn't that just dying for nothing?
Only with their help
can we break into the Lin Estate.
We can't let the momentum drop.
It's not right to let these people die for nothing.
We should get the Daqian soldiers here.
It's too late.
By the time the army arrives,
the master will be in grave danger.
Agreed.
It took your Tianji Pavilion a day to get here.
The army is even further away.
Then what should we do?
These commoners
are too disorganized.
Watch us.
Men,
if you are still men,
go and get your wives and daughters
back.
Acting coy
and hesitant,
are all the men in Luoxian Town women?
A mere Corpse Yin Pill
can't do anything to me.
This woman from Beijing has some skills.
Stop pretending.
If I can cure the poison,
so can you.
You are quite capable,
Your Highness Chu Xiao'er.
How do you know my background?
The only princess in Beijing with such skills
who dares to come to Daqian alone to catch demons
is Chu Xiao'er.
I didn't expect
to be so famous.
Chu Xiao'er,
the Daughter of Destiny of Beijing.
She was the one who destroyed Daqian with Han Qingyun.
Damn.
Are you going to fight here?
I'm not interested in you anymore.
There are so many ghost brides here,
enough for me to make a fortune.
I know you are fine too.
The first time I saw you,
I saw you possess dragon aura
and are immune to evil.
You must be a princess of Daqian.
The young master's sweetheart
is actually royalty.
He has come to save you.
Don't worry.
Where are you going?
How can I escape?
Still haven't found a suitable one.
There's no time.
Let Fan'er choose a pleasing one
and hold the wedding first.
Yes.
Holy crap.
Do I still have to pretend to be a zombie?
Madam.
The number of people is wrong.
Two are missing.
Some rats sneaked in.
I will go
and catch them.
No need.
Business comes first.
They can't run away.
I am an emperor
pretending to be a zombie
and having a ghost marriage.
What a dark history.
Look how much the Lin family has bullied us.
Can you still take it?
Exactly.
Snatching our wives and daughters
for ghost marriages.
Are we going to act like cowards
and swallow our anger?
What's the point of living like this?
What's the point?
Right.
Let's fight them.
Yeah.
Taking down one makes us even.
Taking down two is a bonus.
Fellow villagers.
Why do the monsters of the Lin mansion not come out during the day,
but only dare to come out at night to harm people?
Right.
They are afraid of sunlight.
Now,
now is the best time to deal with them.
Let's go.
Destroy the Lin family!
Save our loved ones!
Destroy the Lin family.
Save our relatives.
Let's go.
I didn't expect
you to pass the test of the illusion.
What would happen if I didn't pass?
You would probably die.
I shouldn't have
assisted that piece of trash.
Otherwise, all my efforts wouldn't have been in vain.
Who are you?
They are demon refiners from Beijing.
To be exact,
we are evil demon refiners.
We were originally righteous demon refiners.
The Beijing royal family was tainted by demons.
We were also polluted.
From then on, we went astray
and couldn't turn back.
You helped Lin Fan hold a ghost marriage.
Why did you help him?
Why did you need so many women?
It was all a front.
We promised
to give the Lin family members demon seeds
to gain a hundred years of life.
They didn't understand your salt-making process
and ate a lot of poisonous salt.
Their internal organs failed long ago,
and they don't have long to live.
So that's it.
What is your real purpose?
I don't have long to live.
There's no harm in telling you.
An ancient demon is sealed here,
named Chamozu.
Chamozu?
It needs the blood of a maiden born in the year, month, and hour of the Dragon
to break the seal.
But such a woman is hard to find.
Therefore, forty-nine women entering a ghost marriage
to gather Yin energy
can also serve as a substitute.
Where is my wife?
She got into your sedan chair.
Where is she?
I'm sorry.
All women in ghost marriages must take the Yin Corpse Pill
and turn into Yin spirits
to complete the marriage.
If you can get out alive,
marry another one.
You,
calm down.
What is the funeral coffin for?
Why turn people into corpse puppets?
You got it backwards.
There was already a thousand-year-old corpse puppet here
from Beijing.
He came here with a grand scheme.
To eliminate the threat,
we specially used the ancient bronze corpse-suppressing coffin
at the hour of Zi on odd days
to capture this great demon.
But he dodged it every time.
Ram it!
At this rate,
it'll be dusk by the time the door is broken open.
Have confidence in Her Maj...
I mean, the Miss.
Don't forget,
she has a trump card too.
One more powerful than all of ours.
I have a divine skill.
With just one strike of my sword,
I can break this door.
But once this sword is drawn,
my energy will be exhausted,
and I will have no combat power left.
Han Qingyun,
later you and your sister will help him back together.
Get up.
Time to work.
Get to work. Hurry up.
Why isn't this bell ringing on time?
Why do you care so much?
As long as we get paid, it's fine.
Wait.
I can't hold on much longer.
If you want to leave here safely,
you must replace Lin Fan.
Replace him?
Do I have to kill him?
It's not that simple.
You beat him in the illusion just now.
Best two out of three.
You need to beat him one more time.
Boss,
let's go.
According to the reward rules,
from the illusion just now,
you can make a wish
and bring it into reality.
Then...
Then resurrect my mother.
Be realistic.
Realistic?
For this family,
I really have no expectations.
How about this?
Thanks.
Wait.
What's that sound?
Is it thunder?
Thunder wouldn't be this regular.
There is a formation set by a great demon isolating this space.
Outside,
they must have started attacking this place.
This sound,
is someone ramming the door.
They...
I urged them to unite a long time ago.
Now they're finally showing what they can do.
Maybe
you lacked some persuasion skills back then.
Let's help them out.
I am Lin Mo, the new head of the Lin family.
Today
is a joyous day for our Lin family.
I order everyone in the Lin family
to open the doors and welcome the guests.
Move aside!
Move that junk away.
My second brother is breaking the door!
Here I come.
My life's
strongest sword strike!
Second Brother.
I don't want to ruin your mood,
but right now,
it seems we don't need you.