Watch on kissasia.li
[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 29]
Have the army proceed as planned.
We'll go on ahead.
Yes.
Grandfather,
this...
Mayor Zheng,
the governor isn't here.
How about you
go look in the estate's garden?
Your Excellency.
Your Excellency!
Darn that brat Qi Zheng.
Grandfather.
No need.
I'll get down myself.
You're so skilled, Grandfather.
Don't let the governor
get under your skin.
Get under my skin?
Who even is he?
The governor refuses to show his face,
making us run around his estate.
He must be trying to show us who's boss.
Show us who's boss?
He doesn't even dare to show his face.
Utterly pathetic.
What brings you here?
Second Brother!
Zheng Shi, you're back.
Granduncle Tao.
Where have you been these past few days?
It took you so long to return.
I left Ling'an for some personal matters,
and was delayed on the way.
So the night my brother had his accident,
you weren't by his side?
Zheng Shi,
do you know why
Granduncle Yuan
suddenly committed treason?
I only know that he'd
been against
democratizing the selection exam
and wanted to maintain
the old system of the Nine Noble Families.
My brother sacrificed his life
for the nobles of Jing City.
Even if we don't
carry on his will to abolish the exam,
we can't let Jing City
be controlled by Ling'an anymore.
Do you mean you want Jing City
to become independent?
What's wrong with that?
It's not like we lack the capabilities.
Why should we submit to others?
Were it not for
concern of my elder brother,
I'd have acted long ago.
Zheng Shi.
This matter concerns the survival of
our Zheng family.
So,
we must stand united and fight together.
Fight?
You came to Ling'an this time
prepared?
I brought the army.
Bringing troops into Ling'an
is considered treason.
This is just a preliminary test
to gauge that brat Qi Zheng's limits.
Grandfather only brought
20,000 troops this time,
and they're stationed
outside the Ling'an checkpoint.
It's just an act of posturing.
No lines will be crossed.
This Qi Zheng sure is infuriating.
Are you sure those soldiers are
stationed outside the checkpoint?
I'm afraid things outside have changed
while you're in here.
What do you mean?
When I entered the city earlier,
I didn't see a single Zheng soldier.
You two really are here.
Dad.
Your Excellency.
Why are you two sitting back to back?
What's going on with you two?
Not talking,
not eating, and not going home?
Yun.
Listen, my daughter,
this man
is just the worst.
Lord Fan Qi is even worse.
He wants to eat my pet turtle.
Your Excellency,
how many times
do I have to explain it to you?
Yours is a softshell turtle,
an aggressive fish-like species,
which can be eaten.
It's my pet.
I know very well if
it's a softshell or not, OK?
Well, living to my age,
I know very well
what can be eaten and what cannot.
I doubt that's true now.
Alright, stop arguing.
So you two are fighting over this?
-That is right!
Sure.
This matter is so important.
More important than
the 20,000 troops of Zheng's Army
about to arrive in Ling'an.
Wait...
You both knew?
Your Excellency.
Right, right.
Yours is a pet turtle.
Take good care of it.
Now there are 20,000
of them aggressive little bastards.
I have something to do. Goodbye.
You...
20,000 of them!
Dad! Dad!
Aren't you going to eat?
When did you find out?
Why are there so many
unexpected obstacles along the way?
I know.
Keep battle formation!
-Yes!
Who's there?
Who goes there?
How dare you trespass
on the Ling'an checkpoint?
My apologies!
So it's Commander Wei.
You misunderstood.
We're merely escorting
Mayor Zheng to the estate
to express his gratitude.
We have no intention of trespassing.
Commander Wei, please let us pass.
This is the Ling'an checkpoint.
We're at least
15 miles away from the moat.
It's clearly drawn here!
The governor changed it.
When did he change it?
Right now.
You haven't told me
how you knew
they'd bring troops here.
No.
No food until you tell me.
Fine, fine.
I'll eat after talking.
Even though I
kept the Zheng family
out of the treason,
Zheng Yuan was a traitor after all.
If Jing City received an order right now
to bring Zheng Yuan's ashes back,
if you were Zheng Tao,
what'd you think?
First of all,
I must have some doubts.
After all,
one shouldn't disobey
Your Excellency's order.
So...
So they
sent troops here to
guard against you.
Subsequently,
I'll find an excuse
to detain him in Ling'an.
Then Jing City
will be leaderless.
If they also thought of this,
they either wouldn't come,
or they'd find
someone else to come instead.
If it were the old Zheng Tao,
that's what he'd do.
But Zheng Tao is currently
the mayor of Jing City.
If he didn't even dare come
pick up Zheng Yuan's ashes,
wouldn't it completely destroy
his credibility in Jing City?
Therefore, not only must he come,
but he must come aggressively.
If he returns in one piece,
it'll awe everyone.
If he does not,
they'll rise up in revolt.
Exactly.
This is also what Elder Zheng thought
is the best opportunity he earned for us.
In any case,
with 20,000 elite soldiers outside,
we still have to be on guard.
We need to come up
with a countermeasure soon.
Or does Your Excellency
already have it all thought out?
Since the fish is already on the table,
can't we just
start eating it from wherever we want?
Here.
Try this.
Excuse me.
The Zhengs are in mourning.
No one is allowed to enter.
I heard Young Master Zheng Shi is back,
so I came to visit.
This is his order.
Please go back, Miss.
Please let him know I'm here, sir.
Just say that I'm...
Fan Yun from the Fan family,
with something to discuss.
Please go back, Miss.
Young Master Zheng Shi.
Fan Yun.
Long time no see.
Young Master Zheng Shi.
Since we parted in Yong City,
we haven't seen each other.
You didn't even
let me know you're back.
How...
have you been?
Let's talk somewhere else.
So much wine.
It must cost a month of your salary.
The last time
you came to the private school
to look for me,
you brought this exact wine.
Have a few drinks with me.
Tonight's moon is breathtaking,
yet I'm drinking alone.
How dreary.
Fan Yun,
can you play another piece for me?
Sure.
Thank you, Fan Yun.
Cheers.
I still remember that
the first time I tried wine
was the day my mother passed away.
That night,
my dad came home
with a large jug of wine.
He drank half of it
and got drunk.
I ran over,
took a few sips,
and got drunk too.
But
that night,
I had a very, very beautiful dream.
I dreamed that my mother
came back to see me again.
I'm worried Grandfather
won't enter my dreams.
After all, I was neither
sensible nor obedient.
I failed the selection exam
and often made him mad.
Maybe he never wants to see me again.
That's not true.
He just
didn't want you to worry.
When he knew our family
disrupted the exam
to test him,
he didn't want me to worry.
When he felt weak and frail,
he didn't want me to worry either.
When he felt that our family situation
was out of control,
worrying about the people,
the family—
about everything—
he still didn't want me to worry.
He shouldered the weight
of the grand scheme alone,
setting up a trap for Qi Zheng
with his life.
♪ I could have ♪
♪ Played every trick in the book ♪
But in the end, as his grandson...
♪ But I chose painstaking devotion ♪
♪ Never caging my love ♪
♪ Even if I had to
trudge through a thousand miles ♪
Young Master Zheng Shi...
♪ Henceforth, I shall wander the world,
plucking petals and holding the moon ♪
♪ Listen to the wind and admire the moon
for days on end ♪
Young Master Zheng Shi...
♪ Accept that I'm not your happiness ♪
♪ Let go of what's before me ♪
Regardless of his merits and faults,
♪ Consider this the best ending ♪
Elder Zheng
was a generation's hero.
♪ I disdain everything
in the vast universe ♪
♪ So why do I care for
a single glance from you? ♪
My condolences.
♪ Drinking a pot of the past ♪
♪ I toast to my withering self
as the curtains fall ♪
♪ And you don't know the reason why ♪
I understand the reasoning.
But I can't help wondering;
if I had been here,
I'm sure I could've found a way
where my grandfather wouldn't have to die.
Young Master Zheng Shi.
Actually, some things
aren't as simple as we imagine.
Some things
can't be changed
by one person alone.
Are you speaking up for Qi Zheng?
My grandfather died in his bedroom,
right in front of him.
Yet you're here
asking me to be the bigger person,
to be more forgiving?
No, you're mistaken.
I just don't want
you to be too sad
and hurting.
OK.
Then let me ask you:
in what capacity are we
having this conversation?
As Zheng Shi and Fan Yun?
Or as Second Young Master Zheng
and Lady Fan?
Today,
I'm your confidant Fan Yun.
I simply hope that
you can
pull yourself together.
Don't let down Elder Zheng's
expectations of you.
OK.
I get it.
Cheers.
[Huiyun Pavilion]
Mayor Zheng, you came all the way
to pay respects and give thanks.
I'm deeply gratified.
If there's nothing else,
stay in Ling'an for a few more days.
I wouldn't dare.
My coming to Ling'an this time,
apart from giving thanks,
is actually to report something.
Go ahead.
Liu Mu, the gate commander of Jing City,
unfortunately died in
an accidental fire.
Accidental?
The specific cause of the fire
is still under investigation.
Currently, it's speculated
that Gate Cdr. Liu,
who slogged for Jing City day and night,
was in deep sleep due to exhaustion,
failing to notice that the charcoal brazier
in his home had tipped over.
So, he passed away in his sleep.
It's truly a pity.
Why is this matter only reported now?
Gate Cdr. Liu is an official
of Jing City after all.
It was an accident,
but...
No matter what, he died within
my Jing City territory.
The Zhengs cannot shirk the blame.
So we decided to
seek an audience with Your Excellency
to report this matter,
and at the same time,
ask for punishment.
In that case,
I'll accord Gate Cdr. Liu
a grand burial with full honors.
It's just that now,
Jing City is without a gate commander.
A new gate commander is needed.
So you're here for this.
No wonder.
Mayor Zheng,
you brought tens of thousands
of your troops
to lay siege to Ling'an.
It seems you came prepared.
You must be joking, Your Excellency.
Before my departure,
I heard there were many bandits
on the mountain roads.
I had to take extra precautions.
But my army was
brought to a complete standstill
before even reaching Ling'an, wasn't it?
You need so many accompanying troops?
I'd say it's
more than enough to take down
the entire Ling'an.
I wouldn't dare.
I'm getting on in years,
and my grandson is inexperienced.
Our Zheng family just went through
a major event
and can't withstand too much turmoil.
The Zheng's Army has stayed
in the tiny Jing City for a long time.
I thought I'd take this opportunity
to let them come out and see the world.
What,
surely Your Excellency wouldn't
disallow this, would you?
Of course not.
Actually, I think your troops are
hardworking and commendable in spirit.
I even wish my troops could
learn a thing or two from them.
How about this?
Let the two armies
have a friendly match.
I'll get to properly witness
how you train your troops.
Your Excellency wants your Qi's Army
and my Zheng's Army to undergo
a joint ceremonial review?
What,
surely you wouldn't disallow this,
would you?
I...
wouldn't dare disobey.
Granduncle Tao, did you
see the governor today?
Grandfather did a great thing today.
He actually wants to
play a war of attrition with me.
Doesn't he know
how many battles I've fought?
But listening to the governor's tone,
how about we just drop the matter
of the gate commander?
Why should we?
After the joint review,
the entire Qi's Army and nobles in Ling'an
will witness
how awe-inspiring our army is.
By then, the position
of gate commander
will be in the bag.
If there's nothing else,
I'll return to my room.
Hold on.
Zheng Shi.
Do you know where
my brother's clan leader ring
might be kept?
"Gone today, forgotten tomorrow," huh?
Grandfather's body is not yet cold,
and you're already coveting his ring.
What are you saying?
I merely
want to keep it safe until the ascension
of the next clan leader...
Lest it falls into the wrong hands.
I don't know.
You don't?
I really don't.
Even the gate commander's death
could be kept completely under wraps.
Jing City is
notoriously brutal for officials.
Previous gate commanders
all had to lower themselves
and collude with the Zhengs
in order to leave office unscathed.
But Gate Cdr. Liu was
famous for being upright.
Since he arrived in Jing City,
he was never once swayed by
the Zhengs' carrots and sticks.
The conflict between them
didn't start yesterday.
So there's even more reason to suspect
whether Liu Mu's death
was really
an accident or not.
The clan leader election
is a private matter for each family.
Governors have never interfered.
But every city's gate commander
has been appointed by governors.
This is to maintain a balance of power.
Now, if Zheng Xian
becomes gate commander as they wish,
the clan leader position
will virtually be theirs.
They want to take over Jing City
in one fell swoop.
Basically, he's establishing
that Ling'an should
stay out of Jing City's business.
They've brought their troops here
with big ambitions.
We mustn't lower our guard.
The upcoming joint review
is especially crucial.
Zheng's Army boasts
elite troops and strong horses,
fighting with great valor.
If
we can outshine them
at the joint review,
such a blow to their reputation
will undermine them
more than
a bloody battle.
As long as we dampen their spirit,
no matter how big their army is,
we have nothing to fear.
By then, we will
have the upper hand.
No one knows me
better than Fan Yun.
The discipline of Zheng's Army
is surprisingly strict,
not inferior to our army at all.
How'd you think they
got their glorious reputation?
However,
they're facing us this time.
When it comes to formations,
the governor's the expert.
Commander Wei, Lord Gao,
we have a new discovery over there.
Come take a look.
Let's go.
This is truly
unbelievable.
Yes.
To think the Zhengs
were secretly raising
a flock of crow soldiers.
When we actually fight them,
those crows will be a problem.
With Zheng Tao and Zheng Xian
still in Ling'an,
their hands are tied,
so they won't act rashly.
Well, go back
and report this to the governor.
I'll handle things here.
Why should I go back?
Why else?
I know you're full of integrity
and wholly devoted to government affairs.
But women,
sometimes,
won't take the hint unless you reject her.
Just for my sake,
humor her.
Lord Wei, actually I...
If you lose a single hair,
my precious sister will
make me search for it with a lantern.
I'd rather avoid any trouble.
You're exaggerating.
♪ Wind sheds rain like tears ♪
♪ Over the whole town ♪
♪ At the second our gazes meet ♪
♪ Past memories roar one louder beat ♪
Not an exaggeration at all.
It really is you.
♪ Perhaps hearts long to seek ♪
Why are you here?
Why didn't you two
say goodbye before leaving?
♪ Etch within our fingertips ♪
You even went so far.
Good thing I have good legs.
♪ Hear crisp footsteps echo clear ♪
♪ Strike out
on a fearless dream's frontier ♪
You mean
the horse out there has good legs.
♪ Though fleeting years rush
without delay ♪
Don't find me a nuisance.
♪ A wisp of softness
tints your brow each day ♪
I heard you were
conducting reconnaissance.
♪ Walk side by side with moon and sun ♪
The wind is strong
in the mountains at night.
I'll leave after
dropping off these clothes.
♪ When all is said and all is done ♪
♪ We'll ride the ups and downs ♪
♪ When deep love dwells within our eyes ♪
My sister,
♪ Our burning longing never dies ♪
can't you
tone it down a little?
Don't always be so eager.
♪ Wander together through wind and frost ♪
Fine.
♪ Every dark night fades at last ♪
♪ When fate resides within our sight ♪
Miss Wei.
♪ Gazing toward each other's
distant light ♪
The front line is dangerous.
Let me escort you ba...
OK!
♪ What do heaven and earth seek
but salvation in companionship? ♪
♪ Don't let the sun down ♪
You can head back now.
Any further, and we'll be in Ling'an.
Enemies can easily hide
within the complex terrain here.
It's almost dark.
Let me escort you through this pass.
If Gao Ran wasn't doing it for my sake,
you'd be going back by yourself.
Actually, there's no need.
I'm a Wei.
They wouldn't mess with me
even if their lives depended on it.
Gao Ran, why don't we
just go back now?
Leave her here by herself.
But a hidden attack is the deadliest.
They've been provoking us
these past few days,
just to vex our spirits.
Gao Ran is right.
When you return in triumph,
I'll make you some pastries, OK?
You might as well make them for me.
Gao Ran doesn't like sweets.
Sure.
Then I'll have to trouble you, Miss Wei.
No trouble at all.
Mayor Zheng.
Does my army look neat?
Your Excellency's army
is certainly elite.
But my Zheng's Army
is also battle-seasoned.
Let the two armies spar,
so my soldiers can witness the prowess
of your Qi's Army.
How on earth can
the Jing City's army compare to
the regular Qi's Army?
Zhao,
since he wants to witness it,
we should show him
what we're really made of.
I agree with Lord Lyu.
How would Mayor Zheng like to spar?
Formations are
an essential military skill.
Tactical flexibility on the battlefield
is the only way to defeat the enemy.
Otherwise, the soldiers
will be like loose sand,
fighting individually.
Why not give us a chance to
study your formation tactics today?
In that case,
since you're a guest from afar,
Zheng's Army will set up the formation,
and Qi's Army will break it.
What do you think?
My intentions exactly.
However, since it's
just a sparring session,
please go easy, Your Excellency.
Don't go all out
and hurt my soldiers.
Naturally.
Please.
The Zheng's Army is keen on formations.
In tomorrow's joint review,
they'll surely play their trump cards.
The Long Snake formation
is true to its name.
if attacked at the middle,
the two ends will connect,
trapping the enemy inside.
The only way to break it is to
attack from both sides,
cutting off the head and the tail.
With the Long Snake broken,
Zheng Tao will
bring out the Double Dragons.
The two dragon heads
are its sharpest elements.
So we must avoid its sharp edges
and attack its foundation.
Next,
Zheng Tao will move on to
the Heaven & Earth Omniverse.
It's indestructible
from top to bottom.
Only the middle is its weakness.
But these 3 formations
transition into each other
flexibly and smoothly.
This formation's weak middle
is very likely to become
the advantage of the next.
So those who don't grasp formations
could get trapped inside
and be annihilated.
This aligns with the Daoist saying:
"One begets Two, Two begets Three,
and Three begets all things."
The only way to break this formation is
to attack here.
Formations on the ground
can't stump Your Excellency,
but I wonder how Your Excellency will
counter formations in the sky.
Lyu,
should I...
Just sit still
and trust the governor.