( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Although the face is swollen,
judging by his features,
he was indeed one of the arsonists
at Buxianxian.
This thumb ring
is extremely valuable
and does not fit the dead man's finger.
It likely was not his.
His face is swollen and purplish.
There is foam in his mouth and nose.
His skin is wrinkled.
His abdomen is filled with water.
He drowned as well.
Time of death was about
twelve hours ago.
Official Di,
look.
This bruise
was caused by a blow from a hard object.
Are there fibers on him
like the previous two victims?
No.
But there are several binding marks
on his arms and back.
The victim was knocked unconscious,
bound,
and thrown into the river.
When he woke up,
he found himself already in the water.
But because of the severe head injury,
he could not swim back to the surface,
and drowned.
It seems
someone is imitating
the water ghost's murders.
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 4=
(Ruanjiang County Bureau)
Your Honor,
please seek justice for me.
My son died unjustly.
Do you know your son killed someone?
My son, Cai
was honest and well behaved.
His legs would shake
even when he argued with others.
How could he possibly kill anyone?
Had your son
been acting strangely lately?
No.
Cai was involved in a murder.
If you refuse to tell the truth,
I can only conclude
that he killed himself
out of fear of punishment.
Besides,
I will also post a notice.
By then,
everyone in Ruanjiang County
will know
that Cai was a murderer.
I...
I'll tell you.
My son worked as a corpse retriever.
People looked down on him all his life.
But that day, he left in a hurry
and said he was about to make a fortune.
Then he could finally marry
and start a family.
I knew something bad would happen.
I should have stopped him.
Where did the money come from?
I asked him,
but he would not say.
(Justice and Clarity)
When did Cai say this?
The night before yesterday.
The timing matches.
Could it have been
a dispute over the spoils?
Do you recognize this man?
No.
Look carefully.
I have.
I really have never seen him before.
Thank you, Lady Du.
Look at him.
Was he one of the arsonists?
Yes.
It was him.
This thumb ring...
I recognize it.
This...
This thumb ring...
This thumb ring belongs to my son.
I had it specially made
for his birthday last year.
Where did you get it, Official Di?
Master Wang,
where is Wang Xian?
Official Di,
what do you mean by that?
Then...
Then shouldn't I be asking you that?
That thumb ring was in your hands.
Where is my son?
Could it be...
Could my son...
My son...
My Xian...
Master Wang.
Why are you crying?
Our official
is still investigating.
No one said he was dead.
Since it's your son,
naturally we must start
by searching your residence.
Official Di,
I...
Master,
I searched the entire Wang residence.
I found nothing suspicious.
Since he claims Wang Xian is missing,
we will search the whole city.
Then we shall see
whether Wang Dingrong
is hiding him or not.
Master, do you also believe
Wang Xian is the killer?
Wang Xian's thumb ring
ended up in Cai's hands.
That only proves
Cai had met Wang Xian.
It is not enough
to prove Wang Xian is the murderer.
One murder after another.
Once we catch the killer,
I'll make sure he pays for it.
Di.
I found a deckhand
from the Wang family's ship.
His name is Laifu.
After Qi Feng died,
he disappeared as well.
According to the people on the ship,
his appearance
matches the other arsonist.
Go inform Magistrate Cao at once.
Duan,
keep an eye on Wang Dingrong.
All right.
How did it go?
Qi Feng survived.
But the Young Master hired two men
to burn him alive.
What about Xian?
The Bureau
found one of the men's bodies
by the river.
That corpse was wearing
the Young Master's thumb ring.
The Bureau believes
the Young Master hired men to kill,
then silenced Cai afterward.
Good.
As long as my Xian is safe,
I can rest easy.
Keep searching.
Bring him back.
Yes.
Wait.
The Bureau
will definitely be keeping an eye
on the Wang residence.
Search in secret.
Even if you find him,
do not let him come back yet.
See what he needs.
Do not let him suffer.
Yes.
Cai is dead.
What about the other man?
A servant from the Salt Bureau's ship.
Laifu.
Find someone
to kill Laifu as well.
Understood.
(Laifu)
(Hengshun Salt Bureau)
Young...
Young Master.
Who stands before the court?
I...
I am Laifu.
Do you know who wanted to kill you?
I do not know.
Someone has accused you
of setting fire and killing with Cai.
Is this true?
If you confess,
you may still live.
If you refuse,
Magistrate Cao
will still get to the bottom of it.
But before that,
do you
want to end up like Cai?
Official...
Official Di, spare me.
I'll confess.
Yes.
A few days ago,
Wang Xian came to us.
He told us to meet at Buxianxian
the next day.
Go.
Set it on fire.
You do it.
Coward.
Do you still want the money or not?
It's...
It's burning.
Do you know
who was burned to death?
His name was
Qi...
Qi Feng.
At the time, Wang Xian
was cursing...
cursing him.
How dare you, Fu!
Then why did you kill Cai?
Please judge wisely, Official Di.
I did not kill Cai.
It was Cai
who...
Who tried to kill me.
That night,
he...
He wanted all the money for himself.
He hit me on the head with a stick
and knocked me out cold.
I still have the lump.
Please take a look, Official Di.
Reporting to Official Di,
there is indeed a lump on his head.
Later, I wanted
to settle the score with him,
but I never expected
him to end up dead.
I figured it had to be Wang Xian
trying to silence us.
I was terrified.
I hid for several days.
I didn't even dare
go ask him for the money.
Then why were you seen
near the Salt Bureau?
Did you see Wang Xian?
I went there to look for him.
He gave me this note back then.
Official Di.
(Cai betrayed us.)
(Blinded by greed.)
(He deserved to die.)
(Come to Hengshun Salt Bureau
tonight for the money.)
When did you receive this note?
Yesterday at noon.
I originally planned
to go home and pack.
I wanted to leave...
Leave...
Leave Ruanjiang.
But the moment I got home,
I saw this note.
Does this thumb ring belong to Cai?
It belongs to Wang Xian.
Look carefully.
He always wears it
on this thumb.
When I saw him a few days ago,
he was still wearing it.
Qi Feng survived the shipwreck
and returned alive.
He learned the truth behind the tragedy.
After that,
he sought revenge
in the name of the water ghost.
Qi Feng survived.
Unfortunately,
Wang Xian discovered it.
Afraid that Du Ruo
would run away with him,
Wang Xian hired men to kill Qi Feng.
In the end,
Wang Xian wanted to cover everything up.
So he posed as the water ghost
and silenced the killer.
That is why
this thumb ring
ended up on Cai.
Master,
I am right, am I not?
Where is the witness
who saw Wang Xian kill Cai?
Well...
What you said does sound reasonable.
But Laifu can only prove
that Wang Xian hired killers.
Even if we confirm
that Cai met Wang Xian afterward,
this thumb ring alone
is not enough to convict Wang Xian.
We still need a witness.
Official Di,
I actually think Lin Buyan has a point.
If Wang Xian did not kill anyone,
then why did Wang Dingrong
send people to kill Laifu?
Exactly, Master.
Wang Dingrong's men already confessed.
It is a fact that Wang Dingrong
wanted Laifu dead.
Wasn't he trying to kill Laifu
to help his son
cover up the truth?
If you ask me,
he definitely knows
where Wang Xian is hiding.
Bring him in for questioning
and the truth will come out.
Do not act rashly.
Even if your reasoning is correct,
once we arrest Wang Dingrong,
will Wang Xian still return?
Do not alert the enemy.
Tell the public
that we are still searching for Laifu.
(Fortune Telling. Divination)
It hurts.
It's killing me.
Master Diviner.
(Medical Shop)
It's killing me.
What ails you, Master?
It feels like my bone is about to break.
Don't worry.
Let me take a look.
Not this leg.
Master,
there is nothing wrong
with your leg.
Nothing wrong?
Maybe you simply can't tell.
Could you be a quack?
I can tell with one touch
whether your leg is injured.
If even I can't find anything wrong,
no doctor anywhere
will find anything wrong either.
That can't be right.
Divine Doctor.
I heard your greatest skill
is finding illness where there is none.
If you say
his leg was broken,
he'd probably believe it himself.
Am I wrong?
If your leg is injured,
I guarantee I can cure it.
But if the problem lies elsewhere,
turn right when you leave
and get yourself a few herbal remedies.
You might still be saved.
Divine Doctor, don't be angry.
I was only joking with you.
I saw a sinister aura
hanging over your clinic,
so I came specially to warn you.
I won't claim
I've never lost a patient,
but my conscience is clear.
Why would I fear some evil aura?
No!
What truly worries me
is someone like you,
who unknowingly
helps evil thrive.
This sinister aura
has lingered here for two years.
I fear your household
has known no peace,
and the resentment has only deepened.
This will be difficult.
Forget it.
Since you are unwilling,
then we
were never meant
to cross paths.
Master Diviner.
Please wait.
You said
this sinister aura
has lingered for two years.
That suddenly reminded me.
Two years ago,
my son developed an eye disease.
Though people call me a Divine Doctor,
I simply could not cure him.
When you spoke
of unrest in my household,
were you
referring to this?
Yes.
Exactly.
If this drags on any longer,
it will not just be an eye disease.
Then how do I resolve it?
Everything happens for a reason.
Why do you think I came here
pretending this leg was injured?
Naturally, because I divined something.
Think carefully.
Two years ago,
did you do something
against your conscience
that led to someone's death?
The leg...
Two years ago...
No one truly died
because of this.
That is strange.
Let me ask this sinister aura.
Move aside.
Leave for now.
I will seek justice for you.
Are you
a diviner or a shaman?
People in our line of work
need to know a bit of everything.
In that direction ahead,
did anyone come here for treatment
two years ago?
The Wang...
The Wang family.
This clinic sits near
the Ruanjiang waters.
The water ghost
has been causing trouble lately.
The water ghost takes lives.
You'd best be careful.
Of course,
an upright man fears no shadow.
Impossible.
Master Wang's leg
truly was broken back then.
But that had nothing
to do with me.
I heard about it too.
But now that you mention it,
it is rather strange.
Why did his leg break
on that exact day?
And why did something happen
to the ship on that same day?
Is there anything else
you find strange enough to tell me?
And...
What?
I...
You have to say it
before I can help you.
Master Wang's leg
was broken
by someone else.
(Preview of Next Episode)
This used to be where you secretly met.
Now it belongs to us.
(You did this)
(to make it look certain
that Wang Xian killed to silence someone.)
(You must hate Wang Xian to the core.)
(Who exactly are you?)
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪