( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
If you want the throne,
come and take it yourself.
I am waiting for your Shanhe Sword.
How did Grandpa's portrait
end up with you?
Guess.
Who doesn't want you to be the Emperor the most?
Dowager Concubine Hua.
Zhang Huazhen.
Good, good, good.
I didn't want to deal with her,
but now
she delivered herself to my door.
Summon the ancestor Emperor.
Grandpa.
Your Shanhe Sword has a higher rank than my Baihua Tower.
But the Shanhe Sword was forged by the ancestor Emperor.
Everything has its vanquisher.
So this is what you rely on.
Your dragon energy is not infinite.
It will soon be completely depleted.
At that moment,
I will devour you.
Lin Mo.
I know you were the one who solved the demon problems
in Huaiyang County and Luoxian Town.
There must be something
profound and unique about you.
If you are willing to help me,
I will truly stay with you forever.
By then,
you can marry as many concubines
as you wish.
I certainly won't stop you.
I am also willing to truly love only you,
and remain forever loyal.
The conditions are quite tempting.
I am not like her,
needing you to coax and indulge me in everything.
You can do whatever you want.
I care for my man the most.
Whatever he wants,
I will give it to him.
Look at her,
providing full emotional value.
Do you need a beating to behave yourself?
I was stalling for time.
Why did you take so long?
Her dancing was so terrible
that I fell asleep watching it.
You demons just keep babbling
about being long-lived
and noble.
Which of your singing and dancing isn't copied from us?
Shameless.
You...
are asking for death.
So what if it's the Ten Thousand Demon Banner?
It can only hold its ground for a moment.
Baihua Tower is her demon domain.
The Ten Thousand Demon Banner won't last long.
This place
is now under my control, Lin Mo.
All demon rules and taboos
are completely invalid.
This thing is too strong.
If you take this to Northern Jing,
you could establish a country.
What is that thing of yours?
Why can it replace the rules here?
This?
It's your annulment letter.
I turned it into a rule-type artifact.
You
actually dare to show your demon core to fight.
In all my life,
I've never seen such an arrogant demon.
You are seeing one today.
The magic of your Ten Thousand Demon Banner
is almost exhausted, right?
This time when I draw my sword,
no one will disturb me, right?
One sword
will make you die with regret.
Retract.
Look at that flower.
Prime Minister Lin.
This is the medicine
Dowager Consort Hua asked me to bring you.
No need.
Madam.
Dowager Consort Hua asked me to pass a message.
It's better to live a bad life than die a good death.
Take this medicine,
and at least
you can spend more time with Prime Minister Lin.
Husband.
Madam, I am here.
Kill him.
Okay.
This...
Prime Minister Lin.
I am Dowager Consort Hua's man.
You can't touch me!
Can't touch?
In this world, except for the Emperor,
there is no one I, Lin Youtang, cannot touch.
You!
Um,
I didn't mean to see it.
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
Through the front door.
Master.
He held the token
of the Dali Temple Investigating Censor.
He just barged in.
We really
couldn't stop him.
Purple Gold Pill.
You're Lin Mo's man.
Is she really that good?
Liu Ruyan,
do you know why
I would never choose you?
Someone as demanding as you
only thinks of yourself.
You don't care about others.
Even
when you tried to recruit me,
the words you said
were to satisfy your needs first.
The Liu family had a bright future.
Why side with demons?
After the Lin family's salt case,
my family was implicated
and ruined.
To protect his son's career,
my father sold me to Baihua Pavilion.
I almost broke down those days
and wanted to end it all.
Until Dowager Consort Hua found me.
She said,
if I turned into a demon
by a high-level hair demon,
I could change my fate.
So what?
You're pitiful,
but aren't the people in the capital pitiful too?
To improve your cultivation,
how many people have you killed?
How many hearts have you dug out?
Winners take all.
I've wiped out the Liu family for you,
so you don't have to raid it.
Cut the crap.
Come.
Let me confirm.
Two?
Why are there two?
Who is the real one?
Where?
Speak!
This is the expression I was waiting for.
Lin Mo,
I win again.
Are you really leaving?
Nothing to miss here.
Nothing to miss.
Things have changed.
But some people in the north
should pay their debts.
Yeah.
It's time for closure.
Let's go.
Brother.
Going to Beijing?
We're on the same way.
Let's go together.
Brother,
I'm just taking my wife out.
Not necessarily to Beijing.
Yeah.
We're not going that far.
My lady.
Are you kidding?
You're old enough to be his father.
You must be joking.
I do look older than my age.
I remember your wife
was already carried away in a coffin, wasn't she?
Village head.
Song Qing didn't arrange a match
for his legitimate daughter either.
When did you two
get married?
Friend.
We don't want any trouble.
We just want to leave here.
A demon domain cannot be formed here.
If you want to fight here,
you two will die by my hands.
We are not in our best condition right now.
Fighting him would probably be a dead end.
This girl knows how to be flexible.
You are from Beijing, right?
Gu Qingfeng.
Master of Princess Chu Xiao'er.
I see.
I met Princess Chu Xiao'er
once before.
I know.
That's why I'm waiting for you here.
Let's travel together.
Your Highness.
Bad news.
What is it?
Why the panic?
Baihua Brothel was breached.
The Empress has successfully wiped out the demon menace.
How is that possible?
How could this be?
Didn't she use the Founding Emperor's portrait?
Su Ningxue's strongest reliance
is the Shanhe Sword.
She did.
But Liu Ruyan,
she still lost.
Liu Ruyan, that useless trash.
I wasted so much
to help her turn into a demon,
and even sent the demon's true form
to help her merge.
Mother,
what do we do now?
Zhang Mu went to Baihua Brothel,
and there's still no news of him.
Eunuch Chang.
Here.
This is my token.
Go to the Imperial Guard camp
and find my adopted son.
Tell him to lead his troops and sneak into the palace.
When Su Ningxue returns,
restrain her.
Yes.
This trip was worthwhile.
Chu Xiao'er.
The demon menace in Daqian
is all thanks to your Beijing.
How are we going to settle this?
First of all,
I am not the Emperor of Beijing,
nor the mastermind.
You can't blame this on me.
Second,
I've helped you a lot,
and I haven't even asked for payment.
You want payment?
Every time you work,
you make a killing.
Don't interrupt.
Third.
Third what?
Haven't thought of it yet.
But the first two reasons are enough.
You're right.
You are a member of the Beijing royal family.
I can't allow this to happen again.
The tragic state of the people in Luoxian Town,
you saw it too.
If there's demon-catching work in the future,
you can call me.
But your business with the Beijing royal family
has nothing to do with me.
I won't get involved.
If you don't get involved,
won't your brother target you?
I suppose
you have made a decision.
Chu Xiao'er.
If you become the Emperor of Beijing,
we will support you.
Don't try to tempt me.
I just want to be a demon refiner.
Think about it.
If you become the emperor,
you can gather all the wealth and resources in the world
to support your demon-refining career.
Why would you need to be like now,
braving the elements to hunt demons all over the world?
Right?
Boss Chu,
where are you going?
Returning to Beijing
to be the emperor.
Is it that easy?
Once all competitors are wiped out,
won't it be easy?
You all,
escort her back to Beijing.
Understood.
And you?
Back to the Mo residence.
Let's go.
Back to the palace.
It's time we cleaned house.