( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Everyone, use the talismans!
It's not enough.
Keep going!
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Don't go!
How much stock does she have?
Those taken by them
must be at least forty or fifty.
Theoretically, there should be forty-nine.
Probably hasn't reached that yet.
Boss,
I'm running out of stamina.
Hold on!
Don't give up!
Wuhui,
can you use your trump card?
I can only use it once.
Then wait a little longer.
You all forgot
my strike.
It hasn't come out yet.
Master Feng,
ignore those evil spirits.
Let's kill that old hag first.
Good idea.
Why did they leave?
I guess
Liu Wancai's side must have gained the upper hand,
so they were sent to reinforce them.
And I suspect
the place where the great demon is sealed
should be in the main house,
where the wedding takes place.
Let's go there right now.
Let's go.
Lin Mo.
If you don't kill me today,
I will definitely kill you.
Lin Fan,
you are doomed.
The Lin family is doomed too.
Let's go.
It seems we really can't get the final payment this time.
Cover me for ten breaths.
One strike
will send that old hag to her grave.
Want to kill me?
You are not qualified.
Finally, everyone is here.
You made me wait so long.
Myriad Demon Banner,
open!
Impossible.
How could this happen?
What is this?
Who are you?
Since you want immortality so much,
why not join my Myriad Demon Banner as sisters?
Absorb!
No!
A great harvest.
This trip was not in vain.
Second Brother,
I don't want to ruin your mood,
but it seems you're not needed again this time.
Second Brother,
don't lose heart.
You will definitely get a chance to show off.
Father, Mother.
Mother.
Mo.
I didn't expect you to pass the test.
I am very pleased.
This is the daughter-in-law of our Lin family.
Since the candidate is chosen,
come here, son.
Get married
and enter the bridal chamber.
What is going on now?
And
why do they look a bit dazed?
It must be because of the bell.
It weakened the great demon's power.
Mother.
Father.
I am now the new head of the Lin family.
I call the shots here.
Lift all the seals in this place.
There's one left.
It'll have to do.
Lin Fan!
Today, I'll avenge my father,
my mother,
and the other victimized women in Luoxian Town.
Die!
This can't kill me.
He can't kill you,
but I can.
Mo Xiaolan!
Lin Fan,
when you defiled Mo Xiaolan
and pushed her into the well,
you should have known this day would come.
I didn't expect...
you to be possessed by the wood demon.
I regret
not locking you up.
Don't kill me.
Don't kill me!
I know I was wrong.
You don't know you're wrong.
You just know you're going to die.
No!
Miss,
are you okay?
This body can't hold on anymore.
You're that...
herb gatherer.
Yes.
Take me out of here.
Okay.
This...
Are we...
Are we in trouble?
Should we keep knocking?
I don't know.
To knock or not to knock?
Keep going.
The seal is finally broken.
My cheat should be arriving soon.
See that statue?
The Demon Ancestor is right there.
How do we seal it?
We're not sealing it.
This time,
we'll settle it once and for all
and completely destroy it.
Destroy it?
How do we destroy it?
You're not the only one with a golden finger.
What?
Sword, come.
Are you making a reference?
It might be a little far.
Wait a moment.
How about we get down to business first?
Shh.
Damn.
That works too?
Then comparing myself to you,
is just infuriating.
This is...
the Shanhe Sword.
What is your relationship with Su Mingyuan,
the founding emperor of Southern Qian?
He is my father.
I spent years of effort
waiting for today.
I won't let you ruin it.
Traitorous son!
What are you doing?
Lin Mo,
No!
Father, Mother.
I have been unfilial.
But I have avenged you.
You are already dead.
You can rest in peace.
How dare you!
Demon Ancestor Sha, is it?
Let me tell you.
I am the second emperor of the Qianyuan Dynasty,
Su Ningxue,
recognized by my royal ancestors and the Shanhe Sword.
On my land,
you have harmed the people
and wreaked havoc.
I,
acting on heaven's decree today,
and wielding the will of heaven and earth,
shall slay demons and eradicate evil.
This is an outrage.
This body has decent strength.
I'll take it.
Watch out!
Lin Mo.
So this is your inner landscape.
Your state of mind is quite pure, kid.
You...
You were acting just now.
Kid,
you figured it out.
If I didn't trick you,
how could I
make my getaway?
What's the deal with you
and those evil Daoists from Beijing?
You have a mortal body,
with mere brute strength,
but cannot cultivate.
What a pity.
Come,
let me see
your aptitude.
Old man,
you want to possess me?
Yes.
Then why haven't you started?
I don't want to anymore.
Your body is so weak
and cannot cultivate.
What's the point of taking it?
I'd still be hunted by the Empress everywhere.
Your Majesty, I am late to your rescue.
Miss,
what's wrong with him?
Chamozu has entered his body.
Protect us quickly!
Everyone,
stay fifty feet away from us.
There's no sign of possession.
He seems to be
immersed in his inner vision.
You lured us here to break the seal,
and then used us to escape.
First of all,
I was never sealed here.
Before the founding of Nanqian,
I was already here.
This place
is suitable for my cultivation.
What did you say?
So many tragedies in Luoxian Town,
have nothing to do with me.
If I wanted to harm people,
Luoxian Town
would have been ruined hundreds of years ago.
It's the Beijing
royal family
who are scheming against me.
Those corpse puppets,
you transformed them.
Let me correct you.
The living dead
you saw
are not corpse puppets.
They are corpse demons.
Corpse demons?
Corpse demons
are refined from corpse puppets.
Those corpse puppets were originally
people of Beijing as well.
At first,
they cooperated with those Daoists,
and were driven by them.
Later, they fell out.
Let me guess.
They outlived their usefulness.
The corpse puppets fear the evil Daoist's bronze coffin,
so they
bided their time
and hid in the town.
Exactly.
Kid,
you are very smart.
I sensed something unusual
inside your body.
Your divine power is not affected by rules.
I don't know what you are talking about.
Don't panic.
I don't care
about your secrets.
I need your inner vision
to nourish my soul.
Let me tell you,
I won't occupy your place for nothing.
At critical moments,
I will guide you a few times
and help you out of trouble. How about that?
A cheat?
That could work.
Only a few times?
Not enough.
Kid,
you are so sly.
Alright.
If you have any difficulties,
just call me.
Wait.
How
can I trust you?
This is soul blood.
Sincere enough?
Hello there.
What?
Is there something on my face?
Where is the Shamo Ancestor?
I locked him up.
Don't be silly.
If I were really possessed,
your two guards would have sensed it,
right?
Your Majesty.
Let's go out first.
Wait.
Tell me a secret
that only the two of us know.
A secret?
You have a mole on your right butt cheek.
Shut up.
Daughter,
my daughter,
are you okay?
It's my fault.
Brother Lin.
Where is my brother?
I didn't see him.
Sister.
Brother.
Why are these women fine?
They were all taken by the Soul-Catching Bell
and haven't been transformed yet.
Let's leave here quickly.
Staying in this place makes me uncomfortable.
Wait.
There's still a great demon that hasn't been eliminated.
Another one?
However, as for this demon,
whether it should be eliminated or not
depends on the decision of the Luoxian Town villagers.
What do you mean?
Let the commoners decide?
Yes.
Let them decide.
Am I right,
Mayor?
Or,
should I call you
Senior Corpse Puppet?
You're quite something, Young Master Lin.
How did you find out?
Ever since your wife awakened as a corpse demon,
I started to get suspicious.
Village head,
could it be
that you are too?
No way.
The village head is...
Don't be nervous.
As long as you don't attack me,
I won't make a move.
All right.
Stop knocking.
They are done over there.
No.
Who are you?
Why do you care?
Don't delay us making money.
You two are fools.
Knocking more won't give you extra money.
Take a break.
It's so noisy. Seriously,
where are you from, bro?
Don't look for trouble.
Exactly.
Our boss is...
You two sleep here for a while.
This foolish girl
dared to barge into Luoxian Town all by herself.
She's such a worry.
I really didn't expect this.
I never thought it would end like this.
It's all fate.
The Shamo Ancestor has already left.
The thing you want
is no longer in Luoxian Town.
I figured.
Even if he didn't run away,
in my current state,
I wouldn't be able to do anything to him.
We're even.
Thank you, Boss Chu.
Hope we can work together again.
Work together my ass.
Did you three help at all?
Didn't I help you catch the wood demon?
Second Brother.
The wood demon was dealt with
by everyone just to save you.
Liu Erzhu, shut up.
Chu Xiao'er,
you've already made a killing.
What are you still doing here?
I'm waiting for you to make a move
and then pick up the scraps.
Your Highness Chu Xiao'er.
My demon core
isn't that easy to take.
Village Head.
Who exactly are you?
Don't you get it?
He is a corpse puppet.
The Lin family's corpse slaves and demons
were all refined from his demonic power.
What?
Village Head.
Actually,
the funeral procession came for you.
You just made your wife take your place.
Right?
She did it willingly.
She was taken by the ghost marriage and became a dark fiend.
I couldn't bear it.
So I converted her again.
So those bronze coffins
are specially meant to deal with him.
Those coffins
only take corpse demons,
not humans.
Xiaoying.
Brother.
I'm sorry.
Xiaoying.