Why is there an extra body?
Commissioner Di!
Did it scare you?
Scared to tears?
It was all...
It was entirely Master's idea.
Master even made me
dance the Nuo opera
to get your attention.
I don't know the first thing about it!
There are no signs
of struggle on the body,
meaning it was a single, fatal blow.
The victim has choke marks on the neck.
Narrow on the left, wide on the right.
The attacker used their right hand.
To inflict both the fatal wound
and these choke marks
from the front, like Buyan here,
the killer would have to
choke with the right hand
and stab in reverse with the left.
That's peculiar.
Too peculiar.
So, the killer must have
struck from behind,
just like you.
Exactly.
The killer is left-handed.
=The Tang Mist S1=
=Episode 9=
(Gambling Parlor)
Small! Small! Small!
Get out!
Broke and still trying to gamble?
Get lost!
Move it!
Out of the way!
Don't ruin my luck!
Filthy drunkard!
No more bets!
Di,
Gu Qi lied to us.
Did Gu Pan'er have
any close friends when she was alive?
My Pan'er didn't really
have any friends.
Gu Pan'er wasn't without friends.
She had a close confidante
named Dong Ling.
Duan,
go keep a close eye on Gu Qi.
Again! Again!
Open!
Big!
- Open!
- Big! Big!
- (Gu Qi is a gambling addict.)
- Open! Open!
Open!
Any more bets?
Betting big or small?
Big! Big!
(I'm one myself.)
Big! Big! Big!
- Open! Open!
- Open!
Hey, you...
Open!
- Open!
You win.
Again.
(Bets)
Big or small?
Big.
- Big!
Why did you bet on small?
You won again.
I'm out of money!
It's all gone!
Do you even have cash?
Are you looking down on me?
Get lost.
Look at this.
A silver hairpin?
You should have shown that earlier!
Hurry up!
Running away after winning?
This place is rigged!
Unless you cough up the money,
no one is leaving.
Get him!
Stop right there!
Catch him!
How am I already home?
Father.
You're back.
Pan'er...
Aren't you...
Father,
Mother is calling you home
for dinner.
Where is Gu Qi?
Darn you, Gu Qi!
You had me chasing you
like an eel all night!
I have never suffered
such indignity!
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Why are you running?
Am I really that terrifying?
It has nothing to do with me!
- What do you mean?
- It wasn't me!
There's...
There's a dead body!
You're not going anywhere.
Stay right here and don't move!
Duan.
What happened?
I followed Gu Qi
to the gambling den,
but I got distracted and lost him.
I searched all night,
only to find out he'd run back home.
By the time I found him,
he was already dead.
Have you forgotten why you were
dismissed from the army?
Exceptional hearing and agility.
Put your talents to good use.
Why are you always gambling?
Sir.
Gu Qi
owes me a huge gambling debt.
I heard from the people at the den
that he actually
used a silver hairpin to bet.
I figured he must have struck it rich,
- so I came to collect.
- A silver hairpin?
But then...
A silver hairpin?
You should have shown that earlier.
The silver hairpin.
Duan, where are you going?
Are you actually angry?
The hairpin
must be at the gambling den!
You know how it is.
Master values his cases
more than anything.
Lin,
do me a favor.
Name it.
Get that silver hairpin!
Who on earth is this guy?
You dirty old man.
Why are you here again?
It seems Master misjudged you.
You're addicted
to women, not gambling.
You can call me a lecher,
but don't you dare call me old.
Just so we're clear,
I don't hit women.
I will return
your money in full right away.
Please calm your anger, Misters.
Who wants your worthless silver?
I want the silver hairpin
from last night.
A silver hairpin?
Yes.
I...
I don't know about it.
Buyan.
Wreck the place.
Wait!
It's just a silver hairpin!
That's the one.
Gu Qi died inside a commode.
Rumors of the Guardian's curse
will only grow wilder now.
Talk of ghosts and gods
can blind the common people,
but it cannot hide the truth.
His Majesty cares deeply
about the morale in Jiangnan.
If this spreads any further,
it will reach the capital from Raozhou.
Commissioner Di,
if His Majesty holds us accountable,
what are we to do?
With Commissioner Di here,
there is no need to fear.
No visible external injuries,
no signs of bleeding,
and no indications of poisoning.
His nose and mouth are clear.
He was stuffed
into the commode after he died.
His pupils are heavily dilated.
His face is twisted in horror.
He must have seen
something truly terrifying.
Was he scared to death?
Or perhaps a drug clouded his mind.
(Wangnian County Bureau)
Master.
Where is Duan?
Master,
Duan said
he is too ashamed to face you.
If he doesn't quit gambling,
it will bring him ruin again.
Master,
to make amends for his mistake,
he wants you to have
this silver hairpin.
Could this be
the weapon that killed Gu Pan'er?
And since
the hairpin was in Gu Qi's possession,
is it possible
that Gu Qi was the real killer?
The footprints don't match.
Furthermore,
neither of them is left-handed.
(I've seen)
(this silver hairpin)
(on Dong Ling's head.)
(Except hers)
(had a tassel attached.)
(Hou Guangming, right-handed)
(Gu Qi, foot length,
23.3 cm, height, 171 cm)
(Dong Ling, silver hairpin)
(Mind-altering powder)
The killer's footprint is 27.33 cm.
And they are likely left-handed.
Every clue points directly to you.
Consumed by unrequited love
and bitter resentment,
you murdered her in a fit of rage,
along with the parents
who forced her to marry.
It's a typical motive for murder.
Tell me,
why should I believe you?
I stand by what I said.
If you have hard evidence,
you are welcome to arrest me.
Do you recognize this?
It belongs to Pan'er.
This is the weapon that killed her.
Pan'er had a close friend
named Dong Ling.
Do you know her?
There is one thing I don't understand.
Since Pan'er was your friend,
and she met such a tragic end,
why haven't I seen you
show even a shred of grief?
The grief you speak of,
is it the kind worn on one's face?
As for mine,
I channeled it all
into my dance amidst the snow
during the Winter Festival.
Every step I take
carries my sorrow.
She was such a precious soul.
I want to share the beauty she left me
with the entire world.
If I could,
I would dance forever.
The silver hairpin in your hair
is quite exquisite, Lady Dong Ling.
My mother gave it to me on her deathbed.
Was it a pair?
It was supposed to be a pair.
Where is the other one?
On the day of my mother's burial,
I gave it to Pan'er.
She is the only family
I have left in this world.
Is this the one?
Yes.
Where did you get it, sir?
From Gu Qi.
No.
Pan'er would never
give it to anyone else.
Perhaps someone stole it from her.
The tassel is missing.
The hairpin is no longer whole.
Sir, could you return it to me?
Once the case is resolved,
it will be returned
to its rightful owner.
Master.
Why didn't you mention
that Gu Pan'er was killed
by a silver hairpin?
This hairpin means
a great deal to Dong Ling.
If she knew Gu Pan'er died
from the very thing she gifted her,
I'm afraid...
Wait, no.
Master,
Dong Ling
gave the hairpin to Gu Pan'er on the day
of her mother's burial.
Which was only a few days ago.
Go on.
But Zhuang Luobai claimed
he last saw Gu Pan'er over a month ago.
How did Zhuang Luobai know the hairpin
belonged to Gu Pan'er?
So, what do you think?
Zhuang Luobai is lying.
Look at you.
You're finally making progress.
Zhuang Luobai is deliberately concealing
the fact that he met with Gu Pan'er.
The truth behind her death
must be hidden within this lie.
The noodles are getting cold.
Come on out.
Di.
Sir.
Go tell Qinglan
to examine the victims' bodies
once more in greater detail.
Master.
Look how thrilled he is.
Buyan,
go keep a close eye on Hou Guangming.
Do you suspect him?
Among all of Gu Pan'er's relatives,
he is the only one left.
Whether he is a victim or the killer,
the truth
is about to be revealed.
(Hou's Residence)
It's you.
(Preview of Next Episode)
If you don't practice hard,
you'll embarrass yourself on stage.
If you perform
the God-Welcoming Dance this way,
how can you be the lead dancer
for the Winter Festival?
My master is not the killer!
Please judge wisely, sir!
Zhuang Luobai didn't kill anyone!
Vice Director Hou,
regarding the deaths
of your wife, Pan'er, and her parents,
I have already unraveled the truth.
Would you care to hear it?
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪