( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
(In the fourth year of Chuigong's reign,)
(Wu Zetian's ambition
to ascend the throne)
(plunges the court and the realm
into great fear.)
(Rumors are rampant,)
(and strange events
occur in succession.)
(Word has it that an omen
appeared in the Luo River.)
(A divine stone emerged.)
(It was inscribed with the words,)
("The Holy Empress Descends to Rule,
The Empire Shall Prosper.")
(The Heavenly Empress is overjoyed.)
(An auspicious date is chosen,)
(and an altar is erected
by the Luo River)
(to proclaim the Heavenly Mandate
to the realm.)
(She then orders
the Directorate of Astronomy)
(to guard the divine stone)
(for the ceremony.)
(Directorate of Astronomy)
(The night before the Heavenly Mandate
Enthronement Ceremony, early Xu Hour)
(The Empire Shall Proper)
(On the eve of the ceremony,)
(42 court ladies died mysteriously.)
(Their deaths are bizarre.)
(A deeper mist of mystery)
(shrouds the Tang realm.)
=The Tang Mist S1=
Something terrible has happened
at the Directorate of Astronomy!
=Episode 1=
(Three days before the ceremony,
Shendu City)
Your Highness,
(Li Youdao, Wu Zetian's trusted minister)
These two women, one black and one yellow,
represent Heaven and Earth.
The other four
represent the four seasons.
Behind them sit 12 more,
representing
the twelve hours of the day.
Another 24
represent the 24 solar terms.
Together, they make 42 court ladies.
Among them, 28 represent
the constellations of the heavens.
13 represent
the 13 circuits of the Tang realm.
And the final one represents
the seat of rule over all under Heaven,
Shendu City.
Their birth dates
and natal charts
were carefully selected.
With them offering worship here,
the Heavenly Mandate
will surely shine ever brighter,
(The Holy Empress Descends to Rule)
blessed with greater favor from Heaven.
The Heavenly Mandate
Enthronement Ceremony
three days from now
shall proceed without fail.
(Wu Zetian, Heavenly Empress)
Li Youdao,
the arrangement
is indeed thorough and meticulous.
It's commendable.
Thank you, Your Highness.
In ancient times, Divine Emperor Fuxi
received the Luo Chart
from the Luo River
and founded the Xia Dynasty.
And now, Your Highness
has received the Heavenly Mandate
from the Luo River
to rule over the Nine Provinces.
Recently,
I've observed the signs in the heavens.
I reckon
(The Empire Shall Prosper)
whoever obtains this white stone
should be honored
with the title of Divine Emperor.
I'm aware
of your sincerity.
You have put great thought
into this.
(Late Xu Hour)
Something terrible has happened
at the Directorate of Astronomy!
Quick!
Move aside! Move!
Big or small?
(Duan Shisi, subordinate of Di Renjie)
(Once served as a military scout)
Small.
(Sharp ears, swift feet)
Move aside!
Small!
Something has happened.
(Lin Buyan,
beloved disciple of Di Renjie)
(Skilled with the staff and portraiture,
uses paintings to identify criminals)
Di.
(The Holy Empress Descends to Rule, The Empire Shall Prosper)
Just as you predicted.
Something has happened
at the Directorate of Astronomy.
(Di Renjie, courtesy name Huaiying)
(Upright and incorruptible,
brilliant at solving cases)
Master, we're still under house arrest
by Her Highness.
House arrest is trivial.
The real problem is
if the crime scene gets tampered with.
We must get there before anyone else.
No worries, Di.
The messenger's horse
(Zetian Gate)
can't outrun me.
The Court of Judicial Review is here
by imperial order to investigate.
Everyone else, stand aside.
Sir.
Officials of the Court
of the Judicial Review, you're fast indeed.
Official Di, aren't you under house arrest
by Her Highness?
Didn't you see the token?
This way, please.
Duan,
guard the door.
(The joints)
(are rigid.)
(Estimated time of death
is around 16 hours ago.)
(Time of death)
(is late Xu Hour last night.)
(The lips are dark purple.)
(Blood from the mouth and eyes.)
(Red blotches across the skin.)
(These are signs of poisoning.)
Who has the audacity
to intrude upon the crime scene?
Duan.
(Xue Huaiyi, formerly a monk)
Xue Huaiyi?
(Favored aide of Wu Zetian)
They are officials
from the Court of Judicial Review.
They claim they're here by imperial order
to investigate.
Oh?
Why have I heard nothing
about this case being transferred
to the Court of Judicial Review?
Keep the case records safe.
This matter is
of significant importance.
The order must've come
directly from Her Highness.
Official Di carries
the Heavenly Empress's token.
Sir,
please show your badge
and clear up the misunderstanding.
I doubt he can.
Di Renjie.
Whether I can show it or not
is a matter for the outer court.
It has nothing to do
with an inner court servant.
You must be exhausted
from serving at Her Highness's side.
Why trouble yourself by coming here?
You were punished
for scolding Zhang Guangfu.
As someone under punishment,
you should be staying confined.
Are you not afraid
Her Highness will punish you
even more severely?
Go on.
Show us your token.
(Earth Four)
Earth Room Number Four.
Using a door key as an official token?
Have you mistaken the Directorate
of Astronomy for an inn?
Send them out.
Master,
why didn't you let me beat up
that fake monk?
If not for his slander,
you never would've been confined.
What a disgraceful monk.
There's no need
to waste your strength on him.
Di,
did you discover something?
Those 42 court ladies
died from poison.
This poison brings great pleasure,
causing the victim to die smiling.
Its formula is reserved exclusively
for the imperial family.
Are you saying
this is an internal royal conflict?
For the Heavenly Mandate
Enthronement Ceremony,
these 42 court ladies
had remained inside the bureau
for two days.
None of them left even once.
This poison takes five hours
to take effect.
Judging by their time of death,
the poison must've been administered
yesterday
between the late Wei Hour
and early Shen hour.
Look into the visitor records
of the Directorate of Astronomy
from yesterday.
I'm heading to
the Imperial Academy of Medicine
to see who obtained
the imperial poison formula.
Understood.
Sir,
(Imperial Academy of Medicine)
these are the recent visitor records.
Please have a look.
Liu Wuzhi?
Why did he come here?
To obtain Frost Flame.
Frost Flame.
Di,
Liu Wuzhi has been arrested.
Not only did he visit
the Imperial Academy of Medicine,
but he also went to the Directorate
of Astronomy before the murders.
Liu Wuzhi is a loyal supporter
of the Li family's rightful rule
who opposes the Heavenly Empress.
So he poisoned the court ladies
to sabotage the ceremony.
He's been thrown into prison.
(But this poison)
(isn't Frost Flame.)
After investigation,
the 42 court ladies
are confirmed
to have died from Frost Flame.
Its formula is kept confidential by
the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
According to the visitor records,
Liu Wuzhi was the only person
authorized to obtain it.
Besides, guards from
the Directorate of Astronomy
and Li Youdao both testified
that during the late Wei hour
of the day of the incident,
Liu Wuzhi
dismissed everyone from the bureau
under the pretense of praying for
His Majesty.
Only he and the court ladies
were inside the hall at that time.
The Heavenly Mandate
Enthronement Ceremony is approaching,
yet Liu Wuzhi brazenly committed
such an atrocity.
(Liu Wuzhi, Grand Chancellor)
The witnesses and evidence are conclusive.
He has now been imprisoned
and will be executed tomorrow
in accordance with the law.
Liu Wuzhi has crossed the line.
Though
I am compassionate,
I cannot tolerate such evil.
In court, the loyal and treacherous
are now clearly revealed.
This shall be a warning to all of you.
Do not follow in his footsteps.
The Heavenly Empress is wise.
His Majesty is wise.
Your Highness,
I, Di Renjie, have something to report.
Di Renjie,
does the punishment I imposed
mean nothing
to you?
Forgive me, Your Highness.
This matter is
of significant importance.
I dared not delay in the slightest.
Huaiying,
rise.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I acted without permission
and investigated the deaths
of the 42 court ladies.
I also went to the prison
without permission
to meet with Grand Chancellor Liu Wuzhi.
But I dare say with certainty,
Liu Wuzhi is innocent.
Are you questioning
my judgment?
I beg Your Highness's pardon,
but I ask to speak
in Liu Wuzhi's defense.
Speak.
Liu Wuzhi is well-versed in medicine.
He knew the heat poison in Frost Flame.
If used in proper dosage,
it could treat
His Majesty's cold illness.
Hence, he went to the Imperial Academy
of Medicine to obtain Frost Flame.
I intended to test the medicine myself,
hoping to ease His Majesty's suffering.
I didn't expect this
to be the excuse to frame me.
That's Liu Wuzhi's side of the story.
Do you have proof?
(The Holy Empress Descends to Rule)
The key
is the timing.
Frost Flame takes eight hours
to take effect.
It would've needed to be administered
around noon.
But at that time,
Liu Wuzhi wasn't in
the Directorate of Astronomy.
Huaiying, are you suggesting
the real poisoner was someone else?
Duan, Buyan.
I'll write out a prescription.
You two investigate
and find out
who was compounding this medicine.
We've checked
every apothecary in the nearby ward.
Does he look like this?
Nice skill, sir.
It's exactly the same.
Li Youdao?
Within a single night,
Li Youdao visited apothecaries
all across Shendu
and gathered the ingredients
for another poison.
This poison takes five hours to kill.
The victims die smiling.
This is the true poison
behind the deaths of the 42 court ladies.
Begonia Red.
Your Highness,
I suppose you remember this poison.
Thirteen years ago,
Crown Prince Li Hong
was murdered with it.
After this incident,
I'm facing condemnation from the people.
I was ordered to investigate
the case of the Crown Prince
in secret.
The culprit has been executed.
Since the poison formula belongs
exclusively to the imperial family,
how did Li Youdao obtain it
without going through
the Imperial Academy of Medicine?
(The Holy Empress Descends to Rule)
I reckon whoever obtains the white stone...
Li Youdao has always
openly supported Your Highness.
Should be honored
with the title of the Divine Emperor.
Begonia Red has always been
a painful wound in your heart.
Without permission,
how would Li Youdao dare
rehash the past?
Furthermore,
you have long been at odds
with Liu Wuzhi.
Official Liu,
why did you go to
the Directorate of Astronomy?
You should ask your Heavenly Empress.
You suddenly summoned him
to go to the Directorate of Astronomy
to pray for His Majesty.
It was an unusual order.
Forgive my ignorance,
but it aroused my suspicions.
So by your reasoning,
I appear
highly suspicious.
If I meant to frame him,
why bother
replacing Frost Flame
with Begonia Red?
Apparently,
Liu Wuzhi was only the first step.
Once something happened at the ceremony,
it should've been kept secret.
Instead, the signal drums were sounded.
- The entire city heard about it.
-Something happened at the Directorate of Astronomy!
(Zetian Gate)
The Directorate of Astronomy is a restricted area.
Even if I had wanted to sneak in,
without Li Youdao's consent,
I would've never gotten inside.
He let me in on purpose,
so I would notice
something was wrong.
Am I right,
Your Highness?
Just because I call you "Huaiying"
doesn't mean you can forget your place.
You're using this matter
to test where the court officials stand.
Those who stay silent
in their own defense
are aligned with you.
Anyone who dares speak out
may well become the next Liu Wuzhi.
Your Highness,
to eliminate your enemies,
the cost
is far too great.
Well, well, Di Renjie.
Whether it is a road
or an abyss
before you,
you'd better look carefully.
Your Highness,
my life and death
have always rested upon
a single thought from you.
But today,
I beg Your Highness
to remember my past service
and spare my life.
And if I insist?
I never earned my rank and title
for wealth or glory,
not for fame and power.
When I vowed to serve the people
all my life,
I wasn't only
paying lip service.
If Your Highness insists on
taking that step,
then the way under your feet
will be paved with blood and lives.
And I, Di Renjie,
would rather die in chains
than serve an unrighteous ruler.
I await
Your Highness's judgment.
Di Renjie,
I'm a man of loyalty and integrity.
You needn't beg for my life.
I wasn't begging for your sake.
I was begging for
the loyal ministers of Tang.
This is the prison.
There's no need for you
to keep pretending
in front of a man who's about to die.
For the loyal ministers of Tang?
What a joke.
You should concern yourself instead
with serving your Heavenly Empress well.
Your Excellency,
I know the kind of man you are.
You never wished to be a servant
of imperial power.
You only wished to be
a servant of the people.
And I
am the same.
A servant of the people...
Many new counties are established
throughout Jiangnan.
Di Renjie is appointed
Imperial Commissioner of Jiangnan
with authority over
promotions and dismissals
to inspect the Jiangnan Circuit
on my behalf.
Master,
you offended Her Highness,
yet you still got promoted?
Promoted, you say?
You truly
are clueless.
Put nicely, he's
the Imperial Commissioner of Jiangnan.
Put bluntly,
it's exile.
Official Di,
did my Godfather leave any word?
Only one.
Do not think of revenge.
(Chu Qinglan, goddaughter of Liu Wuzhi,
skilled at medicine and poison)
I, Chu Qinglan,
am skilled in both medicine and poison.
I can be of use.
Starting today,
I wish to follow you, Official Di.
That girl...
Official Liu's surname is Liu.
Why is hers Chu?
Goddaughter.
Adopted daughter, you know?
You really don't understand anything,
do you?
Time to depart.
Depart!
Di,
I've heard Jiangnan Circuit
is a strange place.
There have been bizarre cases
involving demons and ghosts.
Her Highness is sending you
straight into the lion's den.
Master,
she's deliberately setting a trap
for you.
No evil force, however sinister,
can surpass the treachery
of the human heart.
No challenge, however difficult,
can withstand the power of justice.
(Shendu)
(Ruanjiang County, Langzhou)
(Second, The Ghost Letter)
Ruo,
I'm back.
(Memorial Tablet
of Late Husband Qi Feng)
Ruo,
I'm back.
Qi Feng...
Ruo,
I'm back.
Qi Feng.
(Preview of Next Episode)
He was burned!
- What nonsense are you talking about?
- He was burned to death!
A water ghost!
♪Night covers the long streets♪
♪The city remains silent♪
♪Wind turns the old pages♪
♪Words still left unspoken♪
♪Bloodstains still hold their warmth♪
♪Lamplight slowly tilts aside♪
♪Who hides in the shadows♪
♪Still circling around the truth?♪
♪Love is born from desire♪
♪Hatred rises out of greed♪
♪One thought becomes a snare♪
♪A lifetime trapped within♪
♪Someone once warned me♪
♪To stop upon this shore♪
♪But sunlight burns too fiercely♪
♪Fragile eyes break too easily♪
♪If one thought retreats♪
♪Then all things rest in peace♪
♪But in this world♪
♪Who will make the final judgment?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Let it pierce through♪
♪The illusions before my eyes♪
♪Layer upon layer of deception♪
♪Covering every heart♪
♪How many people♪
♪Weave their own cocoon♪
♪Yet call it♪
♪Fate?♪
♪Life and death♪
♪Balanced on a single line♪
♪Light and shadow♪
♪Hanging side by side♪
♪Goodness is not absolute♪
♪Nor is evil ever complete♪
♪In the end, it is only♪
♪A single misguided thought♪
♪If unveiling the truth♪
♪Requires abandoning tenderness♪
♪Then this answer♪
♪Can it still remain true?♪
♪When love and law♪
♪Stand against each other in silence♪
♪Which figure before me♪
♪Am I meant to believe?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Not for fame or glory♪
♪Nor caring who wins or loses♪
♪Human nature is clouded♪
♪Yet still reflects the stars♪
♪Though this world♪
♪Is filled with mud and mire♪
♪There is still a light♪
♪Worth pursuing♪
♪Every case has its ending♪
♪But night does not always fade♪
♪The wind stops, the pages close♪
♪Yet hearts remain unsettled♪
♪If justice stands♪
♪Without mercy beside it♪
♪Then how is it♪
♪Any different from a blade?♪
♪If truth is cold as a frosted blade♪
♪Still I walk ahead♪
♪Even if the world♪
♪Refuses to answer♪
♪When every hidden truth♪
♪Finally reveals itself♪
♪I only wish♪
♪To hold on♪
♪Within the darkness♪
♪To the heart♪