( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
"Lost To You."
Those who shouldn't get
close, the rain brings together,
and reunites those who
are meant to meet again.
(Episode 3)
Class.
First period this afternoon is art class.
Everyone, head to the art room in a bit.
Okay, okay, let's go.
I'm terrible at this.
It's not so bad.
That problem wasn't too hard.
He came here early by himself.
He's setting up the art supplies for us.
He's usually so cold.
I didn't know he was so nice.
What are you doing here?
Are you the only one allowed to come early?
Since you're here, make yourself useful.
You're pretty bossy.
Hurry up.
Today, we're doing portrait sketches.
We'll need a model.
Any volunteers?
Teacher.
I think...
Xu Yuan would be good.
Xu Yuan?
He can sit still.
He's perfect for a model.
Any other volunteers?
You go. You go.
Mu Zi, Mu Zi.
You go. Go on.
How about you two go?
Why are you telling me to go?
You go. You go.
Alright then, Xu Yuan, you can come up.
Xu Yuan, relax a little.
Look straight ahead.
Xu Yuan, your hand.
Can you not be so stiff with your hand?
Dude, relax.
Seriously.
Can you even do this?
Maybe I should go up there.
Can you turn this way a little?
Fine, you go. You go.
How are we supposed to draw this?
I know, he's so stiff.
Seriously.
Can he even sit properly?
You go, you go, you go.
I already told you to go.
How am I supposed to draw this?
Like this? Who can draw this?
He's like a block of wood.
I should've just gone up earlier.
Look at this.
This is a waste of time.
What bad luck.
Jinx.
Oh, come on.
Such bad luck.
Your spatial relationship is off.
The perspective is wrong.
Teacher.
It's the model's pose that's the problem.
Exactly.
Why is today so unlucky?
The jinx is up front.
Teacher.
Maybe I should just go back to my seat.
No.
He Ya.
I remember your paint was
leaking last week too, right?
I...
And your easel.
All the students have
the same drawing boards.
How can you blame him?
You blame the model
when you can't draw well.
You say it's bad luck
when you drop something.
Do you all even know...
Do you know...
who organizes your drawing boards...
and sets them up for you?
Before every art class,
he sets everything up,
and you all just take it for granted.
But the second there's a
problem, you blame him.
Jinx.
Is it really bad luck,
or are you just used
to pushing the blame...
onto a classmate who won't fight back?
You.
Sit down.
I'm not done drawing yet.
Does this [color] paint well?
Xu Yuan.
About earlier...
I'm sorry.
That...
The easel.
Thanks for warning me about it last week.
I didn't take it seriously.
I'm sorry.
Xu... Xu Yuan.
Just now...
I shouldn't have said that about you.
I'm sorry.
Here's your pencil back.
Quick, quick.
Find a place to take cover.
Hurry, hurry.
I'll go, I'll go.
Zhan Wang, you don't have an umbrella?
Come on, come on.
Walk with me.
Get in here, get in.
Run, run!
This rain came out of nowhere.
Why don't you come over to my place?
Okay.
I'll show you my gaming gear.
I have a ton.
Really?
You know what, I'll let
you use my account.
Okay, sure.
My account is totally maxed out.
I'm telling you,
most people don't get to see it.
I don't even let them play on it.
You had an umbrella and didn't call me.
Why do you always walk alone?
This is why.
I don't believe in that stuff.
Then let's walk together from now on.
Besides, I'm not scared.
And we're going the same way.
Okay.
Let's go.
About what happened in art class,
why weren't you angry?
I'm used to it.
They call you a jinx.
They say being near you is bad luck.
You don't care about that either?
Let them talk.
It doesn't really affect me.
Xu Yuan.
Is there anything you care about?
I care about my family.
What about my grandma?
Do you care about her?
I do.
She was one of the kindest people to me.
That's why I hate you.
Why?
Because I don't think...
you cared about an old
woman who loved you so much.
If you cared,
why didn't you come back to see
her even once in all these years?
Zhan Wang.
Do you have any regrets?
What?
Not seeing your grandma one last time.
Do you regret it?
None of your business.
[extremely offensively]
I'm not trying to hit a nerve.
It's just...
The moment you came back to Hong Town,
you went to your grandma's old house.
You remember the height
marks on the wooden frame.
You remember the
osmanthus tree she planted.
You remember her orange cat.
That's why I wanted to ask.
Since you missed her
and thought of her,
why did she wait until the very
end without you ever coming back?
Enough!
You think I didn't want to come back?
My dad...
said coming back to Hong Town
meant you were a good-for-nothing.
And that I should never get involved...
with anyone from here.
Every time I wanted to come back,
he was the one who stopped me.
It wasn't until my grandma passed away...
that I realized...
I had already lost the most
important person in my life.
Only then...
did I start to fight back.
So it wasn't that you didn't love your grandma,
it was just that it wasn't your choice.
Your grandma gave this
to me before she passed.
She said...
that if you ever came back,
I should give it to you.
I wasn't going to give it to you.
Because I didn't think you deserved it.
Grandma waited for you for so many years.
She waited until she was gone.
And you only came back to claim the house.
I was just so angry.
But these past few days...
I've realized you're not the
person who I thought you were.
You can read it at home.
I'm leaving now.
(For Wang-wang)
The key to this problem...
is the concept of substitution.
You take the complex part...
and treat it as a single entity.
Got it?
No.
What don't you get?
None of it.
I'm not cut out for this school stuff.
So just save it.
Paying your debts...
is just how the world works.
Paying it off with your time...
was something you agreed to.
So what if I'm backing out now?
You tell me.
What's the point of these stupid problems?
Will they make my mom
get better any faster?
Or will they stop the debt
collectors from knocking on our door?
It gives you the chance of having options.
Instead of being like you are now...
constantly on the run from life.
Options?
Like you?
Choosing to come back to this dump?
Or like my dad?
Choosing to just pack up and leave?
I don't know your family situation.
But that's no reason for
you to give up on yourself.
Stop lecturing me when
you don't know a thing.
Don't you get it?
I'm not doing this shit.
These stupid problems.
This stupid town.
And people like you...
with your self-righteous savior complex.
It makes me sick.
Wang-wang.
My dearest Wang-wang,
By the time you read this letter...
Granny will be gone.
Don't be sad.
In my life...
having you as my grandson...
has made me so content.
About the house...
don't blame the Xu family.
I insisted they take it.
Hsu Meixi has had it rough.
That boy, Xiao Yuan...
is so much like you were as a child.
But he's quieter than you were.
He's much more withdrawn.
All that gossip in town...
it's like knives.
And he endures it all.
Your father's heart is
no longer in Hong Town.
But Granny knows...
that a part of your heart...
will always remain here by the sea.
Leaving the house to the Xu family...
is the same as leaving it to you.
You and Xiao Yuan are both lonely children.
You can look out for each other.
That's what makes a family.
The passbook is in the usual spot.
The PIN is your birthday.
It's not much money.
It's what Granny saved up.
You can use it however you like.
Wang-wang.
Remember to eat on time.
Bundle up when it's cold.
Don't always be frowning like your father.
Granny will always love you.
How shameless.
A whole family, perfectly able-bodied...
and they don't go out to earn a living.
Even cheating an old
woman out of her house.
By the way.
I forgot to mention yesterday.
The house.
I'm taking it back.
What is it you want?
I just want to see...
what kind of person the jinx who conned
my grandma out of her house really is.
Is this how you took care of my grandma?
No.
Granny Chang never gave me a hard time.
Mom.
That shipment at the docks...
Uncle Wang didn't try to
lowball you again, did he?
No.
He was surprisingly reasonable today.
It's all thanks to you the other day...
for laying out his accounts so clearly.
That's good.
Come on, you two, eat up.
I'm full.
I'll go close the courtyard gate.
It's raining.
Mom, maybe I should...
It's fine, it's fine.
Xiao Wang?
What are you doing here?
Zhan Wang.
Come in, come in.
It's raining out there.
Why are you getting soaked?
Hurry, come inside.
Xiao Yuan, go get a dry towel.
And find some dry clothes.
Such heavy rain.
Sit, sit.
Have a seat.
Have you eaten?
You can eat with us.
I'll get you some hot soup.
In this downpour... why didn't you find
somewhere to ride it out? You poor thing.
Dry yourself off.
Please, don't go to any trouble, Auntie.
It's no trouble, no trouble at all.
You just sit.
Zhan Wang.
Are you here to see my brother?
The things in the house...
we've barely touched them.
Granny's clivia is still alive, too.
That beat-up old bowl my
grandma used for her money plant...
You even kept that?
I couldn't bear to throw it out.
Here, here, quickly.
Eat up.
It'll warm you up.
Thank you, Auntie.
It's nothing. Go on, eat.
Your grandma...
she loved eating this so much.
When you were little...
back when you were still here...
your grandma...
would come to my place to buy it.
She'd say...
that Wang-wang is just like her.
Even the flavors he likes...
are just like me.
When your grandma was still with us...
she was always talking about you.
She'd say, "Wang-wang loves to eat this."
"Wang-wang can't stand the cold."
"Wang-wang is the most mischievous."
She left a lot of things behind.
I put them all in the house...
inside that camphor wood chest.
I figured...
you'd come back to visit one day.
Back when Granny...
insisted on giving us the house...
we were going to
write an IOU for its value.
And pay Granny Chang
back when we had the money.
But she wouldn't take it.
So we've been taking
care of her ever since.
These are all her hospital bills.
My mom recorded every single one.
Some of the money was
borrowed from neighbors.
We paid it all back slowly.
There's still some left.
To pay off the rest sooner...
Mom goes to the docks
for supplies before dawn.
At night, after the noodle shop closes...
she takes on piecework.
She has a chronic illness.
It's too much for her body to handle.
[An unbelievably
depressing promissory note]
And my brother...
he has to go to work
every day after school.
Xu Nuo.
I'm sorry.
Can I go see the room?
You didn't even move this poster.
I saw it before.
And I put it back.
It was waiting for you to return.
Auntie.
This money is from my grandma.
The PIN is my birthday.
I'll write it down for you in a bit.
Please, take it for now.
Pay off your debts first.
No, we can't.
This is the money your
grandma left for you.
We can't take it.
Granny said in her letter...
I can do whatever I
want with this money.
I think...
if it's for you two,
Granny would be happy.
It's also to make up for for
all the awful things I said.
Also...
Granny told me
that Xu Yuan and I
should look out for each other.
Right?
Friend.
Alright.
Come on.
Sit down and eat these noodles.
They're going to get soggy.
Xiao Wang, don't leave tonight.
It's still raining outside.
It's dark and not safe.
How about...
you share Xiao Yuan's room for the night?
Is that okay?
Does it fit okay?
It's fine.
It's just...
the clothes are a bit small.
These...
Granny left them for you.
You can look through them first.
I'm going to take a shower.
[A log from October of various expenses
related to Zhan Wang from childhood.]
Granny.
Xu Yuan.
Are you asleep?
Thank you.
You're thanking me?
Thank you...
for taking care of Granny for me.
It was Granny who
took care of me.
Growing up,
besides my mom and Xu Nuo,
everyone else treated me like a jinx.
They stayed clear of me.
Only Granny didn't mind.
She always treated me like a friend,
like family.
So...
if Granny treated you like family,
does that mean we're family now too?
Who wants to be family with you?
Fine.
Even if we're not family,
we're friends from now on.
Come on.
Pinky swear.
So childish.
So the jinx actually made a friend.
I know, right?
I heard last night,
he even spent the night at Xu Yuan's place.
Excuse me.
But you weren't that close to Xu Yuan,
and you're just as unlucky.
Can't blame anyone else now, can you?
Their family's dessert
is actually pretty good.
Are you still going to be
my training partner tonight?
You still want me to
be your training partner?
I paid for it.
I want to get my money's worth.
Fine.
But...
you can come to my
place to practice tonight.
It's your granny's old house.
You can go back whenever you want.
But let's drop the roleplay.
It sounds weird.
Deal.
Yeah.
I'll bring you a piece next time.
Okay!
Got a pen?
Thanks.
You used the wrong
formula for this problem.
And you're not holding
your pen correctly either.
How should I hold it?
With handwriting this bad,
they'll dock points for presentation.
What are you doing?
Do you have any mints?
I want one.
Thanks.