( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 4=
You're here.
Nianchi.
I already told you.
I don't want that name anymore.
Now you're Gu Nianchi.
And I'm Lu Shaoyuan.
As long as you don't mind
me using your name, Brother.
Enough of that.
Why did you ask me here today?
Because there's a woman at home now.
Things aren't as convenient anymore.
That sly old fox. He knows
Commander-in-Chief Li will be there tomorrow.
To keep you away from him,
he insisted on
attending the wedding himself.
Back then, he took my name
and became the Commander he is today.
Of course he's worried I'll
tell Li Shuche the truth.
Since he's already
taken the name Gu Nianchi,
I don't want it anymore.
I took my mother's surname.
My name is Lu Shaoyuan now.
He really got
the better end of the deal.
I heard some desperate men
are planning to crash his wedding
with the Xue family tomorrow.
Too many people want revenge on him.
They're already running out of patience.
Are we going?
Do you really think
he wouldn't know what we already know?
Let's just watch the show.
By the way, have you found the person
who sent the secret letter?
Not yet.
That person knows
about the Zhuang family.
We have to find that person.
Understood.
I heard you caught someone here
a few days ago.
How did that person offend you?
Because of a woman.
I'm not like you.
Someone hates you so much,
they even tried
to kill you at your wedding.
So now you know
it isn't easy being
the Commander of a city.
Not only is it exhausting,
one careless move
could cost you your life.
Good thing you didn't go that day.
Why don't you hand me
the military seal instead?
I'm always out there
taking risks for you,
yet I don't even
have anyone protecting me.
If I lose my life one day,
how am I supposed to enjoy myself?
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
Good.
As long as you're
out front covering for me,
I can just sit back and enjoy life.
By the way, that young lady
from the Xue family...
She hasn't noticed anything, has she?
That woman?
She's difficult to deal with.
She's really hard to deal with.
This dress looks nice on you today.
If you like it,
I'll wear it for you every day.
I just like red.
Commander,
what about this green one?
Green suits you too.
You're certainly in the mood today.
Looks like you're
quite good at following people.
What?
Do you enjoy today's opera too?
Commander,
is this your new wife?
She's not even that pretty.
Exactly. And she's so fierce too.
Alright.
You two wait outside for a while.
I want to talk to her alone.
Then I'll wait for you.
Go on.
Following me?
Everyone in Yancheng knows
the Commander loves opera.
So this is how you enjoy it.
They're just women.
Why not
let me serve you instead?
No flower at home
can compare to the wild ones outside.
You haven't even
picked this flower at home.
How would you know if it's sweet or not?
What are you doing?
Giving you what you want.
Isn't this what you wanted?
Let's talk about this tonight
after we get back.
I like getting intimate with you
anytime, anywhere.
Don't you love excitement?
Getting close in an opera house
sounds far more interesting.
Take this sachet.
I blended it myself.
It helps keep your mind clear.
You mustn't fall asleep right now.
Understood?
How is it?
Thank you.
Why do you smell like this?
It's perfume I brought back from France.
(I underestimated her.)
Looks like
your days ahead
won't be easy.
Weren't you the one
who insisted on marrying her?
Even though I was the one
who married her in the church,
the one who spent
the wedding night with her was you.
Since I've already shared
the Commander's position with you,
your sister-in-law can be shared too.
I'm not interested in women like her.
Really?
You didn't seem that way
just now.
I was only trying
to keep you from blowing your cover.
Then I'm relieved.
(I was going to explain)
(that I didn't mean
to offend you today.)
(If you ever see Gu Nianchi's face,)
(you'll be in grave danger.)
Today we stand
beneath the snow together.
One day we'll grow old side by side.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
Yunqiu.
Mm.
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
This is...
This jade pendant
is the only thing my mother left me.
One day,
I'll place a white veil upon you myself.
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
Even if the winter snow melts away,
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
my feelings for you
will never change.
Today we stand
beneath the snow together.
One day we'll grow old side by side.
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
(Why does being around you
feel so familiar?)
(Why do you always remind me of her?)
(Why are you so determined)
(to kill Gu Nianchi?)
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
He loves the sea,
but only its raging waves.
He loves the grass,
but only when it
grows through the ruins.
(This handwriting...)
Report.
A child is here looking for you.
Hello.
Are you Commander Gu Nianchi?
Yes.
A lady asked me
to deliver this letter to you.
(I found the person
and the item you're looking for.)
(Tonight between eight and nine,
at Golden Love Songs.)
(She loves the sea,
but only its raging waves)
(She loves the grass, but only when it
grows through the ruins)
(So it was her who gave me
information about Zhuang Xun.)
Shaoyuan,
why have you either been
listening to opera in the west wing
or practicing shooting here
these past few days?
You still don't have any other leads?
He's harder to deal with
than I expected.
Lieutenant Li
is too difficult to handle.
I need to think of a way
to lower his guard.
Chairman Lin came to see me before.
Maybe
doing business with him
could distract them for a while.
But I don't know
anything about business.
The Xue family runs businesses.
Maybe Xue Wan knows something.
Forget it.
Even if we do nothing,
the Fragrance Gala
will take place in a week.
By then, we'll definitely
get evidence of his crimes.
Shaoyuan,
your aim was off today.
You seem to have something else
on your mind.
I keep feeling
like she's strangely familiar.
Don't tell me you've fallen for her.
Impossible.
You didn't come back last night.
Have you still not gotten used
to being a husband?
Or perhaps
there's something about me
that dissatisfies you?
Everything about you is fine.
I'm just not interested in you.
Since you're not interested in me,
then let's make a deal instead.
The Xue family
is now the wealthiest in Yancheng.
We're no less influential than
the Zhuang family was five years ago.
You know the Zhuang family?
Yancheng isn't that big.
Business families crossing paths
is perfectly normal.
Then did you know
the Young Lady, Zhuang Yunqiu?
You can ask me anything
you want to know.
But I have one condition.
Speak.
Since ours is only
a marriage of power and money,
why not make the most of it?
I'll help strengthen your influence,
and you'll help me expand our business
and broaden my horizons.
I want the Xue family to become more than
just the wealthiest in Yancheng.
One day, we'll become
the wealthiest in the country.
You're quite ambitious.
Isn't that so I can become
a better match for you?
You seem to have many secrets.
And aren't you
just as hard to read?
Alright.
Tomorrow,
I'll take you to the ball.
Pleasure doing business with you.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪