( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 3=
You people who studied abroad
really are quite open minded.
Stop avoiding the question.
Tell me.
Why did you pull a knife on me?
It's because
we had never met before.
We only met yesterday, and we
were already expected to share a bed.
I wasn't ready for it.
As for the spiked wine,
my brother said money
can't compare to power.
The Xue family
will still need your support.
He told me to win your favor.
Commander,
don't be upset.
Last night, Young Lady Xue
was pointing a knife at me.
And now,
you're suddenly
acting so warm and eager.
That's because
after seeing you up close
and admiring your charm,
I've completely fallen for you.
Commander,
can you give me one more chance
to make up for last night?
What a pity.
I'm not interested in you.
If you're not interested,
why did you marry me?
(That's right.)
(Gu Nianchi, you've married your enemy.)
Everyone in Yancheng knows
the Xue family is the wealthiest.
This marriage between us
is nothing more than
a deal of power and money.
Is that all?
I'm still young.
Just because of a family arrangement,
do I have to waste my whole life here?
Let me tell you something.
Before I married you,
there was someone I loved.
And we promised we'd
grow old with the one we loved.
It's just a pity.
After spending all that time together,
I think
you already understood my feelings.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm trying to tell you this.
I'll remember the Zhuang family
of North City.
Don't worry.
Once my eyes recover,
I'll come to your home and marry you.
Commander,
have you ever loved someone before?
That's none of your business.
Xinran.
What is it?
Come here.
I need to ask you something.
You brought that wine
into my room yesterday, didn't you?
So what if I did?
I'm not here to serve you.
Young Master Xue told me to do it.
I only listen to him.
So the spiked wine really was
Young Master Xue's idea.
What did you say?
The spiked wine?
Shameless.
You're the one who sent
that spiked wine to my room.
And who's the shameless one here?
I...
And
another thing.
Since you're working for him,
you should know what he wants to see.
You'd better behave yourself.
Otherwise,
neither of us will end well.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
(I'll remember the Zhuang family
of North City.)
(Don't worry.)
(Once my eyes recover,)
(I'll come to your home and marry you.)
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
(I never forgot that promise.)
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
(It's just a pity.)
(The place remains,)
(but the person is gone.)
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
(Place Hotel)
Thank you.
How did it go?
Did Xue Tian give you a hard time?
No.
He found me
at the newspaper office the next day.
But what's done is done.
There was nothing he could do about it.
By the way,
did Gu Nianchi suspect anything?
Everything's fine on my side.
Don't worry.
Anyway,
be careful.
And don't forget.
Only by finding evidence
can we bring Gu Nianchi to justice.
That way, you won't be blamed
for marrying in my place.
And it won't affect
my brother's business.
Trust me. I'll definitely find evidence
of Gu Nianchi's crimes.
When the time comes,
I'll still need your help. Help me expose him.
Of course.
Playing alone must be boring.
I'll play with you.
The white ball is the beginning.
The black ball is the end.
I only play straight shots.
I wonder
if I can shoot my way into your heart.
You really did study abroad.
You sure know a lot of tricks.
Your turn.
In that case,
let me make things
a little more challenging for you.
Don't try these little tricks on me.
I don't like them.
(The water's been drugged by me.)
(Once you soak in it,
the poison will seep into your bones.)
(This time,)
(I won't let you escape again.)
You've worked hard today.
Why not take a bath and relax?
Is the water not warm enough?
I'll add some hot water for you.
Alright.
If the water temperature isn't right,
then perhaps my wife will do instead.
So you were waiting for me.
Why didn't you say earlier?
Then let me
bathe you myself.
What a coincidence.
I've already bathed.
Then let me join you one more time.
You'd better be careful.
If you fall in,
you'll be in trouble.
Thank you, Commander.
The water temperature isn't right,
make yourself comfortable, then.
(You think I don't know)
(what you put in the water?)
(I'd like to see
what exactly you're planning.)
(You're even harder to deal with)
(than I expected.)
Commander.
Darling.
Didn't you just
go upstairs?
You must've mistaken someone else.
That was Cheng Yi.
Oh.
And that room upstairs...
It's just an ordinary room.
Cheng Yi rests there
sometimes while on duty.
How about
we go eat steak?
Now?
Right now.
Then wait for me.
I'll go get changed first.
No need. Let's go.
You...
Why did you suddenly
want to treat me to steak?
I just suddenly felt like eating it.
Then I'll make it for you next time.
Nianchi.
Call me Commander.
Calling you Commander feels too distant.
Don't you want us
to get closer sooner?
I told you.
Call me Commander.
Alright.
Here, Commander.
This medium rare steak is too bloody.
I don't like it.
You're really hard to read.
Your moods shift without warning.
- No one can predict your temper.
- Then stay away from me.
But I happen to like men like you.
Mysterious men
are the most charming.
You asked me over to eat steak,
but you're not even going to feed me?
Thank you, Commander.
Commander,
how about we go see a movie tonight?
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
I already have plans tonight.
Who's more important
than your newlywed wife?
Some singer from "Golden Love Songs,"
or a dancer from Paramount?
You really
do know me well.
Of course.
You're here.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪