( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 2=
(Xue Tian, young master of the Xue family)
(What if the Commander finds out?)
(Don't worry, Young Master.)
(Young Lady left the country
when she was twelve.)
(Other than the Xue family,)
(no one knows what she looks like.)
I heard the Xue family's young lady
went abroad at twelve.
Who would've thought
she'd be such a beauty?
The Commander of Yancheng
and the Xue family's heiress,
what a perfect match.
It's just a deal of power and money.
The Xue family gains protection,
and the Commander gains wealth.
A fair trade for both sides.
Be careful.
(Li Shuche)
I heard Commander-in-Chief Li arranged the match.
(Commander-in-Chief of Yancheng)
He's here today too.
Isn't he just using this
to line his own pockets?
Darling,
have we met before?
I think you feel the same way I do.
Gu Nianchi,
are you willing
to take this woman as your wife
and enter into marriage with her?
Whether in
sickness,
health,
poverty,
or wealth,
will you stay by her side
and never leave her?
I do.
Xue Wan,
are you willing to marry this man
and become husband and wife?
Whether through sickness,
hardship, poverty, or wealth,
will you stay by his side
and never leave him?
I will...
Nobody move!
Protect Commander-in-Chief!
Protect the Commander and Madam!
Don't move!
Move aside!
Gu Nianchi,
move again and I'll kill him!
Nianchi, save me!
Gu Nianchi, are you out of your mind?
Commander-in-Chief.
I did it to save you.
You...
Lieutenant Li.
Yes, sir!
Escort Commander-in-Chief Li out.
Commander-in-Chief.
Gu Nianchi,
I'll fight you to the death!
You?
You can't even use a gun.
If only you'd shot me dead.
Now you've ruined my wedding.
I'll teach you how to shoot.
Gu Nianchi,
you'll regret this...
Darling, sorry for frightening you.
You're the Commander of a city.
A scene like this
is nothing unusual.
I'll have someone escort you back first.
I need to handle some business.
See you later.
Alright.
(Commander's Residence)
(Gu Nianchi,)
(I prepared poisoned wine for you.)
(We'll leave this world together.)
(That way, the Xue family
won't be implicated because of me.)
(And everything between us
will finally come to an end.)
(Xinran, Xue family's dowry maid)
We're both dowry maids.
Why are you the one
marrying in Young Lady's place?
I heard
everyone in your family
died because of you.
A jinx like you still dreams of marrying
into a powerful family?
I'm already alone anyway.
If they find out I'm an impostor,
the worst that can happen is death.
But you...
You helped cover up the bride swap.
That's a crime punishable by death too.
Are you really willing
to risk your life with me?
You...
If you don't want to die, then behave yourself.
Commander.
You're back.
(That voice...)
(It sounds so familiar.)
You had quite a fright today, darling.
I'm already part
of the Commander's household.
Something like this doesn't bother me.
Oh.
Good.
Then get some rest early.
After all, tonight is our wedding night.
No matter what,
we should at least
share a wedding toast.
You studied abroad,
yet you still care about these customs?
It's not the customs I care about.
It's you, Commander.
A wedding toast
is meant to be shared together.
Alright.
We've finished the wine.
I still have matters to attend to.
I'll leave first.
Gu Nianchi,
after killing so many people today,
Have you ever felt
even a trace of guilt?
Why would I?
True.
If you were capable of feeling guilty,
you wouldn't have
so much blood on your hands.
Get some rest.
You take the bed tonight.
I'll sleep in the study.
What's wrong?
Are you alright?
(The poison should
be taking effect by now.)
(But...)
(Why is he fine?)
What happened last night?
Why can't I remember anything?
Why is my wife up so late?
Did last night
tire you out?
Last night, we...
You don't remember?
Then let me refresh your memory.
Looks like you do remember.
Last night,
you held a knife to me just like this.
Tell me.
Why did you try to kill me?
I just wanted
to make things more exciting.
Didn't you enjoy it, Commander?
The wine was already strong enough.
Did you really need this too?
Then what do you enjoy?
I'll do whatever you like.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪