=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 13=
Stop right there.
(Investigation into Yancheng
Opium Addiction Groups)
How did you get
the documents I gave the Commander?
(Investigation into the ships
at Yancheng Port)
Commander-in-Chief, are you
referring to this document?
It just looks similar.
Commander-in-Chief Li,
I've heard so much about you.
Why didn't you introduce us?
My apologies,
Commander-in-Chief.
This is my wife, Xue Wan.
Didn't I send you to handle something?
I'm sorry.
She kept insisting on following me.
So...
Please don't laugh at us.
Go handle it right away
so nothing unexpected happens later.
All right.
Go.
Darling, then I'll go
see the Commander-in-Chief off.
Commander-in-Chief, this way.
(How does he have)
(the scent of the perfume
from the Fragrance Gala on him?)
Every perfume here
has a completely unique scent.
(This scent...)
(How does this scent
end up on Gu Nianchi?)
(This bottle of perfume...)
(I used it on that masked man.)
(Could it be...)
Look at me. I'm good.
If you don't believe me,
feel my forehead.
It really doesn't seem hot anymore.
Didn't your fever already go down?
The roast chicken is ready.
Come downstairs and eat.
I don't want that.
I want you.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Xue Wan.
Open the door, Xue Wan!
Why are you wearing glasses?
Doesn't wearing glasses
during business talks
make me seem more composed?
Commander.
(No wonder.)
(I always felt like Gu Nianchi became
a completely different person sometimes.)
(Because they were actually
two different people.)
(And I...)
(Only realized it now.)
(So the one who killed my family
wasn't the real Gu Nianchi.)
(From the very beginning,)
(I misunderstood him.)
Commander.
She did it on purpose.
If there wasn't a scar,
why would she get this tattoo?
That's because...
Of course it was because I personally
tattooed it on my wife on our wedding night.
♪Fates intertwined,
right and wrong no longer clear♪
♪The world becomes a prison♪
♪Even fleeting happiness is enough♪
♪This heart and love slowly fade away♪
♪What kind of ending
will this fate bring?♪
Today, we stand together
beneath the snow.
One day, we'll grow old together.
♪Etching our promises
into each other's hearts♪
I'm sorry.
I came too late.
♪So called blame,
nothing more than an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
(And all this time, he's
been silently protecting me.)
♪How can love remain so calm?♪
♪So called blame,
nothing more than an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
(European and American
Dance Star Performing Arts)
Shaoyuan, I've already
followed your orders
and set up roadblocks
along the route they'll take.
If we head there now,
we'll definitely arrive before they do.
Replace the opium.
The timing is perfect.
All right.
Shaoyuan, I think your plan
is absolutely flawless.
By the time they get there,
the opium will already
have been swapped out with fake ones.
This batch of opium is the strongest
evidence of their crimes.
Today,
can we finally confront
Gu Shaoyan directly
and take them all down in one move?
That's right.
We're heading to the docks now.
Once this is all over,
I can finally reunite with Yunqiu.
Why are you only showing up now?
You're already half an hour late.
Sorry.
Something delayed me.
Did you get the evidence?
I found it.
That's great. Give it to me now.
Tomorrow, I'll publish the report.
Then Gu Nianchi's crimes
will be exposed to the whole world.
Xue Wan,
can I discuss something with you?
Can you hold off
on publishing the report for now?
Wasn't this our agreement?
You married him in my place,
found evidence of his crimes,
and then we'd bring him down together.
Why are you backing out now?
I'm not saying we shouldn't publish it.
I'm asking if we can
wait a little longer.
How much longer?
I...
I'm not sure.
Until...
(If the report gets published now,)
(as the stand in,)
(he'll definitely get dragged
into this because of Gu Nianchi.)
(How can I possibly protect both sides?)
You're the one who called me yesterday.
I've already prepared the article.
I even had my coworkers finish
the newspaper layout and send it to print.
All we're missing now is the evidence.
If the report doesn't go out tomorrow,
everyone at the newspaper office
will laugh at me.
At that point, I won't
be able to stay there anymore.
I don't care.
By tomorrow night at the latest,
you must give me the evidence.
Xue Wan,
I'm truly sorry.
But things have changed now.
You can't bear to give up your position
as the Commander's wife, can you?
Do you really think I'm the kind
of person who chases wealth and status?
It's because of the Commander.
Actually...
I don't think it's the title of
the Commander's wife you can't give up.
It's the Commander himself.
You're the one who told me
Gu Nianchi was a despicable man
who committed every evil imaginable,
and told me not to trust him.
So what happened to you now?
Xue Wan,
this situation is complicated.
- But it's definitely not what you think.
- Enough.
You're the one who came to me back then,
saying you knew
I didn't want an arranged marriage,
and that you wanted to protect Yancheng
and its people together with me.
And now?
Just because of one man,
you've forgotten everything
you said?
I haven't forgotten.
Xue Wan, trust me.
I really just need a little more time
to resolve this.
Save it.
Don't forget,
you married into the Commander's
Residence using my identity.
If I don't see the evidence
by tomorrow night,
I'll tell the Commander
that you're not the eldest daughter
of the Xue family at all.
Your name is Zhuang Yunqiu.
Let's see how you'll stay
the Commander's wife then.
Xue Wan...
Sir.
Commander.
Did something good happen today?
Tell me so I can share the joy too.
Sure.
This is your reward.
Thank you, Commander.
Commander.
Commander. Something terrible happened.
The deal went through,
but...
The goods are fake.
What?
Who did it?
We don't know yet.
Then what are you still doing here?
Go investigate now.
Yes, Sir.
Commander.
What goods are you talking about?
Come drink with me instead.
What's wrong with you?
Come on, let's drink.
Drink.
You drink.
All right. I'll drink.
I told you to drink,
and you actually did it!
Get out, all of you!
Move, hurry up and go!
Perfect timing.
You were behind
the opium shipment
at the docks, weren't you?
I was.
And not only that.
I even prepared this for you.
(Investigation into
Yancheng Opium Addiction Groups)
Shaoyuan,
have I not treated you well enough?
Whatever you want, I can give it to you.
Gu Nianchi,
wasn't the reason you approached me
from the very beginning
to make me your scapegoat?
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪