( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 6=
You...
Zhuang Yunqiu...
(Lily?)
(I thought she was dead.)
(She was the one
who sided with Gu Nianchi back then)
(and betrayed our family.)
Weren't you dead?
Yunqiu?
That's right.
Commander,
don't you recognize her?
She's Zhuang Yunqiu,
the daughter of the Zhuang family.
The Zhuang family smuggled opium,
and you executed them according to the law.
You're the one who escaped.
You must be here
to take revenge on Commander.
Commander,
you have to kill her.
This...
Miss Lily?
I'm the Commander's lawful wife,
married into the family with full ceremony.
My name is Xue Wan.
The way you're acting now,
are you not taking me seriously at all?
Xue Wan?
Zhuang Yunqiu,
stop pretending.
I grew up with you.
There's no way I'd mistake you.
Commander,
she must've taken Xue Wan's identity
to come back for revenge.
Have you caused enough trouble?
If you keep this up,
I'll have someone drag you out.
Commander,
I'm telling the truth.
I've been by your side for years.
Don't you know me by now?
She really is Zhuang Yunqiu.
I remember now.
There's a scar on her shoulder.
Let go of me.
You seduced him,
and now you're trying to frame me?
Do you really think
I'm someone you can push around?
Frame you?
Fine.
Then take off your clothes
and let everyone see.
Let's see whether
there's a scar on your shoulder.
Whether I have a scar or not,
he knows best.
Commander,
you believe me, don't you?
No one knows whether
my wife has a scar better than I do.
That's enough, Lily.
Commander,
don't let her fool you.
I'm doing this for your own good.
She really is Zhuang Yunqiu.
And she's no refined young lady either.
A few winters ago,
she ran off for days
without coming home...
Miss Lily,
I think I've already
shown you enough respect.
I'd advise you
not to push your luck any further.
Words mean nothing.
If you're not Zhuang Yunqiu,
then take off your clothes
and let everyone see.
We'll all be witnesses for you.
What?
Zhuang Yunqiu.
Don't tell me you're feeling guilty
and too afraid to do it.
Another woman fighting
over the Commander again.
I've heard about it too.
The Zhuang family had a young lady
who spoke French,
played the piano,
and was quite beautiful too.
Commander.
If this lady is lying,
it'll be easy enough to verify.
Besides,
the Zhuang family's
hidden opium stash
was no small matter.
Miss Xue,
don't tell me you're afraid.
Let go.
I'll do it myself.
This...
Why is it a flower?
You must've used it to cover the scar.
Enough!
Commander,
she did it on purpose.
If there isn't a scar,
why would she get a tattoo there?
Because...
Of course it was something I personally
tattooed on my wife
on our wedding night.
Commander,
you...
How is that possible?
Weren't you...
What?
Do you plan on interfering with
what happens between me and my wife too?
I...
Darling. Let's go.
♪Your silhouette♪
♪Carved through endless hardship♪
♪Love and longing
traced through countless lifetimes♪
♪Fates intertwined,
right and wrong no longer clear♪
Tell me.
What's the story behind that tattoo?
Didn't you already say it yourself?
A little memory from our wedding night.
Speak properly.
♪Crossing through
the barriers of dreams♪
♪Burning away all my devotion♪
Thank you for helping me out just now.
But why did you help me?
♪How can one stay calm in love?♪
Why do you know that song?
♪Nothing more than an excuse♪
Commander, you're hurting me.
Talk.
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
That song?
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
Zhuang Yunqiu taught it to me.
What exactly was your relationship
with Zhuang Yunqiu?
Before I went abroad,
we used to be childhood friends.
We were quite close.
So,
you married me
and kept pulling knives on me
because you wanted revenge
for your dear friend?
♪Fates intertwined♪
You're only half right.
♪The world becomes a prison♪
♪Even fleeting happiness is enough♪
♪This heart and love fade away♪
Zhuang Yunqiu and I
were childhood friends,
but we haven't been in contact
for a very long time.
At first,
I truly didn't want to marry a stranger.
But after spending time with you,
I realized
you're even more charming
than I imagined.
♪So called blame♪
So the two of you seemed alike
only because you knew each other?
The reason you dislike me
is because of her?
When it comes to Zhuang Yunqiu,
do you feel hatred,
love,
or guilt?
♪If the years are wasted for too long♪
♪How can one stay calm in love?♪
♪So called blame
is nothing but an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
Are they back yet?
Not yet.
That Lu Shaoyuan...
Where exactly did he take my woman?
Go find them now.
Yes, sir.
Lu Shaoyuan!
Darling,
I'm Gu Nianchi.
I'm your husband.
What?
Did you forget, Brother?
You're the one
who begged me to be your stand in.
Lu Shaoyuan,
I'm the one who married her!
Really?
But the one who spent
the wedding night with her was me.
What exactly is going on?
Get out of my sight!
Lieutenant Li!
Commander.
Are they back?
He's already asleep in the study.
What about Madam?
She's back in the bedroom.
(Lu Shaoyuan,)
(you'd better know your place.)
(She belongs to me.)
You really enjoy
doing these pointless things.
I like flowers.
Because I think they're just like love.
When they bloom,
they're dazzling and beautiful.
But nothing in this world lasts forever.
They wither so quickly,
just like love fading away.
Didn't you say before
that you had someone you loved?
Are these feelings because of him?
Commander.
Madam.
I offended you both yesterday.
So today, I'd like to treat you
to a meal as an apology.
I'm not hungry.
I am.
Won't you eat with me?
No.
This is braised fish from Guangde Restaurant,
the most famous restaurant in Yancheng.
I specially ordered it for you.
Madam, give it a try.
You should eat it yourselves.
What a coincidence.
I don't eat fish.
Do you not eat fish,
or do you not dare to eat it?
There are too many bones.
I don't like trouble.
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
♪Falling into your smile before my eyes♪
The fish is ready.
Sorry, I can't eat fish.
I'm allergic to it.
I'll break out in red rashes.
Then wait a little longer.
The chicken will be ready soon too.
Chicken is fine.
It's alright.
I can remove the bones for you.
I don't want fish.
Take it away.
Commander,
don't you usually love fish the most?
Then we shouldn't waste Lily's kindness.
You...
You're really going to eat it?
If you don't want to eat,
you don't have to.
Actually,
I do quite like fish.
I just don't like removing the bones.
Especially when a stranger
does it for me.
Commander,
can you help me?
♪In this world♪
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪