( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 1=
Darling,
you look beautiful.
You always know how to make me happy.
Lu Shaoyuan!
You...
Darling, I'm Gu Nianchi.
I'm your husband.
What?
Did you forget, Brother?
You're the one
who begged me to be your stand in.
Lu Shaoyuan,
I'm the one who married her!
Oh?
Really?
But the one who spent
the wedding night with her was me.
What exactly is going on?
Get out of my sight!
(Three Years Ago)
Father!
Qiu, run.
What's wrong, Father?
It's Gu Nianchi.
(Zhuang Yunqiu)
It's Gu Nianchi...
(Zhuang family's eldest daughter)
Father.
You must destroy the opium.
Father!
Go!
(Gu Nianchi, Commander of Yancheng)
It's you.
One slipped through the net.
Thank you for saving me, Miss.
What's your name?
My name is Zhuang Yunqiu.
And you?
My name is Gu Nianchi.
Why?
Today, we stand together
beneath the snow.
One day, we'll grow old together.
The Zhuang family of North City.
I'll remember that.
Don't worry.
Once my eyes recover,
I'll come for you
with a grand wedding procession
and marry you properly.
Didn't you say you'd marry me?
Too many women like you try to
get close to me for their own gain.
What a pity.
(Three Years Later)
Why tattoo it over the scar?
Because I like today's opera.
"The Top Scholar Zhang Xie."
What's it about?
It's about Zhang Xie.
After becoming the top scholar,
he abandoned the wife
who stood by him through hardship
and even tried to kill her.
But she survived.
Later,
they met again.
(Xue Wan, the Xue family's eldest daughter)
What a heartless man.
(Lu Shaoyuan,
Gu Nianchi's younger brother)
Commander.
What brings you here?
Where's the person I want?
Why did the opera stop?
Why is it so noisy outside?
(Gu Nianchi.)
(You really came.)
The person's not here, Commander.
No matter.
Search the place.
Yes, sir.
- Commander, there's really no one here.
- Over there!
Hurry!
Keep up!
Search everywhere!
Yes, sir!
(Cheng Yi, Lu Shaoyuan's sworn younger brother)
Sorry, wrong room.
Those look like Gu Nianchi's men.
Have they found us?
We're not their target.
How do you know?
Commander, we found him!
Listen.
They've already found him.
Let's continue.
Everything here's clean.
Look, Commander.
Commander.
(Gu Nianchi.)
(My uncle Zhuang Xun,)
(is my grand wedding gift for you.)
(And in return, you'll make sure to deal
with that traitor to the Zhuang family)
(Zhuang Xun, Zhuang Yunqiu's uncle)
(the hound you've begun to suspect, for me too.)
Zhuang Xun,
it really took some effort to find you.
Why have you been hiding from me?
Commander...
I haven't.
Where did
the Zhuang family's shipment go?
Are you going to tell me yourself,
or...
Commander,
I really don't know.
So,
you've chosen the second option.
Commander, please!
I really don't know!
Please spare me, Commander!
Commander!
Does it hurt?
That scream just now
made my hand slip a little.
Sorry about that.
Gu Nianchi really is just as you said.
A cruel and merciless man.
That's right.
He was born an executioner.
To him, this sort of thing
is nothing unusual.
(But...)
(only ruthless measures)
(can bring justice to men like Zhuang Xun.)
Well?
Do you remember now?
Commander...
I remember now.
I only found out
about this secret recently.
The shipment you're looking for
was hidden by the Zhuang family
inside a flower.
A flower?
What flower?
This...
I...
I really don't know.
You're marrying in my place tomorrow.
Why insist on tattooing
a red spider lily here?
A red spider lily
blooms for a thousand years,
then withers for another thousand years.
Its flowers and leaves
are never seen together.
Love defies fate,
yet destiny
still ends in life and death.
Are you regretting this now?
The Commander is cruel and merciless,
and I never wanted an arranged marriage.
So I don't want to marry him.
If you're regretting it...
How could I regret it?
On the contrary,
I'm actually looking forward
to going to the Commander's side.
Then why are you doing this?
As a keepsake.
Who else knows about this?
No one.
I only discovered it recently too.
I never got the chance to tell anyone.
Why should I believe you?
Alright.
I should go now.
Be careful.
Commander,
that's really all I know.
Back then, you and I,
and Commander-in-Chief Li too,
worked together from the inside and outside
to frame the Zhuang family!
I may not deserve credit,
but I still suffered for it!
Commander, please spare me!
I've already told you
everything I know!
You worked with me and Commander-in-Chief Li
to frame the Zhuang family?
Yes...
Thank you.
I finally heard what I wanted to hear.
Commander!
Please spare me, Commander!
(Yunqiu,)
(everything happened
just as I expected.)
(The destruction of the Zhuang family)
(was a scheme by Gu Nianchi
and Commander-in-Chief Li.)
(I'll seek justice for you
and your family.)
(Uncle,)
(this is the price
for all the wrong you've done.)
(Once you're gone,)
(make peace with the Zhuang family.)
(As for the one who'll kill you...)
(White spider lilies bloom in heaven,)
(while red spider lilies bloom in hell.)
(Gu Nianchi,)
(tomorrow, I'll marry you.)
(I'll be waiting for you in hell)
(with these red spider lilies.)
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪