( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 5=
(Paramount)
The Commander is here.
Commander.
Commander, over here.
- Look this way.
- Commander, over here.
It's the Commander's wife.
She's gorgeous.
- Madam, look over here.
- Madam.
- Over here.
- This way.
Madam.
Commander, look this way.
Madam, over here.
♪Night Shanghai♪
♪You are a sleepless city♪
♪The lights glow bright♪
- ♪The traffic hums♪
- Commander.
♪Songs and dancing fill the night♪
♪All you see♪
♪Are smiling faces♪
Commander.
You're here too?
Boss Huang.
Enjoy yourselves. We'll head over first.
Alright.
This is where Yancheng's
businessmen gather.
If you want to expand your connections,
Paramount is the best place
to gather information.
Thank you.
♪Drowsy eyes in the hazy dawn♪
♪Everyone heads home with weary hearts♪
♪Following the turning wheels♪
Come on.
♪Entering a brand new world♪
♪A whole new life awaits♪
Commander, it's been a long time.
Chairman Lin.
(Lin Li, Chairman of
the Yancheng Chamber of Commerce)
This must be your wife.
Chairman Lin.
Hello.
This is my daughter.
Greetings, Commander.
Commander.
Greetings, Madam.
Madam.
I've always wondered
what kind of woman you married.
Now that I've met her,
she truly is elegant and extraordinary.
You're too kind.
I heard you studied in France.
What a coincidence.
I happen to know
some French too.
Perhaps we can
speak French together sometime.
I'd like that. But it's been a long time
since I've spoken French.
I'm a bit rusty.
I hope there'll be more opportunities
to speak with you, Mr. Lin.
Commander.
You truly married
a beautiful, intelligent,
and graceful wife.
I'm quite envious.
You're flattering her.
Madam,
I heard you play the piano beautifully.
Would you honor us with a performance
and let us enjoy it?
You play piano too?
It's not as impressive as Mr. Lin says.
I only know the basics.
It's hardly worthy of an audience.
You're too modest.
- If you don't feel like playing...
- I'll play instead.
Good. Good.
Please.
Commander.
I thought after getting married,
you wouldn't have time for me anymore.
(Lily)
Isn't Lily still
the one who understands you best?
Without my permission,
don't come to the residence
looking for me again.
Understood?
Why not?
That was wonderful.
Commander.
He's here too.
We...
(Lieutenant Li, Gu Nianchi's lieutenant)
Keep it down.
Go get the Commander's
uniform from the cabinet.
Alright.
Chairman Lin,
about that last shipment
of military supplies,
I'd still like to discuss it
with you privately.
Of course.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
Even with your eyes like this,
you still roasted chicken for me.
How about this?
I'll sing you a song instead.
Alright.
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
Let's step aside and talk business.
Please.
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
Good!
Excellent performance!
Wonderful. Your piano skills
are remarkable!
Commander,
how about this?
Three days from now,
I'll bring the contract over myself.
Darling.
Commander.
Weren't you
discussing business just now?
Your piano playing
was truly exceptional.
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
Why are you wearing glasses now?
Doesn't wearing glasses
make me look more composed
during business talks?
At a time like this,
let's not talk about business anymore.
Commander.
Alright.
Then it's settled.
I'll take my leave first.
Commander.
Darling.
I still have some matters to handle.
Please excuse me for a moment.
Alright.
Go ahead and take care of your work.
(Dingweilin Foreign Trading Company)
Why do you know that song?
Why did you take your glasses off again?
How did the business discussion go?
Answer my question.
You already know
I studied in France.
Of course I learned it there.
That's a local folk song.
Do they have
songs like that overseas too?
Commander,
we weren't done having fun just now.
Let's continue.
You...
Zhuang Yunqiu...
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪