=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 14=
Shaoyuan,
have I not treated you well enough?
Whatever you want,
I can give it to you.
Gu Nianchi,
from the moment you approached me,
wasn't your plan
to make me your scapegoat?
I'm only taking back
what rightfully belongs to me.
But you're my own little brother.
When I am in trouble,
you should help me.
Instead, you're trying to replace me.
Is that really right?
The one who replaced someone was you.
What you still don't know
is that because of you,
I was separated from the person
I loved most for three whole years.
The person you loved most?
Are you bringing up old history with me?
That was all years ago, wasn't it?
Is there really any need
to mention it again?
Oh, right.
Didn't you like your sister in law?
I can give her to you too.
And besides,
however much money you want,
I can give it to you.
Enough.
Back then, I went off to war
to earn money for the family,
and left you at home to care for Mother.
But what happened in the end?
When I returned with military honors,
I found Mother already dead
from illness at home,
and you had vanished without a trace.
You stole my identity,
and slaughtered the entire village
just to keep the villagers
from exposing you.
So many innocent lives.
Do you really feel
no guilt at all?
Shaoyan.
Guilt?
Shaoyuan,
only the weak use morality
to judge the strong.
And the strong
can keep the weak
beneath their feet forever.
Gu Shaoyan!
What did you call me?
I called you Gu Shaoyan!
My name is Gu Nianchi,
not Gu Shaoyan!
Did you hear me clearly?
My name is Gu Nianchi!
Men!
Seize him!
What are you doing?
I said,
seize him!
What's this?
You've been hiding this thing
inside the opera house.
I found it.
Back when you took my place,
I originally thought that if you could
become a good Commander,
and protect the people,
I would willingly
hand this position over to you.
But every single thing you've done
has filled people
with outrage and hatred.
So,
starting today,
I am the Commander of Yancheng.
Take him back to
the Commander's Residence.
Yes.
Yunqiu.
Where's Yunqiu?
Yunqiu?
Madam.
Oh, Madam,
I haven't seen her.
Yunqiu!
(We were separated for three years.)
(When we met again,)
(I thought you were my enemy.)
(And you thought I was Xue Wan,
the eldest daughter of the Xue family.)
(Fate truly loves to toy with people.)
Find Madam for me, no matter what.
Yes.
(Did you recognize me long ago?)
(While I kept pushing you
away again and again.)
(Have I already broken your heart?)
♪Entangled through lifetimes,
drawn into chaos and schemes♪
♪Your silhouette♪
Have you seen a woman about this tall?
No, no.
♪Love and longing
traced through countless lifetimes♪
Have you seen this person?
♪Right and wrong no longer clear♪
♪The world becomes a prison♪
A woman about this tall.
Have you seen her?
No.
♪This heart and love slowly fade away♪
You three, come with me over there.
Yes.
♪Crossing through
the barriers of dreams♪
♪Burning away all my devotion♪
♪Etching our promises
into each other's hearts♪
♪If the years
are left to waste for too long♪
♪How can love remain so calm?♪
Yunqiu!
♪Nothing more than an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
Yunqiu!
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep♪
Yunqiu!
♪Why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
Were you looking for me?
Gu Nianchi.
♪Fates intertwined,
right and wrong no longer clear♪
♪The world becomes a prison♪
Zhuang Yunqiu.
♪This heart and love slowly fade away♪
♪What kind of ending
will this fate bring?♪
♪Crossing through
the barriers of dreams♪
♪Burning away all my devotion♪
♪Etching our promises
into each other's hearts♪
♪If the years are left
to waste for too long♪
♪How can love remain so calm?♪
♪So called blame,
nothing more than an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
What's your name?
My name is Zhuang Yunqiu.
What about you?
My name is Gu Nianchi.
♪Nothing more than an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
♪I still long to hold you once again♪
♪When love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?♪
♪Let the frost wither
the greenery beyond the window♪
♪Love quietly hides within the wind♪
♪Falling into your smile before my eyes♪
What are you trying to do?
What you have always wanted to do to me.
When did I ever?
Then let me do it instead.
♪Love is so strange,
the way it entangles me♪
♪I still haven't awakened,
though I know I shouldn't♪
Commander.
Remember this.
My name is Lu Shaoyuan.
♪Joy and pleasure♪
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪