( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 7=
Just like you said,
this fish is really delicious.
Commander.
I want another piece.
It really is the best fish
in all of Yancheng.
Commander, you should have some too.
I'll get it for you.
Impossible.
This has to be fake. Zhuang Yunqiu,
you must be putting on an act!
Let me take a look.
You must be covered in rashes.
Lily, if you keep this up,
don't blame me for losing my temper.
Commander.
Get out.
Lily was being unreasonable,
but this fish really is delicious.
I think this fish
is hands down
the best braised fish in Yancheng.
Come on, eat.
Try it.
I haven't had fish in ages.
It's so good.
You should eat too.
What happened to your neck?
I scratched it a few times earlier.
It's a little red now.
What brings you here?
What happened with Lily today
must've upset you.
It's nothing.
I'm your woman now.
It's only natural for you
to be surrounded by admirers.
Is there anything else?
You asked me before
if I'd ever loved someone.
I did.
But that's all in the past.
I don't mind.
But I do.
Now you've made me curious.
What kind of woman
could make you unable to forget her?
She was like...
♪What is there to seek or desire,
trapped in worldly sorrow?♪
A ray of light.
♪Entangled through lifetimes,
drawn into chaos and schemes♪
I'm sorry.
I spoke out of turn.
Please get some rest.
♪Carved through endless hardship♪
♪Love and longing
traced through countless lifetimes♪
(Should I really let myself
soften toward him again?)
(Zhuang Yunqiu.)
♪Right and wrong no longer clear♪
(European and American
Dance Star Theater)
♪Even fleeting happiness is enough♪
♪This heart and love slowly fade away♪
Shaoyuan.
What's gotten into you today?
Do you think there really can be
two people in this world
who are that alike?
Their voice,
their scent,
everything is exactly the same.
♪Nothing more than an excuse♪
♪Where in time did my heart belong?♪
And today, she...
♪Even if time has given up on us♪
What happened today?
♪When love runs deep♪
Forget it. It's nothing.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
Who are you talking about?
Miss Xue?
If she isn't Zhuang Yunqiu,
then why does she look so much like her?
But if she really is Zhuang Yunqiu,
I'm the one who killed her.
And I even saved Li Shuche,
the very man who sided with them.
How am I supposed to face her?
What?
You think they're the same person?
I'm not sure.
But I can't shake the feeling
that she's hiding a lot of secrets.
I heard there was quite a commotion
at the Paramount a few days ago.
No one suspected you, right?
I've already taken care of it.
Don't worry.
How have you been lately?
I'm fine.
That's good.
But there is something
troublesome right now.
You should go first.
Okay.
Speak.
Who told you to follow me?
This is bad.
This isn't good.
Shaoyuan.
Miss Xue has been kidnapped.
They headed toward
the warehouse in West City.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm Xue Wan.
You're about to die,
and you're still refusing to admit it?
Let me tell you the truth.
Who I am doesn't matter
to the Commander at all.
The only reason he keeps me by his side
is because I'm useful to him.
As for you,
you've already lost your value to him.
If I were you,
I'd run before
he decides to kill you.
That's nonsense.
Whether it is or not,
you already know the answer yourself.
Get over here.
All of you, get over here.
What are you trying to do?
I don't care whether
you're Xue Wan or Zhuang Yunqiu.
Today, I'm dragging you
straight into hell.
Then we'll see whether the Commander
will still want a woman
whose reputation is in ruins.
Lily.
Lily, don't go!
Lily!
Come back!
Later,
set this place on fire.
Leave no survivors.
Yes.
Brothers,
how much did she pay you?
I'll give you double.
Just untie me first, alright?
I'm begging you.
Originally,
we brothers were only after the money.
But
you're just too beautiful.
None of us
have ever had someone
this beautiful before.
If you dare lay a hand on me,
I guarantee
the Commander
will kill every one of you.
The Commander?
That's if he can even
find this place first.
Exactly.
♪How can broken love ever go on?♪
♪How much hope must fade into despair?♪
♪In the blink of an eye,
everything falls apart♪
♪Bound by the fate we cannot escape♪
♪You and I caught in
this tangled love and hate♪
♪Fragile hearts can hardly bear goodbye♪
♪How many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?♪
♪I once gave myself
to you so completely♪
♪Still holding on to that heart♪
♪Only to suffer your fatal blow♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet I approach you with such caution♪
♪How could a stand in ever have♪
♪The right to be loved by you?♪
♪If love is nothing
more than endless schemes♪
♪Used and abandoned in the end♪
♪Still I walk into♪
♪The trap you set without regret♪
♪How desperately
I long to hold you close♪
♪Yet keep it buried deep inside♪
♪A stand in can never cross♪
♪The shortest distance between us♪
♪If love can
make someone lose themselves♪
♪Then let me stay by your side♪
♪A substitute♪
♪Needs no reason♪