( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
WE ARE ALL TRYING HERE
When was
the hardest time in your life?
I see
you've never talked about it before.
My friend and I
were taking the subway home after dinner
when they suddenly asked,
"When was the hardest time in your life?"
My heart suddenly started pounding.
I couldn't answer for a long time,
and before I burst into tears,
I just got off.
That day,
I sobbed all the way home.
When I thought about it,
I realized I'd never said out loud
what had happened
back then.
The most terrifying part was that,
even at a young age, I was conscious.
I knew being conscious
meant I was experiencing this vivid fear,
but I didn't know how to make it stop.
All I could do was endure that fear
in vivid detail,
completely helpless and overwhelmed by it.
What I wanted the most
was to grow up quickly
so I could leave at any time,
as if it were nothing.
CLOSED UNTIL THE END OF DECEMBER
I thought about how nice it would be
to reach an age
where walking alone at night
was normal.
I was just sitting there…
when my nose started to bleed.
Crows kept gathering outside the window.
I thought,
"I must be dying."
That's…
when my dad came home
after 28 days.
And my mom…
never came back.
I've never once
talked about what happened then.
I think I lived
by consciously blocking it out.
And then
when my friend asked
when the hardest time of my life was,
I felt a surge of rage,
as if it had just happened yesterday.
Before that,
I didn't feel much
whenever I saw my mom's face
pop up in random places,
as if she had nothing to do with me.
But once I felt that rage…
I couldn't stand to look at her face.
The cause of all my pain.
What happened then…
and the one behind it.
Mom.
The one who left me behind…
was my mom.
Being over 30 means you've lived
more than ten thousand days.
But whenever anything happens,
I end up going back to those 28 days,
as if they are what made me
who I am today.
I hate talking about wounds.
It feels like the language of the weak.
But…
that's what I'm doing right now.
Whenever something goes wrong,
I tell myself I was shattered back then,
and that's why I'm like this now.
I connect everything back to that time.
But…
if my life had worked out…
would I still be holding onto
and struggling with what happened then?
Am I constantly bringing up my past
as an excuse…
for why my present situation
isn't working out?
How can you not bring up your past?
Aren't you being too hard on yourself?
But you don't do that.
You don't bring up the past
to make excuses about the present.
I don't have a past to bring up.
You may not believe it,
but my family
was pretty well-off.
We were a pretty happy family…
until my sophomore year in college.
When my father's business went under,
all that wealth disappeared overnight.
Then my mother
and father
passed away one after another.
I didn't know everything could collapse
in an instant.
I'm sure many people
found some satisfaction
in seeing our family collapse.
I get it.
It's only fair
if things go back and forth.
What's the point of carrying on
what our parents' generation built?
All of our belongings
from when we were well-off
have been sitting in storage
for the past 20 years.
We pay a hefty rental fee every year.
I see you can't let go of those memories.
They're not so much memories
as proof we used to be well-off.
Without that…
I feel like I have nothing to lean on.
I feel like
I can only let it go
once I've improved even a little.
Once I debut with a bang,
I'm going to throw everything away.
Was that
the hardest time in your life?
No.
I see…
you've never talked about it before.
My favorite sound in the world…
is my brother's snoring.
When I hear him snore…
I feel at ease.
"Oh."
"He's sleeping."
"I can sleep now too."
But if I don't hear anything,
I wonder why he can't sleep.
My life has to improve even a little.
I have to achieve something on my own,
even a little.
That way, I can let go of the past
and my wounds.
That way,
I won't feel anxious about you,
Ms. Byeon Eun-a, rising to the heavens,
or worry about why Jin-man can't sleep.
I can't just let go.
Not until I see what I've achieved.
Not until I see what I'm capable of.
Bounce, bounce!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Safe!
Let's go.
Hello.
Thank you.
HANKUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Hello.
Goodness, two strong men
to carry things and help me?
I feel so special.
There's no place like home.
I'm usually not the type
to ask for compensation,
but fixing teeth is expensive.
I got a partial denture, not an implant.
I'll get an implant myself
after I make some money.
Send it to my bank account.
DEPOSIT AMOUNT: 1,200,000 WON
SENDER: MA JAE-YEONG
My youngest aunt has two daughters.
Whenever her reckless sons-in-law
give her a headache, she says,
"If my girls had an older brother,
those two wouldn't act like that."
Some assholes think
a women-only household
is easy to deal with.
Just so you know,
it's not just women at Eun-a's house.
I can't go into details,
but…
if you mess with Eun-a,
you'll be
in real trouble.
I'm serious.
Forget about Knock knock knock.
Your film career
could be destroyed.
Just remember that I warned you.
Don't come back later
saying I didn't tell you.
See you.
Episodes five and six synopses ready?
Will you knock before you come in?
Why?
Were you playing games?
I wasn't playing games.
Does it look like I have time to play?
Why isn't Writer Park here?
Why isn't she here?
We decided to write separately.
Why?
You really think
we should work face-to-face?
-Listen carefully.
-Just say it!
My hearing is fine.
What are you, threatening a kid?
"Listen carefully."
I regret yelling at you.
I'm sorry.
You were on a roll for once,
but I ruined it.
I should've just let you be
until you were finished,
but I lost my temper.
I'm sorry.
Just ignore me and keep writing
with that same excitement.
I mean it.
And…
let's get divorced when the time is right.
I've never once brought up divorce
since we got married.
I told myself not to say it out of habit,
but to say it when the time comes.
I think now's the time.
In order to write,
you have to dive into different emotions,
moving from one to the next,
or sometimes be just downright dirty.
You have to use every version of yourself.
But with your wife
looking over your shoulder…
you can't just go for it.
You're boxed into being a man
who won't raise moral questions.
There are couples who freely accept
each other's emotions
and even support them.
But you and I
aren't built like that.
Everyone knows ruthless women write well,
and ruthless men direct well.
If you can't let go
of that half-decent guy in you,
you won't get anywhere.
So getting a divorce
and just going for it
is the right thing to do.
I'm not saying divorce is easy.
I know I'm the one who brought it up,
but I'm not sure if I can actually do it.
But…
I'm just putting it out there
because I want to set you free.
Don't tie yourself down to me.
Just go for it.
It may be hard right now…
but in time, parting will feel natural.
Let's part ways then.
You need to crack into the watermelon.
A sweet, juicy one.
So just go for it, okay?
She really knows how to make a threat.
I went to a dollar store
and asked an employee where something was.
But they said they didn't know
because they haven't been there long.
They said the exact same thing last week,
and then they said it again this week.
If it were me,
I'd have focused
and memorized it all in two days.
I knew they wouldn't be good at their job.
Their face
was slack.
It was as if it couldn't hold any focus.
It was slack.
My friend works at a dollar store too,
and they always want to meet
in front of one.
They'll come ten minutes early
and observe the store's layout
and how the merchandise is displayed.
-They're an assistant branch manager.
-Oh, really?
They became assistant branch manager
in just five years.
They could be working the same job,
but what separates someone who makes it
from someone who doesn't
is focus.
I might be scatterbrained
and all over the place,
but once I focus, I go all in.
Look at my face.
All my focus is right here.
We can start shooting
in the second half of next year.
I already have all the shots and scenes
planned out in my head,
so we can start filming next year,
no problem.
From now on,
get straight to the point.
Tell me the conclusion first.
Then I'll decide whether to listen
to the details.
If you talk like this on set,
it'll take all day.
Got it. Straight to the point.
And I don't care
if you film next year or not.
Based on my schedule,
it's two years from now
because I'm doing a film
with Director Park Jin next year.
But I heard Director Park's screenplay
is still being revised.
You read my screenplay, right?
No, I haven't!
Why would I read something
that won't be filmed for two years?
I haven't even been paid.
There's nothing to revise. It's perfect.
And the investors are already on board.
Be quiet and shut your mouth.
And from now on,
don't come to the set
under any circumstances.
I can't stay in character.
Stand up.
Come here.
Now, lower your head.
Let's just do ten laps today.
Begin.
-One.
-Louder!
One!
-Two!
-Louder!
Three!
Four!
He wants to film two years from now.
I'm going insane.
I'd start tomorrow if I could.
A whole year will go to waste!
You've waited 20 years.
Can't you wait another year?
I've waited 20 years,
so of course I can't wait!
Who knows what kind of mess
Noh Kang-sik will get into again?
I just want to be done with it
before he causes trouble.
Releasing steam.
Okay. I'll call you later.
What's ingan in English?
What is it in English?
Human.
There's another word after that.
Mankind?
Human being.
B-E-I-N-G.
Not "human doing." It's "human being."
So just be still and exist.
Quit rambling about
what you did or didn't do.
Stop running around "doing" things.
Practice "being."
Just be still.
Do you know how hard it is to be still?
Why don't you stop drinking
and just be still?
Did you watch it?
The AI-made movie, that is.
Just a two-line command,
and it pumps out a movie
with an insanely good story and visuals.
What should take years of effort
is done in just a few minutes.
I mean, I knew the AI era was coming,
but I didn't expect it
to catch up this quickly.
Is this the end for us now?
We can't beat machines.
Everyone's racing to catch the last train
before their screenplays go to waste.
I heard they're just throwing them
at investors.
Looks like Gyeong-se
will catch the last train.
They're filming next year.
The streaming company likes the script,
so they're casting right now.
His scripts are always good.
They just never get shot
the way they're written.
Once they start shooting,
it all goes to chaos,
and everything falls apart.
Then the actors get tense and ask,
"Wait, are you sure
this is right?"
That's why he ends up
becoming enemies with the actors.
-I wouldn't say "enemies."
-Hey.
Name one actor he's worked with
that he's still close to.
Jang Mi-ran?
She's still seething
about being fooled by his writing.
The rumor spread among actors,
so casting won't be easy.
It'll be freaking hard.
The only reason he's still a director
is that Hye-jin went around begging
and gave it everything she got.
If it weren't for her,
I'd say he wouldn't have made it.
He would've been executed.
You're here.
Hello.
Cham, cham, cham.
If you ever
go meet an actor without my permission,
you're dead.
Any meetings with actors
or whatever movie-related work
goes through me first. Got it?
Get up already.
Go upstairs and write.
I said go upstairs and write.
Damn it.
What is it?
Did you bad-mouth him
without knowing he was here?
What did you say?
Whatever.
Do you want a drink?
It's all your fault.
-What did I do?
-Why did you say he caught the last train?
But I…
Gyeong-se, have a drink.
Everyone out.
Leave, all of you.
Close up and head home.
They're worse with people around.
Right now?
Start talking after we leave.
I said get up.
Right, we should go. Let's go.
-Hey, where are you going?
-Home, of course.
Sorry, I didn't know.
I wonder
when they'll close your coffin.
This will end.
Our tiresome relationship
will eventually come to an end.
I wonder how it'll end for you,
and how it'll end for me.
"So he dies in the end."
"After all that bullshit
about never dying,
he dies after all."
I want to end it,
but I don't know how,
and it drives me to tears.
Every night, I dream of dragging you
into the age of duels.
If we were in the age of duels…
In the age of duels,
where everything ends in a single blow…
I used to think
while watching foreign films,
"Why would anyone risk their life
over something so trivial?"
But now,
I want to risk it.
I'm so sick of this endless cycle.
I'd rather end it once and for all.
I've thought about why you piss me off.
It's because you have a sixth sense
for where it hurts me the most.
You know exactly what my weak points are,
and you stab right into them
while laughing.
If I were a bigger man,
I'd laugh along with you, but I can't.
And it frustrates the hell out of me.
Everyone stakes their whole life
on being seen as a decent person.
But you always wreck that.
Your sharp tongue keeps stabbing them
like a broken blade.
I was just saying it for fun.
Talking trash about others
is just for laughs.
You'll keep doing it for fun,
and I'll keep bleeding from the blade
you stab me with for fun.
Let's just stop, Dong-man.
Okay?
I know you don't like me.
Let's end this.
You want to go on a trip?
How about a four-day trip?
Just the two of us.
Let's spend those four days
letting out all the stuff
we've been holding against each other,
and see who comes out on top
from all this.
I won't hold it against you if you do.
Let's end this.
Please.
Okay?
Let's just
end this.
Done.
It's over.
Dong-man.
Dong-man?
It's over.
Dong-man.
Let's end this.
Damn it.
Dong-man, let's just end this!
I just got my tooth fixed!
This isn't new for you.
It's not the first time
you've heard people say
you're a director
who's made five films with no style,
no taste, and no signature work.
You're just pissed
because it's coming from me!
Someone who hasn't even debuted yet!
What, if you're not doing well,
you can't talk trash?
You're just scared that a pathetic loser
like me might catch up to you.
Stop thinking about
crushing the people below you,
and just focus on catching up
with the ones above you!
And let's find out
how you die
and how I die
when the coffin closes.
It's over! The end!
Satisfying! So satisfying!
Damn it.
REGRET
How is this "regret"?
Gyeong-se.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I'm trying
not to talk trash about others.
I really
want to stop talking trash about someone
I used to be close to.
But it's not easy.
There's only one way
for us to get back to
being close.
I have to debut.
We need to be on the same level.
That way, you won't dismiss what I say,
and I won't take your words the wrong way.
When we were on the same level,
when we were both nobodies…
we were freaking amazing.
We were full of energy
and stayed up all night
roasting lousy veteran directors.
We were on our knees like this
and watched Billy Elliot.
We watched it repeatedly,
crying every time.
Remember
Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind?
After watching it…
we felt sentimental for days.
Half of the movies I've watched in my life
were with you.
I've been trying so hard
to get close to you again,
trying to be the same as you,
so we could be close again.
But you've been trying hard
to become different from me.
Gyeong-se.
Let's just be the same again.
Please.
I'll debut and come back
so we're on the same level.
Let's just be the same again.
Please?
Let's be the same.
You're here now,
so just apologize and move on.
Think of it as acting.
You're shooting one apology scene
and making 100 million won.
Damn it!
Come on.
There you go.
I'll talk her down
and get her to apologize somehow.
Don't worry.
Ms. Oh, it's time to go.
How many times do I have to say I'm sorry?
You call that being sorry?
Yeah, this is me being sorry!
This is how I act when I'm sorry.
I go on the defensive when I'm sorry.
What, you want me to cry and beg?
I can't do that
because it makes me cringe.
I was wrong, I've committed a grave sin,
and I'm sorry!
Here, I'll let you hit me.
Go ahead.
Just hit me as hard as you want.
Get on your knees and repeat after me!
-"I'm a crazy bitch."
-Yeah, I'm a crazy bitch.
"Jung Hyeon-u never liked me."
For crying out loud.
No? Then go ahead and tank your career.
I'd rather you just hit me.
I'll die at your hands.
Go ahead and hit me! Come on.
It's just as I expected.
Idiots who don't know how to apologize
or how to accept an apology.
Is Jung Hyeon-u into stupid women?
I bet you think you can just vent, quit,
and live like any ordinary person.
Having your face out there is a curse.
People will always remember you.
If you open a café,
you'll be the celebrity
who tanked their career
after a hair-pulling fight
with Jang Mi-ran.
If you open a restaurant,
you'll be the celebrity
who tanked their career
after a hair-pulling fight
with Jang Mi-ran.
Even when you become an old grandma,
you'll be the celebrity
who tanked their career
after a hair-pulling fight
with Jang Mi-ran.
It'll follow you forever.
Why would my career get tanked?
The person who grabbed my hair
is the one whose career would tank.
You'll both go down.
If you can't live an ordinary life,
wouldn't it be better to keep appearing
on the big screen or on TV?
I'd be open to doing that,
but your daughter
refuses to apologize properly.
What a joke.
She can't act.
You'll never get the apology scene
that will satisfy you.
Just drop it.
Jang Mi-ran won't be engaging in
any public activities for the next year.
She won't take part in overseas promotion
for the drama.
She'll just pay the penalty and skip it.
The settlement amount
will be delivered separately
to avoid any contact with Jung Hyeon-u.
Is there anything else you want?
Other than her apology, that is.
If there's nothing else, we're done here.
I came in the middle of a shoot.
You'd think she was your real daughter.
Why don't you just cut ties
with your troublesome husband
and stepdaughter
and start taking care of
your long-neglected biological daughter?
That's how most celebrities deal with
troublesome family members.
This is your chance.
I'll release the CCTV footage for you.
Hey.
All right.
Release it.
Do it.
I watched the footage countless times
and wondered how ordinary people
would react to it.
You speak quietly until Mi-ran walks in.
Then you show just how petty you are
by laughing over the top,
tossing your head around.
Don't even think about editing it.
Release the whole thing.
I'm sure you know
Jung Hyeon-u is known for using acting
as an excuse to get into situationships.
When you heard rumors
about him and Jang Mi-ran,
you tried to shut them down
by labeling her a crazy woman
who can't separate acting from reality.
I've met every actress he's done that to.
They said they'll back us
if this gets out.
You have to see it through with idiots
who can't tell when to back off or quit.
Get up. Let's go.
You seem curious, so I'll tell you.
My biological daughter
is far more impressive
than the likes of you.
You don't even compare.
She doesn't cling to anyone for support.
Not men, and not even her parents.
Bye.
Why do I keep getting caught up
in these unpleasant emotions?
Feeling abandoned
and feeling hurt…
I want to stop writing stories like this.
What do you think makes a story feel real?
Emotions.
How did you feel
when you accurately identified an emotion
that appeared on the emotion watch?
A bit…
A bit thinned out.
That's right.
Negative emotions are easier to manage
once they're accurately identified.
At the very least, they won't snowball
into more distorted thinking.
As your emotions thin out,
the story naturally loses its strength.
Eun-a,
you've practiced
identifying emotions enough
that you can probably do it
without the emotion watch now.
You should give it a try.
Practice accurately identifying emotions.
-Hello.
-Goodness. Welcome, Ms. Oh.
This way, please.
Go in.
Hello.
This is Producer Byeon Eun-a.
She's one of our development producers.
She has pretty great ideas.
I'm sure she'll be helpful
in this revision meeting.
Take a seat.
Is the writer still against me
playing the role?
No, it's not that they're against it.
They just want to
think it over more carefully.
They seem a bit full of themselves
because it's a good screenplay
and all the actors are after it.
Please tell the writer
that they're not in a position
to turn me down.
It's well written for a beginner,
but it's not first-rate yet.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure how much of the writing
comes from the director versus the writer.
But you should hear this, Director Ma.
KNOCK KNOCK KNOCK
BY MA JAE-YEONG, BYEON EUN-A
Go home and count how many times
"like crazy" appears.
"Run like crazy," "Eat like crazy,"
"Swear like crazy."
"Like crazy" means
the actor is expected to overact
and make up for an empty scene.
Scenes that should be
carefully thought through and developed
are reduced to one very lazy direction.
Why should an actor work like crazy
over such lazy writing?
There are quite a few parts like this
that pretend there's substance
and gloss over it.
If you strip them away,
you'll see
the emptiness underneath.
This isn't the time to argue about
whether the protagonist should be female.
When unpleasant emotions surface…
try to pin them down precisely right then
so they don't get out of hand.
The feeling of having been attacked.
Even if it's an idiom, don't use it
if you're not familiar with it.
Fear.
And then
examine the root.
What is the root of this emotion?
This is what beginners do.
However…
I will not die.
I'm not someone…
who can be killed by your words.
It's okay.
I understand.
You don't have to explain.
I hope you know
that I really enjoyed working with you.
Whenever I tried to write,
it felt like 100 people
were waiting in line to criticize me.
But seeing you get excited
over my writing and ideas,
I thought,
"Hey, I guess I'm not bad at writing."
I'm enjoying writing again,
like a teenage girl.
All right, I'm off to choir practice.
I've been trying too hard for a while,
so I'm just going to pretend to sing
and ride on their coattails.
Being a writer is really brutal.
You're on your own from the start,
so you can't ride on anyone's coattails.
In our next life,
let's just do something
where we can ride on someone's coattails.
I'm sorry!
Promise me
that you'll take all the credit!
Don't share and claim every bit of credit!
Why did you fire Writer Park?
-Please knock before you come out.
-Why did you fire her?
Have you ever seen a bastard share credit?
I'm writing alone and taking full credit.
All the glory and criticism
will be mine alone.
No one will say it's good
if two people write it.
Just wait.
I'll show you how ruthless
and downright dirty I can be.
I'll show you
someone who's truly filthy and vicious.
Damn it.
CEO KO HYE-JIN
I was wrong.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
You did nothing wrong.
I was wrong.
I'll just
aim for third place.
I may not be able to take first place…
but I can take third.
Those are pretty.
Why don't you wear heels?
Because it feels rude.
The clicking sounds.
It attracts attention.
But that's why you wear them.
To attract attention.
You know what?
I've never seen Oh Jeong-hui
wear anything but heels,
except when she's acting.
She uses the clicking sounds
to intimidate people
and changes the atmosphere in an instant,
while exuding this energy
that she's going to win, no matter what.
That's why no one can beat her.
I respect that about her.
When I get old,
even if I don't take care of my father,
I'll take care of Oh Jeong-hui
to the very end.
You know,
like the way
you care for your grandmother.
What does it mean to be impressive?
I know what it means to be cool.
What makes a person impressive?
Oh Jeong-hui said
her biological daughter was impressive.
What does it mean to be impressive?
Huh?
What's wrong?
What is it?
I'm Byeon Si-on.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
It's a good thing
I didn't raise you.
You turned out well.
Thanks.
WEATHER MAKER
BY HWANG DONG-MAN
Hello, sir.
Hey.
Are you sure
we can start shooting next year?
Yes, I'm sure.
All right.
I'll postpone Director Park Jin's film
and do yours first.
Thank you!
Focus.
And be ready, Hwang Dong-man.
Yes, sir! Hwang Dong-man reporting!
I'll focus and be ready, sir!
Will do, sir!
My film's going into production.
Noh Kang-sik will be in it.
I think spring is coming.
HYOWON MANSION
I'm going to be busy now.
I might not make it home often.
But I'll call every day.
What's your purpose in life?
Humor.
I'm just going to live life
with a sense of humor.
You passed.
KICKOFF CEREMONY FOR A SAFE SHOOT
AND GREAT SUCCESS FOR WEATHER MAKER
I had no idea I'd see that leather coat
even in the middle of summer.
WEATHER MAKER
WRITTEN &amp; DIRECTED BY HWANG DONG-MAN
KICKOFF CEREMONY FOR A SAFE SHOOT
AND GREAT SUCCESS FOR WEATHER MAKER
Hello, everyone.
I'm Director Hwang Dong-man.
Hwang Dong-man!
I'm honored to be working with you.
I just have a few words to say.
First off,
-let me tell you a story about this coat.
-Goodness gracious.
-This took part in World War II…
-Come on!
Is there anyone here who doesn't know?
Please just listen.
-There's a twist.
-That damn bastard.
Do whatever you want.
I bought this at a flea market
when I went to the Berlin Film Festival
and was told that it was worn
by a Russian soldier during World War II.
I thought if I wore the clothes of someone
who stood in the center of history,
maybe I could step into history myself.
I paid a fortune for it
and made a point of wearing it
for every important occasion.
Then I got into a life-or-death fight
with someone I absolutely hated,
and it got torn.
Oh boy.
That's when I saw
a date clearly stamped into the leather.
It said 1998.
That's right. I was scammed.
Of course.
So did I lose my affection for this coat?
Nope.
This coat
came with a story full of twists,
so I ended up loving it
even more and more and more and more.
This is what we do. Storytelling.
We love,
we get hurt,
and we regret.
We might as well be dead without stories.
We got it, Director Hwang.
Keep it short!
Okay.
My brother
doesn't watch movies.
Even when his younger brother
pitches an absolute fit to make a movie,
he doesn't care.
He doesn't watch them.
He said
he doesn't like stories.
All stories
are just cries that we exist.
"I exist in such a painful way."
"I exist in such a sad way."
"I exist in such a depressed way."
"I exist in such a humorous way."
We get 100 years at best.
Everything disappears in 100 years…
so does anything truly exist
if it disappears?
To lay those doubts to rest…
you end up desperately writing stories.
-We're in sync.
-In sync.
If you have to write stories…
for as long as you live…
you might as well make them humorous.
I couldn't live that way…
but you can live with humor.
We'll run into many obstacles
while filming,
but I'll barrel through them
like a maniac!
Thank you!
Make it big!
Quiet on set!
I don't know how far this film will reach,
but I'm praying with all my heart.
I hope it never wounds anyone.
I hope it can make a sad person smile…
Ready.
-…if only for a moment.
-Scene 23, shot 1, take 1.
I hope it becomes a moment
that opens someone's heart.
Action.
Two, three, up!
NAM GYU-CHEOL
The person you are trying to reach
is on another call.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
Charges will apply once you are connected.
NAM GYU-CHEOL
I'm sorry, Jin-man.
I won't ask for this kind of favor again.
It's just that there isn't a poet like you
that I know of.
It was announced as two hours,
but you can just do one.
Poet Hwang Jin-man,
I heard critics were very excited
when you made your literary debut.
But…
it's been ten years
since your last poetry book came out.
I'm curious why you stopped writing.
I heard you've been drifting
between manual labor jobs.
Is it that
you don't have much to write about?
Or that a welder who writes poetry
is more striking than just a poet?
Are you trying to give your identity
a stronger presence?
I'd like to know.
What does "drifting" mean?
"Drifting."
"To move from place to place
without deciding on a destination."
I've decided.
It's welding.
When there's no work,
I harvest napa cabbage and radishes.
It's fine to move from place to place
without deciding on a destination.
I shouldn't get hung up
on words like this,
but the fact that I still do
means I have a ways to go.
This is what I don't like.
I don't like the distorted view
that poets who become welders
do it to build some special identity.
If that's such a great identity,
then let's all just quit
and become welders.
To be honest…
I like welding more than poetry.
I guess I should say
it suits me better.
Writing poetry was a continuous cycle
of frustration and self-loathing.
But with welding…
I just keep running the torch,
and it gets the work done.
My mind isn't restless.
When I put the welding rod down
and walk away,
all sorts of thoughts
come rushing back again.
But while I'm welding, they don't surface.
It feels like I'm resting
for the first time.
I'm working,
but it feels like resting.
So yes.
I like welding
more than poetry.
Hello.
It's been a long time.
Excuse me.
What is it now?
Did Dong-man ask you to check
whether I'm drinking?
No.
It's not that.
I have some fans overseas.
So?
I heard some things,
so I posted something on social media
to look for Yeong-sil.
I'm sorry I did that without asking first.
But I received a DM
from someone in Finland.
They say their child was born in 2012,
and her name is Hwang Yeong-sil.
I deleted part of her first name,
and only mentioned her
as "Hwang Blank-sil,"
but they replied with the exact full name,
"Hwang Yeong-sil."
Spring always waits
It waits for the first snow
It waits for the autumn sky
It waits for every season
But it's right now
Spring, summer, fall, winter
It's all right now
Leaves move in the wind
Flashing white
As they turn
DIRECTOR HWANG DONG-MAN
Don't freak out, okay?
Apparently,
Dong-man has gone quiet.
I think he's having a mental breakdown.
None of the scenes are going as planned,
and the crew
is starting to lose faith in him,
so Noh Kang-sik has been giving cues
and running the set for the past few days.
Directors go through this sometimes.
It's not unusual, but…
I was just wondering how to handle this.
Hey, you.
Get up.
Listen.
Do you want to die by my hand today,
or do you want to film?
Choose one or the other.
Do you want to film?
Or do you want to die?
Or do you want to die, you bastard?
If you have to write stories
for as long as you live…
Start filming already, you bastard!
Start filming!
If you have to write stories…
for as long as you live…
Crazy bastard.
Ready.
Action!
Do you know
what weather is?
Do you know how terrifying…
uncontrollable nature can be?
I like how uncontrollable things
exist
in the world.
It makes me feel like…
I might be
something uncontrollable
as well.
It makes me feel like
I might be something…
uncontrollable as well.
-Please enjoy!
-Thank you.
-I had to sit, but--
-Let's hit ten million!
What did they say about the movie?
-Well, they…
-Oh man.
I finally adjusted to digital from film.
But what the hell?
Now it's AI.
So I thought long and hard
about whether to give up,
but today,
I saw Dong-man's film and made a decision.
AI era or not,
I'm going to keep writing.
I'll keep writing to the end,
and keep filming to the end!
Let's do it!
That was great. Well said.
Hwang Dong-man.
I knew you'd turn out--
Don't say you knew I'd turn out well!
You guys know, right?
I never miss out on a sure bet.
Let's sign a contract!
I'll pay you top rate.
You're annoying to the very end.
I love you.
I love you!
What an amazing guy.
He pulled it off!
What the heck?
What is it?
Do you want to have conversations
with me now?
You know what?
I love this bastard.
I think I can even kiss him.
Stop it!
What's wrong with you?
Hey, Gyeong-se.
So? Do you like the movie?
-I love it.
-Yeah?
You know, Dong-man told me
the protagonist is you.
What?
"A sentimental punk
who can't be ruthless when it counts
and ends up perishing."
He said that's you.
I've acted a lot in my life,
but I never thought I'd act out your life.
Sir, I've written 14 screenplays
over the past 20 years.
Twelve of them are about Park Gyeong-se.
He's the most pathetic,
and the most…
lovable guy in the world.
Just you wait.
There are 11 more Park Gyeong-se stories
yet to come out.
Do you know The Lustful Bottle Opener
is about you?
Hey, I'm not that pathetic!
It's about you.
No, it's not!
Now that we're on the same level,
are you ready for some roasting?
-I sure am.
-Are you ready?
I sure am. Are you ready?
All right, then. Ready, action!
There's this scene
where Mr. Noh meets Yeong-hun.
As he ran, I wanted to follow him
with a Steadicam like this,
but the DP insisted on
using a camera dolly
and following horizontally.
And you know
Mr. Noh does whatever he wants.
So he just goes to the front, and the DP
had laid out the camera dolly until…
I wish I could spend my whole life
just watching you.
Hey, that's nothing!
-Remember that car explosion scene?
-Yeah.
Even if you don't create anything great…
Cut. Okay!
It's always comedy with you, like now.
Even when you step into a burning pit,
it's still comedy.
And the makeup team.
-Wait, wasn't it Jun?
-Yeah, Jun!
Depressing stories,
sad stories,
tragic stories…
I want to keep watching you
turn everything into a comedy.
The 48th Korean Film Awards
Best New Director Award goes to…
Hwang Dong-man for Weather Maker!
48TH KOREAN FILM AWARDS
BEST NEW DIRECTOR AWARD
Congratulations, Hwang Dong-man!
Jin-man!
I won an award!
You can look me up online now!
Yeong-sil!
You can look up your uncle online now!
Eun-a!
Thank you so much
for being with me.
From here on,
I'll work even harder!
Thank you!
WE ARE ALL TRYING HERE
Ready.
Action.
Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim