( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
You need to take the kids to Khanin.
He'll take you all to a hiding place.
- Mom!
- No!
Dad!
Dad, look out!
If you want Fire Phoenix
to help you, it'll cost you.
They can take my life.
We'll hunt them down together.
Even if they hide in the shadows,
Fire Phoenix needs to be exposed!
Naruban
is the keyman who's under
Fire Phoenix's protection.
He's a businessman
who'll change the world for the better.
Equality and justice
will come.
Tell Mom I miss her, Dad.
I offered alms
for your wedding anniversary this morning.
Hello!
Hi! It's me again,
your favorite seller, Aru!
Today I've got Korean-style outfits
for you all.
Hurry before someone preorders them.
Whoa, five viewers now! Okay!
Mr. Handsome.
You can buy it for your girlfriend,
or even your mother.
Saranghaeyo.
Does anybody want this dress?
It's so pretty, and form-fitting too.
Okay, looks like no one wants it yet.
I have to take a break now.
All that selling got me hungry.
Watch out for the street cameras.
Where's the designer
you wanted to proudly present?
He turned off his phone.
- Someone's inside.
- How's that possible?
Last time I went there,
it's an abandoned house.
Someone wants what's inside the house too.
The intel Inspector Phumin had
contains evidence on who's involved
with Fire Phoenix.
Maybe Fire Phoenix
already sent someone there before you.
I didn't see their face, though.
You don't have to go there anymore.
I'll keep watch.
You'd do better at 3C, where you can go
in and out without suspicion.
Please thank Pat for me, Sun.
She helped pay off Scene's medical fees
and your dad's gambling debt.
We never could've paid it all off
in our lifetime.
I'll get going then, Mom.
If you need anything, call me.
I'll be going now, okay?
Bye.
Two hot chocolates, please.
If you aren't ready to be my present,
we can stay in the past for now.
ARU
I'll always love you and understand you.
How'd it go with your mom and sister?
Pretty good.
My mom said she really appreciated
what you did.
I'm just glad to see you happy.
Sure.
Won't you read that text?
ARU
Shameless bitch!
Pat, don't!
- Sun!
- Who are you?
Why'd you text my boyfriend?
Do you wanna die?
Let me warn you again,
if you don't want any trouble,
stop pestering me and my girlfriend,
or I'll call the cops.
Sun--
I blocked her.
Pat,
there's really nothing
going on between us.
Please, don't worry.
Pat.
I promise you're my only one.
Don't be mad. I'm sorry.
Please.
I have a cute boyfriend.
Of course I'd be jealous.
You're the sweetest.
Hot chocolate helps with sadness.
Thank you, Rin.
Thank you for being a true friend
when I'm at my worst.
There's a light in all of us.
That's what a friend of mine used to say.
The best friend of my life.
Rin, Rin!
Rin, where are you going?
Mr. Taiga's not here yet either.
Why aren't you here yet?
Hello.
I'm outside now. Looks like
someone got inside the house.
Okay, I'll call you back.
Sorry, I was busy with drawing yesterday,
so I didn't turn on my phone.
It's alright.
Ms. Nun's in a meeting.
She'll be back in a moment.
Ms. Atinuch,
is the aggressive security guard
not here today?
You mean Rin? She's so irresponsible.
Yesterday she took half a day off,
and today she called in sick
early in the morning.
But oh well, she did something great
that impressed the CEO,
so he promoted her so soon.
Do you happen to have her address?
Why would you need
a security guard's address?
I'd like to send her flowers.
But she's just security.
She saved me from the fire
in this building.
A bouquet of flowers
is just a small gesture.
Your heart's warmer
than any microwave, Mr. Taiga.
If I ever get sick, you can come
take care of me at my bedside.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I'm here to see
my girlfriend in that room.
I thought no one lived there.
Must be that girl I rarely see.
I think she's moved out.
You're her boyfriend.
Don't you know anything?
Excuse me.
Sorry, the number you've dialed
is currently unavailable--
If you're trying to track a woman,
there are better ways
than constantly calling her.
Rin's very careful.
You think she's with Fire Phoenix?
She's been keeping me away from Naruban,
and no one really knows her.
She acts like a shadow.
But you know a way to hunt shadows.
Dad, Nun's really crazy
about that mixed designer guy.
Who knows if she wants him
for work or for love.
Your sister's here to work.
Instead of badmouthing people,
why don't you find something better to do?
If I did her job, it wouldn't
have turned out so crappy.
Get some real work done,
and don't you cause trouble
and drain my money again.
Don't think I won't disown you
just because I love your mom!
Thank you so much
for your work today, Mr. Taiga.
My pleasure.
I don't think
I've welcomed you officially,
Mr. Taiga.
Techut,
he's my guest. Mind your own business.
That means he's
Cosmic Central's guest too, no?
As an executive,
I've got to take care of him too.
Mr. Taiga's team is leaving now.
Mr. Techut, please don't.
I didn't even do anything.
I'm just trying to greet her.
Techut.
We hired them to work for us, didn't we?
As the employer, I can talk to them.
Does anyone have a problem?
Call security!
Hey. Come with me!
Yes, you. Don't ask. Quick, follow me!
Come on, hurry!
Let go of me!
Techut, get out now!
Follow him.
Don't let him get on this floor again.
Give me the usual, quick!
‪Yes, sir.
Ms. Ratee.
How come you're serving coffee here?
Of course, I have to take care
of our VIP guest who owns the building.
I own this café.
I just bought it, actually.
Is the coffee good?
Yes.
Stop moving. You'll bruise your cheek.
It'll hurt more if you move.
Can you just stay still for a minute?
Does your arm hurt?
What happened?
I fell down the stairs.
Did you see a doctor?
Want me to take you?
Stay away from me.
Here. Your severance pay.
I warned you not to get
in the way of our bosses.
You're firing me?
But I did nothing wrong.
I even got slapped.
Listen, forget telling the police,
the Ministry of Labor,
or social media.
Take the money and find a new job.
You can have a beef with anyone,
but not Cosmic Central Group.
Take it.
I've taken care of it.
Now that she's got the money,
she'll probably go without a fuss.
This is the type of justice
good, dedicated people get.
I understand how painful it feels.
Come on, hurry!
Just tell me who you work for.
If you don't want to say it,
point at his name.
He talked, sir.
We know who the leader is now.
Who said you can get involved
in this case, Punlop?
I just followed the clues.
We've been investigating this case
for years!
- This is not your duty!
- But I think it is.
I've been tracking
those human traffickers.
I'm sorry, sir.
I just don't want Thailand
to be a channel for human trafficking.
They treat people worse than animals.
They beat them, rape them, and kill them.
They don't have any mercy.
If we call our country
"The Land of Buddhism"
while we turn a blind eye
on those monsters
and let them exploit people for a living,
then we're no different
than those monsters.
All my dedication
really backfired.
I was under investigation for embezzlement
and was about to be fired.
Then the bosses at Fire Phoenix
lent a hand and proved my innocence
so I could go back to work.
Justice…
does exist.
When you submit to no one,
you can't be a good cop
just for praise or for when
the Thai flag covers your coffin.
A cop who can sacrifice
even their own life
must live with honor,
with people appreciating them.
Rest assured, Mr. Taiga.
Rin will no longer be around to bug you.
Please give me a moment.
I need your help. Now.
What are you taking pictures for?
What the hell?!
All reporters outside,
please stop taking pictures.
Please give my client some privacy.
How'd that page get that old video?
You said every video was deleted!
Your firm gets ten million
from my dad every year!
Why'd you do such a shitty job?
Find them and sue them all!
What are you doing?
Can I help?
I like this one.
Ms. Nun!
Ms. Nun,
look.
Go check if my dad's seen it.
He probably did. Everyone's sharing it.
Here we go.
I'm getting so many notifications.
Must be all of my group chats.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Please don't read the news.
"Shocking video, billionaire's son
goes berserk at police station,
tortures women,
treating them worse than dogs."
Don't post anything.
Don't give any interviews.
Just stay as still as you can.
Let our team of lawyers handle it.
I don't know how that video got leaked.
I'm looking into it, alright!
That video's very old.
We already paid them…
We took great care
of the girls in the video.
I don't know why it still got posted.
I did everything I could.
I don't want people to associate
Cosmic Central with Techut.
You did great.
Keep going, okay?
Mr. Taiga, this is my father.
Thank you for your work.
My father's a little taciturn,
but I know that he really likes you.
The members of Fire Phoenix
will pay for every life
taken from Blazing Tiger.
LEARN ABOUT FIRE PHOENIX
GLOBAL SECRET ORGANIZATION, MYTH OR FACT?
Send that designer guy
back to his country.
Ever since that Taiga came,
our company's had so many problems.
Horrible things happened
before he even came.
This happened because of Techut,
not Mr. Taiga!
Nunnapat! Since when
did you start going against me?
Then give me a reason.
A good reason, not some nonsense,
and not from some jealous guy!
Elites like you don't need love.
Prioritize your own benefit.
I'll find you a good husband,
not some weird designer like that guy.
Nun, don't talk back to your father.
Wait till he calms down first.
Weird boyfriends…
They're perfect for you.
Techut!
- Damn you, Nun!
- Techut!
Just leave. This isn't the time
for us to be fighting.
You're siblings, for God's sake.
Leave.
Weird boyfriend.
Why?
I did everything well,
but Dad never loves me.
Techut's messed up countless times,
but Dad still loves him.
Mr. Taiga treats me so well.
I love him, Mom. I love Mr. Taiga.
I understand, honey.
Love is never wrong.
Whoever you love, I'll love them too,
but you need to be patient.
We'll think of a way
for your dad to accept Mr. Taiga.
The websites she looked up…
LEARN ABOUT FIRE PHOENIX
GLOBAL SECRET ORGANIZATION, MYTH OR FACT?
…were about Fire Phoenix.
How many would you like today? Thank you.
You're gonna be late to work today.
I'm not going. I got fired.
Really?
Can I have another?
Don't hold back.
You're still here, Mr. Designer?
Are you not done
saying goodbye to my sister?
Mr. Taiga will keep working here
until our Hi app gets launched.
- That's not necessary.
- It is.
He is my personal designer, after all.
I made a contract hiring him
to be my design consultant.
Atinuch is getting his office ready.
Now Mr. Taiga can come in to work
whenever he wants.
She cares more about a guy
than her own family!
She's defying me on purpose to annoy you.
You know, yet you'll let her?
Can't you see our stock here?
I've got bigger responsibilities
than to fight over one person.
But my gut tells me
that Taiga guy's bringing us trouble.
If you want to win,
you must deal with everything yourself.
Prove to everyone
that Cosmic Central needs you.
Hello, dear customers!
Hello, hello!
And our product for today
is fermented fish!
‪Let me smell it.
The aroma's really strong!
So fragrant and appetizing.
If you want to preorder it,
do it now and you'll get this box
with ten bottles of it, as well
as ten grilled pork skewers for free!
Thank you so much, Rin.
Sales were crazy good today.
When the stuff gets delivered fast,
they preorder more.
There's a light in all of us.
I wonder who said that.
If you don't mind,
you can end your lease
and move in with me.
You can move out once you find a new job.
It'll help save money.
I don't want to bother you, Aru.
No, you won't! You said it
as if we've never helped each other.
You've helped me before, Rin.
Let me help you this time.
Yeah?
You can leave once you finish this glass.
You're getting closer to our target.
So you don't believe
that Lirin, the youngest daughter
of Inspector Phumin, is dead?
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya