Has your dad ever told you
about any cases at all?
Perhaps one about a family
that was murdered ten years ago?
Taiga! Mr. Naruban was poisoned.
You've been through a lot, Naruban.
Soon, your duty will be over,
and you'll take a long break.
That's right.
Hey! Come quick!
- The MV is out.
- Wow, so handsome.
Wow, he's cute when he does that.
- Ryu's so cute!
- Share it.
Everyone has to see this.
- Wow, so good!
- Share the song now!
- Here we go.
- He's back!
Share it!
So adorable!
Give me the song.
Hey, look!
- What should I do?
- Ryu! So cool!
- He's so cool.
- I wanna hug him!
Quick, let me take a photo too!
Ms. Atinuch , why is Ryu here
at the building right now?
Yes!
Excuse me. Can we switch?
Can I join in for a picture?
Can I get a quick photo?
Can I take a photo?
Rin, can you help get Ryu upstairs?
- Who is that?
- Ryu! Ryu Dragon!
People downstairs said Ryu Dragon is here!
Step back. I'm going down to see!
You can take it from here, Ms. Nuch.
Wait, which department do you work in?
Don't bother remembering.
I'm on my last day.
Mr. Ryu, please follow me
to the lounge, this way.
What's that woman's name?
Don't worry about her.
This way, please.
If I let an employee
who walked out keep working,
who would respect me, Mr. Taiga?
I can't just bend the rules
to satisfy one person.
Then I'll take responsibility too,
since I went with Rin.
Is one employee really worth that much?
I see everyone as equally valuable.
You don't have to break your own rules.
Just uphold them the way you want.
Don't you care how much this upsets me?
I'm sorry.
Okay, Rin can come back to work here.
Ryu! Ryu!
- Ryu!
- Is Ryu coming down?!
- Is Ryu with you?
- Ryu!
Hurry up! Someone's waiting.
Ryu's so cute.
You'll be Mr. Ryu Dragon's bodyguard
for the entire time he's in Thailand.
I've never looked after an artist before.
I don't think I'm fit for it.
You're perfect.
I've seen your skills already.
Mr. Ryu has Thai heritage.
He speaks and understands Thai perfectly.
I really'm not good at this. Excuse me.
We'll find a professional
security team instead.
I want to talk to you.
Sorry, I'm busy.
Rin, wait for me in the room.
Is this your boss?
But Ms. Nun said you could work for me.
Rin only works with people
she's comfortable with.
But it's an executive order.
I work for Hi app.
I need someone who can take care of me.
You should hire a professional.
You want to take care of an artist?
It could be fun.
I'm an artist too.
You need to be careful, Rin.
I still don't know
who put Mr. Naruban in a coma.
Who do you suspect?
I have to find them.
Mr. Taiga is our designer.
Whatever look you want,
Mr. Taiga can prepare it for you.
Mr. Ryu.
I have my own stylist.
If I can't use my own people,
I won't take this job.
Well, we've already promoted it
that you will perform
at the Hi app launch.
VIP seats are fully booked,
and all event tickets are gone.
Wait.
No woman's ever run away
from me like you did.
I'm not into stuff like this.
Sorry, I don't know how famous you are.
Try searching.
Or search the tag, Hong Kong.
That's my hometown.
Give me your phone.
I'll show you.
This is my personal number. Call anytime.
Wait!
Don't delete it.
Don't be mad yet, Aru.
I went to the warehouse. They told me,
because I really wanted to see you.
Can I come in and talk inside?
If you have something to say, say it.
I'm not free.
I have a live sale in half an hour.
I miss you.
Got it. That's it, right?
You bastard! You jerk!
Pat! Don't!
- Pat!
- You two teamed up to trick me!
- Pat, stop!
- Let me go!
Go away! Shameless!
Who are you?
Lee?
I'm not Lee, or whoever that is.
Don't come back here,
if you don't want to die. Get out!
That's enough, Pat.
Don't look, Rin.
Don't look at a fool like me.
Hey.
Te, do you want something to eat?
I can make it for you.
Have you gone to visit Dad yet?
You're not Dad's real child.
Whoa, Nun!
Nun, don't do this to your brother.
He's not my brother!
He's the troublemaker in our family.
- Te!
- Hey.
Dad hasn't even gone yet,
you're already trying to take everything?
Don't hurt your sister. Let go.
Nun!
This little thing won't kill me.
I'm not going to let you die so easily.
Just a few scars on your face,
four or five should do.
Film it and show it to any woman.
That's way more satisfying.
- Nun, don't!
- If you can't stay quiet,
then get out!
Don't drag your name
through 3C Corp. I'm building.
3C Corp. you're building?
You dare compare yourself to Dad?
Nun, let it go.
Why cry, Mom? Tears don't help.
Only standing up and fighting
will make life truly yours.
This year, we're planning an event,
Super Global App.
First up,
a uniform makeover
by the renowned Japanese designer
Mr. Taiga.
Next up
is a concert by Mr. Ryu Dragon,
the idol from Hong Kong,
livestreaming fun to the world
through the Hi app.
I'll send the files
of the songs I perform.
Everyone on the team must be my people.
I want to know who's in the VIP seats,
where my official fan club sits,
and most importantly,
I need VVIP-level care
throughout the work here.
We understand the requirements.
We'll arrange everything accordingly.
Anything else?
It's my show. I'm using my own team.
No clothes or accessories
from anyone else,
not a single piece.
I'm handling the 3C Corp. uniforms
because I want to.
I'm not working on the concert.
And if I had to,
I'd have to refuse.
Alright, that's settled.
The two events won't be combined.
Separate events, separate promotion.
Everyone, please enjoy
some snacks and tea
in the lounge, this way.
This way, please.
After you.
I'm flying back today.
You can handle the rest with my assistant.
That's so on-brand.
Ryu Dragon, the bad boy idol.
YOUNG COP TAKES BRIBES
CHASING QUICK RICHES
YOUNG OFFICER KHANIN CAUGHT
IN HUMAN TRAFFICKING NETWORK
Are you sure about this information,
Dhammatat?
I never mess up on intel.
Khanin is a cop
tied to a human trafficking gang.
Then he got fired.
He was your mom's ex
before she married a businessman,
Prin, your father.
Khanin is a member of Fire Phoenix,
just like Naruban.
Let's go.
NARUBAN ASAWAWONG
Dad, are you faking being sick?
I just want to know who's really my enemy.
Now you see who you can trust
and who you need
to get rid of immediately.
Yes. Nun always tries to take your place.
You have to prove everything.
Show everyone clearly
that you're the superior one.
BRUTAL KILLING, YOUNG 3C CO-FOUNDER
SHOT MULTIPLE TIMES
THREE SONS MISSING
Naruban, Khanin, and Prin
are members of Fire Phoenix.
I visited Naruban.
He's not sick! He's fooling all of us.
His son's the one in charge of everything.
Not Nunnapat?
His daughter? Why?
Why doesn't Fire Phoenix
let women hold power?
I don't know!
You think I'm part of Fire Phoenix?
No.
I just thought you might know
more than me.
Ryu Dragon fan meet tickets.
None.
What about photos?
Autographs? The pen he used,
or a cup he drank from,
even a tissue would do.
You've got to give me something!
There's nothing.
- Take that!
- Ow!
No way!
No way! How could you
forget your friend like this?
- Did you hide it?
- Well.
- Really, there's nothing.
Where did you put it? Tell me!
- Where did you put it?
- You won't find it.
Are you feeling better now?
Still a bit weak.
Good that it wasn't serious.
You probably thought
I was on the verge of death.
Well, I didn't know.
When I got to the hospital,
you didn't look well.
Nun, it's good
that your father's recovering now.
I want to go home.
I think you should stay here a bit longer
and get checked.
You're still not fully recovered.
I'm going home.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
The person who must die,
Taiga.
Are you feeling better now?
Yeah.
I can't stay in the hospital too long.
I'm worried about work.
What did the doctor say?
Same as before,
stress and not enough rest.
Good that it wasn't serious.
Seeing you reminded me of my father.
He never got sick.
Until one moment of pain took his life.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You know?
Death is closer than we think.
So close that sometimes
you don't even notice
which direction the strike will come from.
Only cowards
get shaken by the word "death".
But my father always said death
is the fairest judgment.
I don't agree with your father.
Words are the real judgment.
Words can build someone,
destroy someone,
even crush a person alive.
Coffee, sir.
You came at the perfect time.
You can call me anytime.
I was waiting outside the room.
You're close with Taiga, right?
No, I'm not.
I've seen Nun get annoyed
about you and Taiga.
It's nothing. I'm just doing my job.
Then I have one more task for you.
Don't tell me you're secretly complaining
that I'm giving you too much to do.
No, I'm happy to do it for 3C Corp.
You can give me orders anytime.
Besides looking after me,
I want you to keep an eye on Taiga
and report everything he does.
I'll make sure you get close to him.
Don't worry about what Nun thinks.
Yes, sir.
My job is to observe,
manage, and take care
of everything perfectly.
Your person is such a mess.
- I had Rin handle it myself.
- But it's not her job.
It is!
Because it's a task I assigned.
You like that designer.
You're crazy about him
and would do anything to keep him.
You've never cared, never even noticed?
Since he came to 3C Corp.,
it's been nothing but trouble.
But all of that is because of Te,
not because of Taiga.
You'd still favor an outsider?
You could trade an executive position
just for one man, Nun.
I can always promote
someone more suitable,
because I don't play favorites.
I only care about the work
and the profits 3C Corp. will make.
What do you think you're doing?
Even with my father backing you,
don't think I can't find a way
to get rid of you.
I've caused you trouble again, haven't I?
I'm fine. Don't overthink it.
You're full, your brain's probably racing.
Better go back to work on the uniforms,
Mr. Designer.
Check out the photos I sent
and bring her to me.
I want to talk to this girl privately.
Quick!
Hey! What are you doing?
Help! Somebody help!
Hey, don't come any closer!
- What are you doing?
- Run!
- Are you okay?
- Aru!
Aru!
Hello.
What?
Just one woman and you couldn't catch her?
Did your parents even give you a brain?
Aru.
This is your mom's house.
Sit down first.
Mom isn't home.
She took my sister to the doctor.
I didn't know where else to take you,
so I brought you here.
But what were you doing there?
I…
I missed you, Aru.
I just wanted to see you
and apologize.
Aru.
Can you just listen to me this once?
And I won't hold onto you anymore.
Please.
This house is mortgaged.
But I'll take care of everything.
Thank you so much, Miss Pat.
No worries. We're family, after all.
We take care of each other.
Miss Pat must be really kind
to your mom and sister, right?
I can never repay Miss Pat for anything.
Except with your own body.
But honestly,
she's kind of pitiful too, Aru.
Because you're the only one
always by her side,
following her wishes,
the only one she holds onto.
You can be angry or hate me
however you want,
but I really can't abandon her.
I don't want to be cruel
to a woman who's been good to me.
- Sun!
- Aru.
Sun!
Let me stay like this for just a minute.
Just one minute.
Like a couple.
Oh, how did the power go out?
The fuse blew.
Then go replace it.
Okay, just a moment.
Miss Nun, take a break.
I'll bring you some water.
Who sent you in here?
This isn't your business.
Mr. Naruban.
Mr. Taiga, the outfit looks amazing.
Thank you.
Mr. Taiga.
Do you like it?
It's okay.
I thought you'd say you like it.
Who let someone unrelated into this room?
I want you to be my model.
The tears today, they'll turn into a fire
that will burn the enemy
until not even a soul remains.
Buy his trust first, Rin.
Act like bait,
draw everything out of him,
then deal with him.
Taiga!
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn