Greeting me with a bullet, huh, Khanin?
It's the best way to greet an old boss.
It's about damn time you took
responsibility for everything, Punlop.
Pok, Prab, Pun.
- You know this family?
- This kid is me.
I'm the only son who survived.
If we get it wrong two more times,
we're locked out for good.
INSEETHONG FARM
Maybe the answer lies in there.
Mine, in exchange.
Hey!
I'm deleting it.
So you're scared of me?
Looks like there's nothing left here
that's tied to the case.
What did you expect to find?
Whoever killed my real family.
I didn't want revenge.
I just wanted to reclaim my life.
Good morning.
Do you have plans for today? If not,
you're welcome to join
the barbecue at my house.
Listen, avoid using pesticides
or chemical fertilizers that boost growth
to make sure our consumers are safe.
If you run out of herbal pesticides,
we can always give you one.
Okay.
- Are they freshly picked?
- Yes.
- Ah, they look great.
- From the farm.
- This one too, right?
- Yes.
Your fever's gone.
Have you treated your wound?
I did it myself already.
Are you hungry?
Someone invited us to lunch.
It was Mr. Indhorn,
the son of the farm’s owner.
Welcome to Inseethong Farm,
Mr. Taiga, Ms. Rin.
Thank you.
It's so lovely here.
What about Mr. Narumit?
He's got to rest.
He can only walk outside
for a few hours each day.
Kids, feel free to come
get more anytime, okay?
Come on. Let's go.
And this is Piyanuch,
my dear mother.
Hello.
After my dad was in a head-on car crash,
he was in a coma for a year.
He only just got well enough to come home.
Come on, honey. Let's not bring up
such serious topics with the guests.
Right? It's no fun, right?
Please, help yourselves. Dig in.
We made plenty of food.
Go ahead.
So you two work in Bangkok?
Yes, we sell products.
- Please dig in.
- Take it if you can!
Give it to me!
- Give it!
- No way!
Give me that.
Are you okay?
Stop it! What's all this about?
Why are you fighting over it?
Wanna go inside, honey?
I'm fine, Mom.
Go get some rest, okay? Trust me.
Please excuse us.
Get some rest.
Everyone here is ill.
What's the map telling us to do?
Have you noticed anything strange?
Nothing related to 3C.
Mr. Taiga's work sure is interesting.
When are we getting our uniform?
I've been rushing him.
I hope it'll be done
before the Hi app's debut.
As if that could happen.
One minute he's working,
and the next he's gone.
- Techut!
- Hey.
Maybe he's got private matters.
We already found
a great designer, so why don't we
just be patient?
Some things take time.
Oh. Are you running a charity, Mom?
And here I thought 3C was a business.
It's true, I've never run
a business before.
Raising both of you has taken up
enough of my energy and brainpower.
Bring Taiga back to work.
He may be an artist,
but he's on our payroll.
He should learn to be responsible.
I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT OUR UNIFORM
- Let me take care of your wound.
- Don't.
Yes?
I was worried, so I came to check on you.
Someone was watching us.
Who? This place has security 24/7.
Has there been a problem
or a murder case at this farm?
Do you two know something?
I work at 3C.
Uncle Naruban…
So he sent you two.
That's not it.
We've been uninvolved
with him for a while.
After my dad had a car accident,
Uncle Naruban cut ties with our family.
I used to be a policeman.
But the accident changed my life.
I'm inside now. Our latest lead
is that he captured illegal workers here.
I found them. They aren't illegal workers.
They're kids. They're probably
selling them.
I'm saving them.
Don't be afraid.
I'm a cop. I'm here to help you.
I'll free you all.
Escape with your friends.
There are police waiting outside.
Go. Go!
Kid,
why are you still here?
Run as fast as you can.
Let's go.
Time's up.
Indhorn!
Indhorn! What's wrong?
Tell me. What's wrong?
Indhorn. Tell me, honey.
Indhorn, what's wrong?
I've had an untreatable chronic headache,
so I had to quit being a police officer.
I couldn't keep my job and had to run
this farm instead of my dad.
Has your dad ever told you
about any cases at all?
Perhaps one about a family
where the parents and three children
were murdered ten years ago?
Let me take you back to your house.
That's alright.
My workers are waiting for me.
As for the case,
I'll ask my old workers for you.
You should watch the sunset.
It's so pretty. See?
There's a pretty view in front of me.
Why should I look elsewhere?
I'm not anyone's view.
I'm not pretty to anyone either.
As humans, we tend to deny and deceive.
Maybe you met a bad person.
Maybe.
Until I found you.
I might be the most horrible person
you've ever met.
I'll wait till that day comes,
when you'll be
the most horrible toward me.
When I was little,
I was so afraid of the water.
My dad knew,
yet he threw me in the sea.
And so I could overcome the darkness,
the fear in my heart.
Don't make me turn on you here.
Horses like to eat fresh grass
because it's high in protein.
They can eat it frequently, even 24/7.
Twenty-four seven?
If they were humans,
they'd die from eating that much.
That's why they always get gassy.
Do you want them to relax
and train their muscles?
Get seated properly.
Or you'll break your back or a bone.
We're gonna be here for several more days.
Rin.
Can I
join you up there?
Boss, are you… Somebody help!
Boss, Boss!
Taiga!
Mr. Naruban was poisoned.
We can't let this slide. Dad got poisoned.
God gave us a brain.
Learn to use it, Techut.
If word gets out,
both our stocks and the 3C-Coin
will plummet.
You care about money more than your dad?
You ungrateful daughter!
If you're such a great son,
is that all you can think of?
If you're so smart,
why don't you tell me who poisoned him?
Think before you talk.
If you act on impulse,
we're all going down.
Stop! Listen to me.
Don't let anyone know your dad is sick.
He's just hospitalized
because he had a heart attack
and the doctor wanted him
to rest and recover here.
Who would buy that?
Who wouldn't buy it?
Convince everyone
that that's the case, okay?
DR. THANADOL SRISATHUWAT
NARUBAN ASAWAWONG
Don't think you can do anything
because Mom always backs you up.
Even if Dad becomes a vegetable
for ten or 20 years,
3C will never fall into your hands.
Looks like I'm not the one
who's the ungrateful child.
You've been through a lot, Naruban.
Soon, your duty will be over,
and you'll take a long break
with no more worries.
Mr. Taiga.
How's Mr. Naruban doing?
Leave.
Don't blame her.
I took her out to handle something.
And it's more important
than your work at 3C?
It was.
May I go see Mr. Naruban?
Sure.
I'm sure he knows
how worried you are.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Mr. Naruban's doing better now.
A tough man like him
won't go down so easily.
Where's my souvenir?
Next time, okay?
I'm mad.
Just kidding. Go get some rest.
Rin, come look at this.
What's that?
There's one on this shoe too.
You don't need to put a tracker on me.
You sent someone
to follow me to the farm, didn't you?
I had to, Rin,
because if something happens to you
while you're with Taiga,
I should know first.
I'd do anything to protect you
because I've entrusted you
with watching over Mr. Naruban,
the keyman of Fire Phoenix.
Although something bad happened to him
while you're with Taiga…
Hurry and find out who poisoned him.
Think.
Look deeper. Who'd benefit
the most from it?
Currently, 3C Group has taken
a few hits to its reputation,
which directly affects our credibility.
I’d like your approval
to fast-track the Hi app launch
and for me to lead 3C Group
into its next generation.
You called an executive meeting
without me?
Techut, they're all senior executives.
Well, as a senior, do you ever care
about a junior like me?
Techut, apologize to them now.
Now.
Techut! Techut!
- Techut, let go of me!
- Mr. Techut!
Let go of her, Mr. Techut.
That hurts! Techut!
I'm alright. Thank you, sir.
I'd like to apologize
on my brother's behalf.
I'm really sorry.
Should I call an ambulance
or arrange for your funeral?
So, let's continue
with our meeting, shall we?
What'd you get from Mr. Narumit's farm?
Everything surrounding Rin is suspicious,
but there's no evidence at all.
Could it be that love's blinding you?
Okay, maybe it's not love.
Maybe it's empathy,
sympathy, or intimacy.
They can all blind you.
They're emotions.
They're not facts or data.
You're an artist, so you're sensitive
when it comes to emotions.
If your opponent knows
that is your weakness,
they might take advantage of it.
I know what I'm doing.
Just zip it.
No one would admit they've fallen
for a girl's charms anyway.
I'm not blaming you, I'm just saying.
Either way, the one
we should worry about the most is--
Rin.
I'm sure you're aware of your misconduct.
Not coming in due to personal matters,
neglecting my dad during your work hours.
We won't compensate you a single baht.
We can even sue you.
What will you do first?
Are you firing, suing, or killing me?
That'd be a waste.
But you've done it before.
Firing me because you're scared.
Watch your mouth. No one can help you now.
If you hate me, fire me.
Don't act like a spoiled brat.
I bet no one's dared to tell you
how obnoxious that is.
Damn you, Rin!
I want to talk to her in private.
Nun!
He's not my brother.
He's just the troublemaker of our family.
Khanin is one of Fire Phoenix' members…
…just like Naruban.
The one who has to die…
…is Taiga.
Death is so close to us.
So close that sometimes
we forget to watch out
which direction
we're getting stabbed from.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya