This is the information Dad kept.
The Blazing Tiger gang in Japan,
they oppose Fire Phoenix.
They killed our people.
I shot Rin myself.
I told you I wouldn't let Fire Phoenix go,
but you saved Rin and returned her to 3C.
Rin is with Fire Phoenix.
She was ordered to protect Naruban,
and Punlop commanded her to do everything.
Exactly. That's his nature!
He makes everyone a victim,
then tramples his way to the top.
He abandons his subordinates,
destroys everything
to avoid getting caught,
and rises to power with protection.
He's untouchable.
Taiga.
If this keeps up,
one day Rin will die because of him.
He kills anyone who's no longer useful.
But if you care about Rin…
turn the enemy into our side.
We'll take revenge, unmask them…
destroy Fire Phoenix by any means.
But I'm asking you, Khanin.
Don't hurt Rin.
Alright.
I won't touch Rin.
From now on, her life is yours.
Hey.
How's the wound? Want to see a doctor?
I went to the clinic nearby.
Mr. Taiga has disappeared,
hasn't come to 3C Corp. at all.
Did he do anything to you?
I don't mean anything bad.
I just mean,
did Mr. Taiga help you
and ask anything?
Or did you two argue?
Why did he suddenly disappear?
Nothing happened.
Okay.
Oh, I'll tell you first. On weekends,
I'll be doing live sales.
Right now at 3C Corp.,
I'm just gathering info.
Info?
What info?
Everything about 3C Corp.
But Techut said
I'd work in my specialty field.
Next week, I'll probably move
to a new department.
He's rushing to set up this department
and managing everything himself.
Be careful.
I can handle myself.
You stay safe too.
I was worried about you.
Where have you been?
I was hurt, but I've recovered.
What about you, Uncle?
I can handle myself,
you know that.
My dad's hard drive.
FIRE PHOENIX CASES
FIRE PHOENIX CASES 2
Rin.
Did you dare lie to me?
I lost it when we split up.
I went over every inch,
but couldn't find it.
I'm going to kill Taiga.
Are you sure, Rin?
I'll kill Taiga with my own hands.
Do you trust me, Uncle?
Fine.
Taiga's life is yours.
Kill him.
Then return to protect Mr. Naruban,
so he can work
for the future of everyone in the world.
Sorry for coming into this room.
You can come here anytime.
Is your wound still hurting?
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Take care of yourself.
Fingerprint accepted.
What's this?
Work here. No need to contact anyone.
Do your own job,
get paid, spend, relax.
Here. Change into the uniform too.
Okay.
Dad has a new project,
called 3C We Share.
It provides clothes
for underprivileged kids
and make outfits for bedridden patients
in nursing homes,
all requested through the Hi app.
So you want me to design the outfits?
Yes.
But you don't have to use the Kenji brand.
It can be a collaboration
between 3C Corp. and you.
How about that?
Sounds good.
I'd like to give back to society too.
Deal.
Come in.
Is there something you need me to do?
At that desk,
take notes on the chemists' reports
and summarize them for me.
Okay.
But if you're lazy, bored,
or tired of hard work
and want an easier task…
just call me.
Okay.
Thank you. I'll remember that.
I'll start working now.
Yeah.
I pumped the coin and made enough profit
to hire five more top chemists.
How much longer for the experiments?
Depends on how much we invest.
How many more millions?
No need, Dad.
I told you, the profits from our coins
are enough to invest plenty more.
The part your sister's overseeing
is doing well.
The news is even attracting
more investors.
If you want to dominate the world,
just wait a bit.
I'll give you more than that small app.
I'll put the whole world in your hands.
Alright.
Thanks. See you tomorrow.
Hello.
Oh, I just got home.
The report, right?
I'll send it right away.
I'm about to go into my room.
I'll send it as soon as I get to my room.
Not too long. Just a sec, please.
Sure, of course.
Got it.
Okay, sure.
Techut definitely has people watching me.
Honestly, I have no idea what he's testing
under the building.
If we could just get one sample.
That's nearly impossible, Rin.
Everyone who goes there gets checked,
both coming in and going out.
They'd strip-search anyone if they could.
I'll act compliant and make sure
I don't raise suspicion.
If I get the chance,
I'll get it out for you.
Drive me. I'm going
to have lunch with Mr. Eric.
Yes, sir.
Interesting.
It's a good project. Start it right away.
Thank you, Dad.
You've helped 3C Corp. in many ways.
Do you like Thailand?
Do you want to stay here permanently?
Not yet, sir.
Once I finish work here,
I'll go back home.
Don't you ever think
of making Thailand your home?
For me, a home
isn't just land or buildings.
A home means the people
you live your life with.
I hope you find your warm home here
in Thailand soon.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Let's go.
Where are they going?
I've seen them leave many times already.
Bathroom. Food poisoning
started yesterday.
I see.
You're working so hard!
So tough, not stopping at all.
It's a rush job.
Carry on then. I won't bother you.
How are you? Tired?
I'm okay.
There's a lot of paperwork.
I'll summarize it quickly.
Ow!
My stomach.
Nature calls. Excuse me.
Mr. Te.
I'll be right back from the bathroom,
then we can talk.
Ow!
Mr. Techut!
- Get up, quickly!
- No, don't!
What's wrong?
My stomach hurts a little.
Still?
Want to see a doctor?
Ow!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Just need a short break.
I'll get back to work soon.
Then,
let's go have some coffee.
Okay.
Thank you.
Getting out here and smelling the coffee
already makes me feel better.
Gives me energy to work.
If you ever get bored with work,
just call me.
Well, with a boss this kind,
who'd dare get bored?
I'll work my hardest for 3C Corp.
Oh, break time's over. I have to go.
Alright.
Hello, Miss Ratee.
Hello, Mr. Techut.
After you.
I'll take care of this one.
Sure.
Back to her room as usual, sir.
Did any men come by?
No, sir.
Isn't your dad really rich?
Yes, and?
Send it to an overseas lab for testing.
I know a bit about it myself.
Better let a professional handle it.
Wow, you can count on her.
How long until we get the results?
I don't want you getting involved
with 3C Corp. like this, Ratee.
I'll do anything to help you.
Just you.
Nothing to do with Rin and the others.
Okay.
They can be a be involved a bit.
Rin probably wants to know
what they're doing in 3C Corp.'s lab.
3C Corp. has a lab?
Why has Ms. Nun never mentioned this?
This is the work of Naruban's eldest son,
whom he's backing.
It has to be connected to Fire Phoenix.
Sun.
I'm begging you.
Please leave some space
for the good memories between us.
Don't push so hard
that I have to push you away.
All this effort,
it doesn't make me feel good at all.
Calm down, Aru. Listen to me.
I'm trading
this company's coins right now.
It's 3C-Coin.
At first, I invested tens of thousands
and made hundreds of thousands in profit.
Then I invested hundreds of thousands
and got millions back.
But I'm not using the money
to make up for mistakes.
I just want you to know
I can take care of my family now.
And from now on,
if you want my help with anything,
think of me. I'll always help.
I won't bother you anymore.
I'm leaving now.
Wait, Sun.
What can 3C-Coin actually do?
Tell me.
3C Corp. uses its own coin
for everything inside the Hi app.
Soon, 3C-Coin will also be used for loans
and safe investments,
all secured with digital encryption.
Everything's done through a computer
that never lies.
Anyone can do it themselves.
You mean Fire Phoenix
would use 3C-Coin
to launder money illegally?
Yes.
They run it like a pyramid scheme.
Start by recruiting people
to invest in the coin,
find a credible frontman,
someone famous,
with social influence, a stock expert,
to attract investors,
and have solid backing,
like some powerful officials.
They offer insane returns,
so people stop thinking rationally,
and don't consider the consequences.
They use people's greed
to destroy their own lives.
Sun explained 3C-Coin to me.
I'm still a bit confused,
but here's what I got.
The coin makes Mr. Naruban huge profits.
But on the other hand,
it can also be used
as a channel for illegal activities,
since no one can track it yet.
Like the money used for the lab?
Exactly.
Aru, I'll ask you straight.
Yeah.
If Sun helps us…
Rin.
Are you asking to get Sun to help us too?
Rin. This is Rin.
Well, what do you need me
to help with? Just tell me.
We want to know about 3C-Coin.
In-depth, not just trading stuff.
Why do you want to know?
It's not illegal, right?
No. We're trying
to prevent illegal activities.
We want you to work for Techut.
Find the hard drive.
Anyone in the way,
kill them all.
I've got the file.
Where do you want me to deliver it?
Got it.
Hey!
Ugh!
Are you okay? Let's go.
Come here.
Hey, wait!
It's me.
Don't stay here. You'll die if you do.
Let's go.
What do they want?
Or are they after Rin?
Don't worry about anyone else. Go.
- Rin isn't anyone else! She's my friend.
- Go, Aru!
- Let me call Rin first!
- We'll deal with that later.
Whose house is this?
My house.
You said you didn't have a home.
Someone like Dhammatat
can only afford a doghouse.
Madam!
If you didn't bark for once,
you won't enjoy your meal?
Wait.
Before you two start fighting,
clarify this first.
Why am I here?
To survive.
Going to wait there
and get killed in your little hole?
Any leftover bones?
Bring them so he can gnaw a bit.
Some people just don't appreciate help.
You can stay here. This is my place.
I bought it ages ago.
No one will ever find you.
But I still have work at 3C Corp.
I'll hire a driver to shuttle you.
Get off the car
a bit away from the building,
act like you're coming
from the skytrain, then walk in.
Is it really that dangerous?
What about Rin?
Someone already helped her.
Mr. Taiga?
Yes.
- Come here.
- What?
I'm not a dog, you know.
So…
She loves Mr. Taiga?
- Yeah.
- So,
where did Mr. Taiga take Rin?
Be careful.
Thank you.
I helped you…
because you're still useful to me.
Make yourself comfortable.
Inseethong Farm welcomes you.
Thank you.
How's your father doing?
Same as usual.
He's been doing physical therapy
a lot lately,
so he can walk a few steps now.
Do you want to tell me anything?
Your person took mine.
Tell Taiga not to mess with Rin.
What if they both want to be together?
Uncle! Hey, Uncle!
Indhorn, guess I'll have
to pay you a visit, cousin.
Rin!
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn