Aru, gorgeous!
I can do a lot worse than that.
The bullets were directed at me only.
Who do you think did it?
I don't know. Do you?
My dad died because of Fire Phoenix.
Then why aren’t you searching
for the truth?
The mask contains
the code to all the information
of every member.
If we can steal Naruban's mask,
then we can get
to the core of Fire Phoenix.
Can you disable the cameras?
I can't hack it. There are
too many layers of encryption.
I think you'd better get out of there.
The restroom's not on this floor.
What are you doing up here?
What'd you plan to do in my house?
What the hell
are you trying to find here?!
Huh?!
Are you crazy?!
I'm not. You're the one who's crazy!
You're so crazy over him
that you can't even see
he only came to go to Dad's room.
You can't fool me. We installed
security cameras from every angle.
What happened?
See, Mom? He's a scumbag!
He clearly came to 3C with an agenda.
Throw him out.
Nun, take your brother outside for a bit.
Can't you see?
He's trying to go into Dad's room!
I saw him just standing still.
No. He wasn't standing there!
Techut.
I'm sorry for all the fuss
and the misunderstanding.
Taiga, let's leave.
I just got out of the restroom.
I noticed the decorating style here,
so I looked around.
I'm sorry.
We'll get going now.
Let's discuss cooking again.
That was fun.
Taiga's lying. I saw it with my own eyes.
No matter where Mr. Taiga goes,
he's still our guest.
We still need to work with him
and rely on his reputation.
Next time, don't run your mouth
unless you've got irrefutable proof.
It's okay.
I still have my café as a front
in their building,
and my dad's about to buy up 3C's shares.
Soon, I might even get an office
next to Naruban's.
Hey,
can I have one of the floors, then?
I want to lie down and chill there.
Who on earth would give you one?
You, madam. I just need one floor.
Don't be so stingy.
Or are you fake rich? Faking your wealth?
You're just faking it, aren't you?
These are the files my Dad kept.
FAMILY BRUTALLY SHOT
MULTIPLE TIMES AND KILLED IN AMBUSH
3C'S CO-FOUNDER AND HIS FAMILY
WERE CHASED DOWN, SHOT, AND KILLED
What about the other files
besides Prin's case?
I tried to open them.
Some of them required a password.
Give me the hard drive. I'll open them.
Uncle Punlop, run!
Taiga!
Stop moving.
Let's go.
You won't get lucky every time, Rin!
N - ALL FIRE PHOENIX CASE FILES
ALL FIRE PHOENIX CASE FILES 2
Thank God you got there in time,
but it won't be easy
to tap her calls next time.
Don't let anyone come.
Don't let anyone find me and Rin.
Turn off both your phone and Rin's.
I'll go talk to Aru. We'll need her help.
Deal with Ratee for me.
Change the code
on all the doors in the house too.
I'll tell Ratee you're drawing
somewhere out of town.
Thanks.
Dhammatat,
don't contact me.
I'll find a way to contact you myself.
How are you feeling?
Just hurry up and do it.
Ready?
Rin!
Why are you here?
I just wanted to talk to you, Aru.
This is my workplace.
Don't bother me like this again.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to have dinner sometime?
I'm busy, Sun. Just leave.
Anyway, I should get back to work.
Don't worry about Rin.
Taiga's taking care of her.
We should call the police!
I don't think Rin would want that.
Don't go home yet.
If you see a stranger lurking around,
call me right away.
Or just call the police,
because right now,
they'll target you for sure.
Who?
I'm not sure either,
but better safe than sorry.
It's really serious, isn't it?
Just wait for Rin to recover.
Taiga will let us know.
Rin will be just fine. Taiga will take
great care of her for sure.
Taiga's an artist.
When he works on his art,
he likes to get away from annoying people.
At least, he should've called me.
If he didn't call,
it's because he didn't want to.
Right now, he might be drawing
in some forest,
maybe Bali, Brazil, New Zealand,
or maybe he's back in Japan now.
So where is he, really?
Who is he to you?
Are you two just friends,
or more than that?
Why are you getting involved
in his business?
If you can't take it,
then stop working with him.
Easy. End of story.
When you can reach him,
tell him I need to discuss work with him.
Even if I knew, I'd never tell you.
Damn you, Dhammatat!
You'd better not be helping Taiga
lie to me.
Medical Sciences.
Your education's not bad.
I can do any job,
even if it's unrelated to my degree.
What if I can offer you a job
that's related to your degree?
I'd do it.
Are you scared of me?
I'll put you on the job you're capable of,
and if you want to keep your job at 3C
for a long time, you have to do it well.
You changed my clothes?
I had a nurse take care of your wound
and change your clothes.
Does it still hurt?
A little bit.
You got shot.
I don't know who did it.
Your fever's down.
What's the hurry?
You haven't eaten breakfast yet.
- I'm not hungry.
- You still need to eat,
so you can take your medicine.
I made it for you. You have to eat it.
I carried you through gunfire
to bring you here,
you think I'd poison you?
I don't like rice soup.
Don't like rice soup?
Or do you want me to feed you?
You can't contact Mr. Taiga at all?
He's just suddenly gone without a trace.
He turned off his phone too.
Even the team doesn't know where he is.
That's just the way artists are.
Bear with him, okay?
Why am I the one
who has to put up with him, Mom?
Because you love him
more than he loves you.
That's why Mr. Taiga
always has the edge on you.
You mix your work and personal life.
Be a little more patient.
I want you to see every side of him first.
You think he's hiding something from us?
If you learn the truth yourself,
you'll be happy
to know the man you love
better than anyone.
Why can't I contact anyone?
Have they all run off to Mars?
Ugh.
Here to find your people too, Chief?
And you're looking for revenge on me.
Killing me here wouldn't be wise, no?
I'm sure you know
I won't kill you until I've gathered
everything to expose Fire Phoenix.
Fire Phoenix won't fall
just because of me alone.
Who's Damon,
the leader of Fire Phoenix? Where's Damon?
Who are you people?
What are you doing here?
Ugh.
Security? We've got intruders
in the building. Please catch them!
Prin's whole family died.
Now the police will suspect me for sure.
A guy like you would never kill a friend.
I'm sure you'd never kill
a close friend like Prin.
Mom,
we couldn't find those two.
Are you alright, Mom?
I'm fine.
I'm going to kill them. They hurt you!
Calm down.
I'm sending the footage to the police.
We'll surely catch them.
Does it still hurt?
Please eat up.
You should eat up too.
I haven't told anyone I'm here.
You can stay here as long as you want.
You can sleep here.
I'll sleep here too.
Let go of me.
Last night, I lay here and held you.
You had a fever.
I'm fine now.
Blazing Tiger. They're a gang in Japan.
They oppose Fire Phoenix,
and they've killed our people.
Fire Phoenix will wipe them out.
We'll make sure no one survives.
Where are you going?
I need to go back to work.
Ow!
Who gave you permission?
I did.
If I don't give you permission…
Want to kill me?
Do it then!
Do it.
Your job is to kill me anyway.
I'm sending you back to 3C.
We'll act like nothing happened here.
I'm just a designer,
and you just work for 3C.
And if you still want to kill me,
go ahead.
I'll make it so that 3C-Coins can be used
to buy everything on the Hi app.
I'll make sure our coin is the only
digital currency people can use.
Find a way to make every feature
on the Hi app indispensable to everyone.
Every single feature.
3C needs to be like breath,
the very thing people depend on.
Got it.
You know Rin is part of Fire Phoenix,
and she knows you aren't just a designer.
I can't kill her.
Sometimes death isn't the solution.
You did the right thing.
She holds some very important information.
That's why she's being hunted.
You know who was gunning her down, right?
It was Khanin.
Yes.
I could hack one of the cameras
in the warehouse.
Looks like Rin isn't your only target.
Watch the previous video.
Who's that man?
Chief Inspector Punlop,
a chief who was famous
for busting a human trafficking ring.
After that, he disappeared for a while
before quickly getting promoted
and moving into policy work.
But a reliable source says
that he's tied
to several secret operations.
Don't ever mention those two people,
no matter who asks.
Madam Ratee and Aru are the only ones
who'd be desperate to know.
You should be careful too.
Even when Rin's back,
everyone will want to know
who took her away to hide.
Techut rushed to set up the department
and took control of everything.
Find the hard drive.
If anyone gets in the way…
…just kill them all.
- Thank you.
- I only helped you
because you're still useful to me.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya