( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Oh.
The websites Rin looked up
were about Fire Phoenix.
Mr. Taiga's my personal designer.
Now he can come in to work
whenever he wants.
Fire Phoenix…
will pay for every life
taken from Blazing Tiger.
Mr. Taiga, would you like anything else?
I can arrange it.
I'm so happy I get to see
your face for a long time.
Thank you very much. This is enough.
I'll have my team take over from here.
Worried I might not get it right?
You should give me some tips!
I want to have a cool style like yours.
How's the clip situation going?
Such a mood killer.
Same as always.
Everything can be solved with money.
Right now, our legal team
is digging to see
who leaked the clip.
But it's been a long time,
and there's more than one clip.
Looks like I'll have to consult with you
a lot more about this place.
Okay.
I'm more than happy!
Always ready to help, no days off.
You okay?
Someone touch you?
Whatever.
It's a way to pass the time while waiting,
and I get to stay with you too.
Thanks a lot, Rin.
- Aru.
- Yes?
The VIP wants you to dance for him.
Dance?
- Oh, I can't dance! No way.
- Come on, just a little.
Freestyle it. He's already tipped.
Help out. Please.
- Where? What?
- Right here.
Just right here.
- Right here?
- Yes.
Dance right here.
Go ahead.
- A little more.
- What?
A little more!
Hey, the guy at that table
is looking at you.
Sun, come dance with me.
No, I'll just watch you dance.
Don't you get jealous at all?
This isn't fun.
Let me sit inside.
Um…
Pat, I'm going to the bathroom.
Hurry back, Sun.
Hey!
I want to play pool.
Okay, I'll be quick.
Aru, serve the VIP room.
The regular server just called in sick.
Sure!
Sit here.
Finish this drink first, then you can go.
Yes.
Can I go now?
Wait a bit. Stay and keep me company.
Aru.
Aru!
Aru! Are you okay?
Aru, wake up!
- Sorry.
- Yes?
- Can you watch my friend for a bit?
- Sure.
Okay.
Sun, where have you been all this time?
How's your pool game, Pat?
Guess what, I pocketed a bunch of balls.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Well done!
- Let's keep playing.
Let's go.
I fired her, but Te brought her back in.
Actually, you were wrong, Nun.
Rin is doing her job very well.
You don't like her, so you're trying
to push her out for no reason.
If she takes this to court,
how much would I have to pay?
You care about a few hundred thousand,
but not how I feel?
You're going to be the boss.
Why get worked up
over a low-level employee?
You even let Taiga work in my building,
and I didn't scold you.
I agree that Rin should work here.
Her education isn't bad.
She's a university graduate.
She can handle office work.
No more problems, right?
You can use the computer, right?
Yes.
Enter the client info from the files
and send it tomorrow.
Okay.
Mr. Te took her back to work.
Ms. Nun said no, worried it'd get messy.
But she depended completely on Mr. Te.
Now what? She's gone
from security to data.
I only knew her by her name, Rin.
Never knew her full name.
Her surname?
Yes.
Rin Sinkan.
Can I see it?
These are the two daughters
of Inspector Phumin.
The older one, Mew,
is a graphic designer living abroad.
She hasn't returned since her dad passed.
The younger one is Lirin.
She drowned.
Over there.
That's the death certificate.
DEATH CERTIFICATE
LIRIN PONGRIT
STUDENT
You don't believe
that Lirin, the inspector's youngest,
is dead, do you?
Looking good.
Thanks for keeping quiet.
Yes.
Mr. Techut.
What happened?
Hold on.
Someone attacked me.
How did you get in here?
I work here.
Take me home.
Yes.
Want me to do more to repay you?
No, sir.
Just being able to work here
is more than enough for me.
You're not what you seem.
Smart, capable, and adaptable.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for anything I did wrong before.
Forget it. Life starts fresh every day.
You work for me now.
If Taiga does anything shady,
tell me everything.
That guy brings trouble with him.
Here you go.
It's 20 baht. Thank you.
Come again.
The order you placed, right?
Here are the two sets.
Thank you.
Come again!
Hello.
May I ask your name?
Sorry for the delay. I'm sorry.
I hope I won't have to bribe anyone again.
Have you been causing trouble again?
No.
I have high hopes for you.
You carry my blood.
My one true bloodline.
What about Nun?
Remember this.
You'll be the first to have everything.
Protect 3C Corp.
It's our life, mine and yours.
Aru.
Hey, why are you up so early?
Sorry, I had to move you farther.
This was the cheapest place I could find.
It's fine. Moving in together
saves on rent.
You're not mad, right?
I just suddenly asked you to move.
Is something wrong?
Nothing, I just wanted
to save up some money.
I'll go to work now.
Good luck!
Okay.
Do you have anything to request, Mr. Te?
You can also call me to the office.
I'm just here to observe.
- Observe?
- Observe the work in every department
If there's anything,
report to me in the office anytime.
- Okay?
- Understood.
The location info you filled in
on your job application is being tracked
from a phone at Cosmic Central.
You're getting close to the target.
- Hey.
- Yes?
- Who's here? Come quick.
- Okay, let's go.
- See who it is.
- Hurry!
- Hello.
Hello.
I'm Rin's friend from high school.
I heard she moved here. Is she home?
Or am I mistaken?
No, no mistake.
Rin's back sometimes, right?
Yes, but not often. She's busy with work.
Do you have a message for her?
Please tell Rin her friends miss her.
Will do.
Thank you very much.
This is Rin's house.
"A young designer,
heir to the Kenji brand,
keeps to himself,
doesn't like the spotlight."
What are you doing at 3C Group, Mr. Taiga?
Excuse me. Is Ms. Rin here?
She's out.
Is she sick?
She went to check the market.
Do you need to talk to her?
I just wanted to ask a few questions.
Please go ahead.
We're ready to answer.
No, that's okay. Thank you.
Yes.
Mr. Taiga came. He really asked about you!
Thanks! I'll bring some snacks later.
If anyone asks,
just say what you said earlier.
Rin's gone to work.
She doesn't come home often.
What's stressing you out?
If work's no fun,
want to talk about something else?
Our promise.
Ugh!
Ugh.
Thank you
for your courage,
for helping a stranger like me.
This wound
made me realize
who I love the most.
Go to France and see my Daddy, okay?
I can't go yet.
Okay.
If you want to deal
with the people who killed your father,
I'll give you six more months.
Once it's done,
we'll get married right away,
with no excuses.
I designed this suit for Mr. Naruban.
Ms. Nun.
- Ms. Nun.
- Yes?
Do you like it?
I like it!
I'll call Dad right away.
I'm not changing a thing.
I'll wear my outfit as it is.
What's your problem, Nun?
Do what I say.
If I didn't say it, don't do it.
Well, my dad…
Want me to try talking to Mr. Naruban?
He might have a different perspective
on the clothes.
If we talk, he might be more open.
Okay.
If my dad comes, I'll join in too.
What's up? Why are you braking so often?
Looks like someone's following us.
The president is here.
Thank you for working
so diligently for us.
What information did you need, Dad?
Why not call me?
Using a staff member at that level,
what would she know?
I didn't call Rin to ask about the data.
I asked her if she wants to do
another kind of work.
Work?
Bodyguard.
Dad, we have the money.
We can hire a professional anywhere!
Do you know what I just encountered?
Are you okay, sir?
I'm okay.
What about the license plate
of the car that followed you?
I checked with the deputy. It was fake.
This isn't the first time
Rin risked her life to help me.
I should promote and support those
who are brave and capable,
and not put them in a department
that doesn't suit them.
The other staff must be confused
about promotions here.
As long as I'm not confused.
Rin.
Yes, sir.
Go make a new key card
with access to all zones,
and start assisting me from tomorrow.
Yes, President.
Excuse me.
Quick reflexes, just like a bodyguard.
I messed up.
I thought following Naruban would be easy.
It's even harder now.
Rin's now his bodyguard.
Rin again?
Stressed about work, dear?
I want to get rid of one
of Dad's staff. I hate her.
She's trying to stand out
to get his attention.
And it's not just Dad.
She flirts with Mr. Taiga too.
I don't want to lose.
Hey, why are you comparing yourself
to someone at that level?
Everyone's focused on Rin.
They give her too much credit.
How about this?
Let Mr. Taiga meet me.
I can help figure out
what will make him click with you more.
Nothing can happen to Mr. Naruban, Rin.
Fire Phoenix will make this world
completely equal.
No more social inequality of any kind.
And to do this, we'll need to use
everything he has,
money and faith.
We'll tear down the rotten structures
eating this country alive.
No good cop should be bullied.
No officer should die on duty,
only to have a flag draped over their body
and a curse following them.
No more good cops
dying dishonorably, like Phumin.
Don't let anything slip by.
Find out who's attacking
and threatening Mr. Naruban.
You said manipulating the price
would be easy!
Why don't your followers
believe the rumors you spread?
I think something's off.
Someone must be acting as a major player
to crash the price this badly.
Someone with enough money
to take us down like this.
Who are you here to see?
I'm here for Mr. Taiga.
Tell him his fiancée is here.
Dad.
Don't worry.
I'll launch a new platform to raise funds.
Humans are greedy, Dad.
If we hype it in the media
and promise good returns,
even selling blank paper,
they'll give us money.
The law has loopholes
that let us profit from their greed, Dad.
Taiga, did you see the board this morning?
Stocks and 3C-Coin got smashed.
Do you know who did it?
Ratee's father.
With a pretty face and figure like yours,
you'd be better at something fun.
Please me properly, and I'll promote you.
Everything about Taiga, report only to me.
Yes, sir.
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn