Continuing from before
As the saying goes
A fearless youngster hits the county town
One phone call sparks a mix-up
The whole family jumps into action
Going all-in on nails for a brighter future
As they say
A smile melts old grudges
One laugh wipes the slate clean
But this time around
Dandan's ordeal
isn't going to be so easy to get through
Mr. Dongguo and the Wolf.
You and your mother...
You're gonna be the death of me!
You little ingrate!
It's not my fault.
Talking back now?
It's for your own good, so I'm wrong?
I mean, Mr. Dongguo was also wrong.
What did Mr. Dongguo do wrong?
He saw the wolf about to be killed by hunters,
so he saved it.
Wasn't that for its own good?
He could tell at a glance it was a wolf.
What if...
What if it was a Husky?
Full of twisted logic!
You think talking your way out
will get you off the hook?
Go!
Bring me that feather duster.
Yang Fanmei!
You're not gonna beat me again, are you?
That's right!
You little rascal!
You even know
how to run away from home now?
You little...
You dared to run away from home?
I'll teach you a lesson!
Stop right there!
How dare you run away from home!
Qian Zhenqing,
what Mr. Dongguo and the Wolf?
If you're gonna hit the kid, just do it.
Stingy old man!
Won't even spring for a full set of bulbs.
Mom
You finally called me.
I couldn't call during the day.
Your dad's always watching me.
He's afraid I'll transfer you money.
So is he asleep yet?
Right now?
He's fast asleep.
Snoring away.
Then hurry up and send it to me!
I can't transfer it by bank card.
If I use the bank card,
the bank will notify your dad.
Then he'll find out.
Then what do we do?
Mom,
I really want to go study painting.
I don't want to follow my brother
into construction.
I know, son.
Don't worry.
Mom supports you.
Listen to this.
Mom has a secret stash.
I've got cash.
I'll bring it to you tomorrow.
Give me your address.
The address is Donghua Avenue.
I don't know the number.
Anyway, there's an art class there.
It's called Sunflower Art Class.
Did you get that?
Got it.
Alright, son.
I'll bring it over tomorrow.
That's it. Hanging up.
This one looks nice.
Pretty cool, right?
Can you do this one?
It's actually not that hard.
Look here.
First, paint on the color.
Then blend with a sponge, add rhinestones.
Finally, seal it with crystal topcoat.
And it's done.
You're amazing.
What are you two up to?
Looking at nail art.
Nail art?
That stuff is all chemicals.
You're pregnant.
You absolutely can't do that.
You'd better not do it either.
A young girl
with clean, natural nails
looks much prettier.
Oh right.
I called your dad.
Told him
you're spending Mid-Autumn here.
Peeled an apple, it's super sweet.
Have some.
The fruit I hate the most
is apples.
Apples are good for your health.
So sweet. Thanks, Auntie.
I'll go toss this out.
You like them,
so I'll leave them all here for you.
Take your time.
Jingjing, help!
Oh my god, Dandan!
Can't catch you, huh?
I'm your mother,
disciplining my own son.
Grandma, discipline him hard!
Yang Fanmei hits way harder than you.
Yang Fanmei?
I'm your mom, don't call me by name!
All right,
stop hitting him.
Dandan,
you only have one mom.
If you make her die of anger,
you'll be the one crying.
Right?
You hear me?
When she's gone, you'll be sorry.
All right, all right.
That's enough.
All dressed up, huh?
Going on a blind date, right?
Have a good one.
Yang Fanhu.
Today, you're my blind date.
I want to have a romance with you.
No, no.
Not me.
What's there to see in me?
What romance could I offer you?
Didn't you say I'm a good person?
And skilled with my hands.
You...
What?
You were just comforting me?
No, no, no.
I wasn't comforting you.
I...
Right now...
I'm just not in the mood for that.
Not in the mood is fine.
We can slowly develop the feelings.
Didn't you say
we could stargaze on the back hill?
I checked, today's the new moon.
The stars will be extra bright.
Let's go stargazing together.
Stargaze in broad daylight?
Besides,
that slope on the back hill got flattened.
Turned into a pigsty.
Then...
Then come home with me.
I'll steam some buns for you.
No, no, no.
I don't...
eat buns anymore.
I've switched to...
flat... flatbread.
Look, Huanhuan.
I'm already at this age.
I've been on my own,
used to being alone.
I have no other plans now,
just want to
take good care of my old mother.
I'm just messing with you.
Look how scared you are.
You're not that lucky.
I'll never steam buns for you again.
So early in the morning
Where are you off to?
All dolled up like that
Nothing much
Just gonna wander around the market
Don't waste money on junk
Okay
It's not your money anyway
Da Lang
Bye-bye
Right
Gotta go grab something
Young man
How do I get to this place?
It's right over by the intersection
Head this way
Yeah
Thanks
No problem
Are you our new teacher?
No, I'm your classmate
I'm also here to learn painting
You're already this old
Why are you still learning to paint?
An adult your age
shouldn't you be out earning money?
Not all adults
have to go out and earn money
You should go to work
Get a job and make money
Teacher
The brush
You're the one
with the artistic dream
right?
Yes, yes, yes
I went back and discussed it
I still want the
one-on-one course
And my mom will be here in a bit
to come pay the money
Art, you know
can't be measured in money
But this pursuit of yours
I quite admire it
This...
Mom
So you must be
the great mother helping him
achieve his brilliant dream
Yes
This, this is my mom
Xiaowei's mom, hello
Xiaowei
has an extraordinary gift for painting
I'm going to teach him personally
You're the teacher?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
So young
Not at all, not at all
Well
Thank you for teaching our Xiaowei
Don't mention it
Don't mention it, don't mention it
Here
Right here, Mom, Mom
The tuition
Yes, yes, yes
Tuition
Five thousand
Right, yes, yes, yes
No, please, count it
Please, count it
No need for that
No, no, no
Count it, count it
No need
Just count it, count it
It's enough
If you don't count, I will
Wait, why are you here?
Quite a lot, huh, Bie Qiumei.
You... you...
My money!
I...
Old Qi!
Stop right there!
Give me back the money!
You Traitor! You mole!
How much did you sneak him behind my back?
I...
It's my own money!
I'll do whatever I want with it!
You... your money?
The food, the house, all paid by me!
My money! It's mine!
Give it back to me!
Give you back? It's all mine!
I earned this money!
It's mine, I'll give it to whoever I want!
Give it back!
Qi Xiaowei!
Get your ass back home!
How much can your paintings even earn?
Your wife's about to give birth!
Doing this junk is pointless!
Teacher! Teacher! Teacher!
Teacher, I'm sorry.
Um...
Sorry about this.
Just teach me first.
I'll pay you back later.
Young man,
that's not allowed.
We have rules here.
No, wait,
Teacher,
didn't you say it yourself earlier?
Art can't be measured by money.
Just this once,
break through
the chains of money and rules.
Just teach me first, okay?
Art comes from life,
but life is built on money.
If you want to make art,
you have to survive first.
I told you to go win your wife back,
and you ran off to paint?
You're deliberately messing with me, huh?
From this day on,
don't expect a single cent from this house.
You, and you too!
If you dare sneak him money again,
I'll kick you out along with him!
You stay right here
and behave yourself.
Tomorrow you're coming to sell goods with me.
I'm not going.
Not going, huh?
Then don't expect to eat!
You...
Not even allowed to eat?
I'll starve to death!
No work, no food!
I don't feed freeloaders here.
I'm telling you,
don't give him any food!
Let him starve for a bit!
Spare the rod, spoil the child.
Where'd you get the key?
I made a copy ages ago.
Son.
Mom's got your back.
Look at these hands of yours.
Those are a painter's hands.
Don't let your dad hold you back.
Pack your things.
You're going to Shenzhen.
I've got no money.
He took all your money too.
I've been battling him my whole life.
Think I'd let him clean me out?
Mom's gotta go dig it up.
You didn't forget, did you?
No way.
This...
Old Qi
Where's my money?
You wanna mess with me?
I've cleaned out
your whole stash.
Right.
We're raising the money right now.
And if all goes well,
we'll probably come after Mid-Autumn
to sign the contract with you.
Great, great.
See you after the holiday.
Thank you, boss.
All right, come on.
High five!
Almost there. Just need the money.
Just the money.
Money's the hardest part.
You know?
Right now, I can't even borrow
enough to pay for Grandma's treatment.
Let alone this.
Before,
I did save up twenty thousand yuan.
But it all went to Grandma's medical bills.
You've got the skills.
You can do a Technology Investment.
No money needed.
How much short are we?
I've got money.
How much do you have?
Every year's Lucky money,
I secretly saved it all up.
It's quite a bit.
Lucky money?
At least one or two thousand, right?
Two or three thousand?
What?
One or two thousand?
Jingjing,
you really underestimate me.
Monopoly!
I'm...
back when Old Qian hadn't gone broke yet.
You scared me!
Dandan,
why are you here?
Your mom's been looking everywhere for you.
Hurry, go.
Why didn't you knock before coming in?
I...
I knew you'd be staying here
with Xiaofang tonight.
Afraid you'd get cold,
so I brought you a quilt.
You still have to knock!
Everyone's got privacy.
Okay?
I'm your mother.
Why do you always
find fault with everything I do?
If you have any issue with me,
can't we just talk it out nicely?
You remember this.
Everything I've ever done in my life
comes down to three words:
It's for your own good.
Enough, enough, enough.
I don't want to fight today.
Don't talk to me.
You can't just spend your whole life
not talking to your mom.
"It's for your own good, for your own good."
All day long, "It's for your own good."
Does she even know
what's really good for me?
Those words just set me off.
I wish my mom were that civilized.
The moment she says "for your own good,"
those very words,
she's definitely about to hit me.
Beating me is "for my own good."
Well, thanks a lot, Mom.
Poor Dandan.
Just bear with it.
Can't beat her,
but we can always dodge her.
Right?
You can't bear it,
and Dandan, you can't dodge her either.
It all boils down to one phrase:
"It's for your own good."
They really do believe
it's for our own good.
But their methods,
we just can't stand.
Let's work hard.
Work hard to prove we don't need
them looking out for us.
The nail salon is now our chance
to prove ourselves.
But right now, we can't even
scrape the money together.
We can find outside help.
Like who?
Take them down one by one.
How's it going, bro?
What can I say?
Just figuring out my next move.
Come back after the holiday.
I'll plead your case again.
Forget it.
It's pointless.
Stop toughing it out.
Time to bow down to reality.
Bow down?
I've been bowing all along. It's useless.
Let me think it over.
I'm hanging up.
If I can win 500 today,
from two packs!
if I can win 500,
I'll pick myself up
and get back in the game.
Neither ticket won a thing.
I swear...
What a piece of junk.
So annoying, day after day.
I can't believe myself.
I'm so fed up.
Nice weather, isn't it? Yeah.
Uncle.
The weather's really nice today.
Really.
Where have you two been?
And you're alone here again,
pondering life?
I came to wash some veggies.
Aren't we eating soon?
I'm doing prenatal yoga.
Jingjing
I really think
we're incredibly lucky
Such a great nail salon
Been running for two years
with a steady clientele
If the owner weren't in a rush to leave
would we ever get this chance?
Right
We're really lucky
I mean, the beauty industry now
is so profitable
Something like nails
as long as your taste and skills are on point
you're guaranteed to make money
Right?
Exactly
Oh, and I just remembered
Did I ever tell you
I learned latte art
So down the line
let's add another feature to the shop
You
handle the nails on one side
and I'll make coffee on the other
and milk tea
Another stream of income
That's a brilliant idea
Doing this
beats all that flashy nonsense
by a mile, way more reliable
Right?
Exactly
You two say this nail salon
has real potential?
Uncle
Do you want
to buy in too?
Let me think about it
Let me observe first
In the age of big data,
gathering customer information
is key to expanding your clientele.
And this top-of-the-line
laptop computer,
do you have one?
This is an old model, isn't it?
You don't have one.
High-end speakers,
do you have any?
These are a bit old.
You don't have them.
While clients get their nails done,
top-tier speakers
play the coziest music,
instantly elevating
an ordinary street-side nail salon
to a whole new level.
And this,
a gaming console.
Uncle,
why didn't you bring this out sooner?
Look.
The kid can happily settle down
and play games here,
while I
can peacefully get my nails done.
So, Uncle,
you're planning
to use this stuff
as your investment?
Just this?
How shallow.
What I value is this team.
Xiaofang
has the boldest spirit among us.
And our Jingjing
has top-notch skills.
Her nail work is beyond words.
And I
am the indispensable brains,
the wisdom of the team,
the creative director.
What about me?
You've got to be here too.
We'll test the nails on you.
Our little guinea pig.
The brains role is crucial.
We can give you
a ten percent share.
But, Uncle,
right now the top priority is
funding.
Right now, we have 30,000.
But the shop needs a transfer fee,
and it needs some basic renovation.
Everything, inside and out, costs money.
It all takes money.
The renovation won't cost a thing.
We've got everything ready for it.
Look, there's a layer up here.
And then look at this spot.
There needs to be a cabinet here.
Can you do it?
Can't be done.
Let's go, Jingjing.
Next one.
Next, next.
No way, come on.
Knew it, that's more like it.
My uncle's the man.
I knew it.
Who am I?
Who else could it be?
But for this,
I gotta go to the site
and take some measurements.
Okay, okay, okay.
So professional!
Uncle, you can make anything.
Make me a suit of armor.
So no matter how Mom hits me,
it won't hurt at all.
Your... your mom what?
The kind where hitting doesn't hurt.
Right?
Come here, you.
Looks like you're asking for a beating.
Great acting, Dandan.
Does it hurt?
Dad.
I'll give you ten percent shares.
Just help us take care of
the whole renovation.
Twelve.
But no more than that.
Okay, okay, deal.
I've got a bit of money saved up.
How about I give it all to you?
Sure, wire it to my card.
I'll take all of it.
All of it, all of it.
He really doesn't mind taking it all.
Really, more is always better.
Are you really my dad?
Are you really my uncle?
Are you really my dear uncle?
Talk about asking for the moon!
In books, one can find houses of gold.
Nail salon
Secret stash
How should we split this?
Just give it all to me.
Give it back!
Give it back! Give it back! Mine!
Let go!
Where'd you get all this money?
It's my money.
My lucky money.
Give it back, Yang Fanmei!
Give it back!
"Yang Fanmei," seriously?
You little ingrate!
Take a little cash and you won't even call me Mom?
Give it back!
Are you actually biting me?!
This is all my money!
It's mine!
Yours, yours...
Even you belong to me!
What are you doing with all this cash?
I'll hold onto it for you.
When you grow up,
won't it all still be...
Don't try to fool me!
Even when I'm grown, I won't get a cent.
When I grow up,
I'm going far away from you,
so you'll never find me.
You little ingrate!
Just like your Ungrateful wretch of a dad,
exactly the same!
I raised you for nothing!
The money I earn in the future
will be mine and mine alone.
Don't even think about grabbing it!
I'm not some bandit!
If I don't hold onto it,
you'll just blow it all!
I won't waste it.
I'm going to be a boss.
This is my investment money.
Investment?
Investment in what?
We're opening a nail salon.
If my aunt finds out,
this whole thing is definitely off.
Why all the secrecy?
You're a shareholder too?
I chipped in a little.
Not just me.
Bro has shares too.
Everyone put in
a little bit.
Just a tiny bit.
Can it actually make money?
Sis.
Drop the question mark.
Just think about it.
What shops are most common in town?
Beauty, hair, nails.
If it weren't profitable,
would all these people be dumb enough to open shops?
Exactly.
You're a woman too,
and a mother.
Think about why you earn money.
To spend on yourself,
or to spend on the kids.
Sometimes kids don't appreciate it,
so it's better to spend it on yourself.
That's true.
Think about it carefully.
Beauty...
isn't it a money-making business?
Then why did you hide it from me?
We didn't mean to hide it.
We just didn't want my mom to know.
With big sis's temper,
if she found out,
would any of us get a share?
Right.
If the know-it-all found out,
this whole thing would fall apart.
Tell you what.
I'll buy in for twenty percent.
Thanks, Auntie.
Great taste!
She's her, I'm me.
Our money has to be kept separate.
Others rely on Children as old-age security.
But you?
You guard against your own mom at every turn.
That's because you never keep your word.
You borrow my money and never pay it back.
Xiaofang.
When did I not pay you back?
Got any ointment for inflammation?
What about last time? The time before?
I paid those back too.
That's weird.
So early in the morning,
where did everyone go?
Don't squeeze it
Let me see
Let me look
Why are you so worked up?
Jingjing got to you, didn't she?
No need to pretend with me
Here
This is my go-to medicine
Apply it for two days and it'll heal
Thanks
You know what?
When you're angry, let it out
When something's up, speak up
Don't always keep it bottled up
If I were like you
Dandan would've driven me crazy by now
Dandan's just being naughty
Playing and roughhousing with you
That means he's close to you
Not like Jingjing
She won't even talk when she sees me
Won't even call me "Mom"
She's still too young to understand
Girls...
Once she grows up a bit
She'll see how hard being a mom is
Then she'll be close to you
Your good days are still ahead
Unlike me
The young one causes trouble
And the old one's no easier
I don't even dare think
about how I'll get through the days ahead
I've got news about Old Qian
That bastard never contacted me
But yesterday
he suddenly called
Straight up asking for 40,000 yuan
Said if I don't give it to him
he can't even get through the holiday
Where am I supposed to get that money?
But if I don't give it to him
I'm really
afraid something bad might happen to him
Are you thinking of taking out
that investment fund early?
I don't have any other money
But you'll lose a lot doing that
Tell you what
I've got a few tens of thousands
maturing in a couple of days
You take it and use it first
Sis
You're the only one I can count on
I can't let you lose out, though
How about this
You give me 40,000 first
Once the investment matures
I'll pay back the 40,000
And the dividends from it
we'll split fifty-fifty
No way
Then 40 percent, 40 percent
I'm raising Dandan on my own
It's not easy for me either
You really are...
Even sisters
must keep clear accounts
Well, raising Dandan
really isn't easy, you know
The money's in your hands now.
Jingjing.
Do a good job.
I'm counting on it.
The nail salon money for my retirement.
No pressure, huh?
What if we lose money?
What are you saying?
With all of us gathered together,
how could we lose money?
If we lost money, it would only mean
we're just too dumb.
Can't accomplish anything.
Let's just disband.
Disband.
Starting a business
means you Burn the boats.
A matter of life and death.
You gotta have that "come what may" spirit.
Right.
Come what may, huh?
Not a cent from you, just pretty words.
This is my secret savings.
That's all I've got.
We won't lose money.
You're all confident, right?
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
That's more like it.
You want in too?
No objections.
What's there to object to?
It's just spending money, right?
I mean, all this time,
our family's been pinned at the top
of the village gossip headlines.
This is the best time for a Desperate comeback.
This Mid-Autumn Festival,
we absolutely have to spend it
in style and glory.
I want everyone in the village
to look at us with envy.
Fanmei's such a big mouth.
Almost blew our cover.
Take this and buy some gifts.
Sis, you sure love a good ceremony.
Who are these gifts for?
After all this mess between Xiaofang and the Qi family,
and just a while back,
we had that whole fiasco
with her running away from home.
The folks who came to help,
don't we owe them a gift?
Is a thousand enough?
What can you buy with that?
How is it not enough?
It's not like it's New Year's.
Xiaofang's about to have her baby.
Her dad's definitely tight on cash.
Your Old Qian just went bankrupt again.
Can't count on him either.
All the holiday money this year,
I'm covering it all.
I'm being so generous to you two.
Shouldn't you
save me some money too?
Fine.
Thanks a lot.
I'll buy on a budget.
Make sure it's cheap but nice,
something presentable.
You know, the kind with flashy packaging,
what's inside
doesn't matter.
Me, I've got something too.
Go buy me some fireworks and firecrackers.
The kind where one bang
can be heard by the whole village.
Who sets off firecrackers at Mid-Autumn?
With that money,
you might as well bump up my budget.
Put your money where it counts.
Think about it, our family this year
has had so much go wrong.
Set off some firecrackers, Blast away the bad luck.
Sis, those big fireworks you're talking about,
they cost at least a thousand plus.
Your money here...
The mouth under your nose,
is it just for eating?
Go find the fireworks seller,
and tell him,
the ones stashed at the bottom,
the ones that won't sell,
even the ones about to expire,
the duds that got a scolding from your mom,
haggle them down for me.
So, dud firecrackers, right?
Fine, I'll do my best, my best.
Sis, why are you slipping in loose change?
Genius.
What are you up to now?
Letting the whole village
share in our Bit's good fortune.
And let Bit soak up some blessings too.
Look at Sis's grand vision.
Big sis is big sis.
On top of the fridge,
there's the menu for our reunion dinner.
You two go check it out.
Okay, let's have a look.
See what tasty stuff there is.
The reunion dinner menu's all set.
Big sis
For the holidays these days, other families
all get king crab.
It symbolizes that
the whole family can Walk sideways like a boss.
Let's get a king crab too.
Yeah!
Let's get some
fresh stuff to eat too.
Stop making the same old three dishes.
We're sick of them.
I'm telling you,
just look at him,
All hunched over.
Slap a shell on your back
and shove you right in the water,
you could just swim away.
And you,
here in the village,
all dressed up in fancy colors,
you look just like a Pheasant.
A Peacock!
The two of you together
make a famous dish,
Farewell My Concubine.
You're really proving the saying,
"Beggars can't be choosers."
Unbelievable.
This money of mine
has to be saved for Xiaofang and Jingjing,
to buy each of them a new outfit.
What about my son?
He won't be left out.
An old tree blossoms anew
Looks great
Grandma
This is just the basic one
I only put some color on for you
Once our nail salon opens up
And we've got all the supplies
I'll give you a handmade reinforcement
Plus the complete set of
hand care and massage
That'll be amazing
Don't forget the toenails either
Grandma's gonna be the trendiest one
Wonderful
Do you girls have money?
Grandma has money
Yes
Don't worry, Grandma
Just keep your money safe
Then when it opens
I'll bring all my old sisters
right over to your place
But when they sign up
give them a discount, okay?
Absolutely
What are you all talking about? So happy
Look
Jingjing did this for me
Pretty, right?
Really pretty
I'm heading to town
Want me to pick anything up?
I want durian
Okay, durian it is
Mom
I've washed this blanket for you
It's all dry now
Drape it over there
Alright
Well
Xiaofang
You be careful
Don't move around too much
You really need to rest right now
Don't strain yourself, okay?
Go on, I'll watch her
Well then
Okay
Bye, Auntie
I'm off
Yan'er
She's more and more like
your grandfather
Whenever your grandpa went to market
he'd always ask everyone first
"What do you want me to bring back?"
Fanyan
would always raise her little hand and say
"I want Malt candy"
In the blink of an eye
now she's the one saying that line
She's the one nagging now
I bet Grandpa
definitely wasn't as annoying as her
You just love winding up my daughter, huh?
Look
Does it look good?
It looks good
A lot has happened recently
And I've done a lot of things wrong
No matter how you see me
I accept it
Yang Xiaofang
I love you
You're all in on this together to fool me
I guess I'm not family, huh?
Take that! Take that!
Stop
How did I wet myself?