This one's too dowdy
Our old lady's stylish
Hand me that green one
the light green one
This one, right?
Yeah, the pea-green one
This one's not bad
How much?
Forty
Okay, wrap it up
How much for these long johns?
Fifteen bucks a pair
They're on clearance
Hasn't it been two weeks
since the Start of Autumn?
Those three grown kids of mine
never know to bundle up
Each autumn rain makes it colder
I'll take two mediums
You got it
These two are mediums
Good
Pick me an extra small too
Hey there
Are these gloves durable?
Very durable
You see
My brother, he's someone
who works with wood all day
Sure
Good things come in pairs
Give me two pairs
Okay
Hey there
How much for this maternity hat?
Fifty-five
Okay, wrap it up
Take care now! You got it
Thanks
Hi, just having a look
How much is this toy car?
Sixty-five, ma'am
It's a blind box, right?
That's right
Okay, get me six of them
Sure
And add this car too
Here you go.
Come again soon!
How much is this?
What would you like?
This one's 25.
And this one?
Nine bucks.
Hey, boss.
This snakehead's 25 a pound?
Can you go a little lower?
How about 22 a pound?
You don't look like you're short three bucks.
Besides,
it's a holiday, no haggling.
It's exactly because it's a holiday.
What business doesn't involve haggling?
How about this?
Let's meet halfway.
That makes it 22.5 a pound.
Pick me a bigger one.
Hold on—
It's settled then.
Fine, fine, fine.
This one, then.
Deal.
Is that a king crab?
Alaskan king crab!
Don't you dare haggle on this one.
I'll give you the wholesale price straight up.
Two hundred thirty.
That expensive?
Boss,
this is an Alaskan king crab.
It flew in just this morning.
Isn't that Fanyan?
What a coincidence!
You two, as a couple—
one minute selling fake furs online,
the next you're into
the seafood business.
Honestly,
from eggs, small as they are,
to planes and missiles,
there's nothing you two won't trade.
W-Well, it's just to make a living, isn't it?
Besides, the more we earn,
the better a life
our Xiaofang will have someday.
Don't you bring up Xiaofang to me.
Xiaofang has nothing
to do with your family.
Won't mention her, won't.
So you're buying a king crab?
Why waste your money on that?
We've got some at home.
I'll get one for you.
Pick a big one, a big one.
A small one, small, small.
Take this home to nourish Xiaofang.
Tell her it's from her father-in-law,
just a little token of care.
Here.
Boss.
That big king crab—
weigh it for me.
I'll take it at your price.
Sure, sure.
Speak of the devil.
Sucker.
Such a fool.
Stop calling yourself the father-in-law.
It's no good if Xiaofang finds out.
What's no good about it?
Let me tell you,
I'm gonna be Xiaofang's father-in-law, no matter what.
Then give me the money
to study painting.
What the hell's the use of your painting?
It earns less than selling crabs.
Eight hundred eighty-eight.
Fine, I've thought it through.
Since you don't want to work at the site,
then we won't go.
From now on,
you'll learn the trade from your dad, me.
I'll pay you a wage.
How much can you pay me?
By the day.
Two hundred a day.
Two-fifty.
Three hundred, three hundred.
No higher than that.
You're my son,
that's why I'm paying this much.
Keep it in the family.
All right!
Sure.
Take care now.
Will do!
Look at that.
So many people. Business is booming.
Looks like nail salons
really rake in the cash these days.
Uncle's right.
Everyone loves looking good now.
Once we open our shop,
it'll be just as popular.
Definitely more popular than this.
How many times have I shown you?
How'd you scrub the crab like this?
Can you even do this job or not?
If you keep slacking off like this,
today I'm
not paying your wages.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're gonna stiff me?
You promised to pay me.
Come on, what good are you?
You can't even learn to scrub a crab.
Today's pay is definitely docked.
Then I quit.
No pay anyway.
Did you hear?
Apparently Qi Xiaowei
snuck off to town to study painting.
His dad found out
and dragged him home, locked him up all day.
Didn't even give him a single meal.
Useless at everything he tries.
Has he ever pulled off a single thing?
Wait.
So he really went to study painting?
See?
Lost this customer, didn't you?
Wants to learn a real skill, huh?
And this sign, too.
What on earth did you paint here?
It's all weird and misshapen.
And it's cross-eyed too.
You did this to spite me, right?
Who's supposed to look at this?
Mister.
Your shop's sign is so unique.
It's really well painted.
Xiaofang.
Xiaofang's here.
Jingjing, out shopping, are you?
Want something to eat?
So much seafood here, well,
grab some,
steam it up at home.
Right, it's all fresh.
No need, thanks, Auntie.
We'll keep looking around.
Let's go.
Big mouth.
Trying to give her stuff for free?
I was just being polite.
Such a cheapskate.
This kid has no sense at all.
Right here.
Seven bucks, seven bucks, come on!
Wipe this down for me.
Okay.
Did you hear me?
Wipe this down for me.
I won't do it.
Do it or you're fired.
Coming, coming!
Stop it, stop fighting.
Everyone's watching, you know.
Such frustrated hopes.
Forty-five.
With your figure, this outfit fits perfectly
It looks so good on you
Let me look around some more
Come back, come back, come back
I'll give you a discount
You're kidding, lady
Who are you calling "lady"?
Since you said that
Come on, let's go
You look pretty good
And you don't look broke either
Yet here you are doing cutthroat bargaining
Even with money, you shouldn't waste it
Tell you what
All together
Add 80
Come here, kiddo, like this
Just like this
Here, look
Yes, that's right
Like this, like this
How much is this malt candy?
Five a stick
Want one?
Too expensive
It's not
When I was a kid
It was 20 cents a stick
Well, that was back then
Here, kiddo
Uncle
Look, this one
We can buy this
This one works too
Grandpa's seafood stall
Is busy with customers right now
Your mom just had to make me buy you firecrackers
Only 10 yuan worth, got it?
And no making trouble after we buy them
What a coincidence
Run into the Yang family again
You're buying firecrackers too?
Boss
give me 10 yuan of pop-its
You got it
10 yuan worth
Bro
This one's great, 480
It's not even New Year's
What are you two even up to?
Showing off how rich your family is?
That's way too cheap
Boss, do you have anything
a little pricier?
This is too...
Sure, they're all up on the shelf
Grandpa, let's buy some too
Buy my foot, we're not buying
Hey, boss
Do you have the kind
that's super loud?
The kind that dogs
would be scared of
Yes
As loud as you want
Let me get it for you
Boss, boss
I need to scan the code for my 10 yuan
Where do I scan?
I'm busy right now
Just take it and let the kid play
What's that supposed to mean?
So 10 yuan doesn't count as money?
You look down on people
How am I looking down on you?
My family's got big fireworks
And your family only has tiny pop-its
You really do look down on us
don't you?
Fine, kid
No rush
Let me open your eyes
Boss
Give me a string of 100,000-bang ones
100,000-bangs
Grandpa, you're awesome
Of course I am
Boss
Get me a 200,000-bang one
Give me two 200,000-bang ones
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Give me a 2,000,000-bang one
To drive away the evil
To ward off the ghosts
There aren't that many
How about
you just buy the whole lot?
What are you trying to do?
What on earth are you up to?
Spending thousands on all these firecrackers
Have you lost your mind, Yang Fanzhu?
You might as well rename yourself Yang Firecracker
Where did you get all that money?
My brother insisted on buying them
Where's your brother?
Where is he?
On the way home he said
the forest station called him for patrol
Oh, he's a clever one
Knew he'd get scolded coming back
so he just slipped away
He bailed, didn't he?
I knew it
Making me take the blame again
Just look at this
This whole family
messing around all day
And he's about to become a grandpa
Auntie, you don't know
my uncle Hu was standing up for our family
Shut it
This is none of your business
You, why are you yelling
at the kid like that?
And you, Yang Fanmei
Tell me
I gave you money to buy gifts
and what did you come back with?
Take a look
Everyone, take a good look
Spent over five hundred yuan
on this piece of junk clothing
And you got a pair of earrings too, huh?
They came free
Buy one, get one free
So what if I buy a piece of clothing?
You, you...
I bought it with my own money
You're way too controlling
Your own money?
Every time you see me you cry poor
saying you're broke
saying your husband's business went bust
But you've got money for clothes, huh?
Auntie
Little Auntie must have really liked it
that's why she bought it, obviously
It's the holiday, after all
Didn't you also tell me and Jingjing
to buy some new clothes?
Right
Speaking of buying clothes
where are the clothes?
Bring them out, let me see
So where are they?
I didn't see anything I liked
so I didn't buy any
Didn't buy any?
Went and got your nails done instead, huh?
All flashy and gaudy
and pretty expensive too
This cost more than
two hundred fifty yuan, didn't it?
You're such a fool
Enough already, Yang Fanyan
Haven't you said enough?
Is there anyone in this family
you haven't scolded yet?
What is it
Does the whole family have to obey
your orders and arrangements?
No
I just want to get my nails done
I paid with my own money
Did I ask for your money?
I'll give it back to you
I won't take a single cent
Auntie, Auntie, Sis
Sis
I
want some malt candy
Whenever your grandpa
went to the market
Fanyan would raise her little hand and say
she wanted malt candy
Aren't you thirsty?
Someone hasn't had a drink all afternoon.
Your lips are all cracked.
Aren't you thirsty?
Chrysanthemum tea cools you down.
I feel bad for you.
Tell me.
How could she treat me like this?
I gave Jingjing money to buy a gift,
and she ended up throwing the money right at me.
What did I do wrong?
Am I guilty of something?
Was I wrong?
Where did I go wrong?
You be the judge here.
That's a hard one to judge.
What's that supposed to mean?
I just don't get it, Auntie.
You're the one who gave Jingjing the money.
And you're the one who told her
to spend it however she liked, right?
She did exactly that.
And you still blew up at her?
The point is her attitude.
I never said she couldn't spend the money.
For all these years,
I say east and she runs west.
She does it on purpose.
Is it easy being her mother?
Auntie, how good you are to everyone,
we all know it.
We all see it.
And Jingjing knows it too.
She knows you're good to her.
But do you know what she wants?
What does she want?
She wants to drive me crazy.
There you go again.
I'm done talking to you.
Stop, stop, stop.
Come back and sit down, let's chat a bit.
Tell your auntie,
what does she really want?
She's definitely not trying to drive you crazy.
She wants her grandma to live, of course.
I know.
But the doctor already gave
the diagnosis on her grandma's condition.
He said no amount of money can cure her.
So isn't that money just wasted?
It's just like getting your nails done.
In your eyes, it's all wasted money.
But for Jingjing,
it means a lot.
Careful, the road's slippery
Why did you bring me here?
You'll know once we get there
Look
So beautiful.
Xiaofang.
You once told me,
no matter what others say,
we should always see clearly
what's in our own hearts.
And follow our hearts in everything we do.
Right?
What I mean is,
Fang'er,
these past few weeks,
a lot has happened,
and I did a lot of things wrong.
No matter how you see me now,
I'll accept it.
Wrong is wrong.
Even though it was painful,
I think all of it
was worth it.
Because now I've seen clearly
what's in my heart.
I know exactly what
matters most to me,
what's most important.
Xiaofang, it's you.
Yang Xiaofang,
I love you.
Saranghae.
Je t'aime.
This time I won't back down again.
I'll win your heart once more,
Yang Xiaofang.
I love you.
When did this turn into a soap opera?
Where are you going?
Home.
Home? What for?
Come with me to the hospital to see your grandma.
Let's spend the Mid-Autumn Festival with her.
I bought some health supplements.
See if there's anything else we need.
Thank you for all these years
of looking after Jingjing.
Yan'er.
After I'm gone,
you must take good care of Jingjing.
This child...
It breaks my heart to see her.
Grandma.
What are you talking about?
Didn't we already agree?
We're going on a trip together.
I've already planned the whole route.
As soon as you get better,
we'll set off.
All right, all right.
The liver has already failed.
She's very old now.
An organ transplant
would serve no purpose.
Besides,
at her age,
the surgical risk is far too high.
It would only add to her suffering.
I understand.
Doctor,
I was wondering,
if there's any other way,
we'd like to try it.
In cases like this,
we usually recommend moving to hospice care.
Jingjing.
What I'm saying may be hard to hear,
but it's the truth, no doubt about it.
If you told your grandma
you spent all that money keeping her hospitalized,
she'd surely refuse.
I'm definitely going to borrow the money.
Once I've earned it,
I'll pay you back right away.
If you don't trust me,
I can write you an IOU.
It's not that I'm worried about the money.
Your dad and I divorced so long ago,
and he found you a stepmother.
I'm afraid people will gossip.
And then
it might stir up trouble in their family.
Looks like your whole life,
you just live for what other people say.
That gossip
and my grandma's life,
which one matters more?
Then let me ask you,
if it were you lying there today,
would you want me to do this?
Coming through, coming through!
Since you're putting it that bluntly
then let me make my position clear too
If someday
I really end up in that state
don't try to resuscitate me
don't put me on tubes
Better a short pain than a long one
Just let me go quickly and painlessly
so I won't be a burden to you
So you think all of this is a burden
right?
You know what I mean
I do
But that's your choice
My choice
is to ease my grandma's suffering
See, now you've hit the real point
It's just like getting your nails done
In your eyes it's all a waste of money
But to Jingjing
it means everything
Where are you taking the patient?
She's being moved to another ward.
Another ward? Which one?
The hospice ward.
Why are you so stubborn, child?
Was everything we just said for nothing?
Everything I do,
it's all for...
For my own good again, right?
No need.
I can handle it myself.
Fine, fine, fine.
I'll go pay for your grandma.
Alright.
No need.
I've already paid.
You paid?
Where did you get the money?
It's none of your business.
You don't need to worry about it.
You have to tell me,
where did the money come from?
Back so soon?
Sis.
I'm picking persimmons.
Want some?
Auntie, why are you back?
Weren't you at the hospital with Jingjing?
Why are you back so soon?
What's the point of this dinner?
What festival is there to celebrate?
You people...
You all ganged up to fool me.
I'm just an outsider, right?
I finally get a family reunion.
I spent half a month preparing this meal.
What are you doing?
For this family...
I gave up everything.
You people...
You wanted firecrackers.
So I went and got you firecrackers.
You wanted king crab.
So I went and got you king crab.
But how do you treat me?
Jingjing wants to open a nail salon.
Did any of you tell me?
Behind my back.
Pooling money, buying in as partners.
This is how you treat me?
Do you have any conscience?
I get it now.
In this household,
you're all one family.
I'm the only outsider.
Say something!
Aren't you usually so quick with words,
so sharp and clever?
Always scheming, always nitpicking.
Why so quiet now?
Has any one of you
ever once thought about me?
You people...
Forget the festival.
Let this family just fall apart!
Auntie.
Don't be so angry.
Xiaofang.
This was all your idea, wasn't it?
How have I always treated you?
Heaven sees everything.
You...
You treat me like this.
Where's your conscience?
How can you face me?
Auntie.
It's not like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
I took the money everyone gave me
and used it for my grandma's medical bills.
What?
She got hurt.
What happened?
How did she fall down?
Let me see, let me see.
Did you break anything, Jingjing?
What's your grandma's hospital stay to me?
How dare you use my money?
Watch your tone.
Mom.
This is my business.
It's none of yours.
Shut up.
What are you so worked up about?
Obviously!
That's my whole retirement savings.
How can I not be worked up?
Are you gonna support me in old age?
Jingjing, how could you do this?
You lied and swindled money.
You deserve it.
Yang Fanyan.
Say that again.
I said you deserve it.
You deserve it, you deserve it.
You absolutely deserve it.
You're the one who deserves it.
You deserve your divorce.
You deserve Jingjing disowning you as her mom.
You deserve Dou Cheng dumping you.
The Maldives, my foot.
A honeymoon trip.
So obsessed with saving face.
Dou Cheng would rather stay with his ex-wife
at the hospital than be with you.
And you still put on a show for us.
You hit me!
Yeah, I hit you!
You loudmouthed jerk!
Why you...
Stop it! Stop hitting!
Quit it! You're hitting me!
I'll hit you, you shameless brat!
You scold me, but was I wrong?
She's your sister!
So what if she's my sister?
So I just have to take it?
Mom, you always play favorites!
When I was little,
I got leftovers and hand-me-downs.
When I grew up,
you raised Fanhu's daughter,
always sticking up for Yang Fanyan.
You scraped together every penny
to send Yang Fanzhu to college.
And me?
I didn't even finish high school.
Did you ever care?
How is that my fault?
You didn't go to high school
because you ranked second from the bottom!
because you were busy chasing girls!
So what if I had a girlfriend?
Why do you always think you're right?
Why does everyone in this house
get to lecture me?
I've had such a raw deal!
You've all had it rough,
and only I haven't, right?
I worried myself sick over this family.
And any of you,
did you ever say one kind word to me?
Stop it!
Where are your manners?
I'm still standing right here!
Saying all this stuff
right in front of me, what's the point?
Every single one of you,
can't you just let me
worry a little less?
And now you're the ones feeling wronged?
What about how wronged I feel?
All these years,
none of you were home.
I'm the one who stayed with Mom!
Stop!
Why did I just wet myself?
Yes, yes, that's right.
Fanzhu.
Don't panic, don't panic.
Did you get through to 120?
Your dad went to get the car.
Go on.
We have our own car.
Once he's here, we'll go.
Come on, take deep breaths.
Grandma, I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
Don't be scared, okay?
Take a deep breath in.
Breathe out slowly.
Yes, that's it, relax your belly.
Relax.
Are you okay?
Listen, you two...
That's about enough.
Hurry and get her to the car.
The guy's waiting in the car.
Let me take her over first.
Quick, quick, quick!
These two okay, Mom?
Yeah.
Don't be nervous, okay?
Um...
We'll be at the hospital soon.
Deep breaths.
But why don't I feel anything now?
Just now, Bite
was kicking like crazy in my belly.
Now he's gone all quiet.
He's just worn out, worn out.
Why do I have to keep lying down?
Your water's already broken.
And we've still got a ways
to go to the hospital.
If all the fluid leaks out,
the baby could suffocate.
Don't be scared, don't be scared.
Lift your legs up a bit.
It's okay.
Slow down, slow down.
Don't jolt the baby out!
What's wrong, what's wrong?
It hurts!
It hurts.
It's okay.
Deep breaths, deep breaths.
Deep breaths.
Giving birth always hurts.
That's it, deep breaths.
Let me peel a tangerine for you.
Are you brain-dead?
Can she even eat anything right now?
Then don't eat it.
How'll she have the strength to push later?
Here.
Open up, here.
Did you forget?
Back when you had Dandan.
Right, right, she can't eat.
I'll eat it.
Honestly, what a memory.
Totally scatterbrained.
Obviously.
Just like you.
No brains, just sneaky tricks.
Auntie.
What happened when you had Dandan?
She thought she could...
...give birth naturally.
So...
Afraid she'd run out of energy,
she stuffed herself like crazy.
And the result? Let her tell you herself.
Let me tell you,
I really pigged out that day.
That morning I slurped down a bowl of noodles.
Double toppings, double eggs.
Really hit the spot.
By noon I was hungry again.
So I ordered two pounds of crawfish.
Come evening, I figured,
I definitely wasn't giving birth that day.
So I tore into half a braised duck.
Who knew I'd go into labor at midnight?
I was munching on stinky tofu,
and suddenly I couldn't take it.
The baby was coming.
Doctor, I got on the delivery table.
I pushed with all my might.
But it just wouldn't come out.
Then the doctor...
...informed the family.
Said I needed a C-section.
I thought, fine, just cut it open then.
What's the big deal?
But I'd eaten way too much.
So the, you know...
...anesthesia procedure...
...got a bit more complicated.
In your current condition,
you need an immediate C-section.
Cut it, cut it, do it now!
I can't take it anymore!
You've eaten so much,
we can't give you anesthesia.
I want the anesthesia!
It just...
...than other people...
...was a bit more of an ordeal.
I'd forgotten till you brought it up.
You forgot, but I sure didn't.
Back then, her hubby Qian...
...was away out of town.
I went into the delivery room with her.
She was in such pain she was frantic,
didn't know what to do.
Look,
she just bit me.
Bit down and wouldn't let go!
And these little teeth marks...
...are still right here.
See them? Right there.
Seven years now, and they're still here.
See for yourself, are they there or not?
Would I lie? Right here.
Don't lecture me.
When you gave birth to Jingjing,
you weren't any better off.
When Auntie had Jingjing,
what happened then?
Nothing much.
It was just a little bit of...
a difficult labor.
You're worried about face even now?
She nearly died back then.
The doctor told Yin Zhiqiang to sign,
and he didn't even dare to.
He actually called to ask his mom.
I said long ago, mama's boys are useless.
If it were me,
I'd have slapped him across the face.
You mama's boy!
A guy like Yin Zhiqiang,
if you don't divorce him,
I won't stand for it.
You're getting off track. Enough.
Why are you scaring her?
Look at you.
I've got it, I've got it.
Alright.
Here's a hair tie for you.
Tie your hair back.
You look like a madwoman.
Are you okay?
Soon you'll feel contractions.
The more frequent, the closer you are.
When one comes, just...
take a deep breath.
Yes, just like that.
When it hurts, breathe deeply.
Good.
It's okay, it's okay.
Tie your hair up already
Give it here
I can't stand seeing you like this
Just like when we were kids
All right
You're going to be a mom.
What does it feel like to be a mom?
Worrying about everything.
No more freedom from now on.
I'm not even crying, but you two are.
We're just happy for you!
Let's go!
Hurry, hurry, go!
Move out, move out!
It's a manual!
A manual? I can't drive that!
Uncle!
Why do you drop the ball when it counts?
Quick, grab a cab! Hurry!
Good thing I got my license on a manual.
When it really counts,
you gotta count on your old mom.
So cool, Mom!
Let's go!
Mid-Autumn is a time for family reunion.
But honestly, I kind of dread it too.
Why's that?
How can you dread Mid-Autumn?
Isn't it the day for coming home together?
Well, think about it.
Everyone's heading home for the reunion.
So we're all stuck in traffic, right?
Stuck in traffic? No worries.
Just tune in to Traffic FM 997.
Let's have a listen.
Folks, folks!
All you good friends out there!
Traffic's jammed, but don't let your heart jam.
Whatever you do, don't panic.
We've got food and drink, everything you need!
I'll fill you right up!
Alright!
All you folks out there,
eat your fill!
They've got food here.
Boss, what have you got to eat?
Noodles.
Fifteen yuan a bowl.
I'll take one.
Give me a bowl, then.
Sure, one bowl coming up.
Haiyun!
Hot water!
Coming!
Here.
Careful, it's hot! Watch out!
You go over there.
I've got this side covered.
Okay.
Instant noodles! Fifteen a cup!
We've got sausages too!
I'll blast you, blast!
Boss, want some instant noodles?
Gimme a cup of noodles.
Sure, sure, sure.
Fifteen yuan a cup.
Mom, Mom, fifteen!
Mom!
I've already been over there.
You've been there already?
Look at all that sweat, my goodness!
Why are you so happy?
Last night,
I had a great talk with Xiaofang.
You two made up?
Nope.
Then what's with the goofy grin?
If Xiaofang gave in that easily
and just agreed to make up with me,
would she even be Xiaofang anymore?
Now you're taking her side!
Such a traffic jam
How did it get jammed?
No, no, no
Come on, get out
Xiaofang, hold on
Don't worry
Take it easy, Xiaofang
Hello, hello
There's a pregnant woman in labor
Please get back in your car, okay?
Thank you, thank you
The baby's coming
Please move aside
Hi, there's a pregnant woman in labor
Hot water, instant noodles, sausages
I've got everything. Want some?
No, no thanks
Excuse me, excuse me, please move
A pregnant woman's in labor
The baby's coming any minute
Hello, thank you, thank you
Having a ba... baby
Move to the side, will you?
Baby
Dad
Dad, Dad, Dad
Xia... Xiaofang seems to be in labor
Who's in labor?
Xia... Xiaofang
Where is she?
Back there, back there
They say she's about to give birth
Our pregnant woman
is about to give birth
Xiaofang's in labor?
There's a pregnant woman in labor
Please move aside
Huzi
Xiaofang's about to give birth!
How come you're everywhere?
Let me tell you
Today you're gonna...
Don't worry
I'll help clear the traffic for you
so you can get through fast
Everyone, make way
My daughter-in-law's in labor
Finally doing something decent
Make way
Sorry, here's a bowl of noodles
It's on the house
Sorry, someone's giving birth
Make way
Make way, make way, make way
Hello
Everyone, lend a hand, will you?
Move aside, our car needs to pass
There's a pregnant woman in labor
Hey, drivers
Move your cars over a bit
Thank you, thank you
My daughter-in-law's in labor
Thank you
Dad
Xiaowei
That thing...
Xiaofang's in labor
What?
Stuck right here on our road
Quick, help clear the traffic
I'll get right on it
Mom, Mom, Mom
Xiaofang's in labor
Stop fighting, stop fighting
Clear the road
Hurry, hurry, hurry
Okay, get them to clear the way
Stop eating, stop eating
Move that car out of the way
Get in the car
I'm gonna be a grandma!
Come on, everyone, get up
Xiaowei
Dad
The car can't move
It can't move, still won't budge
I'm giving out free noodles
They're all gone. Hurry
Mom, Mom, grab a megaphone
Here it is
Quick, help me, give me a hand
Careful, careful
Everyone, please!
Brothers!
Listen to me!
My wife's about to give birth!
We're stuck back there!
Please, everyone, do us a favor!
Clear a path!
Everyone, pull over to the right!
Hurry, pull to the right!
Thank you all!
He says his wife's about to give birth!
Then let's help him out, quick!
Come on, come on, hurry!
Please, everyone, do us a favor!
Clear a path!
Everyone, pull over to the right!
It's moving! It's moving!
It's moving!
Go, go!
You okay?
I'm fine.
Almost there!
Look
Xiaowei
Xiaofang!
Hold on, Xiaofang!
He's finally acting like a man.
Breathe out
Breathe in
Qi Xiaowei comes running home every day
Holding the baby and won't let go
And I never saw you kick him out
I'm Bite's mom
He's Bite's dad
So the two of us are purely in a
non-spousal kinship
Formula
How can it ever compare to breast milk?
I can't stomach chicken soup anymore
The smell alone makes me sick
Honestly
Didn't drink a single sip
And sent it right back to me
Tomorrow, help me look after Bite
I've got something important to do