( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[Episode 24]
Ever since I was little,
I always thought you were the only one
in the Jin family
who was truly good to me.
That you would never hurt me.
Who was the real murderer of Miss Huo?
Was it Tang Ji?
It wasn't him.
He was only there to give false testimony.
He wasn't the murderer.
Then who was the real murderer?
I'm not sure.
Are you not sure, or do you not want to say?
After destroying so many lives,
- you lived comfortably for 15 years!
- I haven't lived comfortably.
For these 15 years,
I've lived in regret every single day.
I truly feel
guilty toward all of you.
Guilty?
If I had died in that cave today,
you would have breathed a sigh of relief.
When you were little,
during those days at Jujing Hall,
I truly wanted to raise you as my own son.
I made clothes for you.
I taught you how to read and write.
I taught you to memorize the pharmacopeia.
Those things cannot be faked.
Fourth Aunt,
the things you just mentioned...
I have never forgotten them.
For the kindness you once showed me,
I will overlook your part in Tang Ji's plot
to murder me.
But I am not my elder brother.
I cannot forgive you on his behalf.
I want you to testify in court,
state that Tang Ji committed perjury,
and clear my brother's name.
Tell us who the real murderer is.
Even if you don't know the truth,
provide clues.
Tell everything you know
and let the officials investigate.
I must clear my brother's name.
No. No.
Once I testify in court,
I will be despised by everyone.
My family will be disgraced.
Now, Liang Er is an official in Bianjing city.
Lan Er has married into a noble family.
Once what Tang Ji and I did comes to light,
they will be ruined.
A grave injustice to someone else
is, in your eyes,
less important than your children's lives.
Young Seventeenth.
I'm begging you.
Save some face for your cousins.
I know the rules of the martial world.
Martial matters stay in the martial world.
Kill me now.
Avenge your brother's death with my life.
I won't kill you.
My brother's honor
must be restored by your testimony.
You owe him.
I know
my cousins will feel embarrassed and wronged.
But my brother is dead.
No one is more wronged than him.
Young Seventeenth.
Your wound needs to be treated.
It's fine.
I'll handle it once we're back in town.
I struck too hard.
I wasn't in my right mind.
Are you...
I'm fine.
Is that all the skill you've got?
Are you all right?
Seeking revenge for Shengyun Manor?
Why didn't you tell us before?
I didn't want you two to worry.
Jiao Si Yuan's appearance here today
is definitely no coincidence.
Who told you
that I killed your father?
Can't you see that you're being used?
During my father's funeral,
someone sent me a message.
It said that when he was killed,
you were in Xiangyang.
Someone also sent me a message today
to reveal your whereabouts.
I asked my brother.
Your father's death
has nothing to do with Linglong Manor.
Believe it or not.
If you really want revenge,
you should look more closely
into the one who brought you the message.
Where did that sword formation come from?
You'd better think carefully.
If my father and brother find out
that Shengyun Manor is
secretly practicing a sword formation,
deliberately plotting to ambush Linglong Manor,
do you think they'll let it go?
Besides, I've broken your sword formation.
If things really escalate,
I'm afraid
Shengyun Manor will no longer exist.
If I tell you,
will you let this matter drop?
Of course.
You pose no threat to us now.
Why would we feel the need to wipe you out?
Over a decade ago,
my father often trained
and refined techniques with my uncles.
The sword formation was developed back then.
Which year was it exactly?
I was about seven or eight then.
Counting back,
it should be 15 years ago.
15 years? Are you sure?
Yes, 15 years.
It was from that year
that my mother decided to stay in Xiangyang,
never returning to Shengyun Manor.
From that year onward,
every year on my mother's birthday,
I've come to Xiangyang.
15 years ago,
your father came to Xiangyang.
- He did.
- When?
Also in autumn.
On the eve of the Jin family's Suwen Assembly.
[The House of Jiao]
Ling Long.
What are you doing?
Tell me the truth about
what happened 15 years ago,
and I'll let him go.
15 years ago?
On the eve of the Suwen Assembly 15 years ago,
Jiao Chao Gui was also in Xiangyang.
Being in Xiangyang,
he wouldn't stay anywhere else.
The night my aunt died,
he was also in Pagoda Lane.
She admitted it.
What else do you have to say?
What can I say?
What do you want?
Give me a straight answer.
You know exactly what I want.
I want to overturn my brother's conviction.
I want the Jin family to clear his name.
You can only prove that Tang Ji lied.
With just this evidence,
you cannot overturn the case.
For a lost cause,
you'd ruin the Jin family's reputation.
It's not worth the cost.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll take Fourth Aunt to the court.
I'll have her tell the truth.
Do you think the county court
will even take your case?
What official would be foolish enough
to reopen a case from 15 years ago?
If they won't take it,
I'll go to the prefectural court.
If that fails,
I'll go to the Kaifeng Court in the capital.
Enough proof or not,
I'll still take it to court.
Don't think about any tricks to free her.
I'll be guarding the door tonight.
No one is getting away.
In the autumn 15 years ago,
Jiao Chao Gui
did indeed come to visit me.
But that has nothing to do
with your aunt's case.
Aunt, you still refuse to tell the truth.
My cousin said that
although you often stayed in Tanxi Town
after marriage,
you never stayed away for long.
But starting 15 years ago,
you never returned to Shengyun Manor.
Why is that?
Because Jiao Chao Gui
took a concubine.
I didn't want to see them.
Out of sight, out of mind.
He took that concubine 17 years ago.
And she died of illness
in the winter 15 years ago.
Why did you go back when she was alive,
but once she was gone,
you never returned?
15 years ago,
the night my aunt died,
Jiao Chao Gui lived in Pagoda Lane.
Since then,
he has mastered the secret technique
of the Huo family.
He even developed a sword formation
to counter it.
Is all of this just a coincidence?
Jiao Chao Gui killed my aunt,
didn't he?
I don't know.
I really don't know anything.
Mrs. Jiao,
the crime scene was covered in sword marks.
They weren't left by
a scholar like Jin Xue Wen.
Jiao Chao Gui is dead.
He can no longer threaten you.
You don't need to have any more qualms.
Please tell us the truth.
I only want to find out
the truth about my aunt's death.
Rest assured.
If Jiao Chao Gui really killed my aunt,
since he is already dead,
I won't cause trouble for Jiao Si Yuan.
15 years ago...
[15 years ago]
Why did you go to Ling Long's place?
Why are you covered in blood?
Be quiet. Get home now.
Both of you, keep your mouths shut.
Take this and burn it.
What did you do to Ling Long?
When I left,
she was still breathing.
What happened after that, I cannot say.
You killed her?
Why would you do such a thing?
In the world of martial arts,
it's a matter of life and death.
Do you think Linglong Manor
didn't have a backup plan against me?
She died without telling me
where the Linglong Eye was.
I had to be ruthless.
Otherwise,
should I wait for the Huo family
to seek revenge on me?
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have told you that she was there.
- I'm the one who killed her.
- Shut up!
If anyone asks,
you know what to say.
The next day,
no sooner was your aunt's body found
than the authorities claimed
they'd caught the killer.
Jiao Chao Gui
heard that the one arrested was Jin Xue Wen.
He specifically instructed me,
if the officials came to ask,
to say that on that night,
I personally saw Jin Xue Wen
enter your aunt's courtyard.
That way, no one would suspect him.
So Jiao Chao Gui decided to frame Jin Xue Wen
after he had been arrested?
Yes.
To persuade me to testify,
he even said
that Jin Xue Wen
must have committed other crimes
to be arrested.
Even if he went to prison,
it wouldn't be an injustice.
That is all I know.
Not long after it happened,
my two maids
were also killed by him.
After that,
I never returned to Shengyun Manor.
When I heard he died a few days ago,
I only felt a sense of relief.
Justice, at last.
Your aunt's death has been avenged.
You claim to be my aunt's best friend,
yet you treated her like this.
If I hadn't forced you,
when were you going to reveal the truth?
When Jiao Chao Gui was still alive,
I could understand that
you acted out of fear of being killed by him.
But he'd been dead for a long time now.
Did you never think of speaking up for my aunt?
Have you never thought
of clearing Jin Xue Wen's name?
You're right.
For the past 15 years,
I have lived with constant guilt.
I failed your aunt.
She died so tragically,
yet I kept protecting her murderer.
Why do you all wear that same ugly look?
You only start weeping
once you've been exposed.
Do any of you truly feel regret?
Mrs. Jiao,
if you truly feel remorse,
go to court and tell the truth.
Give justice to the victims,
and clear the names of the deceased.
You're not going to talk?
I know what you're afraid of.
If you tell the truth,
Shengyun Manor's reputation will be ruined.
You're afraid the Huo family will retaliate.
Am I right?
Instead of fearing revenge that may come,
you should wonder whether your son
will live to see tomorrow.
I promise.
I'll do whatever you want.
Please spare Si Yuan.
He really doesn't know anything.
Ling Long,
please believe me.
I really want to make up for my mistake.
I've already failed once.
I won't let it happen again.
If you break your word,
don't worry about my father or brother.
I'll kill your son myself.
If you're thinking of running,
consider the consequences carefully.
My aunt died tragically,
and your brother was wronged for 15 years.
In their eyes,
it's as if a "sorry" can erase everything.
They keep talking about remorse,
but when asked to sacrifice their own interests
to seek justice for the deceased,
they start calculating for themselves.
We are getting closer and closer to the truth.
The truth?
Since Jiao Chao Gui had already severely
injured Aunt with a long sword,
why would he use a dagger to finish her?
Plus, Mrs. Jiao said
Jiao Chao Gui only decided to frame Jin Xue Wen
after he was already arrested.
That means the bloody clothes and dagger
weren't placed in the next room by him.
Do you really believe her?
She's telling the truth.
Since she admitted
that Jiao Chao Gui committed the murder,
there's no need to lie about the weapon.
True.
My brother and Jiao Chao Gui had no grievances.
He had no motive to frame him.
If Tang Ji did it
to cover up the poisoning back then,
wouldn't it have been easier
to just kill Jin Xue Wen?
Why go through all this trouble?
I remember you said
that the dagger indeed belonged to Jin Xue Wen.
That's right.
Fourth Uncle gave it to him
on my brother's birthday.
The one who framed him
must be someone close to Jin Xue Wen.
Or at least,
they knew beforehand
that Jin Xue Wen possessed such a dagger.
Only then could they frame him.
Not many would Fourth Aunt
shield like that.
And who knew Jin Xue Wen?
Very few.
Has Jin Zhen Ping made a move?
Not long after you left,
Jin Zhen Ping also left.
It's late.
You all had a long day.
Go back and rest.
I can handle this alone.
No need for everyone to stay here.
Don't worry.
San Lang.
Say something.
Why did they lock up Fourth Aunt's courtyard?
What on earth is going on?
They found out about Fourth Aunt's secret.
Young Seventeenth is shouting
about sending her to the authorities.
What?
What secret could Fourth Aunt have?
And why report it to the authorities?
If she goes to court,
the Jin family's reputation
will be completely ruined.
I said it from the start.
We shouldn't have let
those two troublemakers stay in the manor.
But you wouldn't listen.
What do we do now?
[Empty Light Chamber]
Don't move.
A few days ago,
she wrote a letter to Lord Liang.
This is his reply.
Madam.
Say nothing.
Ask nothing.
That's how you live longer.
Tomorrow, find someone
to deliver these two letters.
One is for Liang Er.
The other is for Lan Er.
Go now.
Yes.
Jin Zhen Ping.
To protect yourself,
you forced Fourth Aunt to her death.
You beast!
What nonsense are you talking?
You forced Fourth Aunt to testify in court.
She was so overcome with shame
that she took her own life.
It was you, Bai Yu Tang.
You are the one who drove her to it.
I drove her to her death?
Then why was she holding your jade pendant
when she died?
What is this?
I've never seen this before.
Fine.
Keep pretending.
Let's see how long you can keep it up.
Brother Bai.
Bai Yu Tang, calm down.
Jin Zhen Ping.
Are you doing this
simply because you fear Fourth Aunt
would bring shame to the Jin family?
Nonsense.
Do you really think a few outsiders
can overturn this case?
Fourth Aunt is dead.
And Tang Ji?
Don't expect him to recant his testimony.
Bai Yu Tang, let me tell you this.
Jin Xue Wen
will never be able to clear his name.
And you
will always be the brother of a murderer.
Jin Zhen Ping!
Do you hate us brothers that much?
What grudge did you have against my brother?
Bai Yu Tang.
Don't act on impulse.
Trust me.
We will definitely overturn the case.
Grandpa Xu.
Hold Fourth Aunt's funeral immediately.
Keep everything simple.
Jin Zhen Ping!
[Empty Light Chamber]
Fourth Aunt was such a kind-hearted person.
How could she pass away so suddenly?
The illness came on suddenly.
There was nothing we could do.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing here?
We've known each other for decades.
Am I not permitted to attend his funeral?
Is this the time for sentimentality?
Don't you understand the situation?
Zhan Zhao and the others are watching.
Zhan Zhao is busy elsewhere.
Si Ming wants Mrs. Jiao and Jiao Si Yuan dead.
Zhan Zhao and his men have rushed to save them.
Without you there,
the others are no match
for Zhan Zhao and his men.
Why should I go there?
Silencing them was Si Ming's order,
but that's not why I'm here.
Driving her to suicide
was not Si Ming's command.
You took it upon yourself,
didn't you?
Don't you realize?
If she fell into Zhan Zhao's hands,
none of us would survive.
Even if Si Ming hadn't ordered it yet,
he would have made the same decision as me...
What does your grudge
have to do with them?
For all these years,
living in your Jin family,
she never had a single good day.
I'd love for the entire Jin family
to be buried with her.
You want to save him?
What?
After all your investigating,
- you still don't know that he is--
- Tang Ji!
We are in the same boat.
- If the boat sinks, no one survives!
- Shut up!
About the struggle between you and Si Ming,
I'm no longer interested in.
Right now, I just want Jin Zhen Ping
to pay with his life.
I'm not trying to save him.
I just don't want him to die so easily.
Everyone says the Tang Sect acts without honor.
You're the chief. Why not change that?
Think carefully.
Is it worth risking your life
for a piece of trash like Jin Zhen Ping?
Let's see if you have
what it takes to put me in the ground.
Say it.
What exactly happened back then?
Tang Ji! Think carefully before you say it.
Do you want the whole Tang Sect
to be buried with you?
This is Tipsy Breeze.
It'll take at least two hours
for you to recover your inner power.
Come here.
What kind of madness is this?
The Jin family is on our side.
Why are you acting like a lover?
I beg Si Ming.
For the sake of Tang Sect's years of service,
please spare Tang Sect.
You failed the mission so badly,
and you still want to negotiate?
The Tang Sect's failure
is due to my poor leadership.
It has nothing to do with my disciples.
In the future,
if you need...
Uncle!
Starting today,
you are the chief of the Tang Sect.
I'll kill you!
Protect...
the Tang Sect.
Uncle!
[Joyful Stay Inn]
Are you applying medicine or carving wood?
Is that a knife in your hand?
Your wound is deep. Of course it hurts.
Spirits are what unlock these remedies.
Of course it hurts.
Aren't you a great hero? Can't you endure it?
That's easy for you to say.
Why don't you be the hero then?
If you've been serving your young master
like this all these years,
I really feel sorry for Zhan Zhao.
What are you doing?
If I don't wrap it tightly,
the wound will easily reopen.
I think you're just being delicate.
No matter how badly my young master
was injured over the years,
he never cried out like you.
Feeling bold, are you?
Zhan Zhao, good taste.
You picked a one-in-a-million servant.
How pretentious.
A reply from the capital.
Lord Bao helped us clarify two things.
First, the plague in Tanxi Town
was never reported to the capital.
Those inhumane acts
were not by His Majesty's decree.
Second,
the Xiangyang magistrate at the time
was the current Governor of Xiangzhou,
Luo Wen Jie.
Si Ming is now the Governor of Xiangzhou.
That is the highest official in Xiangzhou.
It will be hard to overturn the case.
Not necessarily.
Since we know who the presiding judge was
15 years ago,
why not just cut to the chase?
Let's have him preside over it again.
Overturning his own case?
How is that possible?
If it were at the prefectural court,
he wouldn't overturn it.
But if it's before the people of Tanxi Town...
If we lay the evidence before him,
piece by piece, in front of everyone,
he'll have no choice but to confess.
You mean
the Suwen Assembly?
I disagree.
Bai Yu Tang's healing skills
have long withered.
He's just a layman now.
How can he participate in the Suwen Assembly?
Young Seventeenth is a Jin descendant.
He and his brother are
independent of each other.
Not letting him attend
would be unreasonable.
Fifth Uncle.
Fourth Aunt has just passed away.
The whole manor is in mourning.
Can the Suwen Assembly be postponed?
The Suwen Assembly has never been interrupted
for a hundred years.
Nor has it ever been rescheduled
for weddings or funerals.
Tell me first.
Why did Tang Ji kill people at funeral hall?
Are you colluding with the Tang Sect?
Fifth Uncle.
The most important thing right now
is the Suwen Assembly.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Young Seventeenth's mind
isn't on the medical competition at all.
He's here to overturn the case for his brother.
If he really can overturn the case,
that would be a good thing.
It would clear the Jin family's name.
Why are you stopping him?
I don't want to collude with the Tang Sect,
but Fourth Aunt...
Fifth Uncle.
Let me tell you the truth.
If Bai Yu Tang overturns the case,
our Jin family
will surely have another scandal exposed.
Please pass a message.
We are from the Jin family of Tanxi Town.
We invite the Governor
to attend the Suwen Assembly tomorrow.
He's not going.
The Governor said
he's been busy with official business.
He has no time to attend.
Then forget it.
Don't blame us for not warning you
when the time comes.
A noble from the capital
will be attending the assembly.
If the Governor doesn't show up,
I'm afraid he'll cause offense.
A noble from the capital?
Indeed.
He is traveling and passing through Xiangzhou.
Hearing of such a grand event,
he's taken an interest
and wants to see the spectacle.
Forget it. Let's go.
Wait, you two.
Which noble from the capital
are you talking about?
Is everything you said true?
Have you verified it?
Fourth Aunt admitted it herself.
It cannot be false.
Why do you think Tang Ji
went on a killing spree at the funeral?
It's because Bai Yu Tang forced
Fourth Aunt to go to court.
Bai Yu Tang drove her to her death.
Fourth Aunt
protected the Jin family's reputation
and saved her children's dignity.
If she proved that
Jiu Lang went to Flying Petals Col,
their affair would be exposed.
Clearing one stigma
would only lead to another scandal.
For our Jin family,
there is no benefit at all.
Fifth Uncle,
it is better to keep our mouths shut.
It is an old case, after all.
Perhaps
not many people will remember it.
But if Jiu Lang
was truly framed,
then...
Chief.
Old Clan Leader, someone asked to see you.
He claims to be a steward
from the Prince's Residence.
Prince's Residence?
Invite him in at once!
Old Clan Leader.
I'm Zhao Zhi Er,
the steward for Prince Hui of Nanqing Palace.
I bring the Prince's verbal command here.
His Grace will attend
the Suwen Assembly this year.
Prince Hui is coming?
That is correct. His Grace was invited
by his good friend, Bai Yu Tang,
to watch him compete
with the masters of the medical world
in medicine and pharmacology.
Prince Hui's presence at the ceremony
truly brings great honor to our humble abode.