( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
"Yulin Bell"
I just recognized you
It's because of you and other beggars
Not quite the same
What's the difference?
your eyes
real beggar
Never afraid of the eyes of pedestrians
But you just dodged deliberately
Already showing timidity
I know why you are looking for me
It's just that even if I tell the truth
Can Mr. Zhan really vindicate an unjust case?
I've been working here for many years
But they know the methods of these officials very well.
I'll try my best
Moreover
You should also know
I won't get rid of you
They won't give up
If I can't find you again
I'm afraid those people
I'm going to attack your wife and daughter.
you
What to do?
Both he and Wang Xing have handled Jin Xue copywriting
Wang Xing is dead
Except for Luo Zhizhou
The case of that year
Only he knows how to find out
Do you remember
in missing files
What did you write?
Of course I remember
That page of the file
It was destroyed by Luo Zhizhou himself
The sword marks that Lord Zhan mentioned just now
It's recorded on that
That's what's recorded on it
This was the question asked during the first interrogation.
that night
I'm really not here
I stayed in the mountains all night
I went to collect medicine
Jin Xuewen explained
He collects herbs
It was to treat the plague that broke out in the town at that time.
He also said
This plague is actually caused by poisoning
He also wrote down the antidote he developed
Later Jin Xuewen was imprisoned
The prescription he handed over also had no content.
Days pass by
But there are more and more patients in the town
There's something fishy in my mind
At this time, Wang Xing found me
He said that when we inspected the site,
All the sword marks found have been erased
Jin Zhenping was a little anxious
Don't pay attention to him
When you undergo an injury examination
I must have also mentioned the sword marks on the deceased's body.
Those wounds are not fatal
But it's definitely not caused by the dagger
Enough to prove the presence of a third person at the scene
Such an important clue has been erased
You and Wang Xingding want to inform the county magistrate immediately
yes
What sword marks?
never seen
After today
I forgot all
Two
Forget it too
Xie adult
I respect you
Sir, I respect you too
The money given by adults
We dare not refuse
But it is unconscionable to wrongly accuse a good person.
We really feel uneasy
I am even more worried that he will kill someone and silence his family in the future.
That’s why I kept an eye on it
Hidden the file
Although the file is incomplete
But the remaining records above
Enough to prove my testimony just now
Faint official
-Faint official… -Faint official…
officialdom
sailing against the current
Am I not being ordered by someone?
The epidemic was severe that year
I dare not go out
that case
It was handled by Qiu Han.
Go ask him
Qiu Han?
The scribe next to me
The head of the family…
There are a lot of government troops coming outside.
Qinghui Hall was surrounded
Shao Jizu, the military commander of Xiangzhou Prefecture
Ordered to arrest Luo Wenjie, the magistrate for dereliction of duty
And took over the case of Jin Xuewen
All physical evidence and witnesses
Take them to the capital together
joke
first time i heard
When the government handles a case, they still take hostages.
Shao Gou, you are really eye-opening
I think you misunderstood
I'm not holding you hostage
I'm just afraid that something will pop up suddenly
Gangsters
The sword has no eyes
I'm afraid of hurting his life
back off
The witness who just testified to Jin Xuewen
Come out on your own
Don't wait for me to catch you
Whose order are you following?
Arrest Luo Wenjie?
I am the Minister of Fengdali Temple
Cheng Hao's order
Huiwang token is here
He personally ordered Zhan Zhao
Investigating the case of Luo Wenjie dereliction of duty
No matter how great the official position of Dali Temple Minister is,
No bigger than the prince
Parent life?
When did you die?
Did the prince himself tell you that in the carriage?
Exactly
The prince has arrived
I was on the carriage just now
told me about this
The prince is not here
So you have no basis for what you say
Set up a carriage and bluff here
You can bluff Luo Wenjie, but you can't bluff me.
No wonder you didn't disrupt the situation today
It turns out that I had a backup plan.
exhibition adult
Now that the carriage has been prepared
Don't mind if I requisition it
Let's take a look at the witnesses you finally gathered, shall we?
-Feng Shao-in
- Put all the witnesses on the carriage - Yes
Anyone who dares to obstruct will be killed without mercy.
Stop it all
I said you are a little thing
It's really a dog fighting against the power of others
The screams became more and more joyful
I am the prince
It's really cowardly
Anyone can search my carriage
without my consent
Still want to use it?
See King Hui
Okay, everyone is free of charge.
you just said
Who took charge of my brother's case?
Qiu Han
The scribe in my house
You guys, follow me
-yes-yes
Mr. Zhan handles the case
I and you all
Just wait here
Xiao Shao, even if you have official documents in hand
You shouldn't act so recklessly
You can search for this king's carriage as you please.
If others think
What should you do if you despise the imperial power?
I miss you and I have known each other for many years
I won’t pursue it this time.
Don't do it again in the future
Thank you, Your Majesty
Walk
fifth uncle
Where does the secret passage behind the Medicine King Statue lead?
Back Mountain Apricot Grove
My lord, please lend me a horse.
He won't escape
at the moment
He has more important things to do than escape.
Head of the Jin family, everyone
Today, the Suwen Conference was disturbed by the overturn of the verdict.
Really sorry
My lord, I'm afraid there's still danger here.
Why don't you take the magistrate and the witnesses with you?
Follow the official
OK
If you hurry up, it will delay the big thing and I'll take your head off.
Siming
King Hui has really arrived
The most important thing right now is another account book
If it falls into Zhan Zhao's hands
Master these years
All the hard work he put into the government was wasted.
No, you were fooled
They let you back on purpose
Zhan Zhao catches up
Let's go to the city first. There are still people available in the city.
How can you guys beat Zhan Zhao?
Just buy some time
etc.
There is an ambush
Shao Jizu
Bai Daxia
Are you tired from playing?
Would you like to have some tea here?
Commander Shao is still a bit clever.
Wait until we get what we want
It’s never too late to drink
They are all dead soldiers of Zhongxiao Academy
It seems to fascinate them
It’s not Ye Motian at all
This person will be surprised
They were probably the ones who killed Jiao Chaogui.
I just saw the people from Wu Cheng Tang heading to the west of the city.
That's not the direction of the state government office.
People from Tang Clan?
Right now, the most important thing for Siming is to destroy the account books
Not going to the Yamen
That must be his own mansion
Go and protect the evidence
I still have soldiers here who can protect myself.
Si Ming is lost
Leave it to you
Take action
Tang Tianhao
Stop it all
I told you all to stop
Following the order of King Hui
Seize the state government office
If there is any disobedience, you will be arrested immediately.
June of the second year of Jingyou
Kang Liang sued Zhuang Yu for raping a civilian girl
contained in the dossier
Kang Liang said that his daughter refused to obey and hit the pillar and died.
But there is no witness in this case
Hou Kangliang withdrew the lawsuit
This case and Jingyou’s four years
Sued by Mo Erlang of Yi County
Zhuang Duo was involved in the case of raping a civilian girl
Income after verification of household registration
Zhuang Yu and Zhuang Duo are cousins
The two jointly run a brothel in Yi County
After investigation
Kang Liang withdrew the lawsuit three days later
Falling off a cliff and dying
Yes, just put it there, okay
This fish is just like the people in the yamen
What a great meal
Look at that one
So fat
Let's let the white mice catch two and roast them
OK
This is the other half of the lost account books in the Zhongxiao Academy case
Brother Zhan is sealing up the physical evidence
good
I thought that Siming Qiu Han was in a high position
Unexpectedly, he was just a scribe who was familiar with the archives.
Relying on the clues in the records, he
to detect unjust, false and wrongful convictions
Standing behind Zhizhou
Firmly control the officials of all sizes within Xiangzhou's jurisdiction
Isn’t he a talented person?
What a pity
Talent used in the wrong place
What's wrong?
Xiao Tang has taken over as the head of Tang Clan.
He was the one who took the order just now
Destroy these accounts
Just a little bit
you see
You should also take a look. There is a bounty. Take a look.
Have you seen it?
Grandpa Xu
Saburo
Was it really you?
What did I do?
I don't understand what you are saying
Are you still hiding it from me?
I knew it back then
I'm in your fourth uncle's house
Have you seen this dagger?
it should be a pair
Fourth uncle is doing good pharmacology for you two.
I gave one to each of you.
It was in court
Jin Xuewen tried his best to cry out injustice
Then I thought of it
I rummaged through your box
As a result, I found nothing
That year
Why didn't you report me?
Saburo
How can I report you?
You are the Jin family's only hope
without you
The Jin family has no heirs
But it's all over
Grandpa Xu
You don’t even ask me
Why did you kill the girl?
Why should I ask more?
You must be doing it for the Jin family
I did this for the greater good.
I'm here for the Jin family
I really have no choice but to
If I don't kill them
Our Jin family is doomed
But now they are still haunting me and are coming back to haunt me.
They won't let me go
Confused, Saburo
Where does the wronged soul come from?
Who is pestering you?
It's obviously Zhan Zhao's group of people
you're right
It's Zhan Zhao and the others
It's Xiao Qi and the others
They must have guessed it was me.
But how did they know about the dagger?
Why didn't you throw away the dagger?
I…
I use this dagger
I exchanged Jin Xuewen's prescription for treating the plague with Siming.
Si Ming has used this dagger to control me all these years
completion
It's over, something big is going to happen
Saburo
Don't panic
You have been practicing medicine for so many years
I have made so many friends in the world of martial arts
Think of a way
Just tell them to shut up
I don't believe it
No one yet
Can't help you
If what happened back then were exposed,
Don't let anyone have an easy time
Your fourth wife and my uncle are both no longer alive.
The grudges of the previous generation
Ashes to dust, dust to dust
Why did you come to me?
The Seven-Day Drunken Dream concocted by the Tang Sect
Killed so many people
You don’t really think that Tang Ji was buried
Can you get rid of the relationship?
Such a heavy sin
once exposed
Do you know the consequences?
The fate of the Tang clan and the Jin family
They were tied together as early as fifteen years ago
Do you still want to be alone?
Now Zhan Zhao and the others are biting me and won’t let go.
One day I fall into their hands
I will definitely drag Tangmen to be buried with him
What do you want?
Think of a permanent solution
get rid of them
Earlier you and your uncle teamed up for a game
None succeeded
What else can I do?
Are you not with that girl from the Huo family?
Is the relationship good?
I'll definitely find an opportunity to take action.
You've got the wrong person
Linglong no longer considers me a friend
Zhan Zhao knows that I will inherit the throne
I worked hard for Si Ming
The Tang Sect is beyond redemption
Now even you dare to threaten me
Except Si Ming
You are the only one who witnessed what happened back then
kill you
Isn’t it much easier than killing Zhan Zhao?
Sanlang, be careful, Sanlang, go quickly
-Xu... -Let's go, Saburo
Let's go
I didn't expect you to be such a loyal old servant.
Then I'll do the surgery on you first.
How you behave now
He looks a lot like your uncle
you are no match for me
I'll let you go today
I have sealed both of your big holes
Even though you have great abilities
I can't do it either
Tang Tianhao
You really want Linglong to see it
Are you looking like this now?
Grandpa Xu
Conversation between Tang Tianhao and Jin Zhenping
Did you hear it all?
I beg you
Take me to see my fifth uncle
say what you heard
Tell him everything
Jin Zhenping abandoned you and ignored you
Do you still want to help him?
You know his secret now
Do you think he would believe you were keeping secrets?
Will he let you go?
good
I will confess to the clan leader right now
Walk
I save your life
You actually want to kill me?
Xiao Qi
I will repay kindness with hatred, because I can't help you
But I have no other way
If you want to hate, just hate me.
This is for the Jin family, I am for the Jin family
For the Jin family?
Only Saburo
Able to inherit the Jin family's family business
Only he can protect the Jin family
Jin Xuewen
frivolous and debauched
Unlearned and incompetent
Even if he is in the medical field
How to make achievements
Nor is he worthy of being the head of the Jin family.
even though
You know your Saburo is a murderer
Do you also think he is better than my brother?
Yes, he is a murderer
But except him
No one can bear the burden of the Jin family
Compared with the future of the Jin family
your brother
What does he mean?
good
I understand
Just do it
you want to kill me
But you dare not watch me die?
look at me
Xu An's knife
Although it is not inserted deeply
But the central vein
No need for you to talk nonsense
I know I'm dying
Xiao Qi
Don't blame me
I am also doing it for the Jin family
Kim Jin-pyeong
You make me understand
Why did you kill Miss Huo?
Why put the blame on my brother?
Does it matter?
you don't say
I also know why
you are jealous of him
He is more talented than you
Am I jealous of him?
I made Qingyin Powder when I was fourteen
Sitting in the hospital to see a doctor at the age of fifteen
Won the first prize at the Su Wen Conference at the age of 28
Why should I be jealous of him?
What a joke
The antidote to the seven-day drunken dream
It's from my brother's hand
You can't make an antidote
Only my brother can
Are you afraid that he will steal your position as head of the family?
So he was poisoned on the eve of the Suwen Conference.
You're talking nonsense
He is not worthy of competing with me for the head of the family.
What kind of seven-day drunken dream?
I don't understand what you are saying
Stop fooling yourself
After the Suwen Conference
There are already rumors in the town
Except for that prescription
I haven't seen you make any other achievements in these years.
And that year
You can only save people with mild symptoms
There is nothing you can do for the seriously ill
Because that prescription was made by my brother
Shut up
God gave you fifteen years
fifteen years
You still can’t find the morning and evening cocoon
How to lead the Jin family’s treasure?
It was almost lost in your hands
You will never reach the heights that my brother once had
I told you to stop talking
Why?
Why is he smarter than me?
Why no matter how hard I try
Can't you compare to a prodigal like him?
fifteen years
I study medicine every day
In the end, what is remembered by the world is just a prescription
And this recipe was written by Jin Xuewen
You finally admitted it
fifteen years
I should have admitted it long ago
that year
There's an epidemic in town
I know it very well
Who can quell this disaster?
Who can win the first prize in the Suwen Conference?
I went into the mountains
Treat seriously ill patients
But I never expected
I broke up the secret meeting between my fourth aunt and Tang Ji
What I didn't even expect was that
It turns out that the epidemic in the town
It was caused by the seven-day drunken dream that the two of them jointly concocted.
Tang Ji wants to kill me and silence me
- Stopped by the Fourth Aunt - Don't kill him
My fourth aunt told me the poisonous nature of the seven-day drunken dream
I hope I can find an antidote as soon as possible
Can quell this disaster
I also hope to take this opportunity
Become the head of the Jin family
But no matter how I develop it
I can't even make an antidote
Xu An told me that Jin Xuewen often goes to the mountains
I feel very suspicious
I followed him all the way
I heard his conversation with Miss Huo
You really got it right
This plague is indeed caused by poisoning
Where did you learn about this?
Don't ask about this matter
The less you know, the safer you are
Now that you say that, I'm even more curious.
You said you are from a girl's family
Came to our town alone
He still carries such a big secret
Is there any way you can save people?
Look at the whole Xiangzhou
There are only a handful of people who can detoxify this poison.
happen
There is such a person sitting in front of you
Thank you for helping me with this
It's me who thanks you
At first I was embarrassed in front of you
Call yourself a good doctor
Actually
Just so I can talk to you a few more words
later
In order to accept your entrustment
Go to the mountains to diagnose and treat patients
I can only bite the bullet and light up the lamp to read medical books.
He actually brought back some of the medical skills that had been neglected for many years.
So, I should be the one thanking you
I have been studying the recipe for many days
He actually drew it up easily
How could I just look at him?
Take away my position as head of the family?
And the girl surnamed Huo Na
I don’t know how she learned the secret of the seven-day drunken dream.
Once she shakes it off
Then wouldn’t my Jin family become the sinners of Tanxi Town?
So they both must die
must die
The day I took action
I took the incense to Huaihua Lane
But I didn't expect that someone would be one step ahead of me and take action first.
What's terrible is that he didn't kill him thoroughly.
I still need to make up for it myself.
After killing the girl
I went next door and found that Jin Xuewen was not at home
God help me
I have a plan in mind
Why not blame Jin Xuewen for killing the girl?
Let him live a life worse than death
Let his younger brother be unable to hold his head up for the rest of his life
Isn't this wonderful?
Xiao Qi, you have misunderstood Jin Xuewen over the years.
on his deathbed
What he is thinking about most is you, his younger brother.
Qiu Han cheated on Jin Xuewen
He lied to him
The county magistrate took money from the murderer
He will definitely be sentenced to death
He is just a little scribe
But I can’t bear to see Jin Xuewen innocently being wronged
he promised to help him
fake death escape
But there is a condition
Kim Seol Moon must write a confession
In this way, he can give an explanation to the county magistrate.
Jin Xuewen recognized it at first
I agreed to sign this confession.
But when he signs the payment
He regretted
Even though I can survive by writing a confession
But my brother will blame me for this crime
I can't hold my head up for the rest of my life
I can't let him be embarrassed anymore by what I did.
I beg you
Is there any other way?
no way
Hurry and finish writing the confession
No, I won't write anymore
Haven't you finished writing this?
name
I can add it for you
open