(Love In Sync)
(Kim Myung Soo)
(Kang Min Ah)
(Love In Sync)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
Let's do it. The kiss.
How can you suggest a kiss so easily?
You don't know my profession?
I am an actress.
If you run away this time, you are dead.
It is work, just work.
Gosh.
Is it right to cast a supporting actor...
through an audition without consulting it...
with the lead actor?
Do I have to consult with you about something like that?
Yes, you do.
If you cast someone who seems to be of a lower calibre,
the lead actor will also appear to be of a lower calibre.
If you cast someone who stands out too much,
our Yi Jin will be overshadowed,
so how can I not worry about that?
Right? And above all,
this is truly not right, is it?
Right? Why is the lead actor...
who stepped down due to a power abuse controversy...
auditioning for a supporting role?
If she wants to audition, is there any reason to stop her?
There is no justification.
We should stop her even if we have to create a justification.
Things are going strangely.
Why are you being so sensitive?
Thanks to this, the movie is getting promoted, which is good.
Without even needing much marketing,
our movie is very popular these days.
That is the problem.
If Ji An, who is merely auditioning for a supporting role,
becomes more popular than our Yi Jin,
she will be overshadowed. It is her first time...
to be the lead actress.
Oh, gosh.
Don't do the audition.
It isn't too late, so cancel that audition.
I'll pick out a good one from my agency.
Mr. Kim, are you going to keep acting like this?
Acting like what?
If you interfere with every little thing and find fault...
throughout the entire film shoot, then I...
cannot work with Han Yi Jin.
Director, it is a misunderstanding.
Our CEO cares about me, so he is acting like this...
in case I am intimidated. This will not happen again.
If you are so displeased, then just cancel the contract.
- What? - It isn't too late...
since filming has not started yet.
No, Director Moon.
What?
Anyway, Mr. Kim, you are quite a character.
Me? What?
Let's talk later.
Director Moon.
Please wait.
Anyway, that guy is too arrogant because he is doing well.
Hey.
If you came along, you should be a supporter, not a hindrance.
Why are you silent as a stone?
That's why I told you I wouldn't go along with you from the start.
What's the big deal about a supporting role audition?
Do you know how much I'm struggling because of you?
Frankly, if you just had star power,
would I be doing this humiliating thing?
Look now.
If you search for the movie title on portals,
news about Ji An's supporting role audition comes out first...
before news about you who plays a lead role.
Do you think it makes sense?
That's just buzz.
Buzz is popularity, and popularity is star power.
Something you can never take from Yu Ji An.
I guarantee you, if Ji An gets a role through auditioning,
and joins this film as a supporting actress,
it's only a matter of time before you, the lead, get overshadowed.
So, if you don't want to lose what you just barely took back,
you need to stay focused.
I've made up my mind.
What decision are you talking about?
For a life without regrets, I'll put aside temporary embarrassment.
And I'll do my best with what I can do now.
Oh, no, no. Just now,
I must have misheard you, right?
You heard correctly.
The sound of my heart.
Why are you doing kisses by time of day,
changing locations and weather?
Well, I have no choice.
The audition is coming up soon, and a kiss is definitely...
what causes emotional transference.
Since I could not find any other variable to make it possible,
we have to try everything we can.
Then I will start.
No matter how much I think about it,
this isn't the right thing to do.
There isn't anything else we can do right now.
Still, this is a bit much.
What is it?
Are you perhaps afraid that you will really fall for me?
Oh, well...
- No, I am not. - Then why?
It is business, just work.
Who got the audition?
(Closed)
(Tok Tok Mental Care)
Finally, we succeeded in kissing...
at all hours of the day.
But we failed to reverse the situation.
What should I do?
Today is the day of auditioning, but...
If there is no emotional transference...
You know well about my acting.
Why don't you start practising the acting...
Aren't you thirsty?
Do you want some sparkling water?
I will take it right away.
Please stop it.
Why are you doing this now?
Just leave me alone.
Ji An, are you okay?
(Mom)
Ji An...
actually attempted it before.
There are rumours that it was due to family matters.
There are also rumours that it was because of money.
The first time I lived with my mother...
was when I was seven years old.
Before that, I lived in relatives' houses...
and my maternal grandmother's house.
Then eventually,
she sent me to the orphanage.
Do you know where my mother first took me...
after taking me out of the orphanage?
An audition for child models.
Thank you.
It is funny, right?
Someone said that.
That child models earn a lot of money.
I was pretty even when I was young.
You know, a born natural beauty, right?
I should have been a little less pretty.
Then such a tragedy would not have happened in my life.
Do you know what the biggest tragedy for my mother and me is?
My mother always needs me.
You cannot live as a member of "I Want" forever.
Now is the time to become star Yu Ji An.
Not in a cheap place like this,
we can live in the most luxurious penthouse.
As befits us.
I foolishly loved...
that kind of mother.
Just...
I just wanted to be loved by my mother.
("Idol Group 'I Want' Is Disbanded By Yu Ji An's Leaving")
But one day, I realised.
Is it true?
This isn't the time to be getting my makeup done leisurely.
I had become someone no one loved.
So I ran away with all my might.
I came all this way, fighting for my life.
But you still love your mother so much.
So I am afraid...
that she will appear before me again...
and ruin me.
I am afraid that I will go back to those old days.
If it happens,
I will protect you.
I am your manager.
I am sorry.
Mister.
I always thought about it after that day.
If only I hadn't let go of my sister's hand...
I am the one who made the biggest mistake.
Why am I the only one...
who is perfectly fine?
You must have had a very hard time.
I finally found it.
So, you finally snagged a judge's seat?
Why are you doing this?
I am also a legitimate investor in this film.
I have every right to be in this position.
Isn't that right, Director Moon?
Next, number 358, Yu Ji An, please come in.
Hello.
I am Yu Ji An.
It has been a long time.
You have a performance prepared, right?
Yes.
(What are you talking about?)
(The data is gone? Are you serious right now?)
What? What are you talking about?
The data is gone?
Are you serious right now?
Are you saying she betrayed us?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
You don't know what kind of situation we are in right now?
We are almost there.
I am finally able to expose all of her schemes.
But now, betrayal?
Then we are just creating a way for her to escape.
But you are so calm saying that now?
Go find that woman right now.
Somehow, right now.
("Yu Ji An Passes On The Audition, Assuring Her Comeback")
If Ji An gets a role through auditioning,
and joins this film as a supporting actress,
it's only a matter of time before you, the lead, get overshadowed.
Was I that cute?
No, I was not thinking like that.
It is an error of emotional transference. An error.
I told you it was not. It was an error.
Oh, where is the error?
That is perfectly accurate.
Do not misunderstand. There could be such a thing...
as an empathy error. Gosh.
Should we take a picture?
That's great.
Dong Gyeong, please take a picture of us.
Me?
(Congratulations on Yu Ji An's Comeback!)
Okay.
Okay, I will take it.
One, two, three.
I told you it was an error.
- I don't think so. - Okay.
Then go on in.
What was that?
I am not someone who got caught cheating.
There was a call from the real estate agent.
The people who saw the house today want to sign a contract.
I want to sign a contract tomorrow, right away.
- Song Hwan. - You may not know this,
but for someone like me, this kind of house is inconvenient.
Then I will call the real estate agent tomorrow.
When spring comes,
let's move then.
When winter passes and spring comes...
If we leave the house in spring,
I think I will feel less cold.
Gosh, so this was meant to be.
It took a long time to get here.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you too.
But how did your acting skills...
improve so much in such a short time?
There is a secret to everything.
Then I can look forward to it.
Of course.
Ha Yul, are you okay?
Gosh.
It hurts.
- Ha Yul. - It hurts.
Stop it. Please stop crying!
What happened, Song Hwan?
He...
abandoned me.
The sound of a child crying...
He said he was sick and tired of her crying.
But Eun Hwan,
I am also so sick and tired of this.
I am so scared of myself.
What should I do?
What should I do about Ha Yul?
Please, please help me.
It's okay. It's okay, Song Hwan.
I am here for you, right?
Don't worry too much.
Kids just get hurt as they grow up, you know.
Is Ha Yul okay?
Yes, she is okay.
You don't have to worry.
- Is she okay? - Don't...
Don't touch my child.
I was just worried.
Who are you to say that?
By what right?
If it hadn't been for you...
If it hadn't been for someone like you, my father and I...
Song Hwan.
Please.
I am sorry.
Please pass me Ha Yul.
- Please take care of Ji An. - Okay.
Song Hwan is a bit prickly.
We will leave this house as soon as Ha Yul wakes up.
Song Hwan.
I don't want to be treated like baggage by you anymore.
You have done enough, I suppose.
Now, you don't have to be held back by me. Live comfortably.
You are not disabled, not like me.
You hate Ji An, don't you?
Yes, I hate her.
I hate her so much.
Every time I struggle with misfortune,
I'm angry because I feel like it's all her fault.
Every time she smiles in front of me,
pretending she doesn't know anything,
I want to spit on her.
Are you done?
But Song Hwan,
I feel sorry for that woman.
Living with guilt on her back...
It seems like she's similar to me.
I know how suffocating it is to live...
while enduring the gaze of someone who resents me.
I know it best.
- Cha Eun Hwan. - I know.
Song Hwan, I know everything.
That is why I am hesitating.
I stop and will not go any further.
Just three months.
Just three months in this place.
During that period...
Can you please cut me slack?
Cha Eun Hwan.
- What happened? - I don't want to be...
involved with you anymore.
- Is she okay? - Don't touch my child.
Who are you to say that? By what right?
What business do you have with me?
I think I need to know now.
The inexplicable hostility you showed me...
from the first time we met,
and Eun Hwan's mind...
which made him confused while looking at me.
I want to know the reason of them.
Tell me.
What did you mean yesterday when you said...
it was because of me?
Do you really want to know?
It meant nothing.
What?
Yesterday, you clearly said it was because of me.
I was just angry and said whatever came to mind.
I am tired, so please leave.
- Are you alright? - Please save me.
I will definitely save you.
Aren't you getting ready?
Today is the day for your costume fitting.
- Excuse me... - You will be late.
Please get ready quickly.
If I had not touched Father's respirator,
perhaps all this misfortune would have passed us by.
Right.
It cannot be.
I will definitely save you.
I am sorry, mister.
It cannot be.
Yes.
Why? What is it?
Well... Thank you for this morning.
I have no other intentions.
It is just that I hate things getting complicated.
Anyway, all we have to do is leave, right?
It will be spring, right?
If we pretend not to know until then,
then it will be fine, right?
Yes.
Thank you, Song Hwan.
But do you know that?
You are more cruel to Yu Ji An than I am.
You are at least preparing for this,
but from Yu Ji An's perspective, it will feel like she is struck...
by lightning.
She'll feel that miserable feeling,
being abandoned by someone for no reason.
How could...
Both of you...
Right.
Say hello.
This is Manager Cha, who is now my real manager.
I am also suspicious of that.
Because the alibi times match exactly.
Jung In speaks with an excited face,
which does not suit the situation.
Right. It is like he wants...
to play a game with us.
It's making me excited.
It is like he put us into a game that was already set up.
Have you met that woman, his wife, by any chance?
Next, scene 33. Su Ji hears the news of her husband's death...
and cries out like a wailing beast.
Say hello. This is Manager Cha, who is now my real manager.
So, if you don't want to lose what you just barely took back,
you need to stay focused.
No.
That cannot be.
Why my husband?
Who did this?
Detective, please.
Please save my husband.
What should I do?
How should I live now?
I am not intimidated by Yi Jin.
I am worried.
Because tomorrow is my first shoot.
Who said anything?
You just said something.
I heard everything.
You always reveal other people's true feelings...
without permission.
Shall we go to Han River?
Once filming starts, I will not be able to move.
So, we can heal ourselves before then.
You are an actress, and you're not managing your condition?
What if you catch a cold?
It will affect the shoot.
No, who said I would be there for a long time?
Let's get some fresh air for a moment.
What if you get caught up in a baseless rumour like last time?
If you get into a scandal with a manager...
who you have no relationship with,
it won't be good for your image.
Alright. I am not going.
Is that enough?
What kind of relationship do you have with Yi Jin?
Is she someone special to you?
Yi Jin and I are simply a client...
and a counsellor.
Right?
I thought so.
It's just that she was my first client, so it's a bit more special.
Special, my foot.
What did you consult her about?
She didn't seem to be struggling at all.
What is this?
This feeling of being curious about me?
I am just proud of you.
I am so proud of you...
because you're finally curious about such things.
However...
The content of counselling must not be disclosed to others.
That is a counselling principle.
If you are really curious, think about it.
Why a young female celebrity named Han Yi Jin...
came to a counsellor after her group disbanded.
Thinking about such things...
That would be empathy.
Ji An, how about this outfit for today?
It's good.
Should I wear this one next?
Oh, yes, that will be nice.
You know how to cinch the waist here, right?
- Oh, I know, I know. - Like this. Okay.
I know you are pretty, but today you are especially pretty.
- Hello. Yu Ji An from I Want. - Hello.
Would an interview be possible for a moment?
Thank you. Let's move slightly.
We will move slightly.
You've returned with I Want's album with all members this time.
Please say a word to your waiting fans.
Yes, until now, I Want...
Just a moment.
Ji An, could you please do it?
Yes, to all the fans who have waited for us until now,
thank you very much.
We prepared this album very diligently,
so please give us a lot of attention and endless love.
Then, so far, I Want!
- Yes, I Want... Yes, thank you. - Thank you.
Please look forward to I Want's full-group album.
Thank you.
("'I Want' Is Disbanded And Yu Ji An Will Debut As A Solo")
Please walk slowly.
You are walking this fast because it's the first shoot?
Just come with me.
Why are you doing this? You are embarrassing me.
Am I a grade schooler?
You're not an overprotective parent.
What? You're embarrassed?
Hey, why are we doing this for?
Is it because of me?
Of course.
As a rule, no one dislikes it when you feed them.
The one who feeds gets more respect than the one who does not.
That is how life is.
Who knows.
They might even give you an extra reflector over Ji An.
That Ji An is truly something.
Just stay still.
We will take care of everything.
Ji An was also raised this way.
Speak of the devil, and she shall appear.
That is a very good thing.
I like that it isn't obvious.
How is it, being a manager?
It isn't easy, is it?
Not really.
I know everything without you saying it.
Ji An's temper isn't ordinary.
Her capriciousness is also deadly.
Even now, if she isn't in a good mood,
she acts up, doesn't she?
- Not really. - What?
Why have you been speaking informally to me since earlier?
Because you spoke informally to me first?
You seem to care a lot about your actors.
The CEO even comes to the set in person.
Even though I am a CEO of the company,
I care for them with the heart of their fathers'.
As for me,
I truly think of my actors as my own children.
Indeed.
But it seems Ji An was disowned.
No, during the power abuse controversy,
it seemed like you didn't protect her like parents.
There was no attempt to settle with the victim, no media control,
and no legal action at all.
Oh, that was...
The timing was so bad at that time.
She wasn't even our agency's actress anymore,
so what right did I have?
Frankly, what obligation did I have?
Indeed. I also find that very strange.
How such a controversy erupted at a perfect time...
for Ji An to take all the blame alone.
As if someone did it on purpose.
Alright, let's take a picture before the first shoot.
Everyone, please gather around.
Yes, please gather here.
Yes.
Well... That spot is for the lead actor.
Right.
It has become a habit.
Alright, we are shooting.
One, two, three.
Ready. Action.
What? What did you just say?
What is he doing?
He should be watching Ji An's acting, not the script.
He doesn't have basics down.
What do you want me to do?
I am not an actor who moves according to the script they wrote.
CCTV footage that appears to be Kang Jun Ho has been found.
We both fell for their scheme.
Hang up for now.
Who interfered and how?
It means there is someone in this team helping them.
Cut.
Ji An's emotions are so good.
Oh, really?
Yes. Is this your first shoot, right?
Your immersion is incredible.
- Still, let's try one more take. - Okay.
You saw people were surprised when I was acting earlier, right?
I am telling you I saw it more than ten times.
I even heard Director Moon's praise.
I am also telling you I heard it more than ten times.
Thank you.
This is all thanks to Eun Hwan,
no, Manager Cha.
Should we just sign a lifetime contract?
This time, I will sign a contract with you...
with the best treatment in the industry.
How long are you going to rely on my emotions?
Ji An, you are an actress.
Then you should try to feel your emotions yourself...
and act.
Who says I won't?
I am just grateful, anyway.
Three months.
When that contract period ends,
we will go back to our respective places.
Don't forget that.
Sometimes, I lose my temper, but I don't hold grudges.
Why am I suddenly angry now?
No, I cannot understand.
Ji Woong has a lot of schedules.
Our Ji An also has just as many schedules.
- No. - It isn't polite...
to give one person the first and last scenes.
It was not my anger.
If he's going to act like that behind my back,
why did he act like that in front of me?
Look over there.
I saw it. Why?
That man is my manager.
Are you bragging about your current manager...
in front of your former manager?
Is this EXchange or something?
I won't send you text messages from now on.
I am sorry. Just a moment.
Yes, I am Yu Ji An's manager.
Yes. A commercial?
Oh, yes.
Gosh. How long has it been...
since I smelled the scent of the advertising agency?
Is it that good?
You seem happier than when you were cast in a movie.
This commercial is a measure of popularity.
Among them, only the top of the top can film a shampoo commercial.
And most importantly, the unit price is high.
What?
I need to earn money quickly to lift the provisional attachment.
At one time, all the posters hanging here had my face on them.
Oh, I heard we were doing a test shoot today,
I practised some poses for the first time in a while, so take a look.
Okay.
You are fluttered, right?
No, what nonsense.
– Is it really not true? – I said it isn't.
Is that so?
Your heart is beating so fast.
You fool.
Do you think you can hide it?
What kind of relationship do you think we have?
A relationship where feelings are conveyed.
No matter how mean you are to me,
I wouldn't fall for it.
I know it isn't sincere.
So,
please stop being cold to me on purpose.
I already feel like I am being ostracized...
by everyone in the world these days.
If Eun Hwan does that too,
then I will have nowhere to lean on.
I need to go to the restroom before the meeting.
Wait a moment.
Yes, hello.
We are near there. Right in front... What?
You want to cancel the contract now?
We don't want to do this either, but...
Have you not seen the article yet?
("Brand Loves Her, But Consumers Still Refuse Her")
("Yu Ji An's New Controversy About Her Commercial")
I'm Han Seo Jun, a reporter from the Taejin Sports entertainment desk.
If you have time, let's do a quick interview.
Do you want to go to Han River?
So this is...
It is the Han River for comfort.
It is alright.
You don't have to worry that much.
It isn't like this is the 1st or 2nd time this has happened.
At this point, even wounds...
I don't get used to them.
It still hurts.
Because the truth has not been revealed yet.
When the truth is revealed, then...
What is the...
truth?
Eun Hwan, do you really believe...
I didn't do that?
The Yu Ji An I know...
would never do such a thing.
Gosh.
You're serious.
That's touching.
But what should I do?
I did it.
I was so embarrassed that I didn't want to say this.
That video...
They said it wasn't manipulated.
They said it was the original.
So,
they say I really did that...
to Mi Jeong.
What should I do?
I feel sorry for Mi Jeong.
You have no idea what kind of situation this is...
What is it now?
Are you brutally executing someone who turned themselves in?
Just look at it first.
You have no idea, right?
Oh, this is so frustrating. It is so annoying.
What are all these problems after recruiting a wrong person?
Isn't something a little strange?
What is it?
You know that your language proficiency...
is lacking compared to the general standard, right?
Me? Not at all.
I have never heard that before.
Is that so?
Since you heard it now, keep it in mind from now on.
Someone like Ji An,
who lacks language proficiency and are immature in emotional control,
their words would be all jumbled up when they're angry, but look.
She is speaking so precisely and smoothly, isn't she?
Why are you crying?
- Because of you... - It's like she is reciting lines...
from a drama she memorized.
I told you not to cry.
Did you practice lines with Mi Jeong...
a lot in the past?
Almost every project.
So, what you're saying is...
I was not actually abusing my power in the video,
but practising lines?
And Mi Jeong maliciously edited it...
and uploaded it as an abuse of power video?
Probably.
No, why?
Why would Mi Jeong do that to me?
I don't know.
We will only know for sure after meeting her.
It could be for her own personal goal.
Or it could be that she was paid by someone...
who wants Ji An to fall.
Can you even think?
You have no idea what kind of situation this is, do you?
The video isn't manipulated, so the situation cannot be false.
What are all these problems after recruiting a wrong person?
What cases are there where it isn't the truth?
Hey.
I am genuinely curious, so I am asking you.
Does your family know you act like this?
Oh, look at her.
Are you crying?
Hey, why are you crying?
Who should be crying because of you right now?
Don't cry.
I told you not to cry.
(Universe in the Room)
I received the call and checked.
The Universe in the Room was an independent film.
An independent film?
A top star like Ji An?
Back then, she was pretending to be artsy for a long time,
so she made many special appearances in independent films...
to build up her acting skills and to transform her image.
But why can't I find any information about the film...
when I search for it?
There is no way you would find any.
The production was cancelled early on.
So, there is no data.
Is that so?
Then what about the script she received at the time?
That's gone too.
I don't know about anything else,
but one thing I remember clearly is this.
They were worried the script would be leaked,
so they only sent the parts Ji An appeared through quick service.
However...
Why are you so curious about that movie?
- It's nothing. - Okay.
I will be going now.
What are you doing?
Do Hoon.
Isn't the stigma of being a traitor...
- difficult for you? - What?
You are someone who cares about Ji An.
Can you see it, Counsellor?
That mind toward her?
I am a psychological counsellor, you know.
That is why I want to give you...
a chance to clear your name...
from the stigma of being a traitor.
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
Oh, yes. I dropped a coin.
Where did it go?
This was yours.
It's good to be thrifty. Right.
Hey, Manager!
You found my coin, so I will buy you a drink.
How about it?
- That's good. - Oh, yes.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
So...
Is there only one you found out? The film director's name?
I tried contacting the Film Commission...
and the Independent Film Association,
but they don't have his contact information.
Of all people, that film director's name is Kim Min Su.
It is a very common name in Korea.
Hey, if you search for Kim Min Su...
on social media, there are thousands of them.
Are you telling me to search through all those thousands of people?
Are you crazy?
We have no choice.
This is the best option in this situation.
If we find that director, we can clear...
Ji An's rumour from the power abuse accusation.
Oh, I don't know. Hey, why do I have to do that?
- Because... - I am not doing this...
as a former fan club president.
- Because you are my brother. - What?
Dong Gyeong!
Add the honorific.
My dear Dong Gyeong.
Every time something happens, you always find me.
I will take a look.
Why are you working so hard?
Are you really going to switch to being a manager?
Are you crazy?
Then what is it?
Just...
I thought breaking up with someone who is smiling...
would hurt less.
Oh, you fool.
Why would you break up with someone who is smiling?
How sad.
They say the two of them were close from the beginning.
Our CEO as an entertainment CEO.
And Reporter Han as a paid journalist.
A paid journalist?
A journalist who writes articles for money.
He makes potential artists to be famous...
and sends away those unnecessary ones.
So, there were only articles about Yu Ji An...
in his recently written articles.
If a paid reporter publishes a few articles,
the paid commenters rush in and shape public opinion...
in the desired direction.
That is how it works.
Anyway, Reporter Han's wealth accumulation...
was thanks to our CEO.
So, Counsellor, do you think the culprit who ruined Ji An...
was my boss?
As you can see,
it is just a suspicion based on circumstantial evidence.
I...
I think...
Oh, it's nothing.
One more thing, our CEO is reporting about Ji An...
somewhere.
Reporting?
To whom?
I don't know that.
Manager Kim didn't know either.
Is it an unofficial power broker? A mastermind?
That is all he said.
But what is that?
Someone is sitting and someone is standing.
Oh, it is like a rule in our industry.
The lead actors sit, and the supporting actors stand.
This must be Ji An's first time experiencing something like this.
If it had been the old days, Ji An would have mentioned...
about her class and she would have flipped the set.
And she would have just gone home immediately...
if she had felt bad.
She has changed a lot.
What is popularity?
Indeed.
She has changed so much.
Alright, we will resume filming.
Let's move.
Ready.
Action.
Because of the promotion card the president gave you?
Just for that?
What are you talking about, senior?
You are the one who is doing this...
for a promotion.
Hello, Detective. What's up?
Then you know well?
How you ruined the hard work of many people.
This is your last chance.
- Okay, then let's meet tomorrow. - Cut, cut!
Ji An, your acting is so good this time.
– Really? – It is better than expected.
Let's continue shooting the next scene without needing another take.
Yes.
(Dong Gyeong Kitchen)
Yes, welcome.
Oh, Ji An, it has been a while.
Please, have some tea.
Oh, my.
Well...
I don't know much about Eun Hwan's father's accident.
It's a forbidden topic.
You don't know what kind of accident caused his death?
Yes, you know.
Eun Hwan feels guilty about that accident.
He does not bring it up first,
so I felt awkward asking him about it.
What I know is that...
Song Hwan was also injured in that accident.
Even his sister...
Then she became disabled...
because of that accident?
Yes, and after that,
Eun Hwan suffered a lot.
His suffering was beyond words.
That's about it.
Eun Hwan must have had a very hard time.
Isn't it obvious?
His mother was gone, his father passed away,
and his sister was injured.
He practically lived as a young head of household.
Now, he is doing well on his own,
but that guy has a heartbreaking life story...
that would make you cry.
How can you go on a private schedule...
without the manager's permission?
Did you forget that tomorrow is the day...
of highlight scene filming?
Is there any emotion you don't understand?
No, not really.
But why did Su Ji leave Jun Ho?
She said she loved him.
She probably left him...
because she loved him.
- Why are you asking it? - That does not make sense.
Leaving because you love someone.
If you love someone, you should stay with them no matter what.
Even if being together makes you both unhappy?
Why would you be unhappy with someone you love?
Not being together is what makes you unhappy.
Because it could be a love that can never come true.
If it can never come true,
then being together would only be a punishment for each other,
wouldn't it?
You're lying.
Where is there such a thing as a love...
that can never come true in this world?
Those are just excuses made...
by people who want to cowardly run away.
If I love someone, I will never leave them.
I will stay by their side no matter what.
And I will never forgive anyone...
who says they love me and then leaves.
Never.